<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 19:31:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3868193</guid>
      <title>Amazon delivery caught on camera stealing dog from yard</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARKER COUNTY, TEXAS  A woman and her boyfriend got busted after stealing a random person's dog while on the job.On July 5, Mycah Wade and Devanta Lynn Mooring were delivering packages for Amazon when they spotted a daschund in a neighborhood yard in Parker County, Texas.They then stopped by the yard. Mooring got out of the van, grabbed the dog, named RJ,  and the two sped away, according to the Weatherford Democrat.A neighbor's doorbell camera had caught the duo in action. They immediately informed the owners of RJ: Anthony and Amanda Phillips.The Phillips called  the police who launched an investigation.Local county Property Crimes Investigator Ethan Stark told the Weatherford Democrat that the two had asked a construction crew about RJ's owners. But instead of returning him, the two had placed an ad for the dachshund on Craigslist. They wanted $100 bucks for the daschund.The investigators were able to track down the couple and return RJ to the Phillips.Amazon issued a statement to the newspaper saying that the two are no longer delivering packages for the company.In the statement, Amazon said, "This does not reflect the high standards we have for delivery service partners," adding that they are glad that the Phillips' have reunited with their family dog.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 06:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/31/3868193/3868193_0F1E67FD687D4D7588ED76F0F39CBC6A_190731_3868193_Amazon_delivery_caught_on_camera_stealing_dog_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8D9/736/8D97368355836109155E02A098C48F8C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, amazon driver, amazon driver steals dog, amazon driver steals, amazon delivery driver stealing, amazon driver stories, family dog stolen, family reunited with stolen dog]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868191</guid>
      <title>Clown sparks cruise ship buffet brawl</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#clowns #clownfightcruiseship #clownbrawlNORTH SEA CIRCUS  A glamorous black-tie event aboard a British cruise liner turned savage following the appearance of a clown, reports The Guardian. Or did it?P&O Cruises' Britannia ship was sailing from Norway to the UK on the return leg of a week-long trip when the rumble broke out in the buffet area during the wee hours of Friday morning.British journalist Richard Gaisford[b] was aboard and on hand to tell the world how 'It' went down on Twitter. He explained the punch-up came after an afternoon of 'patriotic partying' during which copious amounts of hooch and similar beverages were consumed.Gaisford, citing a witness, explained that it got nasty when a guest in a clown get-up stopped by the buffet.  Police told the BBC that half-a-dozen people were injured during the fighting and that a man and woman, both in their early 40s, were nabbed on suspicion of assault. But in a twist, the cruise liner said there was no clown on board. And speaking to Metro.co.uk, police said quote "There was no clown on board or involved in this incident." Well, guess that's 'It' then.Thumbnail via https://www.flickr.com/photos/tipsfortravellers/16114660384https://pixabay.com/photos/clown-fun-cheerful-mood-face-2878245/]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 06:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/31/3868191/3868191_4CB6EB5DC2A7461C9548A1E325F87304_190731_3868191_Clown_sparks_cruise_ship_buffet_brawl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/678/5DC/6785DC4E1F87FA029DC314AED4D4BD7F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, clown fight cruise ship, P&O brittiania cruise ship clown cruise ship brawl, cruise ship fight, cruise ship brawl, cruise ship clown, clown, it, p&o clown, clown fight boat, clown fights, brawl on cruise ship because of clown, p&o cruise britannia, cruise ship brawl, passenger in clown suits, cruise ship clown, cruise ship clown brawl]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868136</guid>
      <title>White-supremacist sets fire
to 1763 synagogue... and himself</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EXETER, U.K  Arsonist, Tristan Morgan was seen on CCTV approaching the third oldest synagogue in Britain around 8 p.m on the 21st of July, 2018. After beating at the window with a small axe, he sheathed his weapon into his jacket and then calmly strolled off, only to return with a petrol can.Morgan then funneled fuel through the window, took his time to settle the can to the ground and then light a scrap of paper which he tossed into the fuel soaked synagogue.The petrol instantaneously caught ablaze and engulfed an unsuspecting Morgan in a fire blast from head to toe.He was then seen casually walking to his Mercedes Vito white van, where he drove away.Plymouth Live reported that far-right Morgan, who cackled as he walked away from the incident, actively encouraged terrorism by distributing a song called, 'White Man' to Soundcloud.Local Policing Commander Superintendent Matt Lawler said, "It is only by sheer chance that the synagogue was empty and indeed that Morgan himself sustained only minor burns."The London Bulletin reported that Morgan was also given a ten-year terrorist notification order, meaning that if he is ever to be released, he will require long-term police monitoring. Morgan was charged with collecting information and encouraging terrorism. The judge sentenced him to an indefinite hospital order under the Mental Health Act.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 04:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/07/31/3868136/3868136_A4E90F3B60D54B79B1E2DFF6DB3CA9E1_190731_3868136_White_supremacist_sets_fire_to_1763_synagogue____2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B40/A1B/B40A1B85348F9940E1879F7FCE1780C6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, white-supremacist sets fire to synagogue, white-supremacist sets fire to himself, anti-semitic attack, Exeter Synagogue arsonist Tristan Morgan kept in hospital, terrorist firebomber is blasted by flames during arson attack on Exeter Synagogue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868876</guid>
      <title>China bans citizens from solo travel to Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Beijing has banned individuals free travel to Taiwan, amid what it says are rising cross-strait tensions.According to CNN, China's Ministry of Culture and Tourism has announced that beginning August 1, solo tourists from 47 Mainland cities will no longer be allowed to travel to Taiwan.Nikkei Asian Review reports that Taiwan received over a million visitors from those cities last year, which accounts for 40% of Mainland arrivals.Only business travelers and tour groups will be allowed to visit Taiwan, according to the South China Morning Post.Several travel agents in China told Nikkei that they've stopped processing individual travel permits to Taiwan on Wednesday, following instructions from authorities.With the Chinese making up 30% of tourists in Taiwan in the first six months of this year, Gordon Sun, director of the Taiwan Institute of Economic Research, says the move will likely affect Taiwan's tourism industry.Popular destinations for Chinese tourists such as Nantou, Chiayi, and Hualien may be hit particularly hard.The ban comes weeks after the U.S. approved a controversial $2.2 billion arms deal with Taiwan  a move that Beijing opposed. Taiwan President Tsai Ing-wen's visit to New York in mid-July also angered China.According to Bloomberg, the ban may be yet another attempt to isolate both Taiwan and its independence-leaning president, as well as hurt her chances at re-election next January.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 10:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/01/3868876/3868876_1DE8B4CB172140F4A01DFDDFB9423112_190801_3868876_China_bans_citizens_from_solo_travel_to_Taiwan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ACA/D2D/ACAD2D7B2AB92996E327866C2BABA2CD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwan travel, Taiwan travel ban, Taiwan travel permit, China travel ban, China bans Taiwan solo travel, Taiwan solo travel ban, Taiwan tourism, Taiwan tour, US Taiwan arms deal, China tour group, Taiwan tour group, Chinese tourists, chinese solo travelers, 2019 Taiwan elections, Taiwan presidential election]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868742</guid>
      <title>Glitch outs 'young' Chinese live-streamer as 58yo auntie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINESE INTERNET  A popular Chinese live-streamer inadvertently outed her true self after a technical glitch caused her beauty filters to fail. Epically.According to the Global Times, "Your Highness Qiao Biluo" is a Chinese video blogger worshipped as a "cute goddess" by her 130,000 fans on streaming platform Douyu. They've given her some serious cash over the years  as high as $15,000, despite never actually seeing her real face.Turns out it takes a lot to get her looking like a goddess  a lot of beauty filters, that is.People apparently didn't realize this until a July 25 joint live-stream with fellow user Mix. While hiding her face to get fans to send $11 Gs worth of cash gifts, a technical glitch caused Her Highness's filters to sashay away. Fans weren't pleased to realize their goddess was in fact a 58-year-old auntie, and hightailed it outta there.Auntie herself didn't realize the jig was up until she noticed the mass exodus from her VIP access room.Needless to say, Qiao Biluo is now several thousand poorer, both in fans and in internet cash. But while she's being called out for conning her fanbase, many have pointed out the followers' lack of smarts, since they were gullible enough to send cash gifts.Still, seems the catfishing scandal hasn't dampened Auntie's spirits, since Asia One reports she's back at it, and even working on a rap track.Try and try until you die, I guess?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 08:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/01/3868742/3868742_F0AFE1D11550459B8BFAFC4B0E1F1BBA_190801_3868742_Glitch_outs__young__Chinese_live_streamer_as_58y_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/883/A7D/883A7DEF55239EB76003BA7506326653.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, beauty filter fail, fake face, face filter fail, chinese vlogger, chinese livestreamer, beauty filters, livestream glitch, chinese vlogger identity reveal, qiao biluo, your highness qiao biluo, face filter, chinese social media]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868721</guid>
      <title>North Korea fires two ballistic missiles into the Sea of Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WONSAN, NORTH KOREA   North Korea launched two unidentified short-range ballistic missiles on July 30 from the Kalma area near the eastern port of Wonsan, according to a statement from South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff.The first missile was launched at 5:06 a.m., while the second was launched at 5:27 a.m.Both of the missiles were estimated to have flown around 250 kilometers at an approximate altitude of 30 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan.North Korea fired two other ballistic missiles, identified as KN-23, last week, according to the Korean Herald. One flew around 430 kilometers while the other flew around 690 kilometers. Both flew at an estimated altitude of 50 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan.North Korea had previously said the missiles were intended as a warning to the South, over its joint military exercises with the U.S.South Korea has said that the consecutive missile launches aren't reducing tensions on the Korean Peninsula and called for North Korea to "halt these acts."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 07:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/01/3868721/3868721_A6F943BABD5C4F239FB78739E4D41C13_190801_3868721_North_Korea_fires_two_ballistic_missiles_into_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7AC/BF1/7ACBF15FC29874D7B579EFA149DD4CD5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north korea missile launch, north korea missile, kim jong un, north korea weapons, north korea firepower, north korea, north korean missile, north korea fires missile, north korea fires ballistic missile, north korean ballistic missile, short range missile, unidentified projectiles, ballistic missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868711</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia all set for new Hyperloop One train system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KING ABDULLAH ECONOMIC CITY, SAUDI ARABIA  Virgin Hyperloop One and Saudi Arabia have announced plans to build a 35 km long hyperloop test track in King Abdullah Economic City as part of the country's Vision 2030 plan.Plans include a research and development facility along with a manufacturing plant for the hyperloop, reports the BBC.Saudi Arabia plans to diversify its economy, develop the country's tourism and infrastructure, and invite investment into the country as part of its Vision 2030 plans.According to Virgin Hyperloop One's website, the hyperloop consists of a magnetic linear motor and a rotor connected at the bottom of the pod. This allows the vehicle move forward via magnetic levitation.The company says the technology would shorten travel time from Riyadh to Jeddah from over 10 hours to just 76 minutes.The hyperloop would travel at speeds of up to two to three times faster than high speed rail trains, according to Virgin Hyperloop One.Virgin Hyperloop One has also proposed the futuristic mode of transport for the state of Missouri, India and Spain.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 07:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/01/3868711/3868711_40604EF85A4146D294B83B209C9F3681_190801_3868711_Saudi_Arabia_all_set_for_new_Hyperloop_One_train_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3C4/9A0/3C49A07A8FF1246B0ADEDF5909DD67C8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, saudi arabia hyperloop, Virgin Hyperloop One, Virgin Hyperloop One saudi arabia, king abdullah economic city, king abdullah economic city hyperloop, hyperloop, future transportation, technology,  saudi arabia, hyperloop, hyperloop track, hyperloop tube]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868703</guid>
      <title>North Korea reveals new ballistic missile submarine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA  North Korea's state-run Korean Central News Agency on July 23 shared photos of leader Kim Jong Un inspecting a brand new submarine for the country's military.North Korea has debuted a new diesel-electric submarine that seems to be a modified version of the Soviet-era Romeo class submarine, the Washington Examiner reports.According to defense analyst H.I. Sutton's website, the vessel may be able to carry two to three ballistic missiles, such as the Pukkuksong-1, in its expanded sail.The nuclear missile has a range of around 745 miles or 1,200 kilometers, the Drive reports.The submarine will be deployed soon and will operate in the Sea of Japan, according to the Korean Central News Agency.Citing analysts, Reuters reports that the vessel is being used to send a clear message to Washington to take North Korea seriously. Joel Wit, founder of 38 North, a Washington-based think tank that analyses North Korea, told Reuters the North Koreans have historically displayed weapon developments "to bolster deterrence and demonstrate that they will not be intimidated" by the U.S.He explained that North Korea's show of military strength may be due to the upcoming U.S.-South Korea joint military exercises in August.North Korea has routinely called for the U.S. and South Korea to halt combined military exercises as the nation sees the exercises as a threat to its sovereignty.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 06:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/01/3868703/3868703_0CB3AABBCBBF4CE495F80CC1B3A67DAE_190801_3868703_North_Korea_reveals_new_ballistic_missile_submar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C1C/787/C1C7875BB04E5E8DE45A72EE3088E405.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north korea, north korea submarine, ballistic missile submarine, north korean ballistic missile submarine, Pukkuksong, north korean ballistic missile submarine, Romeo-class submarine, SSB, diesel-electric ballistic missile submarine, Pukkuksong-1 missiles, kim jong un, kim jong un submarine, submarine-launched ballistic missiles, modified romeo class sub, romeo class attack submarine, north korean military technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868657</guid>
      <title>Russian next-generation missile defense system ahead of schedule</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Russia's next generation missile defense system could be delivered sooner than expected, according to recent statements given by defense conglomerate Rostec and Russian Minister of Industry and Trade Denis Manturov to Russian media, the National Interest reports.Russia's S-500 missile defense system will consist of a long-range radar that tracks the target, a command vehicle that identifies the target and coordinates the missile launch, a launcher and an engagement radar that helps guide the missile. The system fires two missiles per target.Website Army Recognition cites Russian sources as saying that the S-500 is an advanced version of the S-400.The defense system will have a detection range of up to 800 kilometers, an intercept range of up to 600 kilometers and a maximum intercept altitude of up to 200 kilometers, according to Global Security.org.The S-500 can target intercontinental ballistic missiles, hypersonic cruise missiles and aircraft."The defense system will be capable of intercepting aircraft or missiles directly with two missiles: the 77N6-N and 77N6-N1, according to Army Recognition. These missiles will reportedly be able to hit targets flying at speeds of up to 7 kilometers per second.Rostec CEO Sergei Chemezov told Russia's Interfaks news agency that the first units will go into service with the Russian army in 2027, according to a report cited by the National Interest.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 05:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/01/3868657/3868657_9550FBEEE68B48B0826AA9298B74CD26_190801_3868657_Russian_next_generation_missile_defense_system_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/33E/0F7/33E0F74342C685BA91AE4AF1B10B5970.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, russia, russia missile defense system, s-500 missile defense system,  s-500 missile defense system russia, russian missile system, russia new missile defense system, s 500 air defense missile system, Russian military missile defense system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3868594</guid>
      <title>Will refreezing save the Arctic and Antarctica?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA  Scientists have suggested plans to save Antarctic glaciers and Arctic sea ice by refreezing them.According to Reuters, scientists believe the West Antarctic ice sheet is on course to disintegrate due to the effects of global warming.This would trigger a global sea level rise that would leave many coastal cities, such as New York, underwater.To prevent this from happening, a new study published in Science Advances has proposed using 12,000 wind turbines to pump sea water to the surface, turn it into artificial snow and then pump it onto two glaciers on the West Antarctic coast.According to study co-author Anders Levermann it would take 7.4 trillion tonnes of snow over a 10-year period to result in a two-centimeter drop in sea level, though the  artificial snow would weigh the glaciers down and improve stability.Other research suggests warm water currents may be melting the glaciers from the bottom up, prompting an idea to construct giant sills or underwater mounds to prevent the water from seeping under the ice shelves.CNBC reports that Arizona State University physicist Steven Desch has similar refreezing plans for the Arctic.His Arctic ice management strategy calls for the use of wind-powered pumps to spray water to the surface of sea ice, where it would freeze and thicken the ice cap.Many scientists believe the consequences of global warming are already inevitable, and when they do occur, just turning down the temperature won't cut it. Since efforts to curb this problem aren't keeping pace with the Paris Agreement, Desch suggests it's time to start looking into unconventional options.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 03:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/01/3868594/3868594_B05739245515445CA21C1734C4530245_190801_3868594_Will_refreezing_save_the_Arctic_and_Antarctica__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F82/F63/F82F6382E660D5D3A89515164B54B84E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, polar geoengineering, geoengineering, refreeze Antarctica, refreeze arctic, artificial snow, arctic ice management, west antarctic ice sheet, ice sheet collapse, global warming, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3869460</guid>
      <title>Japan approves human-animal embryo experiments</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Japan has become the first country to greenlight a controversial experiment involving hybrid human-animal embryos.According to Nature magazine, experts at Japan's Science Ministry have approved a University of Tokyo proposal to grow human stem cells in mouse, rat, and pig embryos, and transplant them into surrogate animals.Lead researcher Hiromitsu Nakauchi says the goal is to create animals with human organs than can then be used for transplants.The proposal is the first one approved since Japan lifted a ban in March on developing animal embryos with human cells beyond 14 days, and bringing them to term.Nakauchi told Nature that they will be creating animal embryos that lack a gene to produce certain organs. Once injected with human induced pluripotent stem cells or IPS cells, the embryo will use the IPS cells to make the organ.He says he plans to grow mouse embryos for 14.5 days until they are almost to term. Rats will be grown to near term for 15.5 days, and pigs for up to 70 days.Nakauchi's 2017 experiment saw him and his team successfully cure a diabetic mouse by growing a healthy new mouse pancreas using a rat embryo.Science Alert reports that while the treatment is meant to target only the organ being grown, the experiment will be suspended if the team detects more than 30% of the animal's brain to be human.This is apparently one of the Japanese government's conditions, in order to prevent humanized animals from ever coming into existence.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 10:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/02/3869460/3869460_E46C9E2C6C6C46A7998B862231FA4BD0_190802_3869460_Japan_approves_human_animal_embryo_experiments_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/493/199/49319960A39CFA03C9CC334E3263B2EE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, human animal hybrid, mutant embryos, hybrid embryos, mutant experiments, hybrid experiments, human animal experiments, human animal hybrid experiments, stem cell research, stem cell experiment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3869350</guid>
      <title>Seabirds becoming tinier in size due to plastic pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BATTERY POINT, AUSTRALIA  New research from the University of Tasmania has found that seabirds are becoming smaller in size due to their consumption of plastic.Researchers analyzed the flesh-footed shearwaters on Lord Howe Island, Australia and found that their wings and bills had become shorter.The study was published in the journal Environmental Science & Technology. It found that plastic had caused the birds to have a lower body mass and decreased kidney function.Jennifer Lavers, lead author of the study, explained in a university news release that they took blood samples from the seabirds and found that the birds had a higher cholesterol, a higher concentration of uric acid as well as reduced blood calcium levels.According to the researchers, the consumption of plastic is resulting in a decline of the flesh-footed shearwaters as they are feeding their offspring tiny pieces of plastic, instead of fish.In the news release, Lavers said their research suggested that any amount of plastic ingestion is enough to have an impact on the health of an individual.The number of seabirds who die every year from eating plastic waste is estimated to be around 1 million, according to a United Nations Ocean conference factsheet from 2017.Seabirds mistakenly consume plastic as it looks and smells like food and floats on the surface of the water, according to the World Wild Fund for Nature Australia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 08:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/02/3869350/3869350_B88C9D3B29394BF9A314B023358773FE_190802_3869350_Seabirds_becoming_tinier_in_size_due_to_plastic__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2D5/B8A/2D5B8A2F7015024E44E2FB0C3B55466A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic pollution, plastic ingestion, seabirds, flesh-footed shearwaters, flesh-footed shearwaters plastic consumption, plastic pollution seabirds, plastic pollution animation, plastic pollution animals, animals suffering from plastic pollution, plastic pollution impact on animals, sea animals plastic pollution, plastic pollution affecting animals, plastic pollution impact on animals, sea birds getting smaller]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3869325</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy jet crashes in Death Valley's Star Wars Canyon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DEATH VALLEY, CALIFORNIA  An F/A-18E Super Hornet fighter jet has crashed in Death Valley National Park.The aircraft was flying over Death Valley National Park during a routine training exercise on July 31 at approximately 10:00 a.m. local time when it crashed near the Naval Air Weapons Station China Lake, according to a tweet from the U.S. Naval Air Forces. Death Valley National Park spokesman Patrick Taylor told CNN that the crash caused seven visitors to suffer minor injuries. Taylor explained that this particular area of the park is known as Stars Wars Canyon and is a popular site for visitors to observe military training flights.In a statement to the United States Naval Institute News, the Navy said search and rescue units were sent to the scene. The pilot's status is currently unknown and the cause of the accident is under investigation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 08:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/02/3869325/3869325_2E6B7A75EA064BEF94E0AD50F4097174_190802_3869325_U_S__Navy_jet_crashes_in_Death_Valley_s_Star_War_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/05D/200/05D20047F3A0422BF00CE4B7251F0916.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, star wars canyon, jet crash, navy jet crash, military jet crash, star wars canyon crash, super hornet jet, fighter jet crash, us navy jet crashes, f/a-18 jets, f/a-18 fighter jets,  f/a-18 navy fighter jets, f/a-18 jet crash, f/a-18E Super Hornet jet, death valley national park, jet crashes, us navy, us military]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3869281</guid>
      <title>Tech saves skydivers life after he's knocked out in mid-air collision</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OTTAWA, ILLINOIS  Two skydivers jumped from a plane and crashed mid-air at Summerfest Skydiving Festival at the Skydive Chicago resort in Ottawa. CBS 2 reported on the death-defying clash. The two seasoned skydivers collided around 11:00 a.m on Tuesday morning, resulting in one of them, 81-year-old Bill Morrisey, being knocked unconscious.  Morrisey was falling fast towards the earth, but fortunately for him, he was wearing an automated activation device inside a parachute pack.So, what's an automated activation device?Anthony Ebel of Skydive Chicago says it best, "Essentially, it's just a device that measures how fast the person is falling and what altitude they're at  once they hit a certain threshold, it then starts the deployment process of the reserve parachute."The life-saving device opened his chute, bringing him gently back to earth alive and still kicking.U.S News stated that as he was unable to steer, he landed in the Fox River.Both jumpers were taken to OSF St. Elizabeth Medical Center and miraculously both were fine bar minor injuries.  Morrissey, who has jumped more than 7,000 times spanning 62 years, said: "I wear an automated activation device because that's what common sense tells you to do."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 07:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/02/3869281/3869281_4F5B11837E474FBFA151FBEEAA2C3698_190802_3869281_Tech_saves_skydivers_life_after_he_s_knocked_out_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B15/738/B157389AECFDE6A0CEC09A3BF0240328.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, skydiving fail, skydiving gone wrong, skydiving accident, skydiving chicago, skydiving Chicago il, Tech saves skydivers life after he's knocked out in mid-air collision, Ottawa Skydiver Accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871046</guid>
      <title>Woman dies after falling off cliff looking for the toilet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EAST SUSSEX, UNITED KINGDOM  A woman is no longer around after accidentally plunging off a cliff edge while looking for the bathroom. According to the Eastborne Herald, 22-year-old Faye Reed was with some friends on the night of March 25 when they stopped at Beachy Head in East Sussex so she could hit the head. According to the paper, Charmane Dixon, Nicole Davies and Reed were being driven by their friend Rayan Kalhei when they asked him to pull over so they could take a leak. Unfortunately, it was really dark where they were. Reed didn't realize she was right next to the cliff's edge and stumbled over it. The paper said her friends heard a scream and realized she had fallen from the top of the cliff. They immediately called the police while they tried to search for Reed. Coast guard helicopters were then dispatched and her body was found later. Dixon said they three had drank a little bit, and a toxicology report found Reed had a small amount of alcohol in her system. According to the Eastborne Herald, Detective Sergeant Chris Milner said there was only a small patch of grass between the road and the cliff's edge. He said it was a "tragic accident" and there were no suspicious circumstances.  Next time you want to go, make sure you can see WHERE you're going.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 23:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/06/3871046/3871046_B0FEDFD3F8944B55AC25CB5FAE8FF153_190806_3871046_Woman_dies_after_falling_off_cliff_looking_for_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC6/E6B/DC6E6B49671E27E6415B5E8A43473EB2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, woman looks for toilet, woman looking for bathroom, looking for bathroom, somewhere to spend a penny, Beachy Head East Sussex, Beachy Head accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870835</guid>
      <title>Raccoon unstuck from sewer grate after 2 long hours</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWTON, MASSACHUSETTS  It took practically a village to rescue a raccoon that found itself in a bit of a tight spot.According to the Washington Post, a man cycling to work called the Newton Fire Department Thursday after spotting the four-legged critter with its head poking out of a sewer grate.The poor thing had already been stuck for a while at that point. Even though no one knows how, we're pretty sure food is involved.Firefighters responded to the scene intending a 99% effective slip n' slide-out with soap and water. It didn't work, and only left a very wet n' wild raccoon.Next, rescuers lifted the grate out and swaddled the fury guy in bandages in an attempt to decompress its body and squeeze it out. That didn't work either, and just made the little dude even more distressed.Eventually, firefighters called in a vet to sedate the very not chill Rocket, and the two-hour rescue saga ended with the animal finally being freed.Waltham Animal Control later posted a Facebook update saying the raccoon had been released back into the wild.Here's hoping he learns his lesson and stops squeezing into tight spaces.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 11:48:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/05/3870835/3870835_C5F64E1182BF40ED9408AAD3F588DF8E_190805_3870835_Raccoon_unstuck_from_sewer_grate_after_2_long_ho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/181/0A2/1810A226CFC4C4EB32E315A29934193B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, raccoon, stuck raccoon, raccoon stuck in drain, raccoon stuck in sewer, trapped raccoon, raccoon rescue, rocket raccoon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870825</guid>
      <title>Church of the Apostles may have been unearthed near Galilee sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIT HABEK, ISRAEL  Archaeologists have discovered an early Christian church rumored to be built over the house of the apostles Peter and Andrew.According to a press release from the Center for the Study of Ancient Judaism and Christian Origins, a large church from the Byzantine period has been unearthed at Beit Habek, near the northern shore of the Sea of Galilee.Archaeologists believe the structure is the Church of the Apostles, which Christian tradition indicates was built over the home of Jesus' disciples Peter and Andrew in the village of Bethsaida.A Bavarian bishop named Willibald had written about the church in 725 C.E., having seen it while traveling from Capernaum to Kursi.According to the press release, the church is part of a monastery complex, but only the southern rooms have been excavated.So far, the team has uncovered ornate mosaic tiles, marble fragments from a chancel screen, and a fragment of a chalk carving showing a cross.They also unearthed a Roman-period home about 100 meters north of the main excavation area, which contained Jewish stone vessels, oil lamps, and over 20 Roman-era coins and lead fishing weights.R. Steven Notley, a New Testament professor at Nyack College who blogged about the excavation, says the archaeologists have been digging at the site for four years, and will need another year to completely excavate the remains of the church.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 11:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/05/3870825/3870825_54084878F0B94C6C9099672953746FE3_190805_3870825_Church_of_the_Apostles_may_have_been_unearthed_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C26/032/C260327095BE5D37287502F94A89D94B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, church of the apostles, sea of galilee, ancient church, byzantine church, Bethsaida, ancient christian church, early christian church, jesus, apostles, peter's house, peter and andrew's house, apostle's house, apostle house, biblical archaeology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870735</guid>
      <title>Chinese wave pool malfunction causes tsunami, injures 44 people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONGJING, CHINA  A Chinese water park went off the deep end when its "tsunami pool" did just thatit sent a huge artificial wave through one pool while it was packed with unsuspecting swimmers. Video footage shared on Chinese Twitter knockoff Weibo shows a whole mess of people tubing in a packed wave pool at the Yulong Shuiyun Water Park in Longjing. According to CNN, the day was going along swimmingly, when a massive 10-foot-tall artificial wave is seen barreling through the pool, swallowing up every unlucky person in its path.According to a statement from Longjing city officials, a total of 44 people were injured in the little mishap. Officials said in the statement that the city emergency department, the cultural and tourism department, and market regulators have launched a joint investigation into the artificial tsunami. Apparently, the wave machine control room's power box had some slight issues. A water park spokesman had originally said the pool would be back in business the next day, but local officials pulled the plug on that idea.   According to the park's website, Yulong claims to be the largest water park of its kind in Jilin province, with a tidal rafting river, Ferris wheel and spa pools. Guess now they can add an ACTUAL tsunami pool to that list as well.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 08:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/05/3870735/3870735_8F6C4FFBEDC746E6B11BC591FF86BB3F_190805_3870735_Chinese_wave_pool_malfunction_causes_tsunami__in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9E9/232/9E9232558CD278130C7AB70C80F44B3F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tsunami, tsunami pool, water park, China water park, Jilin water park, Yunlong Shuiyun Water Park]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870554</guid>
      <title>North Korea fires ballistic missiles for the third time in eight days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YONGHUNG, NORTH KOREA  North Korea has launched additional unidentified short-range projectiles on August 2.According to a statement from South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff, the missiles were launched at 2:59 a.m. and 3:23 a.m. from Yonghung in South Hamgyong Province. Both landed in the Sea of Japan.The statement didn't mention the exact number of missiles that were fired.This is the third time North Korea has fired projectiles in the past eight days, according to Reuters.On July 25, North Korea launched two short-range ballistic missiles, identified as KN-23 off its east coast, according to the Korean Herald.The first missile flew around 430 kilometers while the second flew around 690 kilometers. Both flew at an estimated altitude of 50 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan.On July 31, North Korea fired two more unidentified ballistic missiles from its eastern port of Wonsan.Both of the missiles were estimated to have flown around 250 kilometers at an approximate altitude of 30 kilometers before landing in the Sea of Japan, according to the Korea Times. South Korea's Joint Chiefs of Staff said they are monitoring the situation and are "maintaining a readiness posture."North Korea had stated that the missile launches are intended as a warning to South Korea over its joint military exercises with the U.S. later this month.Pyongyang also said the joint military exercises could cause a shift in its talks with the U.S., according to Reuters. The country warned it may put an end to its freeze on nuclear and long-range missile tests that have been in place since 2017.U.S. President Donald Trump reacted by referring to the missile tests as "very standard" and said he would be willing to negotiate with Kim Jong-Un despite the North's consecutive missile launches.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 02:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/05/3870554/3870554_13A78D6BD07B4CAA8CB1CB7DA0158C0E_190805_3870554_North_Korea_fires_ballistic_missiles_for_the_thi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C15/A64/C15A6447486784E8EA047B544857F6B6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north korea missile launch, north korea missile, kim jong un, north korea weapons, north korea firepower, north korea, north korean missile, north korea fires missile, north korea fires ballistic missile, north korean ballistic missile, short range missile, unidentified projectiles, ballistic missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870546</guid>
      <title>Plane makes an emergency landing on Washington highway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  State Trooper Clint Thompson's patrol turned Hollywood when a prop plane glided towards the highway in a clip that was caught on his cruiser's dashcam. KOMO News reports that the emergency landing occurred Thursday around 8:00 am on Pacific Avenue South, also known as State Route 7. The single-prop KR2 aircraft was being flown by pilot David Acklam who told KOMO News that he was flying to work when his engine quit on him.Dennis Diessner, a motorist on the road at the time, said the small plane came so close to his vehicle that he thought he could have reached out and touched it.Many motorists gawped in amazement as the plane touched down on the tarmac and then appropriately stopped at the red light.Pierce Sheriff Department took to Twitter to say that the prop plane ran out of gas and that it was taken off the road promptly.Public Information Officer for Washington State Patrol, Johnna Batiste tweeted that after 21 years on patrol, this was a first for Tropper Thompson. Fortunately, the spectacle resulted in no damages or injuries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 02:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/05/3870546/3870546_1DF44BF6652E48BEB02FD978C2043972_190805_3870546_Plane_makes_an_emergency_landing_on_Washington_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7FF/C07/7FFC074E739FEC19327CEC672305D5BB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plane makes emergency landing on Washington highway, plane lands on highway, plane lands on road, plane emergency landing, plane lands on Washington highway, emergency plane landing on highway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3870537</guid>
      <title>Mosquitoes spreading brain-infecting virus in Florida</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORANGE COUNTY, FLORIDA  Health officials in Orange County, Florida have issued a public advisory warning residents of an increase of mosquitoes carrying the Eastern equine encephalitis virus.According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the virus is spread from avian hosts such as chickens to mosquitoes. The mosquitoes carry the virus and transmit it to humans.Florida officials had found that sentinel chickens in the county tested positive for the disease.Symptoms include sudden headache, high fever, chills, vomiting and swelling of the brain. After contracting the virus, symptoms take around four to 10 days to develop. The CDC's website states that there is currently no human vaccine available against the disease.Florida's health officials advised the public to drain standing water to prevent mosquitoes from multiplying. Officials also advised the public to wear long-sleeved clothing, apply mosquito repellent and close the windows to prevent mosquito bites.According to the CDC, an average of seven human cases of the deadly virus are reported in the U.S. every year. Most of the cases reported have been from Florida, Massachusetts, New York and North Carolina.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 02:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/05/3870537/3870537_8AA3624C5740405ABB37A49E8316B7BD_190805_3870537_Mosquitoes_spreading_brain_infecting_virus_in_Fl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/890/058/89005867208DA31F35F122AC5B4F2CC9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mosquitoes, mosquito bite, mosquito infection, mosquito virus, mosquitoes florida, brain virus, mosquitoes brain virus, EEEV, eastern equine encephalitis virus, mosquito virus florida 2019, mosquito virus brain, mosquito borne disease, brain infecting mosquito virus, brain infecting virus florida, human EEEV, EEEV florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871546</guid>
      <title>Greta Thunberg will sail to New York for UN climate summit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ACROSS THE POND  Greta Thunberg is set to attend climate talks in America, but she won't be flying there. Instead, the teen activist will be crossing the Atlantic on a sailboat.According to the New York Times, the 60-foot racing yacht Malizia II is a zero-emissions vessel that generates electricity using solar panels and underwater turbines.CNN reports that in mid-August, 16-year-old Greta Thunberg and the crew of the Malizia II will sail from the U.K. to New York, where Thunberg will attend the UN Climate Action Summit on September 23.She will also go to Canada and Mexico, and plans to attend the UN COP25 climate conference in Santiago, Chile in December.The journey to New York will take roughly two weeks, according to the Times, with zero comfort onboard.Boris Hermann, the boat's skipper, says he warned Thunberg that she will likely eat freeze-dried and vacuum-packed meals, and that the crossing may be choppy, as peak Atlantic hurricane season is in August and September.Thunberg doesn't fly due to the high carbon emissions associated with air travel.Citing German nonprofit Atmosfair, Graphic News reports that a London to New York flight generates 3,408 kilograms of CO2 per person, which is double the annual carbon footprint per capita in India.According to the New York Times, the Malizia II will only be dropping Thunberg off across the pond. No news yet on how she plans to get back home to Sweden.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/07/3871546/3871546_135F7AFAC3464590AE7C856C50EAC23D_190807_3871546_Greta_Thunberg_will_sail_to_New_York_for_UN_clim_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B2/3CE/3B23CEB03D69717116B651CEA7881F39.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Greta Thunberg, zero emissions yacht, low carbon footprint, climate change, global warming, UN climate summit, Greta Thunberg sailing route, Greta Thunberg sailing, sailing across Atlantic, carbon emissions, flight emissions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871423</guid>
      <title>7-year-old boy in India had 526 teeth removed from his mouth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENNAI, INDIA  A 7-year-old Indian boy who was suffering from on again off again toothaches was found to have a whopping 526 teeth inside his jawtalk about a mouthful. According to a press release from the Saveetha Dental College and Hospital, the boy was taken to the hospital with swelling in his lower right jaw, where he was found to be suffering from compound composite odontoma  a benign tumor.  According to the Guardian, the army of teeth were crammed inside a 7-ounce sac that was tucked away in the molar region of his lower jaw. According to the hospital, each tooth had a crown covered by enamel and a root-like structure, and ranged in size from 1mm to 15mm. Doctors said this was the first time they've ever come across so many teeth in one person's pie hole.  The surgery bit into five hours of the boy's time, as surgeons meticulously removed every single extra tooth. According to CBS News, when the boy was 3 years old, he was taken to the hospital with a swollen jaw, but refused to cooperate with doctorsprobably because he was only 3. So his condition was left undiagnosed. The Guardian reports that after chilling in the hospital for three days, he was discharged and is doing fine. Looks like the tooth fairy is going to be taking quite the hit for this motherload of teeth. Hopefully she brings enough cash.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 12:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/06/3871423/3871423_869AC8CF88B4413A86130F91137AA58C_190806_3871423_7_year_old_boy_in_India_had_526_teeth_removed_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EC6/AE1/EC6AE1D2F6EF261715CDAB3A8E9696A5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, boy has 526 teeth removed, Indian boy 526 teeth, 526 teeth removed, boy 526 teeth, tooth fairy, tooth removal, tooth extraction]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871148</guid>
      <title>Couple shows off good brains posing too close to train tracks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEIZHOU, CHINA  Humans are a rather ingenious species with a special knack for doing the extraordinarythis however is not one of those times.According to a clip posted on Miaopai, a boneheaded selfie couple from Guangdong province had the fantastic idea of trying to film themselves posing next to some train tracks, in order to catch a train speeding by directly behind them. Apparently, Thing 1 and Thing 2 positioned themselves a bit too close for comfort next to the tracks. As the locomotive zips past the couple of the century, it clips both of them, introducing their faces to the ground in front of them. The two survived their meet and greet with the train. The female was taken to a hospital where she was treated for some broken bones. The boyfriend was not seriously hurt. As for the train, it looks like it will continue choo choo-ing along.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 04:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/06/3871148/3871148_40D75AB672AA43E19185025B2CA3408F_190806_3871148_Couple_shows_off_good_brains_posing_too_close_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D3D/EE6/D3DEE67D68B6B6ECF11133FAFF18D181.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, selfie, selfie couple, selfie fail, train tracks selfie, train tracks selfie fail, couple poses by train tracks, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871080</guid>
      <title>China's massive atmospheric laser radar explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China is building a powerful laser radar facility to help researchers study atmospheric particles that protect against cosmic rays and solar winds.The laser radar will have a range of 1,000 kilometers, according to a statement by the Chinese Academy of Science. Atmospheric lasers typically have an estimated range of 100 kilometers, according to the South China Morning Post. The radar will send out a high-energy laser beam that will penetrate through clouds and reach the edge of the earth's atmosphere, the South China Morning Post reports. The beam will then hit atmospheric particles such as high-altitude atoms.Several large optical telescopes will then be used to pick up and analyze faint signals reflected by these particles.According to the South China Morning Post, the laser radar is part of China's Meridian Space Weather Monitoring Project which started in 2008. The project consists of multiple ground-based observatories that monitor and forecast solar activities. The project plans to build facilities in the Arctic, the South China Sea, Central Asia and South America among other places by 2025.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 02:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/06/3871080/3871080_F8BE25DB20F04DD6AA10A5123F7C6F4D_190806_3871080_China_s_massive_atmospheric_laser_radar_explaine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CC9/B42/CC9B42C5555D755362CBDC0D3B5A6140.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, radar, china laser radar, chinese radar technology, powerful laser radar, laser beam, high energy laser beam, laser radar, china's new laser radar, atmospheric particles, cosmic rays, solar winds, World's most powerful laser radar, chinese laser radar]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871068</guid>
      <title>World's first cross-border cable car planned for Russia and China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLAGOVESHCHENSK, RUSSIA  Dutch architectural firm UNStudio has been chosen to design a cable car terminal in Russia that will connect the Russian city of Blagoveshchensk to the Chinese city of Heihe.The terminal will be a multi-layer structure that will overlook the Amur River, a natural boundary between Russia and China.According to UNStudio's project website, the cable car system will consist of two lines, with four cable car cabins each. Each cabin will have a capacity of 60 passengers. The cable cars are designed for travelers to have a clear view of the river, which is often frozen during winter time.The cable car terminal will also include an urban green space and terraces for passengers.Russian consulting company Strelka KB is helping UNStudio to manage the project.Ben van Berkel, founder of UNStudio, explained to Dezeen that the new cable car system will be the first to join two countries and cultures.UNStudio told CNN that construction of the site is expected to begin in 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 02:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/06/3871068/3871068_A53B2DCA0D2746A281957FEB7E729A22_190806_3871068_World_s_first_cross_border_cable_car_planned_for_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/74F/803/74F80392580C18FBEBA3A44A2C6A5C72.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cable car, russia-china cable car, Blagoveshchensk Cable Car Terminal, the world's first cross border cable car, russia china cable car system, Amur River,  Blagoveshchensk - Heihe cable car, international cable car, UNStudio, cross-border cable car, cross-border cable car russia china, transportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871983</guid>
      <title>Pentagon testing surveillance balloons across the Midwest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Pentagon is using high-altitude balloons to conduct surveillance test in six Midwestern states, the Guardian reports.The U.S. military is using the balloons surveil vehicles in the midwestern states of South Dakota, Minnesota, Iowa, Wisconsin, Missouri and Illinois, according to documents from the Federal Communication Commission.The surveillance balloons are carrying small-satellite-like vehicles with synthetic aperture radars, sensors and communications equipment, the Guardian reports. The balloons travel at altitudes of up to 65,000 feet and are able to track vehicles via the synthetic radars in all kinds of weather.The documents reveal that the tests are being conducted to "provide a persistent surveillance system to locate and deter narcotic trafficking and homeland security threats."The balloons use an advanced mesh networking technologies which allows them to share data and communicate with one another, reports the Guardian. They are also able to relay the data to receivers on the ground.According to the documents, the U.S. military has acquired a license to operate the surveillance balloons from mid-July until September.The tests are being commissioned by the U.S. Southern Command, or Southcom, which is responsible for disaster response, intelligence and security operations in the Carribbean and Latin America.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 13:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/07/3871983/3871983_B180EC0A52FC4E6486BBF78E05A4C20C_190807_3871983_Pentagon_testing_surveillance_balloons_across_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A33/7CC/A337CC5A454A2EE7ADC59618D48BE471.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pentagon, pentagon surveillance balloons, surveillance pentagon, high-altitude balloons, solar-powered balloons pentagon, balloon radar, surveillance balloon tests, US military surveillance tests, surveillance balloons, military surveillance balloons, military surveillance balloons, surveillance balloons US, balloon surveillance system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871975</guid>
      <title>Toilet explodes after lighting strike hits Florida home's septic tank</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORT CHARLOTTE, FLORIDA  A Florida homeowner is picking up the pieces of what used to be her toilet after it blew up in a freak accident caused by a lightning strike. According to homeowner Marylou Ward talking to WINK News, it all happened in a millisecond, but it was the loudest sound she has ever heard.According to NBC 2 News, Ward was in bed with her husband and three dogs listening to the rain and thunder on Sunday morning when tragedy struck the crapper. According to their plumber, after the lightning struck the septic tank, it most likely caused the methane gas from fecal matter built up in the pipes to ignite.This then led to Marylou's toilet exploding and shattering into hundreds of pieces everywhere in the bathroom.Besides destroying the can, the lightning also shattered Ward's master bedroom window and scattered her yard decorations all over the place.    Luckily, no one was hurt. Ward said, "I'm just glad none of us were on the toilet. That's the main thing."  So does this mean one should stay off the can during thunderstorms? According to the plumbing company, exploding toilets are about as rare as someone getting struck by lighting.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 13:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/07/3871975/3871975_45D45FF7F8094EC48FCAC4F59B671C2A_190807_3871975_Toilet_explodes_after_lighting_strike_hits_Flori_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FC9/771/FC977134C6450196CFBACD333A6F94A1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, lighting strike, toilet, lightning strike toilet, lightning strike septic tank, Port Charlotte lightning strike]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871907</guid>
      <title>Man fires gun at national park over Bigfoot sighting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#Bigfoot #sasquatchMAMMOTH CAVE NATIONAL PARK, KENTUCKY  A Kentucky couple had a doozy of a camping trip after crossing paths with a man who claimed he saw a sasquatch...and then tried to shoot it. CNN reports that while camping in Mammoth Cave National Park, Brad Ginn and Madelyn Durand were awakened in the middle of the night by strange noises and a light being shined into their tent.Outside, a man with a young son told them something had destroyed his campsite. He showed them his gun, warning that they were in "Bigfoot country" and to run if they heard shots.The father and son soon walked away, and the couple went back into their tent.10 minutes later, sasquatch hunter was back. Ginn and Durand heard him yell "I see it!" and watched as he shot into the darkness some 20 yards from the side of their tent.He later claimed Bigfoot had emerged from the bush and was coming at him, but when the couple shined a flashlight on said bush, there was nothing there.The two were understandably freaked at the gunfire  the non-existent sasquatch, not so much  so they called 911 and hiked the five miles back to their car. Park rangers are currently investigating the incident, but did confirm no one was hurt.Bigfoot is commonly associated with the Pacific Northwest, but loads of people have claimed to have seen the hairy beast all around 'Murica. Still, there's no legit proof that the big boi actually exists. "Bigfoot hairs" analyzed by the FBI in the 70s turned out to be from deer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 10:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/07/3871907/3871907_906CE63625664287AE1FEC99D7509652_190807_3871907_Man_fires_gun_at_national_park_over_Bigfoot_sigh_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0CB/88B/0CB88B4DE68088593EC657CC66ADE666.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bigfoot, sasquatch, bigfoot sighting, sasquatch sighting, bigfoot country, mammoth cave national park, kentucky, campsite, bigfoot campsite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871844</guid>
      <title>Man dumps fridge in ravine, cops make him haul it back up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALMERIA, SPAIN  Spanish police have forced a very intelligent man to retrieve a fridge he dumped down a ravine near the city of Almeria.How did authorities connect the refrigerator at the bottom of the ravine to the man? Because he had his friend make a video of it, which then went viral over social media.  The 24-year-old criminal mastermind is seen pushing the fridge down the hill, while his friend says, "We're going to recycle it. How many twists and turns has it done?"Apparently, Einstein was working for a waste management company, who has since fired him. The human brain was then fined $50,000 and forced to dispose of the appliance correctly. In some hilarious footage posted by the Spanish cops, two men equipped with ropes and straps are seen struggling to pull the fridge back up the steep hillside. According to the Guardian, Megamind said to local media, "I really regret what I've done because it's meant I've lost my job and has aggravated the problems I have with anxiety. All I want now is for this to go away."Maybe you should just dump it into some ravine.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 09:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/07/3871844/3871844_AFF52611249B42B586458534107640AF_190807_3871844_Man_dumps_fridge_in_ravine__cops_make_him_haul_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5C3/DA4/5C3DA46A443E56928B2FA6D79D6E822D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man dumps fridge in ravine, man hauls up fridge from ravine, spain man dumps fridge, cops make man haul up fridge, police make man haul up refrigerator]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871699</guid>
      <title>McDonald's paper straws not recyclable says leaked memo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Mickey D's attempt to go green tanked spectacularly after a leaked memo revealed their new paper straws aren't recyclable.According to the BBC, the fast food giant axed plastic straws from all it's UK branches last year, which got it many pats on the back for being environmentally responsible.Customers were made to use paper straws, which ended up being insanely unpopular because they were so annoying to drink out of.But as it turned out, the much-hated straws weren't even recyclable  at least, not yet. According to an internal McD's memo obtained by The Sun, the paper versions needed to be binned and burned. Ironically, the old plastic straws were 100% recyclable. While the chain claims chucking the paper straws is temporary, it seems that was the final straw for customers, who hated the damn things anyway.The BBC reports that there's now a petition to bring back the plastic straws, signed by over 51,000 customers.The old plastic straws have been hot on eBay, apparently, with one chap even paying a small fortune for a 100-piece bundle. Crazy!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 04:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/07/3871699/3871699_000292FA7CD84FD7943E4D70206A2FFF_190807_3871699_McDonald_s_paper_straws_not_recyclable_says_leak_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EB6/16C/EB616CC882CC903BAEE01FF8FA5FC110.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mcdonalds, mcdonalds paper straws, paper straws, plastic straws, recycling, eco friendly, mcdonalds leaked memo, straws, fast food straws]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3871639</guid>
      <title>'Muscle man' breaks into 
vending machine for life-size doll</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  CCTV images of a man in China who smashed his way into a vending machine stocking rubber dolls on the August 2 have gone viral over Weibo.China Press was on hand to report on the man who, after breaking free the life-sized doll, went into the corner and 'got busy' for about 40 minutes. The owner of the machine admitted to remotely watching the then live surveillance with his friend and was happy and excited to stream his stock 'being used'.That was until he checked the transaction history and realized that the man hadn't paid.Furious at the, what the report calls, "muscle man" for not processing the right kind of transaction, the vendor drove to the scene with police in tow.Music: Sexy by Bensoundhttp://www.bensound.com/]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 02:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/07/3871639/3871639_6BA9209D513C4BC29161E5A5CAA9656E_190807_3871639__Muscle_man__breaks_into__vending_machine_for_li_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man breaks into vending machine to steal life-size doll, man in china steals doll from vending machine, Chinese viral videos, china videos, Chinese man steals a life-sized doll from vending machine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872539</guid>
      <title>Kissing couple plunge to their deaths from bridge in Peru</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUSCO, PERU  A couple in Peru is sadly no longer around after toppling over a bridge while kissing. According to local reports, the incident occurred around 1 a.m. on Saturday, August 3. According to news outlet Panamerica, 34-year-old Maybeth Espinoza and 36-year-old Hector Vidal were on their way home from a club when they stopped for a passionate embrace on Bethlehem Bridge. Panamerica reported the couple were climbers who had moved to the region to work as tour guides. CCTV footage released by Canal N captured the moment Espinoza was sitting on top of the bridge railing and she loses her balance. She can be seen trying to wrap her legs around Vidal as he attempts to pull her back.Unfortunately, both end up falling over the railings off the bridge and dropping down 50 feet below. Local reports say both were still alive when emergency crews arrived on scene. Both were immediately rushed to the hospital, but Espinoza passed away while in the ambulance, and Vidal while at the hospital. Authorities say the incident was investigated, however it's unclear if it is still ongoing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 12:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/08/3872539/3872539_06EE4A42CB9C46418CFD6B98D3506943_190808_3872539_Kissing_couple_plunge_to_their_deaths_from_bridg_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE4/EE5/BE4EE51E19816786377AFC7F7E7A0A9D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, couple kissing on bridge, kissing on bridge, Cusco Bethlehem Bridge, Bethlehem Bridge incident, kissing couple Bethlehem Bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872465</guid>
      <title>U.S. plans to build new naval base in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DARWIN, AUSTRALIA  The United States could be putting up a new military port in Australia.According to Reuters, Australian Foreign Minister Marise Payne said Tuesday that the U.S. Navy plans to build military infrastructure in the country, once Congress approves $211.5 million in funding.While Payne did not specify the type of infrastructure, Australian media reported that Washington's plans are for a new port.Multiple officials told the ABC the facility would be in Darwin's Glyde Point, and could eventually accommodate large amphibious warships like Australia's Landing Helicopter Docks, and vessels such as the USS Wasp.Each year, 2,500 U.S. marines are deployed to Australia in an annual rotation for training, and are housed at an Australian army base in Darwin. With the new facility, American marines could operate more readily in the region, according to ABC.Reuters reports that the plan comes amid increasing concerns with China's expansion in the Pacific.The existing Port of Darwin is currently leased to Chinese company Landbridge for 99 years, and is located just 40 kilometers from the future U.S. port in Glyde Point.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 10:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/08/3872465/3872465_C6EBA7AB72EF42C6B9F55F144FD765BF_190808_3872465_U_S__plans_to_build_new_naval_base_in_Australia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/042/905/042905320EF6B11B088B965AD701BEBA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, us naval base, us base, us base australia, port of darwin, glyde point port, glyde point base, australia naval base, us military base]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872439</guid>
      <title>Philippines declares dengue epidemic as deaths rise</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHILIPPINES  The Philippines' dengue virus outbreak has just reached epidemic proportions. According to the Philippine News Agency, health authorities declared a national dengue epidemic on Tuesday, after more than 100,000 cases from January to July this year, and 622 deaths.The country's Health Secretary Francisco Duque said the declaration will allow local government units in badly hit places to access quick response funds to help fight the outbreak.Government agencies will also be carrying out a campaign to destroy mosquito breeding sites.According to the Guardian, the mosquito-borne viral infection is found in tropical countries, and can cause joint pain, high fevers, and a rash, among other symptoms.Nature reports that in severe cases, it can cause plasma to leak out of the capillaries, leading to breathing problems, hemorrhagic fever, and organ failure.Dengue has no specific treatment, but according to The Guardian, medical care is necessary as it is critical to maintain a person's fluid levels.An existing vaccine called Dengvaxia has been banned in the Philippines after several dozen children died during a government immunization campaign in 2017.The U.S. FDA approved the Dengvaxia vaccine this year, with several restrictions. The New York Times reports that other vaccines are currently being developed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 10:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/08/3872439/3872439_E588141713004324A28FC73AF5C0F1BA_190808_3872439_Philippines_declares_dengue_epidemic_as_deaths_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CC8/281/CC82812802E936D1379C83C8EF895099.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dengue, dengue epidemic, dengue virus, philippine dengue epidemic, mosquito virus, viral infection, dengvaxia, dengue vaccine, dengue symptoms, dengue treatment, severe dengue, plasma leakage]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872271</guid>
      <title>North Korea stole $ 2bn in cyberattacks to fund its nukes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA  North Korea has conducted cyberattacks to steal an estimated US$2 billion to fund its nuclear weapons program, Reuters reports, citing a confidential U.N. report.The report says North Korea continued to strengthen its weapons program over the past six months, even though they have not conducted any nuclear tests or intercontinental ballistic missile launches.According to Reuters, experts said North Korean hackers used "sophisticated attacks" to target financial institutions and cryptocurrency exchanges to generate income. The U.N. was investigating at least 35 cyberattacks by North Korean military intelligence in approximately 17 countries. Experts are also investigating whether North Korea took part in cryptocurrency mining activities to earn money.North Korea has recently been in the news for launching projectiles into the Sea of Japan four times in a span of two weeks. The country has said the consecutive missile launches are a warning against the U.S. and South Korea for carrying out joint military exercises, according to Yonhap News Agency.Reuters says that the U.N. report was completed before North Korea's missile launches last week.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/08/3872271/3872271_854CB66AA6454030B40EA6DC1E84B96B_190808_3872271_North_Korea_stole___2bn_in_cyberattacks_to_fund__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/43B/834/43B83465A006E4FCE36AFCAC1BE8FFDC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, north korea, cyber attacks, north korea cyber attacks, north korean cyber attacks, north korea weapons, north korea news, north korea 2019, kim jong un, north korea cyber attacks weapons program, north korea weapons cyber attack, pyongyang cyber space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872217</guid>
      <title>Burger King drops Impossible Whopper across US restaurants</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  Burger King has dropped the plant-based Impossible Whopper burger throughout its stores across the Good 'Ol U.S. of A. According to Today, B.K. announced last week that its meatless option would be available 'Murica-wide starting today.   According to FoodBev, the burger is made from meat-free patties pumped out by California-based Impossible Food. It will be offered for a limited time starting this week.The Impossible Whopper features a flame-grilled plant patty with tomatoes, onions, lettuce, mayonnaise, ketchup and pickles on a toasted sesame seed bun.Unfortunately, for vegans and vegetarians, the Impossible Whopper may be impossible for them to eat as the Impossible patties will be cooked on the same broiler used for beef and chicken. Another thing that annoys vegans is that the Impossible Whopper has mayo, which is made with eggs. So for people who eat normally, that's an added bonuseating a plant-based burger and getting to annoy ultra-annoying vegans.  But if you're looking to shed some pounds, the Impossible Whopper may not be the way to go as it contains nearly the same amount of calories as a regular Whopper and actually has more carbs and sodium than the meaty option. Either way, introducing a plant-based burger option to the U.S. is a step in the right direction.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 04:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/08/3872217/3872217_4E76AB8BBA2A44B7991971B40AC8367C_190808_3872217_Burger_King_drops_Impossible_Whopper_across_US_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1DA/8E1/1DA8E11C1A132669F4F771B865A1EDC8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Burger King, Burger King Impossible Whopper, Impossible Whopper, Impossible Foods, plant-based burger, plant-based whopper, impossible burger, vegan burger, vegetarian burger]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872968</guid>
      <title>China deploys Robocops with facial recognition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANDAN, CHINA - Handan police officials took to Weibo on Wednesday to share three new members to China's traffic police.The three first-of-their-kind robocops each have their own specialty, with one patrolling, another in traffic accidents and the last, providing information.What can a Patrolling robot do?These are equipped with automatic navigation and can lock onto a car's plates and snap pictures of vehicles. And if you're thinking of jaywalking, forget it! This guy will give you a warning.What about the traffic bot?These data-filled fellas help answer questions at the vehicle-managing bureaus when prompted by querying members of the public.And what about those accident robots? Well, as the name suggests, they're trusted to keep order at the site of a traffic accident.Engineers have installed facial recognition software on all of them, and if that wasn't scary enough, they've added in physical attributes too!These bots can take down perps in the event of an emergency.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 08:35:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/09/3872968/3872968_402C1BC899CB406CAEB58C640DAA84FF_190809_3872968_China_deploys_Robocops_with_facial_recognition_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5AC/C92/5ACC929B014516BBB33B3DB6BBA373B2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  robocop, robocops, robot police, China, AI, robot police, facial recognition, chinese police robots, police state, surveillance, china police robot, china police, nanny state]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872947</guid>
      <title>Moment woman goes crazy over a beach pebble in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANTAI, CHINA  A woman went crazy when her daughter was stopped from pocketing a souvenir stone from a beach on Changdao Island. It's just a stone, right? Wrong! A part of what makes Changdao Island a hot spot for Chinese vacationists is the little round pebbles that make up its beaches. The woman unsurprisingly failed to convince staff when she screamed, "For a 20 dollar entrance fee, I should be able to take one rock!"The Shanghaiist reported there are signs deterring people from pocketing rocks.In October a regulation will be put in place that punishes these stone-stealers with a fine of up to $2,800.Apparently, screaming hysterically is not the bedrock of getting your own way who would have thought?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 08:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/09/3872947/3872947_DF7EE578F2BC4585B388B60374196254_190809_3872947_Moment_woman_goes_crazy_over_a_beach_pebble_in_C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/39F/E4F/39FE4FD40D2AC2C2570E5DF7039E5E90.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, chinese tourists, chinese tourists stealing, bad behaved chinese tourists, stealing stones from a beach]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872946</guid>
      <title>Europe launches EDRS laser satellite to space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KOUROU, FRANCE  The European Space Agency and Airbus have launched their second space laser satellite, the EDRS-C. It was sent into space on an Ariane 5 rocket from Kourou in French Guiana on Aug 6.The EDRS-C will join its sister satellite, the EDRS-A, and operate in geostationary orbit, according to the European Space Agency.  This is approximately 35,786 kilometers above the surface of the Earth, according to Science Direct.Both form part of the European Data Relay System, a satellite constellation.The BBC reports that they will use lasers to collect data from lower orbit Earth satellites called Sentinels. These watch over the planet and capture images of the surface."According to the ESA, the Sentinel-1 orbits at 693 kilometers high, while Sentinel-2 orbits at 786 kilometers.The EDRS can relay data back to Earth at a rate of up to 1.8 gigabits per second. According to the ESA, these satellites were previously only able to transmit information to earth whenever they were in direct line of sight with a ground station. This was every 90 minutes.The addition of EDRS-C cuts that delay to almost nothing, allowing satellites to send data to Earth in almost real-time. The ESA explained that the technology would allow for a faster response to emergency situations.According to the BBC, a third satellite, EDRS-D, is expected to launch before 2025.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 08:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/09/3872946/3872946_D72963761D984DD18F060E71A39F65F4_190809_3872946_Europe_launches_EDRS_laser_satellite_to_space_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE8/A3C/BE8A3CB771EFBE646AE57D7F9F708B33.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, europe, space, space launch, space exploration, EDRS, laser communications network, EDRS space laser telescope, EDRS space laser satellite, european satellite, space laser satellite, europe space agency, european space agency, European Data Relay System, european space exploration, europe's second satellite, EDRS-C, EDRS-A, High Throughput Optical Network, europe space race, airbus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872799</guid>
      <title>Brainwave-detecting headbands being used in Chinese schools</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Chinese schools are using U.S.- based startup company BrainCo's brain scanning headbands to measure students' attention spans, the South China Morning Post reports.The Focus 1 headband uses electroencephalography sensors, or EEGs, to detect students' brain signals. These signals are then translated by an AI algorithm in real time to determine how focused a student is.Signals from the headbands are able to be monitored through a dashboard in real time, according to BrainCo's website. The students' attention levels will be indicated by the color appearing on their headset, the South China Morning Post reports. Blue means the student is relaxed, yellow means the student is focused, and red means the student is extremely focused.BrainCo explained in a statement on Weibo that the headbands are only being used on a trial basis in a few schools in China and that their only purpose is to help students increase their attention span.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 04:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/09/3872799/3872799_3F993AAE0A284B4E9C9D75F9FD882785_190809_3872799_Brainwave_detecting_headbands_being_used_in_Chin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BD0/3D0/BD03D01BB640740894104DE60346092C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, china surveillance, headbands, brain-reading headbands, chinese surveillance, china mass surveillance, china ai system, surveillance, surveillance state, china surveillance, police state, china surveillance system, total surveillance, china brainwave-detecting head bands, chinese classrooms, BrainCo, BrainCo china, brainco tech, brainco headband, brainco eeg]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3872776</guid>
      <title>Tiny 'water bears' may be alive on moon after crash landing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOON  Earth's most indestructible organisms have crashed into the moon, and may still be alive.CNN reports that thousands of micro creatures called tardigrades were onboard Israel's Beresheet spacecraft when it crash landed on the moon in April.According to the BBC, tardigrades are about a millimeter-long, with eight legs, claws, and a sucker-like pharynx to spear prey. They are more commonly known as water bears or moss piglets.CNN reports that they live in water or on plants like lichen or moss, can withstand being heated to 150 degrees Celsius, and frozen to almost absolute zero.The non-profit Arch Mission Foundation dehydrated the water bears, which caused the organisms to enter a state of suspended animation, where metabolism lowers to 0.01% of the normal rate.They were then encased in amber and loaded onto the Beresheet, along with a 30-million page archive of human history called the lunar library.Since the tardigrades are resilient, researchers say it's likely they survived the crash. But they will need to be reintroduced to water in order to reanimate.Until then, guess the little buggers will just be chilling out on the moon. Though if something else gets them first, it could just be a sci-fi horror movie come to life.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 03:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/09/3872776/3872776_1DDF7CE83F774CCE88E899C02753797B_190809_3872776_Tiny__water_bears__may_be_alive_on_moon_after_cr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/086/829/0868295829C6DA8A3D7928B0AC641589.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tardigrades, water bears, water bears in space, tardigrades in space, moss piglets in space, moss piglets, Beresheet spacecraft, tardigrades on moon, moss piglets on moon, water bears on moon, moon creatures, Beresheet crash land]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3873389</guid>
      <title>Disney's new streaming bundle wants to compete with Netflix</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  Disney has finally dragged its clunky feet into the streaming race by offering a bundle of its three streaming servicesDisney+, ad-supported Hulu, and ESPN+ for $12.99 a month starting November 12. The $12.99 price coincidentally happens to be the same as Netflix's standard service tier and Amazon Prime Video. Disney really has the pulse of consumers. Hulubut with commercials? Isn't that just cable TV? But who doesn't like a fewor a tonof annoying ads while streaming shows? Mickey really connected with a grand slam including ESPN+  especially since the bundle is only offered in the U.S.  where finding sports content or fat people talking about sports is next to impossible.Disney+ is the diamond in the rough that people will come for. All your favorite Disney cartoons, their live-action remakes, their eventual remasters, which will hopefully then get recycled back into cartoons, all in one placethe Disney creative circle of life.     But the real questionactually the only onehow many times will Disney let you share your password?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 06:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/10/3873389/3873389_0C06716B65C04DE6A2BD4B67C23DAE7C_190810_3873389_Disney_s_new_streaming_bundle_wants_to_compete_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE4/898/CE48987F1D4156588C6DEB20FCFE3A91.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Disney streaming, Disney+, Disney v Netflix, Disney vs Netflix, Disney live action, Disney streaming service]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3873371</guid>
      <title>China to boycott Taiwan's Oscars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Beijing will be boycotting Taiwan's answer to the Oscars in its latest attempt to rain on the island nation's parade.According to the South China Morning Post, China's film regulator announced Wednesday that Mainland movies, directors, and stars won't be participating in this November's Golden Horse Awards in Taipei.While no reason was provided, it doesn't take a genius to figure out China is hijacking the culture and the arts as a way to throw a massive tantrum.Beijing was likely still butthurt from last year's ceremony, when Taiwanese director Fu Yue took to the stage for her acceptance speech and expressed hope that Taiwan would one day be recognized as an independent country.The Taiwanese weren't terribly fazed by news of the boycott.Democratic Progressive Party legislator Karen Yu said she's grateful China had willingly withdrawn. At least now, the Taiwanese and other Chinese folk not from the Mainland can enjoy the festivities without having to tiptoe around the large red elephant in the room.And China being China, they'll probably be trying to come up with their own Golden Horse knockoff. Golden Panda Film Awards, anyone?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2019 06:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/10/3873371/3873371_4517D3BCC964407790EE6FCFFDA0F0BB_190810_3873371_China_to_boycott_Taiwan_s_Oscars_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9B2/811/9B281176A336458A2B800021D801BDCA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china boycott, taiwan film festival, taiwan oscars, golden horse, golden horse awards, golden horse film awards, chinese oscars, china film boycott, china tantrum]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874529</guid>
      <title>Scientists develop vaccine to help people with cat allergies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZURICH  Life may be getting a lot easier for folks who adore felines but can't stop sneezing or wheezing around them.According to a study published in the Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology, cat allergies are typically caused by the protein Fel d 1, which is found in feline saliva, tears, and pelt.When the protein enters the system of someone with a cat allergy, it triggers a reactive rush of histamines, leading to itching, wheezing, and other symptoms.Ten percent of the general human population suffers from cat allergies, but there is no safe or efficient therapy currently available. The usual recourse for patients is to treat allergy symptoms and avoid cats.Three point four million cats are abandoned at U.S. cat shelters each year, and allergies suffered by owners, family, and friends are a leading cause of the abandonment.According to a news release from Hypopet, scientists in Zurich have developed a vaccine, which when injected into a cat instructs the immune system to produce antibodies that target and destroy the Fel d 1 protein.Testing on 54 cats in four different studies found that the antibodies successfully neutralized the allergens. The vaccine, called Hypocat, was also reported to be well-tolerated without any over toxicity.According to Fox 13, the vaccine could be available within three years, with both humans and animals benefiting from the treatment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 15:58:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/12/3874529/3874529_B1C4D58401B64FE48324DD50BCD7A662_190812_3874529_Scientists_develop_vaccine_to_help_people_with_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E3D/9DA/E3D9DA690D4AF179BBB3EDFB0DC735C8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cat allergy, cat allergy vaccine, animal allergy, feline allergy, cat allergy cure, cat vaccine, hypocat, hypopet, cat allergen, allergens, histamines, allergies, how allergies work]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874382</guid>
      <title>Daredevil dies trying to parachute from 150 foot chimney in Spain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALICANTE, SPAIN  A daredevil who had the bright idea to sneak into a factory during the middle of the night to jump off a 150ft chimney is no longer around after his parachute failed to open. According to the Sun, 29-year-old Ruben Carbonell and a friend apparently hopped a fence to get into the Cemex cement factory in hopes of making a smash hit video for social media.The Sun reports that once the two were inside, they both climbed to the top of a chimney.According to LadBible, Carbonell lept from the chimney first, but unfortunately his parachute didn't open and he plummeted to the ground. His friend immediately called emergency services, but it was clearly too late.According to Metro UK, Cemex confirmed that neither Carbonell or his friend had permission to be in the factory. Authorities are now investigating how the two were able to get in and to the top of the chimney. They're also looking into why Carbonell's chute didn't open. Carbonell was a fan of extreme sports and enjoyed sharing videos of him jumping from bridges and paragliding. Friends and fans visited his fan pages to pay their respects and say their goodbyes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 10:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/12/3874382/3874382_57FA520E4358426F8B0ED95626662C59_190812_3874382_Daredevil_dies_trying_to_parachute_from_150_foot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0B6/D64/0B6D6458C9B5D5C1DDF1A67E65FE5202.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, daredevil, parachute, chimney, parachute chimney, Ruben Carbonell, youtuber Ruben Carbonell]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874378</guid>
      <title>Indian man pushes birthday BMW into the river</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YAMUNANAGAR, INDIA  An Indian manor more like a man-childgot so angry with his dad for buying him a brand new BMW he pushed the new ride into a river. According to the BBC, video posted on social media shows the fine German automobile floating down the river in the northern Indian state of Haryana. According to News 18, Mr. Entitled apparently demanded a Jaguar, so it totally makes sense to throw a man-sized temper tantrum when you only get a Beemer instead.   Unfortunately for Richienot so rich you can buy your own carthe car then proceeded to get stuck on a bank of tall grass in the middle of the river. And luckily, millennials always have the brains to film themselves doing dumb things and then sharing it on the internet for the world to enjoy. The spoiled brat of all brats is then see trying to get the car out of the river with the help of local divers. According to the BBC, police are investigating the incident. Apparently BMWs cost around $49,000 in India, while Jags can run up to around $70,000.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 10:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/12/3874378/3874378_A917285F80494267AF8E595902561B6C_190812_3874378_Indian_man_pushes_birthday_BMW_into_the_river_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0F5/9C2/0F59C2CC518960574A7E546EC8A4CC65.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man pushes BMW in river, Indian man pushes BMW in river, son pushes BMW in river, India, Haryana BMW river]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874226</guid>
      <title>Bear falling on deputy's car causes crash and wildfire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOOP, CALIFORNIA  Hit-and-runs are a dime a dozen in the good ole US of A, but have you ever been hit and run by a bear?One California deputy definitely has.KRCR reports that on August 3, the Humboldt County sheriff's deputy was on his way to the scene of a drug overdose when a bear, of all things, suddenly fell maybe jumped?  from a steep embankment.The animal landed right smack on the car, smashing the hood and the windshield.But it doesn't end there. As a result of the bear cannonball, the patrol car ended up striking an embankment, flipping over on its side, and catching fire. Luckily, the deputy managed to crawl out of the wreckage.The flames ended up engulfing the entire car, and sparking a wildfire after it ignited nearby vegetation on the embankment. While the deputy wasn't seriously hurt, no one's got a clue what happened to the bear, except that it fled.The wildfire burned about half an acre before eventually being put out by responding firefighters.Damn, all the trouble because of a bear.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 06:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/12/3874226/3874226_57B4090FBCAB44BE9EFD732A8A2B2297_190812_3874226_Bear_falling_on_deputy_s_car_causes_crash_and_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F58/685/F58685D12ED56F70CA66FF09B266D07B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, falling bear, bear falls on car, hit and run bear, bear drops out of the sky, car crash, wildfire, california wildfire, car accident, bear trouble, yogi bear, california bear]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874149</guid>
      <title>Higher levels of toxic mercury found in tuna and cod</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  New research has linked an increase of toxic mercury in marine life to global warming and overfishing.Research by Harvard scientists analyzed data from the Gulf of Maine in the Atlantic Ocean.  According to Reuters, it found a 23 percent increase of methylmercury, a type of organic mercury, in cod fish and 27 percent in bluefin tuna over the past 30 years.The study, published in the journal Nature, found that as the climate warms the oceans, bigger fish such as bluefin tuna eat more because they need more energy. This means they consume more prey with higher levels of methylmercury."Researchers also found that overfishing of smaller herring and sardines had changed the diet of Atlantic cod, with the fish now eating larger herrings and lobsters. Both contain higher levels of methylmercury.The research notes that the consumption of contaminated fish could impact human health. It says that methylmercury has been associated with long-term neurocognitive dysfunction in children that were exposed to methylmercury while in the womb.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 03:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/12/3874149/3874149_DBA6558EC6AF48EFADF7C459221225AC_190812_3874149_Higher_levels_of_toxic_mercury_found_in_tuna_and_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/541/82B/54182B4CBF61C72EC3FB4CA0C6B6287F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tuna, climate change, toxic fish, fish climate change, overfishing, cod, tuna overfishing, effects of climate change, climate change marine line, climate change fish, impact of climate change on fisheries, toxic mercury tuna, methylmercury, climate change mercury, fish full of mercury, mercury in fish]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875079</guid>
      <title>End of El Nino may lead to more active Atlantic hurricane season</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SILVER SPRING, MARYLAND  The chances of an above-normal Atlantic hurricane season in 2019 have increased now that El Nino is over.According to the NOAA, El Nino occurs when sea-surface temperatures in the equatorial Pacific are warmer than average, and east winds blow weaker than usual.The agency declared Thursday that El Nino has ended and transitioned into a neutral state, bringing normal water temperatures and atmospheric conditions to the central and eastern Pacific.El Nino typically suppresses hurricane activity in the Atlantic, so its end could mean a busier hurricane season.The NOAA says oceanic and atmospheric conditions are now favorable for an above-normal Atlantic hurricane season.It is expecting 10 to 17 named storms, 5 to 9 of which will become hurricanes, and two to four major hurricanes with winds of 111 miles per hour or greater.However, Colorado State University tropical scientist Phil Klotzbach has noted that continuing warmth in the central Pacific over the next few months could prevent winds from becoming too hurricane-favorable in the Atlantic and Caribbean.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 14:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/13/3875079/3875079_09921C7907444DA08244A79BECF9E635_190813_3875079_End_of_El_Nino_may_lead_to_more_active_Atlantic__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AAC/807/AAC807B79FB2F46FB0A7C855A5596477.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, El Nino, ENSO, ENSO neutral, La Nina, weather, weather patterns, extreme weather patterns, atlantic hurricanes, hurricane season, atlantic hurricane season, storms, atlantic storms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874989</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong airport cancels flights as thousands peacefully protest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Hong Kong International Airport axed all departures on Monday because of thousands of peaceful anti-government protesters. According to the BBC, many in attendance were protesting police brutality. Chinese authorities on Sunday were filmed firing tear gas and non-lethal ammunition at super close range indoors. In a Monday afternoon statement, Hong Kong's Airport Authority said they were canceling all flights that were not yet checked in. The BBC reported that over 160 flights scheduled to leave after 6 p.m. local time on Monday faced the chopping block. According to the BBC, officials said arrivals that were already on their way to Hong Kong would still be cleared to land, but other scheduled flights had to be canceled. Hong Kong policewith the blessing of Beijing no doubthave increased their use of non-lethal bullets and tear gas. Several videos posted to social media on Sunday show Hong Kong police dressed in riot gear storming enclosed railway stations firing tear gas.Footage from another station shows officers firing non-lethal rounds at point blank range and mobs of police beating people with batons.   How much longer will the protests continue before Beijing sends a bloodier message? Either way, Hong Kong will continue to stand strong.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 11:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/13/3874989/3874989_37423F8CD5BE4A1BAEC3734753457D4E_190813_3874989_Hong_Kong_airport_cancels_flights_as_thousands_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5EE/4AC/5EE4AC07B5F27CDAB5BD539A3099C992.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong protesters, Hong Kong airport cancels flights, airport cancels all flights, Hong Kong Airport protests, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874881</guid>
      <title>Dog survives plunge from  building roof in New York</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A French bulldog miraculously survived a plunge off a six-story building in Manhattan on August 2.On a Reddit post, the bulldog's owner, Emma Heinrich, explained that she had just finished walking her dog, Winston, when he suddenly dashed up a flight of stairs in their apartment building after she removed his leash. Winston managed to get through the roof's access door and towards the edge of the roof.Emma chased him up the roof only to see her beloved dog fall off the top of the building.Winston crashed through the sunroof of a parked car and landed in the front seat, according to an Instagram post by Emma. She immediately rushed downstairs and found that her French bulldog had survived! She pulled him out of the car and rushed him to the vet. Winston bruised his lungs and had to stay in an oxygen chamber for 36 hours. Remarkably, he didn't break a single bone.Emma told CNN that Winston is home already and is starting to return to his playful self.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 09:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/13/3874881/3874881_81AC357C0E47453D89B75C64B6989637_190813_3874881_Dog_survives_plunge_from__building_roof_in_New_Y_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/39E/AF2/39EAF2055BE33563F6E8043C10B95761.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dog falls from building, dog survives fall off building, dog survives fall, dog falls off building and survives, bulldog car sunroof, animals, pets, dog falls sunroof, dog falls through car sunroof, french bulldog, lower east side, dog crashes through car sunroof, french bulldog fall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874786</guid>
      <title>Versace apologizes over t-shirt that triggered thin-skinned China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Versace apologized on Sunday after one of its T-shirts accidentally listed Hong Kong and Macau as separate countries, triggering the outrage of thin-skinned Chinese netizens. According to Reuters, the Italian luxury brand is the latest to get tangled up in political issues involving Beijing and its policing of how foreign companies describe the former European colonies.The company said in a statement, "Versace reiterates that we love China deeply, and resolutely respect China's territory and national sovereignty."Translationwe're glad Chinese people spend money on Verace crap and understand that this lame apology will be enough to keep you suckers buying. The T-shirt, which was posted on Twitter knockoff Weibo, features a list of city-country pairs like "New York-USA" and "Rome-Italy" in a super creative Times New Roman font. So Versace made this using Microsoft Word? That's luxury for you. Anyways, when it got to Macau and Hong Kong, they were listed as "Hong Kong-Hong Kong and Macau-Macau." Cue the ultra-triggered Chinese netizens and the hurt feelings of the Chinese people. Maybe what Versace should make next is some thicker skin for Chinese people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 07:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/13/3874786/3874786_6A4CD702249C4A7C8C0999C8C3B18CB0_190813_3874786_Versace_apologizes_over_t_shirt_that_triggered_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/09F/93B/09F93B7134F5048D417462075EC575F2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Versace, Versace apologizes to China, Versace Hong Kong t shirt, Versace Macau t shirt, Chinese netizens angry]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874687</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong police fire tear gas, rubber bullets into metro station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Activists in Hong Kong continued to protest the Hong Kong government for the tenth weekend in a row.The protests are against an extradition bill that would allow suspects to be extradited for trial to mainland China. Those against the bill believe that Beijing may use it as a way to extradite political activists, dissidents and other critics in the city.The Hong Kong government has suspended the bill, but protesters are calling for the government to withdraw it altogether.On Sunday, protesters were taking part in a peaceful rally in Hong Kong's Victoria Park when they defied police orders and starting marching along Cheung Sha Wan Road, a major thoroughfare in the city.Activists used the flash-mob strategy to appear in different parts of the city and threw two petrol bombs at police, injuring one officer, Reuters reports. As the protesters made their way to a metro station in Kwai Chung, an urban area in Hong Kong, police attempted to disperse the crowd by firing tear gas and rubber bullets, according to Hong Kong Free Press. Other police officers were filmed chasing people and using batons to hit them while on the metro escalator, reports the BBC. Peaceful protests have been taking place at Hong Kong's International Airport since August 9 as an attempt to seek international support for Hong Kong's ongoing protests.Activists have called for Hong Kong's leader Carrie Lam to resign. They are also pushing for an independent investigation into alleged police brutality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 03:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/13/3874687/3874687_488BFCEF34DC47409963D39A11B1F8CD_190813_3874687_Hong_Kong_police_fire_tear_gas__rubber_bullets_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D6D/552/D6D552601B310C4737B0C6790DBA85EB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, HK mass protest, Hong Kong mass protest, China extradition, China extradition protests, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong,  Hong Kong protest 2019, Hong Kong protest today, hk protests latest news, hk protests 2019, hong kong police protest, hong kong protest 2019 tear gas, hong kong police fire tear gas, hong kong protests metro, hong kong metro tear gas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3874670</guid>
      <title>Sustainable park with 'solar trees' planned for Ho Chi Minh City</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HO CHI MINH CITY, VIETNAM  Australian architectural firms LAVA Architects and Aspect Studios have partnered together and won a competition to design Ho Chi Minh City's new sustainable Central Park.The park will replace the existing September 23 Park, which is in the city's central urban district, according to LAVA Architects' project website. The sustainable public park will include artificial plants and futuristic "solar trees" with angled solar panels to generate renewable energy to power the park's digital information screens and Wi-Fi system.The park will also feature "water purification trees" and "ventilation trees." The "water purification trees" will gather and recycle rainwater for watering purposes, drinking fountains and fire hydrants, while the "ventilation trees" will be used to generate fresh air and reduce heat in the park.Central Park will include open green spaces with music and theater performance pavilions, playgrounds and sculpture gardens for the general public.The architects plan to link the park with Ho Chi Minh City's new Ben Thanh metro station, which is still under construction.LAVA Architect's website states that construction on the park is to begin in 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 03:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/13/3874670/3874670_D435243A61B449C384181F7C23C58BD2_190813_3874670_Sustainable_park_with__solar_trees__planned_for__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7A3/AA9/7A3AA9DF3920886E83677122B81C97FF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, infrastructure, architecture, sustainable architecture, ho chi minh city central park, September 23 Park, Aspect Studios, Laboratory for Vision Architecture, ho chi minh city architecture, sustainable park, solar trees, LAVA architecture, vietnam architecture, ho chi minh architecture]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875599</guid>
      <title>Bear breaks into house, leaves by smashing through wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ESTES PARK, COLORADO  A bear in Colorado cartoon-smashed its way out of a house in a scene straight out of a Looney Tunes skit...or a juice commercial.Homeowner John Sliwinski told 9News that he'd taken the trash into the house Friday night so it wouldn't attract any bears, but then went upstairs without closing the door.In no time at all, a bear sauntered in and went straight for the deviled eggs in the garbage, accidentally shutting the door in the process.The perp was frantically chewing and scratching at the wall when officers arrived. But rather than risk police custody, it opted for a daring escape and smashed straight through the wall.Guess watching all those Kool-Aid commercials finally paid off.Estes Park Police posted about the incident on their Facebook page. They also put up a warning to lock houses and vehicles and keep the wildlife wild  which translates to: stop feeding the damn animals.Bears are pretty smart. Feed 'em once and they'll keep coming back to your house or car whether you're there or not.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 14:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/14/3875599/3875599_CBBF373F25024A4B8EB9F2F2ECBFA21E_190814_3875599_Bear_breaks_into_house__leaves_by_smashing_throu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/320/B31/320B31B52C958AFC579C1AB1ACB5F861.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bear, bear breaks into house, bear escape, bear dramatic escape, Kool Aid, Kool Aid man, bear smashes through wall, cartoon smash, bear escapes police]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875517</guid>
      <title>Guy is only passenger on Delta flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ASPEN, COLORADO  A passenger on a Delta flight had the time of his life when he turned out to be the only one riding on it.Vincent Peone turned out to be the only passenger on a Delta flight from Aspen, Colorado to Salt Lake City, Utah, so naturally he took to Twitter to chronicle his good fortune. According to Business Insider, his video starts out with him being the only person at the gate when boarding is announced for flight DL3652. He then chats up the ground crew as he walks out to the Delta connection flight operated by SkyWest Airlines. Vincent also filmed ramp workers loading sandbags into the aircraft cargo hold in order to give the plane enough weight since it wasn't carrying any passengerswell, besides Peone.The flight attendant also welcomed him with his own personal message saying, "Good evening, Vincent, and welcome aboard. We look forward to taking care of you today." The hilarious video ends with Vincent thanking the pilots and him posing by the airplane door like a true balleron a budget. According to Business Insiders, flights like this don't normally get canceled because airlines need to get the plane and crew to the destination for later flights.So next time if you have to ride Delta, make sure to ask them if you can be the only passenger.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 11:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/14/3875517/3875517_0CB87CE373634CD3A4725820F5A694EB_190814_3875517_Guy_is_only_passenger_on_Delta_flight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/42D/B96/42DB96D7E475D2B88895C8DCF14086C5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Delta, Delta airlines flight, single passenger Delta flight, single passenger on plane, one passenger on flight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875415</guid>
      <title>Chinese mom lets son piss by her feet on public bus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FOSHAN, CHINA  Riders were treated to some fresh man-made lemonade when a mom just sat back while her bundle of joy relieved himself on a public bus in China.  Video footage posted to Miaopai shows a bus full of commuters in Guangdong province when nature comes calling.  The clip shows the mom of the year just leisurely sitting back while little man goes number one right onto the floorewwww.Mommy dearest is clearly unfazed by all of this as doesn't even bother to move her feet to avoid the obvious splash back. And as for good parenting, this woman definitely gets an A plus. Sure, maybe she could have told the driver to pull over. Or found a bottle or bag for little dude to let loose in. Or apologized to the other bus riders. Or just not let him go. Alright, maybe a B minus in parenting.Hey, we've all been in emergency situations when you just got to go. Maybe just not directly onto the floor of the bus next time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 09:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/14/3875415/3875415_673B2E8D47D24239A5C92A2211036B91_190814_3875415_Chinese_mom_lets_son_piss_by_her_feet_on_public__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A2B/771/A2B7713FDAE599FA60976D401366A3E1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, china public bus, Guangdong public bus, mom, Chinese mom, Chinese mom on bus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875389</guid>
      <title>Ninja's phone number stunt just data-gathering marketing scheme</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRAYSLAKE, ILLINOIS  Self-titled streamer, 'Ninja' has been caught fooling fans into giving up their personal details for a data-gathering marketing scheme. YouTuber Tyler 'Ninja' Blevins shocked thousands of fans on the 11th of August when he tweeted a video giving out his personal number with the promise of privately messaging those who contacted him and even playing Fortnite with them. After messaging him, fans were required to fill out some personal information such as name, gender, birthday, city, and the optional choice of email. However, Ninja here was actually fooling fans into a data-gathering marketing scheme managed by a company called Community.  According to gaming site Polygon, who investigated the suspicious post, clicking on the terms of use shows that by sending off your info to Tyler, you're also signing up to automated alerts from Tyler's public relations team, including marketing material.Community also says that by agreeing to the terms, you understand that a message coming from Tyler may not even be from him, but instead from Ninja's team.Community also collects your IP address, your browser selection, device, and your location.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 08:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/14/3875389/3875389_D78BAE15D5404A559DB080F039E3D1BF_190814_3875389_Ninja_s_phone_number_stunt_just_data_gathering_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3D5/93F/3D593FE3326A9EB5906E63AC90FB7DAA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Ninja, Twitch, Tyler 'Ninja' Blevins, Fortnite, Ninja data gathering, ninja's phone number, Ninja's phone number stunt, Ninja marketing, Ninja phone number scam, ninja phone number real]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875293</guid>
      <title>Fungus wiping out the world's bananas reaches the Americas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOGOTA, COLUMBIA  Officials from the Colombian Agricultural and Livestock Authority have confirmed that the tropical race 4 fungus has spread to the country's Cavendish banana plantations.Cavendish bananas dominate the global export market. The Cavendish are a monoculture, meaning they have identical genetics and are therefore equally vulnerable to the fungus.Food producers tend to raise crops with little to no gene diversity in order to grow fruits and vegetables efficiently and at a lower cost.Panama disease Tropical Race 4, also called TR4, is spread through infected planting material as well as infested soil and water, according to Promusa.org, a platform that shares information related to bananas.Once the fungus is in the soil of the Cavendish banana plant, it stops water from entering the plant, essentially disrupting its vascular system. The infected plants eventually stop producing fruit.According to Promusa.org, the TR4 fungus cannot be removed from the plantation soil by use of fumigants, a type of pesticide for fields, or by fungicides, a type of chemical to destroy fungus.The website suggests rotating the banana plants with fungus-resistant crops such as leeks in order for bananas to continue to be produced in the same soil.The TR4 fungus was first identified in Taiwan and has since been found in Southeast Asia, Australia, the Middle East, Africa and now in Latin America, according to the National Geographic. This is not the first time the banana industry has faced this kind of crisis. In the 1950s, the Gros Michel[g][h][i] was the main variety of banana grown for export. It was declared commercially extinct in 1965 due to a different strain of Panama disease. Gros Michel trees were burned down and it was replaced by the Cavendish, which was immune to that disease.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 05:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/14/3875293/3875293_9C788DF1A7784A3A8A3CDDF16787DB0F_190814_3875293_Fungus_wiping_out_the_world_s_bananas_reaches_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/74F/B22/74FB22263C3B18810FAED863A0A22038.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, banana, banana fungus, banana fungus columbia, tropical race 4, tropical race 4 banana, banana fungus 2019, cavendish banana, cavendish banana trees, cavendish banana extinction, banana plantations, panama disease tropical race 4, banana farms, banana farms columbia, TR-4 banana, Fusarium, banana extinct, fungus threatens banana]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875263</guid>
      <title>Archaeologists find evidence of Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JERUSALEM  Archaeologists may have unearthed evidence to confirm the Biblical account of Jerusalem's destruction by the Babylonians.Haaretz reports that an international team led by the University of North Carolina at Charlotte has uncovered layers of ash deposits on Mount Zion, which contained artifacts such as a rare piece of jewelry and arrowheads.According to UNC Charlotte professor Shimon Gibson, this combination of artifacts indicates some kind of destruction or devastation at the site, since "Nobody abandons gold jewelry and nobody has arrowheads in their domestic refuse."Haaretz reports that the ash layers were dated to the Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem in 587 or 586 B.C.E. using pottery fragments and oil lamps typical of the period.The arrowheads were identified as Scythian, made of copper alloy and iron. They are known to have been used by Babylonian archers, according to Ancient Origins.Haaretz reports that the discoveries support the hypothesis that Jerusalem was a sprawling and rich city when it was besieged by the Babylonians, and not a small hilltop citadel like some have suggested.The UNC Charlotte team may have also found what may be a significant structure from the Iron Age. As the building lies beneath layers from different periods, it has yet to be excavated. Archaeologists say they will likely begin in 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 04:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/14/3875263/3875263_E52F1F2591AE479E84C63D6A16A5CA52_190814_3875263_Archaeologists_find_evidence_of_Babylonian_conqu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A38/FCC/A38FCCAA6D78D1C1BABB2247AE3BFE96.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, archeology, mount zion, ancient jerusalem, Babylonian conquest of Jerusalem, Babylonian destruction of Jerusalem, old Jerusalem, Iron Age Jerusalem, David's Jerusalem, Biblical archaeology, Bible]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875241</guid>
      <title>Ovary lump with teeth and hair found to be woman's twin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BURNTWOOD, STAFFORDSHIRE, U.K   A 23-year-old mum-of-two was shaken to find that a cyst on her ovaries was actually her very own twin, teeth and hair included. Hannah Bridgewater from Burntwood, Staffordshire, now 29, was nine months pregnant with daughter Lexie at the time when she collapsed and was rushed into hospital. The Sun reports that in 2012 doctors discovered a 'lemon-sized cyst' on her right ovary before unearthing remnants of teeth, hair, and nail that matched her DNA. Initially, medics believed the body parts must have belonged to Lexie's twin, however, they soon realized they were too old for that to be true.Doctors told Hannah that it must have been her own twin that she had been carrying around inside her before she was even born.Hannah said, "it had always been there, they just never found it  Twins do run in my family, my aunties are twins and I also have twin cousins."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 03:49:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/14/3875241/3875241_F8BCC0E9DE7F46E289AB3FD67A9EADC4_190814_3875241_Ovary_lump_with_teeth_and_hair_found_to_be_woman_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F51/CE2/F51CE26E43DC21ADD9BE432BAD996226.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ovary cyst is twin, ovary lump with teeth and hair, ovary lump is twin, twin growing inside woman, U.K woman twin inside her, woman's cyst is actually twin, cyst teeth hair]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876265</guid>
      <title>How can China intervene in the Hong Kong protests?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  With the Chinese government strongly criticizing the now months-long protests in Hong Kong, many have wondered when the party's patience will end and what route Beijing will use to quiet the dissent.Here are a few of their options.According to CNN, Chinese military forces seen near the border city of Shenzhen are fueling speculation that China could use them to quell protests in Hong Kong.But the BBC reports that under the city's Basic Law, direct military intervention is possible only if the Hong Kong government requests it. Instead, the South China Morning Post reports China is putting pressure on Hong Kong's police force to end the protests.According to the BBC, China could also turn to political intervention, since Hong Kong's Legislative Council is only partly democratic, and largely pro-Beijing.China is already showing its power by refusing to accept Chief Executive Carrie Lam's resignation and to let her formally withdraw the controversial extradition bill.Another possibility is for Beijing to target activists, as even without the extradition law, China is capable of detaining individual citizens.According to the South China Morning Post, some Hongkongers have had China immigration officers at the border check photos and messages on their phones.Despite fears of direct intervention, however, the BBC reports that Beijing's most effective tool may be economic. It can target the Hong Kong economy by redirecting investments to other Chinese cities, effectively making them more reliant on China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 15:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/15/3876265/3876265_580EF1206F8146D9A78DFDD96D54ADFA_190815_3876265_How_can_China_intervene_in_the_Hong_Kong_protest_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AB2/D2B/AB2D2B6043F5BD4F2165F0B92274AD7E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hong kong protests, hk protests, hk extradition protest, China military intervention, hk police, China military forces, hong kong unrest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876035</guid>
      <title>FDA warns that drinking bleach won't cure cancer or autism</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SILVER SPRING, MARYLAND  A miracle solution being touted as a cure-all for practically every major illness is apparently nothing more than a household cleaner.  The U.S. FDA had to send out a warning on Monday urging people to stop drinking Miracle Mineral Solution, MMS, and any chlorine dioxide solution, since it's pretty much bleach. According to NBC, the bleachy solution was first promoted two decades ago by a former Scientologist, who went on to establish his own cult of health.It was peddled years later to parents of autistic kids by a former Chicago real estate agent who is not a doctor. From there, it gained a following on social media, akin to the anti-vaxxers and flat earthers.Contrary to what online snake oil peddlers want you to believe, it's not a remedy for cancer, autism, HIV, or any other condition  unless you count dying as a remedy.Specifically, the FDA says MMS and all its other iterations can cause "severe nausea, vomiting, and life-threatening low blood pressure from dehydration."Any sane human would take one whiff of the solution and flush it down the toilet. But apparently some folks are desperate or delusional enough to move past that, feed the noxious liquid to their kids, and expect good results.Data from the American Association of Poison Control Centers indicates that there have been over 16,000 cases of chlorine dioxide poisoning in the last five years. Fifty of these were life threatening, and in eight instances, people actually went kaput.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 09:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/15/3876035/3876035_C1F6D7723CAD479A9CC4EAF0027A7069_190815_3876035_FDA_warns_that_drinking_bleach_won_t_cure_cancer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/094/92C/09492C30E51FC8068DECF26C9DEB1560.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, miracle mineral solution, miracle solution, MMS, miracle cure, chlorine dioxide, autism cure, cancer cure, HIV cure, AIDS cure, bleach, cure all, snake oil, chlorine dioxide solution, FDA, FDA warning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875933</guid>
      <title>Dogs die after playing in pond with blue-green algae</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WILMINGTON, NORTH CAROLINA   Several dogs have become fatally ill after swimming in lakes and ponds and ingesting water contaminated with toxic algae.According to the North Carolina Department of Health and Human Services, toxic blue green algae or cyanobacteria blooms typically infest bodies of stagnant fresh water during warm weather.The New York Times reports that while they can look like floating green sand or scum, some lurk beneath the surface or attach to plants, and may not be immediately visible. Winds can also blow alage from one area into another.Dogs swimming in contaminated lakes or ponds can drink in the algae while in the water, or lick pieces of it off their wet fur.Those playing near the water can also nibble at or eat toxic algae that have dried into clumps on the shore.According to Blue Cross for Pets, toxins produced by blue-green algal blooms can stop a dog's liver from functioning properly.Exposure to toxic algae is almost always fatal, with some types capable of killing a dog just 15 minutes to an hour after ingestion.The dangers of exposing pets to blue-green algae gained national attention this year when a woman in North Carolina lost her three dogs after they went swimming in a pond.Pet owners in Texas and Georgia have also reported dog deaths following exposure to algal toxins.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 07:10:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/15/3875933/3875933_7E123C84C1DF42DF95F9CDDE4CC86A51_190815_3875933_Dogs_die_after_playing_in_pond_with_blue_green_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4DD/A46/4DDA464AB8FD66124CFD4CA0550BC105.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, toxic algae, blue green algae, cyanobacteria, algae dogs, can algae poison dogs, algae ponds, toxic algae ponds, toxic algae warning, blue green algae warning, algae poisoning, cyanobacteria poisoning]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875810</guid>
      <title>Carbon nanotubes may be used to remove microplastics from ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA  A university of Adelaide-led research team has created a carbon nanotube that could help fight microplastic pollution in our oceans.Their research was presented in a study published in the journal Matter and was a collaboration between Australia's University of Adelaide, Curtin University, Edith Cowan University and China's Guangdong University of Technology.The carbon nanotubes are spiral in shape and have magnetic properties. The nanotubes are coated with nitrogen and embedded with manganese in their interior.The nanotubes are then mixed with peroxymonosulfate, a compound used as an oxidizing agent, to generate reactive oxygen species, or chemical reactions, to break down marine microplastics. The result is that the microplastics are converted into salt compounds, carbon dioxide and water.During a trial, researchers found that the spiral nanotubes were able to reduce the volume of microplastics present in polluted water between 30 to 50 percent in the span of eight hours.The nanotubes are retrieved using magnets for later use.Professor of Chemical Engineering from the University of Adelaide, Shaobin Wang, senior author of the study, explained in a news release from the university that the nanotubes are strong enough to break the microplastics down into compounds that aren't harmful to the ocean's ecosystem.Wang said that the byproducts of microplastics could be recycled and turned into an energy source for microorganisms, such as food for algae growth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 04:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/15/3875810/3875810_96355325CF854DB9876FD9A29B7B820B_190815_3875810_Carbon_nanotubes_may_be_used_to_remove_microplas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1A2/AA6/1A2AA60104917F0CDD14B8F78AD25B26.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, microplastics, plastic particles, microplastics pollution,  plastic bags, plastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, plastic litter, tiny spirals, microplastics, tiny spirals microplastics, getting rid of microplastic in the ocean, microplastics in the ocean, microplastics in water, microplastic pollution, microplastic ocean pollution, microplastic ocean, plastic ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3875776</guid>
      <title>Metal wing covering falls off China Eastern Airlines after takeoff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  Passengers onboard China Eastern Airlines Flight MU588 from New York to Shanghai were in for a surprise when metal covering the airplane's wing fell off after takeoff on August 12.Shocked travelers were quick to share images on social media.The flight took off from John F. Kennedy International Airport at 7:02 p.m., two and a half hours after its scheduled time of 4:25 p.m., according to Flight Radar 24.It's unclear why the flight was delayed.Hou Yangfang, a Fudan University professor who was traveling on the flight, told the Shanghai Daily that several passengers had noticed that the plane's left wing was missing part of its metal covering shortly after takeoff. They were quick the warn the flight's crew members.The flight's captain then made an announcement saying that the aircraft would be heading back to New York's JFK International Airport. But first, the plane circled many times past Albany. Hou explained that the aircraft did this to discharge fuel.After the plane landed in JFK International Airport at 7:25 p.m., all 300 passengers had to wait for an hour and a half inside the airplane. They also had to wait an additional two hours for their luggage.Hou told the newspaper that they weren't given any more information about the situation, though, he added, they had been accomodated.In a statement to the Shanghai Daily, China Eastern Airlines said that a malfunction in Flight MU588 was detected shortly after takeoff. The company added that another flight would be arranged for the passengers soon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 03:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/15/3875776/3875776_AA50E77E9A514238BCB4B07972772AAD_190815_3875776_Metal_wing_covering_falls_off_China_Eastern_Airl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China Eastern Airlines, Flight MU588, China Eastern Airlines Flight MU588, China Eastern Airlines take off, flight heads back after wing cover falls off,  China Eastern Airlines JFK international airport, metal falls off airplane wing, China Eastern Airlines wing metal, airplane wing metal falling, Flight MU588 airplane wing metal falls off]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876832</guid>
      <title>Mulan star's post supporting HK police sparks #BoycottMulan trend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#BoycottMulan #BoycottDisney #FreeHongKongHONG KONG  The Chinese-American star of Disney's live-action Mulan film has sparked rage and a massive boycott for siding with Hong Kong police in the city's ongoing fight for freedom.For those not up to speed, Hong Kong's boys in blue have been using excessive force to deal with protesters and journalists  think tear gas in enclosed spaces or rubber bullets at point-blank range. So yeah, not ok. But apparently Liu Yifei, the chick who plays Mulan, begs to differ.Newsweek reports that on Wednesday, Liu took to Twitter knockoff Weibo to share a photo posted by Chinese Communist mouthpiece People's Daily. The photo reads, "I support Hong Kong's police, you can beat me up now", to which Liu added: "What a shame for Hong Kong" and #Ialsosupporthongkongpolice#.Well, word got to the Twitterverse, and they were plenty pissed. People pointed out the hypocrisy of Liu  a naturalized American citizen  crapping on folks fighting for democracy.As one wise-cracking dragon once said, "Dishonor! Dishonor on you, dishonor on your cow, dishonor on your whole family!"A call to #BoycottMulan is now trending online, and with any luck, every cinema outside of Xi Jin-pooh land will be empty. Sorry not sorry. Your move, Disney.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 16:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/17/3876832/3876832_139788FEF47249008C77DBAB904C42D3_190817_3876832_Mulan_star_s_post_supporting_HK_police_sparks__B_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/542/330/542330D34862B979D7D5384AF025AE10.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mulan, live action mulan, boycott mulan, #boycottmulan, disney mulan, liu yifei, mulan star, hong kong police, anti HK, anti Hong Kong, HK protests, Hong Kong protests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876756</guid>
      <title>Hero pilot makes crash landing after bird strike in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  A Russian pilot whose airplane lost power in both engines after a bird strike miraculously made a successful emergency landing in some cornfields, saving the lives of everyone on board. According to the Associated Press, the Ural Airlines Airbus A321 was carrying 226 passengers and seven crew when it took off from Moscow's Zhukovsky Airport for Simferopol in Crimea on Thursday. According to a statement from Russia's Federal Air Transport Agency, shortly after takeoff, the plane "collided with a flock of gulls" and some of the birds were sucked into the engines. According to 23-year-old co-pilot Georgy Murzin, the strike caused the left engine to stall immediately. More birds then got into the right engine, causing it to become unstable and eventually stall too. Pilot Damir Yusupov then made the split second decision to land the fully loaded plane with its wheels up in a cornfield. The 41-year-old pilot was able to bring the aircraft down so smoothly that everyone survived.According to the Emergencies Ministry, 74 people asked for medical assistance after the crash landing, but all were released except for one person following check-ups. The pilot and crew are now being hailed as heroes. The AP reports that bird strikes occur regularly, but it's rare for them to disable both engines. Russian officials have said an investigation into the incident has been opened.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 13:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876756/3876756_3E33BA94D894407C88710960B5B03209_190816_3876756_Hero_pilot_makes_crash_landing_after_bird_strike_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B8D/D5D/B8DD5D609B0893F3AF8033B2D3C8A720.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hero pilot, russian pilot crash landing, russian plane bird strike, russian crash landing no casualties, russian plane crash landing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876731</guid>
      <title>Geek gets $12,000 in parking tickets after 'NULL' plate backfires</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA  A genius in California tried to prank the DMV, only for it to backfire. Hard.According to Wired, the poor chap in question is security researcher Joseph Tartaro. Tartarto, who goes by Droogie, presented his very unfortunate experience at the DEF CON hacking conference in Vegas.So the story goes that back in 2016, Droogie decided to register "NULL" as his new vanity California license plate. He'd done it for giggles, but also on the off chance it would confuse the DMV's automatic license plate readers and ticketing system and render him invisible.It was smooth sailing for the first year or so, until Droogie got a legit $35 parking ticket.After he paid it off, more tickets addressed to him started coming. They were for cars he didn't have, cited in places he'd never been to, coming out to an eye-popping $12,049.Turns out a private citation processing center had a whole database of outstanding tickets rendered "null" due to incomplete data, that have since been linked to Droogie's "NULL" plate and mailing address. Ah, the irony.Droogie tried to call the citation center and explain his situation, but they gave no Fs. Lucky for him, the DMV got in touch with the private citation company and got his $12,000 worth of fines erased.But the bad news is, the system remains unchanged, so the tickets, they're still a-comin'.At DEF CON, he said the system had about $6,000 worth of tickets pegged on him, but insists he won't pay a damn penny. He's not changing his plates either, despite both the California DMV and the LAPD telling him to.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 12:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876731/3876731_52D9789B5F8D4467B25301AC6A61C693_190816_3876731_Geek_gets__12_000_in_parking_tickets_after__NULL_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/90E/226/90E22664AD0EAABA855AD753EED16E18.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, license plate fail, DMV prank, DMV prank fail, NULL plate, NULL license plate, parking tickets, California DMV, NULL, vanity license plate, prank fail, prank backfires]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876660</guid>
      <title>Teen tweets from smart fridge after mom takes her phone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TWITTERSPHERE  It's not often there's a story that combines amazing ingenuity AND possibly a sign of the end of days. According to New York Magazine, a 15-year-old Ariana Grande super fan from Kentucky named Dorothy went to some hilarious lengths just so she could tweet.The Guardian reports she was forced to MacGuyver some ways to reach her thousands of followers by using a handheld Nintendo device, a Wii U gaming console and then by far the coolest onean LG Smart fridge. Dorothy told New York Magazine it all started when her mom confiscated her phone after she was boiling some rice and watching YouTube on her phone when the stove caught fire. After the wheels got going, she started coming up with increasingly clever ways to daisy-chain systems not originally designed for tweeting.  First she was able to use her Nintendo 3DS handheld to reach the twittersphere, until mom quickly put an end to that. Not to be deterred, Dorothy then hopped on her Nintendo Wii U video-game console to fire off some more tweets. Her mom eventually took away all her electronic devicesall that is except the family's smart LG fridge.Dorothy told New York Magazine her mom now plans to have the fridge removed.  After the story went viral, even Twitter joined in the calls for Dorothy to be returned to the Twitterverse, tweeting #FreeDorothy. Imagine if all that energy went into reading books.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 10:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876660/3876660_CB04D22327244FA8AE3B6D6B663B380B_190816_3876660_Teen_tweets_from_smart_fridge_after_mom_takes_he_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/061/860/061860D37A9A80AA0563A7904250C2DE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Twitter, Tweet, Teen tweets from smart fridge, teen tweets from refrigerator, mom confiscates phone, mom confiscates electronics, #FreeDorothy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876658</guid>
      <title>Fashion firms apologize for saying truth about Taiwan and H.K.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOO HOO BEIJING  A number of global fashion brands have had to put out lame apologies for apparently implying that independent Taiwan and protesting Hong Kong are separate from China. When you mix Chinese netizens with reality, you get the hurt feelings of the Chinese people. According to the Guardian, Coach and Givenchy luxury brands, Asics, Calvin Klein and Fresh beauty brand have all had to issue apologies to China because Taiwan and Hong Kong were not part of China on company websites and on T-shirts. As massive anti-Beijing protests rage in Hong Kong, Chinese netizens with too much time on their hands have taken to crying about companies that don't support the fairytale one-China principle. The Guardian reports that as protests shut down the Hong Kong airport on Monday, a blogger posted a 2018 Coach T-shirt that listed Taiwan and Hong Kong as separate countries. This caused Chinese people to rage over Twitter knockoff Weibo on Coach, which then caused Coach to issue a boring apology. Givenchy and Asics also issued statements so Chinese people could feel better about themselves. The funny thing is...Chinese consumers will still continue to spend their money on foreign brands despite their supposed outrage, because what's the alternative? High end Chinese brands!?Well there's always knockoffs. If only they had those in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 10:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876658/3876658_63237455D9A94883903B895CB9867F19_190816_3876658_Fashion_firms_apologize_for_saying_truth_about_T_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD0/C93/FD0C9300CBF342B6FBED884F3CA298B1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Coach China, Givenchy China, Versace China, Taiwan, Hong Kong protests, Beijing upset, China hurt feelings]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876651</guid>
      <title>Pok&#xE9;mon cards sell for over $100,000 at auction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUNNEMEDE, NEW JERSEY  A complete set of first-edition Pokmon cards from 1999 actually sold for $107,010 at auction. According to CNBC, the 103 card collection was sold in mint condition and included a rare Charizard card, which supposedly can sell for up to $20,000. The set was a collection of first-edition cards printed in English. Auction house Goldin Auctions said in the listing on its website that each card was graded at GEM-MT 10, which we all know stands for Gem Mint. In plain English that means the cards are in near perfect condition. CNBC reports the bidding started at $25,000, with the set receiving 12 bids before the auction closed on Saturday. According to the auction house listing, "for many Millenials, the original 1999 Pokmon video and card games remain a staple of their childhood, providing what seems like a lost art in a nostalgic feeling."According to CNBC, the auction house said a similar Pokmon set was sold in December 2017 for just under $100,000.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 10:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876651/3876651_1585D1939FB148EFADF26AE829425489_190816_3876651_Pokemon_cards_sell_for_over__100_000_at_auction_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D91/161/D911610E4D5A4B54806B2869C5EBC529.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Pokmon, Pokmon set $100,000, Pokmon auction, Pokmon 1999 auction, Pokmon cards auction for $100,000]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876541</guid>
      <title>Old woman sits on a kid who
didn't give up his bus seat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHEJIANG, CHINA  A video from Monday's rush hour in Zhejiang province shows an elderly woman sitting on a kid because she wanted the window seat, and he was in her way. Citing the Southern Metropolitan Post, the Mirror reports passengers as saying the old woman stood in front of the boy and then started sitting down.As she does, she tells the boy's mother to make her son move so she can sit down.Passengers said that the mother did, in fact, offer the seat, but asked her to not squeeze in and sit on her son.Passengers described the child as "seven or eight years old" and that after the elderly woman sat down anyway, he was forced to move.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 08:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876541/3876541_5D4F464F68C24217994E2D9DFD12C0FB_190816_3876541_Old_woman_sits_on_a_kid_who_didn_t_give_up_his_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4A3/D1D/4A3D1DB71B236E893624FBD593FD324B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, old woman sits on kid, bus seat, woman sit boy china bus, bus in china videos, Chinese bus videos, elderly woman sits on a boy, woman sits on boy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876452</guid>
      <title>Taxi driver sees extremely rare
Siberian tiger on the road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUNCHUN, CHINA  Taxi's usually pick up their most challenging customers at night, but this driver almost definitely wasn't expecting to have a Siberian Tiger at the side of the road. Citing the Beijing Time, the Shanghaiist reported that the ultra-rare tiger was spotted late at night on a highway in the city of Hunchun, near the borders of both North Korea and Russia.In the footage, the tiger is watching the taxi from the side of the road, before it crosses and begins walking away.According to WWF, as little as 540 of these magnificent creatures remain, despite this, China dealt a massive blow to conservation efforts when it lifted a ban on the use of tiger parts for traditional medicine.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 05:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876452/3876452_9E71AB44460F4652B68A3142573456A0_190816_3876452_Taxi_driver_sees_extremely_rare_Siberian_tiger_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/439/379/4393790F18D5D1FB27AFBA8BA5DE6232.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, taxi driver tiger, Siberian tiger on road, china tiger, taxi china tiger, Siberian tiger highway, taxi driver sees tiger, tiger spotted on highway, Siberian tiger on road]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3876386</guid>
      <title>Scientists find microplastics in rain in the Rocky Mountains</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCKY MOUNTAINS, COLORADO  New research from the U.S. Geological Survey has found microscopic plastic fibers present in rainwater from Rocky Mountain National Park in Colorado.According to a study published by the U.S. Geological Survey, researchers obtained rainwater samples from different altitudes from the Front Range of the Rocky Mountains. The samples were collected using buckets lined with plastic bags. Scientists analyzed the rainwater samples with binocular microscope fitted with a digital camera.Plastic was found in more than 90 percent of the sampled rainwater, according to the study.Researchers discovered that the samples mostly contained plastic fibers in a wide range of colors such as red, silver, purple, green and yellow. They also found beads and shards in the rainwater samples.Microplastics have previously been found in the depths of oceans, lakes and rivers across the U.S. and even the Pyrenees mountains, the Guardian reports. According to the U.S. National Library of Medicine, microplastics are able to absorb and give off chemicals and pollutants. These may build up over time and persist in the environment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 04:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/16/3876386/3876386_FFD02714E0484506AF216CFC68630E90_190816_3876386_Scientists_find_microplastics_in_rain_in_the_Roc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/28D/F4D/28DF4D7610B8CC36F14CAC605893D7E3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,Microscopic fibers,Microscopic fibers rocky mountains,plastic pollution,microplastics,plastic particles,microplastics pollution,plastic bags,plastic pollution,plastic pollution,microplastic particles,plastic waste,plastic litter,plastic falling from the sky]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877982</guid>
      <title>Scientists detect mysterious radio signals from space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OKANAGAN VALLEY, CANADA  New radio waves from outer space have been detected by the Canadian Hydrogen Intensity Mapping Experiment radio telescope, also known as CHIME.The findings were submitted to the Astrophysical Journal Letters. It described eight new repeating signals that were detected by the radio telescope.According to the EU Research & Innovation Magazine, these fast radio bursts, or FRBs, typically last only a few milliseconds but are able to emit more energy than 500 million suns.The telescope consists of four cylindrical reflectors, each of which are lined with 256 antennas. It continuously scans separate points in the sky, 24 hours a day, seven days a week, searching for FRBs, according to CHIME's website. In a separate study published in the journal Nature in January, CHIME had previously detected 13 fast radio bursts, only one of which was repeating.Researchers noticed that among the radio bursts studied, those that sent off signals multiple times tended to send out bursts that lasted a bit longer than radio bursts that only sent out signals once.These repeating FRBs could shed new light on the origin of these radio waves and what exactly causes them, according to the newly submitted paper.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 11:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/19/3877982/3877982_B891E8FD6B1940F2AE4CA12B2EAD7B0D_190819_3877982_Scientists_detect_mysterious_radio_signals_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2EA/26E/2EA26EC6F9B6FAE591E16A058DEED0EE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, radio waves, radio telescope, mysterious radio waves from space, mysterious radio burst, radio astronomy signals, astronomy radio waves, fast radio bursts, fast radio bursts 2019, Canadian Hydrogen Intensity Mapping Experiment, CHIME telescope, fast radio bursts from space, CHIME, astronomy, space exploration, radio signals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877946</guid>
      <title>Woman survives 5,000 foot fall after parachute fail</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEBEC, CANADA  A 30-year-old skydiver is miraculously still around and kicking after her parachute failed to deploy, causing her to plunge more than 5,000 feet to the ground. CBC reported the incident occurred on August 10 at the Parachutisme Adrnaline skydiving facility in Quebec, located close to the airport. According to eyewitness Denis Demers talking to CBC, he realized something was wrong last Saturday evening when he saw the woman descending way faster than all the other skydivers. That's because the woman's main parachute didn't open. But that's what the backup chute is there for. Only problem is, the woman's reserve chute didn't properly deploy eitheryikes. After dropping like a load of bricks from more than 5,000 feet, the woman's fall was broken by several trees, which she crashed through before landing in a wooded area. According to CBC, she suffered multiple non-life threatening injuries, including broken vertebrae and several fractures. She is now recovering at the hospital. Skydiving deaths are rare considering how many people willingly throw themselves out of perfectly good planes every year. According to the U.S. Parachute Association, in 2018 there were only 13 skydiving-related fatalities in the U.S., which averages out to about one death in every 253,669 jumps.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/19/3877946/3877946_8E3AF6DB02B24623B31609E561FFE413_190819_3877946_Woman_survives_5_000_foot_fall_after_parachute_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/523/978/523978BC6AD71A56037E7FD3D5ECC691.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, skydiving, skydiver survives fall, skydiver survives parachute fail, skydiver survives 5,000 foot fall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877944</guid>
      <title>Chinese 'rappers' come out in support of Hong Kong police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Hip hop has always been music for the people. Unfortunately in China it's for the peoplethe People's Republic of China.  As millions of brave Hong Kongers continue to peacefully stand out against Chinese interference in their city, some rappers from China have come out in support of Beijing and police brutality. According to Radii China, Chinese artists Higher Brothers, Melo and DZ Know all shared images of China's flag on their Instagram accounts. Other sellouts, like "The Rap of China" champion PG One reposted a CCP propaganda People Daily's post reading "I support Hong Kong police, you can hit me" in Mandarin characters and "What a shame for Hong Kong" written in English underneath it. Radii China reported, PG One wrote in a Weibo post, "support Hong Kong police, resist violent atrocities!!! I hope everyone is safe and secure."Miss Vava, apparently another clown for "The Rap of China", posted on her Instagram with the captions "Hong Kong is part of China forever." Another chump named After Journey also shared the post on IG with the caption "Compatriots, remember this day, remember this moment."But it's good to see hip hop in China is keeping it realreal authoritarian.   However, maybe if these artists really love Beijing so much, they should stop using Instagram as it's blocked in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 10:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/19/3877944/3877944_A19262A63DF343259DC45C75BA5128A8_190819_3877944_Chinese__rappers__come_out_in_support_of_Hong_Ko_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5F1/ACD/5F1ACDB53813F0F820156FE3406976D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong anti-China protests, Chinese rappers, Chinese rappers support HK police]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877927</guid>
      <title>Salmon dying off due to heat wave in Alaska</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALASKA  Alaska is hotter than ever this summer, and the salmon are dying because of it.CNN reports that large amounts of salmon are dying off in Alaska due to the unprecedented heat wave that gripped the state in July and caused water temperatures to reach up to 81.7 degrees Fahrenheit.In a Twitter post, Yukon Inter-Tribal Fish Commission Director Stephanie Quinn-Davidson said she and other scientists counted 850 dead chum salmon when they checked a 200 mile stretch of river during a July expedition.According to the Independent, it's normal for salmon to die off after they spawn. But since most of the dead fish were found with healthy eggs still in their bodies, scientists believed they died of heat stress before reaching their spawning grounds.According to Sue Mauger, science director for the Cook Inletkeeper, fish can't get oxygen moving through their bellies in warm water.Temperature can also affect metabolism and organ function, making the fish less able to fight off parasites and pathogens.The Independent reports that scientists stopped seeing dead salmon as soon as the temperatures cooled back down.According to CNN, extreme heat brought about by climate change isn't the only thing stressing North American salmon populations.In southwestern Canada and Northwestern Washington, salmon are being threatened by overfishing. A mining project in Alaska that's no longer being opposed by the EPA could also devastate one of the world's most valuable wild salmon fisheries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 10:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/19/3877927/3877927_744F92FC21324CF194318EC7399A352A_190819_3877927_Salmon_dying_off_due_to_heat_wave_in_Alaska_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8EF/FDE/8EFFDEFA53D8C48BD87316F73D51B5BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, salmon die off, salmon dying off, Alaska heat wave, Alaska salmon, Alaskan salmon, salmon heat wave, salmon climate change, climate change, dead salmon, salmon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877830</guid>
      <title>New pain-sensing organ discovered in the skin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STOCKHOLM  Swedish scientists have discovered a new organ under the skin that helps process certain kinds of pain.According to National Geographic, mechanical pain was typically thought to be perceived through sensitive nerve cell endings in the epidermis.Unlike other nerve cells, these lacked a protective layer and was thus believed to be responsible for pain sensation.But researchers from Sweden's Karolinska Institutet recently uncovered a sensory organ between the skin's outer and inner layers, consisting of a mesh-like network of gliall cells with multiple long protrusions.This newly discovered organ has been dubbed the nociceptive glio-neural complex, and is highly sensitive to mechanical stimuli such as pinpricks or pressure. It is less sensitive to discomfort caused by heat or cold.To test the organ's functionality, the team genetically modified mice so that gliall cells on the skin of their feet could be stimulated by light.When light was shone on the cells, the mice exhibited behavior that indicated pain, including lifting their feet, and licking, shaking, or guarding their paws.While the organ has been identified in mice, scientists have yet to confirm that it exists in humans, though the probability is high.Assuming it functions the same way in humans, the findings could change the way we think about how pain starts and progresses. It may also be significant in the understanding of chronic pain.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 08:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/19/3877830/3877830_41C308F198B24C20BB89390872DCA5E0_190819_3877830_New_pain_sensing_organ_discovered_in_the_skin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F1F/512/F1F5127839B74FCB27E42ABAF96CE8CC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pain organ, new pain organ, pain perception, mechanical pain, glio neural complex, schwann cells, nociceptive schwann cells, nerve endings, nerve cells, sensory organ, new organ]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877685</guid>
      <title>Robert Ballard-led team to search for Amelia Earhart's plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NEW HAMPSHIRE  Researchers have long wondered about what really happened to Amelia Earhart, the first ever female aviator to fly solo.On July 2, 1937, Earhart and navigator Fred Noonan disappeared without a trace during an attempt to fly across the equator. Earhart sent their last radio transmissions at 8:43 a.m. that day, in which she said : "We are on the line 157 337."This means the plane was flying over Howland Island in the Pacific Ocean.On the basis of those radio messages, researchers believe that the two either flew northwest to the open ocean or to the southeast to Nikumaroro Island.Now, a new expedition is all set to explore the waters off the island to find out more about the disappearance of Amelia Earhart.A group of researchers led by National Geographic Explorer Robert Ballard are embarking on a mission on the E/V Nautilus ship to waters off Nikumaroro Island to search for the remnants of Amelia Earhart's plane.The ship is equipped with multiple exploration tools, including an autonomous surface vehicle developed by the University of New Hampshire called Bathymetric Explorer and Navigator, or BEN.According to a news release by the university, the vehicle includes features such as the Kongsberg EM2040P multibeam echo-sounder and the Applanix POS/ MV navigation system. This allows the self-driving vehicle to create 3D topographic maps and acoustic backscatter maps of the ocean floor.Once the autonomous surface vehicle returns to the ship, researchers will analyze data from the maps and then deploy two remotely operated vehicles called Hercules and Argus, according to National Geographic. These are typically launched at night and can reach depths of 4,000 meters.Hercules is able to provide a first person view of the seabed, while the Argus is a smaller vehicle that captures footage of Hercules. Hercules can collect samples found in the seabed and store them in a container in its side for researchers to analyze.The mission is the subject of a two-hour documentary titled Expedition Amelia and will air on National Geographic on October 20.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 03:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/19/3877685/3877685_5F95DC94067D45B8A43C543553627994_190819_3877685_Robert_Ballard_led_team_to_search_for_Amelia_Ear_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/11A/7A5/11A7A5C9F9735A6A444489750EBFEEE3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, amelia earhart, amelia earhart mystery, amelia earhart plane, mystery of amelia earhart, researchers look for amelia earhart plane debris, autonomous watercraft, autonomous robot used to solve amelia earhart mystery, Bathymetric Explorer and Navigator, airplane mysteries, search for Amelia earhart's airplane, Nikumaroro Islands, amelia earhart nikumaroro island]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3877648</guid>
      <title>Massive collision could be the answer to Jupiter's strange core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON, TEXAS  A cosmic collision between Jupiter and a protoplanet billions of years ago could explain the unexpected readings from NASA's Juno space probe.According to a press release by Rice University, data from NASA's Juno space probe reported gravitational readings that suggest Jupiter's core is less dense and more extended than expected. Rice astronomer Andrea Isella said the readings are puzzling, and that something happened that may have "stirred up the core".After running thousands of computer simulations, the research team deduced that a fast-growing young Jupiter from some 4.5 billion years ago could have "perturbed" nearby embryo planets, resulting in a massive impact.  Isella said that because of Jupiter's, "strong gravitational focusing," head-on collisions were more common during the simulations. The dense high energy impactor would have been, "like a bullet", cutting the atmosphere and hitting the core of Jupiter directly.Isella stated that before an impact, the core is extremely dense as it is surrounded by an atmosphere. A head-on collision would "spread things out" and "dilute the core".Isella states that by understanding how Jupiter and other planets evolve, we might be able to answer the biggest question of all, whether life-supporting conditions exist anywhere else in the universe.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 02:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/19/3877648/3877648_0232C89EA0B14791A5C296DE7C92CDDD_190819_3877648_Massive_collision_could_be_the_answer_to_Jupiter_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AB2/EAC/AB2EAC6DD39B9DFF752175A135845771.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Jupiter core, Jupiter collision with planet, NASA's Juno, Jupiter's strange core, collision made Jupiter's core weird, planetary collision, Jupiter simulation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878489</guid>
      <title>Pitbull fights off shark to save owner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SONOMA, CALIFORNIA A 100-pound pitbull reportedly fought off a shark that had bitten its owner in northern California while he was out fishing.According to NBC Bay Area, James White was out with his dog Darby fishing last month in Sonoma County's Bodega Bay when he hooked something large. White snagged a 6-foot long sevengill shark, and after a 10-minute struggle, was able to drag it ashore.NBC Bay Area reported that when he went to pull out the hook from its mouth, the shark got loose and dropped to the ground, where it then bit into White's ankle.He yelled for help to other fishermen, but they were too far away to be of any help. Enter the hero of the dayDarby, who was chilling in White's car parked a few yards away. After hearing his owner's calls for help, Darby managed to open one of the doors and sprint down to White. Darby hurled himself at the shark and bit into its gills, causing the shark to bite down even harder on White's ankle. After White told Darby to back off, Darby then repositioned himself and sunk his chompers into the shark's tail. White told NBC, "he literally ran up the hill with it and pulled it off my leg."  White then tossed the shark back into the water and it swam away. James said he couldn't be prouder of Darby. "He's been a part of the family from day one. Just now a little more. If it wasn't for him I would have been a lot worse."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 12:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/20/3878489/3878489_590D70CD2AA1482CB906A5ECA1FD34ED_190820_3878489_Pitbull_fights_off_shark_to_save_owner_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/661/646/661646A583A111FAB82B56D74B0D4A44.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pitbull, pitbull fights off shark, pitbull saves owner, pitbull attacks shark, pitbull comes to rescue, shark]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878477</guid>
      <title>U.S. tests previously banned missile under the INF treaty</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN NICOLAS ISLAND, CALIFORNIA  Washington has conducted its first test of a missile that was previously banned under the Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces Treaty, INF, after the U.S. President Donald Trump's administration formally withdrew from the treaty on August 2.On August 18, the Pentagon conducted a flight test of a conventionally configured ground-launched cruise missile from San Nicolas Island, California.In a statement sent to Newsweek, a Pentagon spokesperson said that the missile "was a variant of the Tomahawk Land Attack Missile."The test missile was launched from a ground mobile launcher and precisely hit its target after flying more than 500 kilometers, according to a news release by the U.S. Department of Defense. The missile used a conventional warhead, not a nuclear warhead, the Associated Press reports, citing the Pentagon. The Tomahawk Land Attack Missile has a range of around 1,600 kilometers, according to the U.S. Navy. The Pentagon said that it intends to begin testing of another non-nuclear ballistic missile with an estimated range of around 3,000 to 4,000 kilometers.The U.S. Department of Defense said in a news release that data collected from this missile test will "inform our development of future intermediate-range capabilities."The Intermediate Range Nuclear Forces Treaty, or INF, was signed between the Soviet Union and the U.S. 30 years ago. The treaty banned the use of nuclear and non-nuclear missiles between the ranges of 500 and 5,500 kilometers.The U.S. withdrew from the INF nuclear weapons treaty after accusing Russia of violating the treaty by deploying its SSC-8 ground-launched cruise missile, according to CNN.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 11:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/20/3878477/3878477_D50F3ABBB9C646909F3F8F536D8980FA_190820_3878477_U_S__tests_previously_banned_missile_under_the_I_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/569/09E/56909EF9C51C667525C7060792E5B8FD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  INF treaty, pentagon missile test, pentagon tests missile banned under the inf treaty, tomahawk missile test, US, Russia, us russia inf treaty, us russia inf treaty explained, nuclear arms agreement, intermediate-range nuclear forces treaty, inf treaty explained, inf treaty trump, inf treaty withdrawal, inf treaty russia, abandoning the inf treaty]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878458</guid>
      <title>Ocean Cleanup redesigns its plastic-catching barriers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROTTERDAM, NETHERLANDS  The Ocean Cleanup, a non-profit organization developing technologies to rid the oceans of plastic, has launched the second version of its cleanup system.The Ocean Cleanup has redesigned its cleanup system and added a parachute for the system to collect plastic waste at a more consistent speed.In the new system, called System 001/B, the parachute will work to slow down the cleanup system and allow natural winds and waves to move plastic into the system. This is to prevent the plastic from floating out of the cleanup system.According to the Ocean Cleanup, the previous system, called System 001, would sometimes travel faster than the plastic and sometimes travel slower than the plastic.This means that the plastic would float into the cleanup system, only to float out again.The system's plastic-collecting screen has also been moved forward to prevent fracturing to the system's floating barrier. The floats of the current cork line are 15 centimeters long and are used to hold the screen in place.The company will add bigger floats to the cork line to increase its buoyancy. Each float will be 32 centimeters in diameter, according to the Ocean Cleanup's website. These are to be stacked on one another in order to prevent plastic from floating to the middle of the plastic-collecting screen and the floating barrier.The company said on its website that the new cleanup system is ready and will soon be deployed to the oceans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 11:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/20/3878458/3878458_BDBE6190D3A04A518CCEFA4E0D0B48C0_190820_3878458_Ocean_Cleanup_redesigns_its_plastic_catching_bar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/695/0D2/6950D20F5308FE17833400172A60A67D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ocean, ocean cleanup 2019, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup project, ocean cleanup technology,  ocean cleanup project 2019, ocean cleanup, garbage patch, Great Pacific Garbage Patch, floater, plastic, plastic in ocean, beta cleanup system, plastic parts, pollutants, plastic pollution, polluted oceans, technology, cleaning up the oceans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878316</guid>
      <title>Florida woman gets probation after pulling gator from her pants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PUNTA GORDA, FLORIDA  Weird news comes out of Florida on a daily basis, but no one takes the cake like this lady, who pulled a gator out of her pants during a traffic stop. CBS Miami reports that back in May, a Charlotte County Sheriff's Deputy stopped a pickup after it ran a stop sign. The driver, 22-year-old Michael Clemmons, said he and his passenger Ariel Machan-Le Quire had been collecting frogs and snakes underneath an overpass.The cop wasn't buying it, and asked to search the vehicle.According to USA Today, he ended up finding not one, not two, but 42 striped mud turtles and a softshell turtle inside a Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles backpack, which was by the passenger's feet. When the deputy asked asked the pair if they had anything else in the truck, 25-year-old Marchan-Le Quire reached into her yoga pants and pulled out a live, foot-long baby gator. Needless to say, crazy alligator lady was charged for illegally possessing wildlife. According to the Miami Herald, she's since been sentenced to six months probation, 200 hours of community service, and has to donate 500 bucks to Florida Fish and Wildlife.Charges against Clemons are still pending.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 07:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/20/3878316/3878316_D7FA54A6A8514C8484D9125C068C42F2_190820_3878316_Florida_woman_gets_probation_after_pulling_gator_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5E6/FBC/5E6FBCAE3044A4C939C5E808D11A0E6E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, gator in pants, wildlife trafficking, wildlife smuggling, woman smuggles gator in pants, alligator in pants, Florida, Florida gator, Florida alligator, Florida gator in pants]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878236</guid>
      <title>Researchers find microplastics in Arctic sea ice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE ARCTIC  Researchers aboard the Swedish Icebreaker Oden as part of the Northwest Passage Project, an 18-day expedition through the Northwest Passage, have found microplastics polluting ice from the Arctic Ocean.The researchers first used a helicopter to land on ice floes, Reuters reports. They then used a drill to obtain a total of 18 ice core samples from four locations. The team shared images of the sampled ice containing visibly different shapes and sizes of plastic beads and filaments.The team plans to analyze the ice samples to get a better understanding of how plastic particles in ice could affect fish, seabirds and large ocean mammals in the Arctic.The Northwest Passage Project's main aim is to make assessments on how climate change is impacting the Arctic. According to the project's website, the mission specifically focused on four research areas. Scientists gathered data on water mass and circulation inside the Canadian Arctic Archipelago to analyze how the water column chemistry affects greenhouse gas accumulation.They also examined how microscopic habitats are transitioning because of climate conditions and monitored marine bird distribution in the Arctic region.The expedition took place between July 18 to August 4.In a separate study published in the journal Science Advances, scientists found microplastics present in Arctic sea ice, as well as the Arctic water column and its surface waters. Researchers in the study assessed that the plastic particles found in the Arctic are transported by the wind.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 05:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/20/3878236/3878236_C9066A07213D43B088013CE001E93FC2_190820_3878236_Researchers_find_microplastics_in_Arctic_sea_ice_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DDB/506/DDB506ED6184B369AB0D4E3273BBF326.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Arctic, arctic ice, arctic sea, arctic ocean, microplastic in arctic sea ice, microplastic arctic sea, arctic sea ice microplastics, climate change, global warming, effects of climate change, effects of climate warming, global warming, global warming arctic,  microplastics, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, plastic litter, microplastics in the arctic, microplastic pollution, microplastic arctic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878154</guid>
      <title>Greedy landlord turns one pad into 11 apartments</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A condo owner in New York's Lower East Side has been busted for creating a new floor in his modest home and converting it into claustrophobic, makeshift micro-apartments. The New York Post reported that apartment owner, Xue Ping Ni split his 634-square-foot home horizontally to make eleven illegal windowless subunits that had ceilings as low as 4  feet high.Not one to take risks, Ni considerately put up bubble wrap to protect his tenants from knocking themselves out cold from the low-hanging pipes. One renter told The Post that Ni was charging him $600 per month and that there was a "good amount" of people cramped up there. A female occupant revealed that she was paying $2,800 per month and that is was a "revolving door of people".After a call was made to authorities, the mini-village was raided and shut down on Wednesday and tenants were forced to evacuate. They were offered immediate relocation assistance by the American Red Cross. Inspectors slammed Ni with a fine totaling more than $144,000 for failing to have a sprinkler system, proper electrical, structural and plumbing permits.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 03:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/20/3878154/3878154_381AF8CAFBA14EB18901717BBA0855D3_190820_3878154_Greedy_landlord_turns_one_pad_into_11_apartments_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/731/7E0/7317E0F3006019E4C15D6F3760E455CB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, New York landlord, landlord 1 apartment to 11 apartments, landlord turns his home into 11 apartments, bad landlords, new york apartments, condo owner builds new floor, landlord makes new floor, landlord splits condo in half horizontally]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879003</guid>
      <title>Parasitic worm yanked from man's dome after 30 years of headaches</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGZHOU, CHINA  A Chinese man who had been suffering from crazy headaches for about 30 years finally got his head right after doctors discovered a parasitic worm chillin in his dome. According to Pear Video, the 59-year-old man, surnamed Zhang, told local news that he had been experiencing dizziness and splitting migraines since 1989.He was misdiagnosed by other doctors has having epilepsy and given the wrong medications, so it's no surprise the headaches didn't subside. The man finally figured out what the cause was after a recent visit to a hospital in Guangzhou. A head scan revealed a 10-cm-long worm had taken up residence in the guy's noggin. The little squirmer was finally removed through surgery, and Zhang is now headache free. Apparently Zhang had developed a habit of drinking unboiled stream water and eating uncooked frogs and snakes. Doctors told him that's probably how he developed the parasitic infection.Remember, next time you're experiencing a pounding headache, Advil might not help, because it may JUST be a parasitic worm.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 12:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/21/3879003/3879003_4B1347C8B48F4F19AE5A56A849CDC1C1_190821_3879003_Parasitic_worm_yanked_from_man_s_dome_after_30_y_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AE/D2D/1AED2D7EA4C76504F5A61C9F92606AE1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, parasitic worm, parasitic worm in head, parasitic worm in skull, worms, China, eating raw frogs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878894</guid>
      <title>Florida palms suffering from Lethal Bronzing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FLORIDA  Palm trees in Florida are under severe threat from a condition known as Lethal Bronzing Disease, an illness that turns palms to a crisp in months. The University of Florida details the condition as being caused by parasitic bacteria and spread by common sap-sucking insects.Brian Bahderm, an assistant professor at the University of Florida explained to the Miami Herald that Lethal Bronzing is transmitted through the saliva of sap-sucking insects when they feast on the palm's leaves.Lethal Bronzing occurs when the bacteria known as phytoplasmas, multiply in the bottom of the tree and "clog the circulatory system." This build-up creates a blockage, resulting in the tree being starved from sufficient nutrients, giving it the tell-tale shade of bronze leaves. Researchers from the University of Florida identified four more palms that are susceptible to the disease; the Pindo palm, Carpentaria palm, Coconut palm, and the Chinese fan palm, bringing the tally now to 16.They also state that Lethal Bronzing has spread statewide to include eight new Florida counties, with tens of thousands of palms already dead as a result. Bahder stated that getting the disease under control is vital as it has the potential to, "drastically modify our landscape".However, The University of Florida states that antibiotic treatments are "ineffective" because phytoplasmas don't have the cell wall that most of these treatments target; thus deeming infected trees fatal.The New York Times informs that the disease has already massively damaged Jamaica's coconut plantations and that Brazil is now taking precautionary action against the disease.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 09:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/21/3878894/3878894_F809F98074FE4182833F99D84BFF43D4_190821_3878894_Florida_palms_suffering_from_Lethal_Bronzing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4E5/D66/4E5D66F9B9A2AD803356865B07FA06E5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, florida's palm disease, Florida's palms threatened, Lethal Bronzing disease, Florida lethal bronzing, palm tree disease Florida, Florida palm disease, Palm tree disease in Florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878848</guid>
      <title>Nicotine-free e-cigarettes constricts blood vessels: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA  New research has found that vaping temporarily is enough to impact the body's blood vessels.Scientists from the University of Pennsylvania asked 31 nonsmoking participants to inhale electronic cigarettes 16 times for three seconds each. The e-cigarettes included ingredients such as propylene glycol, glycerol and flavoring, but did not contain any nicotine.Researchers involved in the study, published in the journal Radiology, took MRI scans of the participants after they vaped. They found that all of the participants' blood vessels in the brain, heart vessels and femoral arteries had become constricted by 30 percent.In comparison, a separate study from the British Journal of Pharmacology found that smoking cigarettes reduced blood flow by 31 percent.In a statement emailed to Wired, Juul, an e-cigarette company that controls over 70 percent of the vaping market in the U.S., noted that the study called for the participants to inhale an unrealistic number of times in a short period of time.This caused a reduction of oxygen flow in the blood vessels by 20 percent.In an email to Reuters, lead author of the study, Alessandra Caporale from the University's Perelman School of Medicine, explained that the usage of e-cigarettes is not equivalent to inhaling water vapor, even if the e-cigarette does not contain any nicotine.Caporale said that the impact of vaping on the blood vessels was temporary. Though, she added, long-term effects of vaping could include inflammation and deterioration of blood vessels.The researchers are planning another study that would take an in-depth look into the impact of vaping on e-cigarette users, cigarette smokers and non-smokers over time, according to Reuters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 08:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/21/3878848/3878848_0463716BFA7E4BE89152269701D58834_190821_3878848_Nicotine_free_e_cigarettes_constricts_blood_vess_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/436/9AE/4369AE64848A035C2192CBEF81275726.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, vaping side effects, vaping, effects of vaping, how vaping affects the body, e-cigarettes, dangers of vaping, vaping damages blood vessels, nicotine free e-cigarettes, nicotine free vapes, e-cigarettes harmful, side effects of e-cigarettes, vaping alters body]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878834</guid>
      <title>NASA plans to launch Europa Clipper mission by 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA  NASA has announced plans to launch the Europa Clipper space mission to examine Jupiter's icy moon Europa by 2025.The mission aims to identify whether or not life could exist on Europa, according to the U.S. space agency's website.The Europa Clipper spacecraft will orbit around Jupiter and make 45 flybys to Europa from altitudes ranging from 25 kilometers to 2,700 kilometers above the moon's surface.The Europa Clipper mission will consist of a Europa Clipper spacecraft that would carry instruments such as an ice-penetrating radar to determine the thickness of the moon's outer crust. A thermal instrument will also be carried onboard to search for recent eruptions of warmer water on the moon's surface. The ice-penetrating radar will also look for subsurface lakes underneath Europa's frozen surface.In 2012, NASA's Hubble Space Telescope detected water vapor above Europa's south polar region, providing strong evidence that there could be water plumes  and potentially a subsurface ocean  on Europa.The mission will also search for evidence of tiny particles and water in Europa's atmosphere. Cameras and spectrometers are to be taken onboard to take images of Europa's surface and to determine its composition.According to NASA, the space agency is targeting to have the Europa Clipper spacecraft ready as soon as 2023, in order for the mission to be cost-effective.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 08:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/21/3878834/3878834_94415F6E9F4345118668E09386AC0BA3_190821_3878834_NASA_plans_to_launch_Europa_Clipper_mission_by_2_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa, space exploration, europa clipper mission, jupiter, jupiter's icy moon, nasa europa mission, nasa europa clipper, jupiter's moon, Europa, jupiter europa, europa moon nasa, space exploration nasa, nasa's mission to jupiter's icy moon, jupiter icy moon, jupiter icy moon mission, NASA, mission, astrobiology, jovian moons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3878696</guid>
      <title>Vomiting, puking vultures take  over Florida neighborhood</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST PALM BEACH, FLORIDA  A New York couple's swanky vacation home in lovely Florida has been hilariously taken over by a bunch of no good, freeloading scavengers. According to the Palm Beach Post, dozens of black vultures have taken over the Casimano family's $702,000 house they bought earlier this year near the Ibis Golf and Country Club. The vultures have destroyed screen enclosures and overtaken the pool and barbecue. The Palm Beach Post reports that the few times the family has visited, they've had to park their car in the garage to avoid the vultures attacking it. Waitthese people thought it was an inconvenience because they had to park their car IN their garage? Life can be so difficult sometimes. Apparently, a neighbor regularly feeds the vultures, racoons and other wildlife in the area a ton of dog food, sandwiches and roast chicken. According to Siobhan Casimano, after the birds have their fill they roost on and around surrounding houses, including the Casimano's crib. Casimano told the Palm Beach Post, "the vultures just vomit everywhere. Defecating and vomiting. It's just gross. We can't even go back down to the house."Some people have tried fireworks and balloons to scare the birds off, but that stopped working already. As for the vultures, they appear to be having one hell of a summer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 03:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/21/3878696/3878696_E52E74A4BC67484EBD8B46A0F36580CE_190821_3878696_Vomiting__puking_vultures_take__over_Florida_nei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8E4/448/8E44489D3C98541F661330465B7C2BE7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, vultures, vultures overrun vacation home, vultures take over florida town, vultures in pool, vultures barbecue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879690</guid>
      <title>Insanely priced bed with 70-inch built-in TV will be end of humanity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MILANO, ITALY  With all the smart technology and gadgets hitting the market, the last thing anyone needs is probably a smart bed, but luckily Italy's Hi-Interiors made one anyways.  And one of the best things about the bed is clearly its price, which is a steal anyway you look at itaround $40,000. If you're looking to become an actual embodiment of a Wall-E human, than this super smart bed is right up your alley.   According to Business Insider the bed comes with its own app, which operates the built-in 4k projector, retractable 70-inch screen and speakers. The genius bed apparently can track your sleeping patterns and measure your body weight. Apparently people like to know they are just as fat as when they went to bed the night before. The bed can also monitor the room temperature, air quality and noise level. For the price of a car, this bed also comes with pretty lights that can be used as a night light, reading light, or alarm in the morning. The HiBed is currently available for suckers to pre-order on Hi-Interior's website, although the actual price hasn't been revealed yet. The first version of their smart bed went for around $40,300. Apparently, the HiBed will also give you suggestions to get a good night's sleep. Here's a hintit's not staring right into a brightly lit 70-inch screen at the foot of your bed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 14:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/22/3879690/3879690_D516D40D1C8E4062A90496EBBE8EDF06_190822_3879690_Insanely_priced_bed_with_70_inch_built_in_TV_wil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, HiBed, HiBed 70 inch TV, Hi-Interiors, luxury bed, smart bed, smart technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879385</guid>
      <title>Most advanced F16's 
headed to Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. / TAIWAN  In a deal worth $8 billion dollars, the Trump administration has officially cleared the sale of 66 F16 fighter planes to Taiwan, the most updated model of Lockheed martin's multirole fighter.Lockheed Martin details their new-build Block 70 F16 as having a speed of 1,500 miles per hour, a wingspan of 31 feet and an empty weight of 20,300 pounds.The latest F16's have received upgrades such as the Active Electronically Scanned Array radar, which provides pilots with superior target detail, greater "situational awareness" and digital maps to its high-resolution 6"x 8" screen which can be customized with "slew" and zoom features.The fighter also comes with a structural upgrade that extends the aircraft's lifespan by more than 50 percent compared to the previous model.Most crucially, the F16 commands the Automatic Ground Collision Avoidance System, which is designed to reduce incidents of controlled flight into terrain which is responsible for 75 percent of all F-16 pilot fatalities.The system predicts imminent collision and performs flight maneuvers to avoid ground impact.The new fighters could replace Taiwan's current 50 or so Mirage 2000s as well as their aging F-5s.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 08:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/22/3879385/3879385_3BD76F8D279D4D1DA247074B2CC65B9C_190822_3879385_Most_advanced_F16_s__headed_to_Taiwan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DEA/54E/DEA54EC57E9CD21C01A887D9B6653D44.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, F16, US sells F16 Taiwan, Taiwan wants F16's, F16 top speed, F16 specs, F16 crash, F16V, F16 model, Trump approves F16 sale]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879236</guid>
      <title>Twitter, Facebook take down Chinese disinformation accounts</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  Twitter and Facebook say they have dismantled a state-backed social media campaign birthed in China that sought to undermine peaceful anti-Beijing protests in Hong Kong. According to Reuters, Twitter suspended 936 accounts which appeared to be part of a coordinated state-backed effort coming out of China. Twitter said these accounts were just the most active portions of this campaign and that a larger, spammy network of about 200,000 accounts had been proactively suspended before they were really active. Facebook said it had removed a few accounts and pages from a small network after a tip from Twitter. Reuters reports Facebook said its investigation found links to individuals associated with the Chinese government. According to CNBC, Facebook removed seven pages, three groups and five accounts which displayed coordinated inauthentic behavior targeting Hong Kong. Facebook said that about 15,500 accounts followed one or more of the now-dead pages, while roughly 2,200 accounts joined at least one of the groups. Twitter and Facebook are blocked in China, but available in Hong Kong, which is now going into its 12th week of peaceful anti-government protests.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 05:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/22/3879236/3879236_6EE59518AFEB475AA01261C86D57CA5B_190822_3879236_Twitter__Facebook_take_down_Chinese_disinformati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/504/3F0/5043F0E18107FD7C94602B0FA3809DC2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Twitter, Facebook, Twitter suspends, Facebook suspends, China disinformation campaign, Beijing Hong Kong protests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3880153</guid>
      <title>Man fined for driving with a car filled to the brim with trash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UPPER MOUNT GRAVATT, AUSTRALIA  A man in Australia was pulled for driving with a car that was so full of trash he couldn't see where he was going.The driver was going about his day in Upper Mount Gravatt when the cops pulled him over on August 17.As the officers approached the car, they were shocked to see it filled to the brim with junk. The garbage completely blocked the driver's view of the side and rear windows, according to a statement by the Queensland Police.The cops immediately issued the man a fine of AUS$311, which is around US$210. Officers also politely reminded the man when trash collection day is in their city.Commentators praised the police with one saying, "It's the police officers' job to enforce the road rules. Inform the person what they've done wrong and issue the penalty." He added, "The police here did their job."However, some online commentators felt that the police should've done more than just issue a fine.One woman said in a comment on Facebook, "I don't think a fine was the way to go here. The danger is immediate. The car should not be driven until the rubbish is cleared."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/23/3880153/3880153_A36E5FE886804D9E822364F32A6C8D09_190823_3880153_Man_fined_for_driving_with_a_car_filled_to_the_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A00/F64/A00F64FDF2AD6F0814E21B26C6DEB2D4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, driving, driving, driving with trash, car filled with junk, man drives with car full of rubbish, car full of trash, car full of junk, car full of rubbish, car filled with trash, australia car trash, car stuffed with trash, pile of trash in car, garbage in cars, trash in cars, car stuffed with junk]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3880147</guid>
      <title>Japanese bullet train runs with an open door while going 280 kph</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  A bullet train in Japan had to make an emergency stop after one of its doors were found open.The train operator told the Japan Times that a cleaner forgot to close a device on the train that prevents the door from opening on its own.The bullet train left from Sendai Station and was traveling at a speed of 280 kilometers per hour with an open door as it entered a tunnel.The train's conductor noticed a warning light indicating that the train's ninth carriage had an open door, Japan Today reports. The conductor then checked the carriage and found the open door. The conductor immediately made an emergency stop while inside the tunnel. A checkup was conducted on the bullet train after which the train resumed its journey.It arrived in Tokyo 19 minutes after its scheduled arrival time.None of the 340 passengers on board were injured, reports NHK.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 11:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/23/3880147/3880147_2DF0D25033FA45E087A2FE6B062589E0_190823_3880147_Japanese_bullet_train_runs_with_an_open_door_whi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/590/019/59001979FDC6872335B371D5434C9DE9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bullet train, japan bullet train, Hayabusa number 46 bullet train, japan bullet train door opens, japan bullet train door, shinkansen bullet train, shinkansen  train japan, shinkansen japan, shinkansen door opens, japan bullet train door opens, japan bullet train runs with door open, japan bullet train door accidentally opens, japanese high speed rail]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3880020</guid>
      <title>Pepe the Frog being used as
resistance symbol in Hong Kong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Across Hong Kong, protestors are rallying against the authoritarian CCP and have selected none other than Pepe the Frog to represent them.But why have protesters in Hong Kong adopted the Alt-right symbol to represent their resistance?The New York Times reports that many protestors didn't know about Pepe's dark side and instead just like him.One protestor wrote on an anonymous forum that, sad frog meme is the "symbol of youth in the movement."Hongkonger, Paper Chu, a peaceful protestor, told the South China Morning Post that her fondness for the frog was based on its "irreverence" and that it feels "appropriate" to have him represent the attitudes of the Hong Kong people.She goes on to say that she applauds his "reincarnation" as a local hero and that she congratulates him on "becoming a Hongkonger."So far, his face has been spray-painted on the city's walls, emblazoned on fliers, pinned onto backs and has been propped up on picket signs. In the Times, Matt Furie who created the frog back in 2005 wrote that " Pepe is whatever you say he is, and I, the creator, say that Pepe is love."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 08:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/23/3880020/3880020_5D64405DACAE49A0AE1CB1FFAC9C686D_190823_3880020_Pepe_the_Frog_being_used_as_resistance_symbol_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0D0/764/0D0764FB7AD40E2F7EF71AEAFFAB3E11.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong, Pepe the frog, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong Pepe the Frog, extradition bill]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879840</guid>
      <title>Man gets surgery to remove fish bone stuck in his small intestine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANKOKU, JAPAN  A man in Japan ended up in the hospital after swallowing a tiny fish bone.The 73-year-old was enjoying his meal until he ate a yellowtail fish and felt pain in his lower abdomen.Citing a study from the New England Journal of Medicine, Live Science reports that the guy went to the emergency room where the doctors performed a physical exam and found tenderness across his lower abdomen. He let the doctors know that he had eaten a yellowtail.The doctors took a CT scan of the 73-year-old's abdomen. They noticed his small intestine had been punctured by a tiny fish bone.The man underwent surgery and the doctors successfully removed the part of his intestine that contained the 2-centimeter-long fish bone.The doctors also prescribed the 73-year-old with antibiotics to avoid infections from having a punctured small intestine.The man recovered after spending eight days in the hospital, according to the report.A separate study published in the World Journal of Gastroenterology found that less than one percent of ingested fish bones cause a tear to the intestines.The study also noted that more than 90 percent of fish bones are capable of passing through the intestinal tract without causing much problems.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 03:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/23/3879840/3879840_EF4F60AEF4F842E48C047518963B477C_190823_3879840_Man_gets_surgery_to_remove_fish_bone_stuck_in_hi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/229/FBA/229FBAB5B7F526974F2CADBECDF4E200.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fish bone, tiny fish bone, fish bone accidents, man swallows fish bone, accidently swallow fish bone, yellowtail, yellowtail fish bone, fish bone pierce hole through intestines, fish bone tears hole through man's intestine, fish bone stuck in intestine, fish bone stuck, fish bone removal, fish bone removal from intestine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3879825</guid>
      <title>Vulnerabilities found in Google's Indoor Nest cameras: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAINVIEW, CALIFORNIA  A new report by Cisco Talos, a cyber security intelligence and research group, has found eight different vulnerabilities in Google's Indoor Nest cameras.One of the bugs, called CVE-2019-5043, allowed multiple connection attempts to the camera's TCP, or Transmission Control Protocol, which would cause the camera's system to crash. While another bug allowed attackers to acquire and read sensitive information from the cameras.Two code security vulnerabilities, named CVE-2019-5038 and CVE-2019-5039, allowed attackers to exploit the camera's security system by luring users to open a malicious command on Google's open source network Weave, which is used by Google's Indoor Nest cameras. The researchers also found a bug in which attackers could potentially gain control over the security camera devices.In a statement to ZDNet, a spokesperson from Google said that they have fixed all the bugs and are in the process of updating all the Nest Camera IQs. The company added that the devices will automatically update so that users don't have to update it themselves.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2019 02:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/23/3879825/3879825_6AD3A2D922D840C1999BD07A45A056E9_190823_3879825_Vulnerabilities_found_in_Google_s_Indoor_Nest_ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/450/280/45028044DBE6AF0EBCAA0400E88B0A0D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, google, google nest cam indoor, nest indoor cam, google security camera, nest cam indoor security camera, nest cam, google nest cam security, google controversies, google nest cam controversy, google nest cam vulnerabilities, Nest Cam IQ Indoor camera, google nest cam data leak, google nest cam iq indoor security camera, google nest cam cisco talos, google home security camera]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3880396</guid>
      <title>Apple advises you not to put your Apple Card in leather</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA  Fanboys across 'Murcia are lining up to get Apple's latest and coolest game-changing productthe Apple Card. Okay, so some of you are probably saying to yourself, that's just a credit card. Well you're right. But not just ANY credit card, one that you actually have to clean.According to Engadget, Apple actually posted a cleaning guide for the card, one that warns against storing it against leathersoooo like most wallets and purses?  and denim, in case it causes discoloration that "will not wash off."The guide also advised against putting it in direct contact with other credit cards or loose items in case you scratch the titanium surface. If dumb enough to get the Apple Card, you're probably also dumb enough to clean it. In that case you can wipe it down with a microfiber cloth moistened with isopropyl alcohol. And think about this quote from Popular Mechanic about the Apple Card, "it might be a good option for people with less-than-perfect credit who like Apple products."Translation, if you're too poor to buy Apple products, use their credit card to borrow money from them which you can pay back with interest.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 03:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/24/3880396/3880396_570C92715C904DB19670963D39D7489F_190824_3880396_Apple_advises_you_not_to_put_your_Apple_Card_in__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/570/00D/57000D4AB52F1386CA74BD553A2C9032.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Apple Card, Apple credit card, Apple card cleaning guide, Apple card, Apple Card cleaning instructions, Apple Card discoloration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881547</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong police use water cannons on protesters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Hong Kong police and demonstrators faced off for the twelfth weekend in a row, with police firing a gun and deploying water cannon trucks, the BBC reports.The protests began in June as the Hong Kong government proposed an extradition bill that would allow suspects to be extradited for trial to mainland China.Those against the bill believe that Beijing may use it as a way to extradite political activists, dissidents and other critics in the city. The Hong Kong government has since suspended the bill, but protesters are calling for the government to withdraw it altogether.The protests have since morphed into a larger movement calling for greater autonomy in the territory.On Sunday, protests started in Hong Kong's Tsuen Wan district and spread to Tsim Sha Tsui. Some of the demonstrators threw bricks and petrol bombs at the police, BBC News reports. Protesters were also seen chasing the police with metal pipes, while four police officers were filmed drawing their guns and pointing them towards a group of people, CNN reports. One Hong Kong police officer fired a gunshot into the air on Sunday night as a warning to the protesters.The police deployed two water cannon trucks equipped with surveillance cameras and multiple nozzles, against the demonstrators for the first time, according to the Hong Kong Free Press. Activists are calling for the resignation of Hong Kong's leader Carrie Lam and are also pushing for an investigation into alleged police brutality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 14:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/26/3881547/3881547_BAAC4F3447944FBEBC75A328A0A8ED22_190826_3881547_Hong_Kong_police_use_water_cannons_on_protesters_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/70B/F8D/70BF8D952F98B71BD8DD9C7A1AF44673.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, HK mass protest, Hong Kong mass protest, China extradition, China extradition protests, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong,  Hong Kong protest 2019, Hong Kong protest today, hk protests latest news, hk protests 2019, hong kong police protest, hong kong protest 2019, hong kong police fire gun, hong kong police water cannons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881422</guid>
      <title>Man poos himself in supermarket, fails horribly trying to hide it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KARASU, TURKEY  A shopper in Turkey was caught on camera soiling himself in the middle of the supermarket and then failing horribly attempting to cover his tracks. According to the Sun, the footage starts with the man doing some shopping when he realizes the kids need to be dropped off immediately at the pool. CCTV footage then shows the man duck behind some shelves in LOO of an actual bathroom.  According to LadBible, the man then slowly penguin waddles over to the checkout, trying to play it off like nothing happened. Everything was going according to planwhen unfortunately for the manone of the deuces makes a not so clean break onto the supermarket floor.After putting his items down at the register, another little dookie makes a break for it down his leg. The guy then tries to use his Crocs to kick the stool under an ice cream freezer. Let's just say that didn't go so well. This is when the supermarket cashier walks up to the register and starts to smell something fishywell maybe it wasn't fish.  The man nonchalantly pays for his things and then just leaves, making a not-so-clean getaway.   According to the Sun, it's unclear if the supermarket is investigating into the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/26/3881422/3881422_F092084D6C7C4F969715BAD453F0B459_190826_3881422_Man_poos_himself_in_supermarket__fails_horribly__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7A8/9B3/7A89B34DC955798E8A1A0D9C47606A6F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man in supermarket, shopper in supermarket, Turkey supermarket, caught on camera, CCTV footage, shopper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881384</guid>
      <title>Ice cream licker on the loose!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORT ARTHUR, TEXAS  In a bid for attention, an ice cream enthusiast licks Blue Bell ice-cream straight from the tub and then puts it back in the freezer.KFDM reports that the incident took place in a Walmart in Port Arthur, Texas and that investigators have identified the man as 24-year-old D'Adrien Anderson.But in a twist, surveillance footage surprisingly shows him purchasing the ice cream for himself before any customer could. So, if he bought it, what's the big deal, right? Jefferson County District Attorney told KFDM that the store lost money because they, unsurprisingly, had to replace a ton of ice cream.The desperate act has resulted in a warrant for his arrest, which, if convicted of the Class A Misdemeanor, Anderson could face up to one year in jail and a fine of up to $4,000.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 09:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/26/3881384/3881384_4C83AFAB5968411498F504304AB64DB7_190826_3881384_Ice_cream_licker_on_the_loose__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/18B/F35/18BF350874E4BEBFF391FAA48EF717F5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ice-cream licker, blue bell, ice cream, Walmart ice-cream videos, licking ice cream, social media stunts, ice-cream licking, ice cream licking Walmart challenge, ice cream licking identified, ice cream phase, ice cream epidemic, ice cream jail time]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881319</guid>
      <title>Giant asteroid to fly past Earth next month</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  A massive asteroid will fly past earth early next month.Asteroid 2000 QW7, also known as 467317, will fly by earth on September 14, according to NASA's Center for Near Earth Object Studies. The approaching asteroid is currently moving at a speed of around 14,400 miles per hour.The asteroid had previously passed by our planet on September 1, 2000.According to the agency, Asteroid 2000 QW7 will be around 0.03563 astronomical units, or 3.3 million miles from earth as it approaches our planet. The asteroid's diameter is estimated to be around 950 feet to 2,132 feet.The asteroid orbits the sun and only occasionally passes by earth, according to NASA. It is next expected to fly by our planet on October 19, 2038.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 07:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/26/3881319/3881319_A9EDCC0BF5344C3CB7DD9F4A35A83FFC_190826_3881319_Giant_asteroid_to_fly_past_Earth_next_month_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B19/A0D/B19A0D7F6214D595A84AF779A74ED3DC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, NASA, space exploration, asteroid, asteroid in space, asteroid 2000 QW7, giant asteroid,  CNEOS, giant asteroid, giant asteroid to fly by earth soon, nasa giant asteroid, nasa tracking giant asteroid, giant asteroid to zoom by earth, asteroid 467317, space rocks, asteroid to fly past earth, asteroid to pass by earth next month]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882062</guid>
      <title>German boy jacks mom's car AGAIN for high-speed joyride</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DORTMUND, GERMANY  An 8-year-old boy who had already taken his mom's Volkswagen for a quick spin on the German autobahn earlier last week was at it again. According to CNN, local police said little man borrowed mom's VW Golf last Wednesday for the first time and took it for a short ride on the autobahn, reaching speeds of up to 87 mph. His mom called to police at 12:25 a.m., letting them know her son had taken the car. He was found by his mom shortly after at a service station along the autobahn about 5 miles from his house. According to CNN, the boy had parked the vehicle with the hazard lights on and a warning triangle to secure the area.  Apparently, he felt uncomfortable traveling on the faster freeway. According to DW, Tiny Torreto reportedly told police, "I just wanted to drive a little bit."After a stern warning, the authorities let him go with no criminal charges. Thank god, because little guy was able to come across his mom's keys again last Friday, driving from his hometown of Soest to Dortmund, about 30 miles away.DW reported Speed Racer reportedly hit speeds of 110 mph. Looks like he got over his fear of faster highways. Police said in a statement, "red traffic lights and traffic laws in general did not seem to interest the driver." Unfortunately, the boy's sequel hit a few bumps along the way. Police found him in a parking lot along the motorway, where he had a bit of a fender bender with a trailer of a parked truck. Luckily, no one was hurt. Too bad the same couldn't be said for mom's Golf. Police said the boy will now have to go to counseling. Counseling? Get this kid a movie roll.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 14:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/27/3882062/3882062_08BC747355344BE4B08B61DA67797C77_190827_3882062_German_boy_jacks_mom_s_car_AGAIN_for_high_speed__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/867/BA9/867BA92D6960CC4EFF42E7DF0547E5F7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, autobahn, German autobahn, Volkswagen Golf, joyride, Soest, Dortmund]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882043</guid>
      <title>Cunning monkey uses rock to smash his enclosure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HENAN, CHINA  A Capuchin monkey in Henan zoo has been caught utilizing his environment to smash his glass enclosure.Zoo staff rated this particular monkey as smart because he is more capable than the rest; he even employs tools to smash open walnuts while the less gifted simply bite into them.The report states that the zoo has since cleared all the stones from the monkey's enclosure.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 13:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/27/3882043/3882043_D491CFA9D2AB4B319C7AA9E2827BC14A_190827_3882043_Cunning_monkey_uses_rock_to_smash_his_enclosure_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1B4/383/1B4383E33999693B23B50A48241AEA97.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, monkey smashes glass, china zoo, monkey uses rock, the planet of the apes, monkey in zoo, monkey zoo video, money smash glass, money rock smash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881922</guid>
      <title>Doctors remove venomous spider from woman's left ear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KANSAS CITY, MISSOURI  A woman from Kansas City got the shock of her life when doctors informed her that a poisonous spider was living in her ear.Susie Torres told 41 Action News that she heard "swooshing" water sounds in her left ear when she woke up in the morning last week.As the sound wasn't going away, she decided to pay a visit to the hospital. A medical assistant first checked her ear and immediately ran out the door.She returned with a few other medical personnel and told Susie that there was a spider in her ear. More specifically, it was a venomous brown recluse spider.Susie was shocked. She told the news channel that she never knew spiders would crawl into someone's ear or any other part of the body.The doctors then used their tools and pulled the spider out of the woman's ear. Luckily for Suzie, the doctors told her the poisonous spider hadn't bitten her.According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, a brown recluses' venom is able to destroy a person's skin tissue and can cause severe bruises.Suzie said she isn't taking any chances and is now putting cotton balls in her ear before going to bed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 10:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/27/3881922/3881922_F17638A568EA4C3ABCDD36DC9F30648E_190827_3881922_Doctors_remove_venomous_spider_from_woman_s_left_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/71E/773/71E773C89CE713AFF513254DC82DD600.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, spider in ear, spider in ear canal, woman ear spider, woman finds spider in her ear, brown recluse spider, venomous brown recluse spider, venomous brown recluse spider found in woman's ear, spider in ear tomonews, removing spider in ear, venomous spider in ear, spider removed from ear, woman gets spider removed from ear, spider removed from woman's left ear]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3881683</guid>
      <title>Chinese mob harasses Taiwanese restaurant in Chile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTIAGO, CHILE  Chinese nationalists across the world have taken to the streets to show how butthurt they are over pro-democracy protests in Hong Kong. According to Taiwan's Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Chinese d-bags were harassing a Taiwanese restaurant in Chile last week after reportedly showing support for Hong Kong.According to the Taipei Times, the Representative Office of Taiwan in Santiago was in touch with Taiwanese owner surnamed Chang of Pollo Chang.   A video posted by Tony O'Donnell on YouTube shows a Wechat-organized Chinese mob in Santiago shutting down the fast-food and bubble tea shop. The winners in the video were seen hanging up the CCP rag in the restaurant.A bunch of other Jackie Chans can be seen carrying and waving their yellow and red flags around for everyone to laugh at. In another video posted up on social media, a really brave Chinese man is seen taking a leak outside on Pollo Chang's sidewalk while the store is closed.  China apparently thinks that by acting like spoiled little brats they're win over the hearts and minds of the free world. Good luck with that.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 02:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/27/3881683/3881683_363C823A549F43A1ACC7978232FA9217_190827_3881683_Chinese_mob_harasses_Taiwanese_restaurant_in_Chi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8C1/152/8C1152583276DCCB3C7238B2A4D931D9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese mob, Chinese nationalists, Chinese harass Taiwanese restaurant, Pollo Chang, Chile Pollo Chang, Hong Kong protests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882721</guid>
      <title>Woman plunges 6 stories
attempting yoga pose</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN PEDRO / MEXICO     A 23-year-old woman was posing for photographs on her balcony when she slipped and fell six stories, yet miraculously survived.The now-viral photo shows Alexa Terrazas balancing upside down on the railing.Citing local media outlet, El Imparcial, Ladbible state she slipped and fell 25 meters where she was then taken to a local hospital in the Mexican state of Nuevo Leon. An 11-hour surgery was conducted to "reconstruct" her legs, however, doctors claim she might not be able to walk for three years.Local reports say she is now in the hospital in critical condition. Some of her injuries include fractures to all four limbs and pretty serious injuries to her hips and skull. According to watchful neighbors, this was not the first time Terrazas has been observed practicing dangerous yoga on the balcony. Neighbors told El Imparcial reporters that they frequently saw the woman trying out dangerous stunts.  An investigation carried out by the Nuevo Leon attorney general's office showed that there were no structural failings in the balcony.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 23:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/29/3882721/3882721_8B02DE0D76EF4854B4ED895183BF94A4_190829_3882721_Woman_plunges_6_stories_attempting_yoga_pose_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AAC/A91/AACA9177CC21450FAE39DDED5BD74A0B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, yoga fails, yoga accident, woman falls off balcony, balconing, woman falls of balcony doing yoga, woman falls mexico, selfie fails, yoga mexico balcony, mexico woman falls of balcony]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882439</guid>
      <title>China is collecting citizens' DNA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China is gearing up to collect DNA from its citizens on a nationwide scale.According to a Radio Free Asia report, local governments in China are spending millions of yuan on DNA sampling kits, testing instruments, sequencers, and other tools.Online records of government contracts and tenders shows that U.S. firm Thermo Fisher is supplying most of the DNA instrument analyzing technology.Authorities are believed to be focusing on identifying male relatives and building family trees.In Hubei, a male DNA database project is expected to trace the male line across five generations, as well as identify adoptions, and children born outside officially sanctioned limits and norms.In the RFA report, China analyst Willy Lam said the DNA collection may be linked to plans to open up the hukou or Chinese household registration system.Any DNA database will also likely be used alongside existing AI systems, facial recognition technology, and the social credit system, making it convenient for government surveillance.DNA collection is also being extended to newborns. In June 2018, authorities in Guangzhou issued the first electronic birth certificate with a DNA barcode.In this instance, a consent form was part of the process to collect the babies' DNA. But that isn't always the case.Human Rights Watch previously reported that in Xinjiang, DNA samples, fingerprints, iris scans, and blood types are being collected from all citizens aged 12 to 65, under the guise of a free health care program.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 09:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/28/3882439/3882439_AA4FC55EC0094CA18C2C6D195C456F40_190828_3882439_China_is_collecting_citizens__DNA_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/08F/D51/08FD51DABDCE34303DAA951AEB28DF9C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, DNA collection, DNA database, China DNA database, China DNA, DNA samples, China surveillance state, facial recognition tech, China surveillance, hukou, household registration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882433</guid>
      <title>Feeding cows pink seaweed can help reduce methane emissions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRISBANE, AUSTRALIA  Australian scientists have found a puffy pink seaweed that can rid cows of their environmentally devastating methane burps.According to the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency, microbes in cows' stomachs produce methane as part of normal digestive processes.The gas can pass through either end of the animal, but does so primarily through the mouth, in the form of burps.As a greenhouse gas, methane may not be as prevalent in the atmosphere as carbon dioxide. But it is far more effective at trapping radiation, and is 25 times more potent than CO2.To combat methane emissions from cattle, researchers from Australia's University of the Sunshine Coast turned to a pink seaweed called Asparagopsis, which grows naturally off the Queensland coast.When added to cattle feed at a ratio of two percent, the seaweed reduced microbes in the cows' guts, which eliminated methane production by up to 99 percent.According to USC Associate Professor Nick Paul, who heads the Seaweed Research Group, Asparagopsis is not a particularly abundant species.As such, the team is currently trying to determine the perfect growing conditions for the seaweed, with the goal of growing it sustainably, at a much larger scale.If enough pink seaweed can be grown and fed to every cow in the country, Professor Paul says Australia could cut its greenhouse gas emissions by 10 percent.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 09:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/28/3882433/3882433_E9792819A99A4EF39409EF95D21FD7A8_190828_3882433_Feeding_cows_pink_seaweed_can_help_reduce_methan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/092/44A/09244A93C3DFBA8A17842D8BFF5E940A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pink seaweed, methane reduction, methane emissions, cow methane emissions, cow seaweed diet, greenhouse gases, climate change, global warming, cow burp, asparagopsis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882326</guid>
      <title>First Costco opens up in Shanghai, closes early because of crowds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  Costco opened up its first physical store in China on Tuesday, but then had to close it early because it was swamped with China-sized crowds. According to CNBC, videos posted to Chinese social media show hoards of Chinese shoppers descending upon the store like it was packed with nothing but the latest Jordans. "The store has been clogged up with crowds," Costco said in a text message to customers. "To provide you with better shopping experience, Costco will suspend business in the afternoon. Please don't come." According to CNN, the police had to be called in to help corral all the crazy shoppers, restore order and manage traffic jams around the store. Photos posted by the police show one Costco sign reading, "the parking lot is full. It takes three hours to wait."CNN reports that Costco has had an online presence in China for five years in a venture with Alibaba. Their first physical store marks a big investment. According to CNN, annual membership costs around $42. Wonder how long it will be before Chinese consumers realize you probably didn't need a year's supply of peanut butter?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 06:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/28/3882326/3882326_73D956E1A18447DFA00ACDE266EC363A_190828_3882326_First_Costco_opens_up_in_Shanghai__closes_early__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/739/E2B/739E2BF57979ADC9BA3E38C5155FC282.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Costco, Costco opens in China, China Costco, Shanghai Costco, Shanghai Costco crowds, China Costco crowds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882309</guid>
      <title>KFC teaming up with Beyond Meat to test meatless chicken</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA, GEORGIA  Looks as if old Colonel Sanders will be testing out the fake meat market by teaming up with Beyond Meat to offer customers a faux chicken option.CNBC reports that KFC will start taste testing plant-based fried chicken at one of its restaurants in Hotlanta. The fake chicken will be supplied by Beyond Meat, making KFC the first national US fast food joint to test the company's chicken-esque product. The Colonel will be trying out plant-based nuggets and fake meat boneless wings. Complimentary samples will be offered to people buying other thingslike actual fried chicken. Bloomberg reported that according to a KFC statement, "customer feedback from the Atlanta test will be considered as KFC evaluates a broader test or potential national rollout." According to Bloomberg, Beyond Meat is starting to appear on restaurant menus across the U.S. and Canada as plant-based meat alternatives rise in popularity at chains like Dunkin' Donuts, Tim Hortons and Carl's Jr.  Bloomberg also said competitor Impossible Foods Inc, has teamed up with Burger King for the Impossible Whopper and sliders for White Castle. But probably the best part about KFC's fake chicken is that annoying vegans won't be able to eat it because the Beyond Fried Chicken will be cooked in the same fryers as the real finger licking good chicken. Will faux chicken help KFC get beyond Chick-fil-A and Popeye's though? What do you think?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 06:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/28/3882309/3882309_C64E5C7E902541F09983CCD6F120F643_190828_3882309_KFC_teaming_up_with_Beyond_Meat_to_test_meatless_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3DC/46E/3DC46E505BAADA90695DEFF6D05E0A92.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, KFC, KFC Beyond Meat, KFC fake chicken, KFC plant-based chicken, KFC faux meat, KFC testing fake chicken]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882283</guid>
      <title>Bed bug army completely takes over house in Maryland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARYLAND  A pest control company had quite the welcome when they discovered a massive bed bug infestation at a house in Maryland. According to Storytrender, Rory McCarty, owner of Bug Boys Pest Control was out on call at a residence on July 17.When he had a peek under the owner's bed, he was shocked to find an army of bed bugs had taken over. In a video posted to Facebook, McCarty warns his other workers to keep a safe distance from the bed before going into battle against the little buggers. When the crew lifts the mattress off the springs, a ton of disgusting bed bugs drop onto the floor and scatter. Bed bugs were found in the cushions, chairs and curtains in the bedroom. Unluckily for the homeowner, the bed bugs had spread throughout the entire house.And the crazy thing is, the homeowners were still sleeping in the bed bug bed up until the exterminators came.According to McCarty, "bed bugs can be one of the most expensive bugs out there to get rid of."He also added, "I've been doing this for 25 years and it still amazes me seeing bad infestations, but I still get very excited like it's the first time seeing them because we're really good at what we do." Probably also helps a little bit that they're so expensive to get rid of.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 04:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/28/3882283/3882283_9F8E9C6B1D704130AB5FE6792633232E_190828_3882283_Bed_bug_army_completely_takes_over_house_in_Mary_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/019/F19/019F193202EBC614EE538FC83521D954.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bed bugs, bed bugs infestation, bed bug infestation, bed bugs in mattress, bed bugs in cushions, bed bugs furniture, Bug Boys Pest Control]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3882191</guid>
      <title>Huge pumice raft could help save Australia's Great Barrier Reef</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PACIFIC OCEAN  An enormous floating raft of volcanic rocks is drifting along the Pacific Ocean towards Australia, where it could help with the recovery of the Great Barrier Reef's corals.According to NASA's Earth Observatory, an underwater volcano near Tonga is believed to have erupted on August 7, spewing out pumice stones of different sizes.The BBC reports that over a trillion pieces of pumice are floating together on the Pacific Ocean, stretched out over 150 square kilometers.According to CNN, the pumice raft is roughly the size of Manhattan.Queensland University of Technology Associate Professor Scott Bryan told the BBC that the pumice is currently drifting west toward Fiji. It will likely pass New Caledonia and Vanuatu and possibly reach Australia in about a year.According to CNN, the pumice will bring with it microorganisms and other marine life as it drifts across the ocean. This could potentially bring in diverse colonies of corals or barnacles that could help restock the damaged Great Barrier Reef.Experts say pumice fields are one way the ocean can redistribute sea life. They aren't uncommon, and are typically spotted every five years or so.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 01:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/28/3882191/3882191_68E8F7162DC946B38D3C19FB3AF7B7DF_190828_3882191_Huge_pumice_raft_could_help_save_Australia_s_Gre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E54/EFF/E54EFF906287F7B8A534A86D9038A081.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pumice, pumice raft, floating pumice, great barrier reef, volcano eruption, underwater volcano eruption, underwater volcano, save the great barrier reef, coral restocking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883198</guid>
      <title>Indonesia plans to relocate capital city to Borneo island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAKARTA, INDONESIA  President Joko Widodo has announced plans to shift Indonesia's capital city from Jakarta to the province of East Kalimantan on Borneo island.Part of the new capital will be in the province's North Penajam Paser regency while the other half will be in the Kutai Kartanegara regency, reports the Jakarta Post. The region was chosen for being relatively free from earthquakes and volcanoes.Indonesia plans to relocate from its current capital, Jakarta, as the city is overpopulated and faces severe congestion, according to Reuters. Jakarta is also sinking 10 to 20 centimeters per year due to severe land subsidence, reports the Guardian. The Indonesian government said it wants to build a smart, green city. A government official was quoted by the South China Morning Post as saying that they would not disturb any existing protected forest as the island is filled with tropical rainforests.If President Widodo's plan is approved by the Indonesian parliament, the new capital will begin construction across a plot of around 40,000 hectares next year.In a televised speech, the Indonesian president said that the location is strategic and explained that the shift would ease Jakarta's burden as the center of business, finance, trade and government.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/29/3883198/3883198_14761FD4D3D841C1A3E5D23C2087965D_190829_3883198_Indonesia_plans_to_relocate_capital_city_to_Born_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F92/631/F9263180EA18FE14A614447D584DC4AA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, indonesia, indonesia capital, indonesia new capital, indonesia capital city move, indonesia capital city change, indonesia capital sinking, indonesia capital relocation,  indonesia capital city sinking, indonesia capital city 2019, indonesia capital borneo, indonesia new capital borneo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883169</guid>
      <title>'Fastest woman on four wheels' Jessi Combs dies in jet-car crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FIELDS, OREGON  Professional racer, fabricator, and television personality Jessi Combs died in a jet-car crash on Tuesday while trying to break her land-speed record. According to CBS Sports, Combs broke 398 mph while driving a North American Eagle Supersonic Speed Challenger in 2013, where she also picked up the nickname "fastest woman on four wheels." Yahoo reported that in 2016, Combs broke her own record at 440 mph. Then last year while attempting a run which ended prematurely due to mechanical issues, she hit a top speed of 483 mph.  She was using the same 52,000 horsepower jet-car while attempting to break her personal best when she fatally crashed on the dried lake bed of the Alvord Desert.  According to KTVZ, the Harney County Sheriff's Office said it received a 911 call shortly after 4 p.m. Tuesday reporting the crash in the desert. According to CBS Sports, Combs wasn't only a racer but a builder and fabricator and was part of the American Welding society. She was a frequent guest on TV shows like "Mythbusters," "Overhaulin" and "All Girls Garage." Combs was one serious bad ass that will truly be missed. Godspeed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 11:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/29/3883169/3883169_AC7F0413E8754AEFB50E885B2CBE66C1_190829_3883169__Fastest_woman_on_four_wheels__Jessi_Combs_dies__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7D2/735/7D273533B3D5F7A9560F4C1B1A2021D5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Jessi Combs, Jessi Combs crash, Jessi combs jet car, Jessi Combs land speed record, Jessi Combs Mythbuster, Jessi Combs accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883144</guid>
      <title>Robber's car gets stolen while he's breaking into a store</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENNEWICK, WASHINGTON  There's just no honor among thieves these days, which one man experienced the hard way.According to KEPR, Kennewick Police responded around 6 a.m. last Sunday to reports of a car being stolen. KEPR reports that the owner of the truck, William Kelley, called authorities saying someone had jacked his red 1992 Chevy pick-up. Police say a man noticed that Kelley had left his keys on his seat, so he did what anyone would dohe stole the vehicle. The funny thing is, after the cops reviewed surveillance video of the incident, they discovered Kelley had parked his truck because he was busy breaking into a business across the street. Kelley was tossed into Benton County jail on a warrant and a new burglary charge. Now all the police need to do is find the person that boosted Kelley's Chevy. If you have any information and you don't mind being a snitch, call the Kennewick Police Department.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 11:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/29/3883144/3883144_FC05B3D8529348FD987E9C56D00A41BA_190829_3883144_Robber_s_car_gets_stolen_while_he_s_breaking_int_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CFE/4A7/CFE4A7578B92D2EC2A464D3371E3DC1E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, robber gets car stolen, robber's truck gets stolen, instant karma, Kennewick Police Department]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883039</guid>
      <title>U.S. fears cyber attack on next year's presidential elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. government is increasing its efforts to protect election databases and electoral systems from hackers in the run-up to next year's presidential elections, Reuters reports.The Cybersecurity Infrastructure Security Agency, CISA, which is a part of the Department of Homeland Security, issued a statement and a set of guidelines in order to prevent next year's elections from being compromised.The agency warned that hackers may try to target voter databases and attempt to manipulate, disrupt or even destroy voting data by conducting ransomware cyber attacks.In an ransomware attack, hackers lock a computer with malicious software until someone remits money, usually in the form of cryptocurrency, to the attacker, according to Reuters.CISA said in the statement that they will be working with the Election Infrastructure Information Sharing and Analysis Center to provide remote vulnerability scanning and risk assessments for state governments upon request.CISA issued a set of guidelines urging local governments to regularly back up critical data on the system and to store backup files offline.However, an unnamed senior Homeland Security official told Reuters that there is no standard regulation stating how often backups should be created.CISA also urged local governments to have a clear plan to address the cyber attacks and to request assistance from their agency or the Election Infrastructure Information Sharing and Analysis Center if an attack occurs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 09:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/29/3883039/3883039_01CB61E72094476F9F5960601A9E6101_190829_3883039_U_S__fears_cyber_attack_on_next_year_s_president_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D57/13E/D5713E9F9FD9A020C9781CFDE981BFA4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US elections, US elections 2020, ransomware attack, CISA, ransomware outbreak, US fears cyber attack on US elections, 2020 presidential elections, 2020 presidential elections hacking fear, cyber attack USA, cyber attack US, cyber attack, hacking elections, hacking elections USA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883853</guid>
      <title>Metal from tattoo needles found in human lymph nodes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRENOBLE, FRANCE  A new study published in the journal Particle and Fiber Toxicology has found that tattoo needles deposit metal particles such as nickel and chromium into the skin during the tattooing process.These particles are then transported from the tattoo site to the body's lymph nodes, where their sizes ranged from 50 nanometers to 2 micrometers, according to a news release by the European Synchrotron Radiation Facility.Researchers analyzed a tattoo needle by using a scanning electron microscopy to take a closer look at the needle before and after the tattoo process.They found that the needle showed abrasions from certain tattoo inks that contain titanium dioxide, a white pigment that is usually mixed in bright colors such as green or blue. Researchers did not find the same result with carbon black ink.The news release noted that further studies would be needed to understand the metal particles' impact on tattoo allergy formation and long-term impact on human health.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 13:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/30/3883853/3883853_14B10567E34141CB8C8D723E033DDB16_190830_3883853_Metal_from_tattoo_needles_found_in_human_lymph_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/959/F8D/959F8D1CA5CFB5B6DD61546380CA442D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tattoos, tattoos metal particles, European Synchrotron Radiation Facility, tattoo needles, tattoo needles metal particles, tattoo metal particles lymph nodes, tattoo lymph nodes, tattoo ink in lymph nodes, lymph node tattoo pigment, tattoo needle lymph nodes, tattoo needles metal particles lymph node]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883828</guid>
      <title>Boris Johnson has Queen put parliament in time out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Britain's new Prime Minister Boris Johnson threw down the gauntlet this week on Brexit by setting in motion the suspension of the UK parliament.Parliament is going to be put in time out for five weeks ahead of doomsday on October 31 when the UK is set to say sayonara to the EU  B.J. made the dramatic move by asking the Queen to suspend parliament. Although this is just a formality, it would have been unprecedented had she refused. She didnot.Johnson is proroguing he says to give his administration a fresh start to set out its "very exciting agenda."But look past the hair and you see the real reason for the moveBrexit. By putting parliament on ice between Sept. 11 and Oct. 14, PMs would only have two weeks to stop or stall the UK's likely divorce with the EU on the 31st.  Boris was a key figure in the Leave campaign and has promised to complete the break up "do or die"with or without a deal.    Many fear a no deal Brexit would hammer the British economy, shoot up prices and restrict access to the UK's biggest market. How many more stops will there be for the slowest trainwreck in history?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 13:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/30/3883828/3883828_F49337BF6969460080E3AA52AEDC00C2_190830_3883828_Boris_Johnson_has_Queen_put_parliament_in_time_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/205/29B/20529B039B3786C47A2C16E2F6B713D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Brexit, Boris Johnson, Boris Johnson suspends parliament, prorogue, Queen suspends parliament, Boris Johnson Brexit, Boris Johnson No Deal, No Deal Brexit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883804</guid>
      <title>U.S. tries to block 8,000-mile
Google &amp; Facebook sea-cable</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Google and Facebook are building the fastest underwater data cable ever built, however, it's at risk of being abandoned on the grounds of national security. Google's 8,000-mile subsea cable, known as the Pacific Light Cable Network, plans to provide ultra high capacity internet transmissions between LA and Hong Kong by using new fiber optics with a capacity of up to 120 terabytes of data per second.Google details the cable as not only being able to bring faster internet speeds and heightened security but most impressively being able to support 80 million simultaneous HD video conference calls between Asia and North America.However, The Wall Street Journal reports that a panel led by the Justice Department known as "Team Telecom" has signaled opposition over national security concerns with the cable's private Chinese backer, the telecommunications company, Dr. Peng.Business Insider states that many Chinese companies maintain a close relationship with the Chinese government to ensure a "favorable business environment," thus making them susceptible to being utilized by the CCP.If successful, the cable could grant U.S. companies greater access to other developing markets in Asia, such as the Philippines and Malaysia.Regardless of the potential benefits, the cable's fate is uncertain with the tensions between the U.S. and China continuing to escalate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 12:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/30/3883804/3883804_ABC3B28AEEFB4DF48420EFF2CC6C8092_190830_3883804_U_S__tries_to_block_8_000_mile_Google___Facebook_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9FD/410/9FD410C478A01B9F95152F550C0D77D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, google subsea cable, google facebook sea cable, national security threat, china google, LA to HK google cable, Google cable, US try to block Goggle cable, LA to Hong Kong cable]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883415</guid>
      <title>Nestle plans to take 1.1M gallons of water from Florida spring</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HIGH SPRINGS, FLORIDA  Nestle sparked intense outrage among environmentalists over plans to pump an obscene amount of water from a spring in Florida.According to the Guardian, Nestle is seeking permission to take over 1.1 million gallons of water a day from Ginnie Springs in Florida's Sante Fe river, to sell as bottled water.Opponents of the plan say the river system is in recovery, and cannot withstand the proposed pumping. Residents also say taking that much water will harm the springs and its ecosystem, and deplete their own drinking supply.Nestle denies all these, claiming that spring water is a rapidly renewable resource. For a million gallons a day? Riiight.The Guardian reports that Nestle has spent millions buying and upgrading a nearby water bottling plant, anticipating that permission would be granted.But in order to proceed, it would need the Suwannee River Water Management District to renew an expired water use permit held by local company Seven Springs, from which it plans to buy the water.Though Nestle has promised a 'robust' management plan for the spring, local environmentalists don't trust the company's intentions.They are also worried that the plan might threaten the 11 native turtle species and four non-native species who call the spring system home, and rely on vigorous water flow and river levels.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 03:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/30/3883415/3883415_FEF7A77A6C4147168A48D3AD8E297B02_190830_3883415_Nestle_plans_to_take_1_1M_gallons_of_water_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E43/C79/E43C7937FCCB178619A4DFEB2ED38AB9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nestle, nestle spring water, nestle bottled water, ginnie springs, spring water, boycott nestle, santa fe river, florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883408</guid>
      <title>Prorogation in the U.K. and what it means for Brexit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson has asked the Queen to prorogue Parliament. Here's what that means and why it's important.According to The Guardian, prorogation is a formal mechanism to end a session of parliament. When this happens, the House of Commons is suspended, and any unfinished legislation from the current session stops progressing.Prorogation must be approved by the Queen, following guidance from her Privy Council. It typically lasts only a short time, with the start of a new session marked by a speech from the Queen detailing the government's new agenda.While these proceedings are normal and happen yearly, the five-week prorogation requested by Boris Johnson is unusually long.It is set to begin no earlier than September 9 and no later than September 12, and will last until October 14.With the Brexit deadline set for October 31, MPs have just a little over two weeks to scrutinize Johnson's Brexit plans. Such a long prorogation would likewise restrict MPs from pushing legislation to block a no-deal Brexit.Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn has called Johnson's move a "smash and grab" on the country's democracy.The BBC reports that hundreds protested the prorogation outside Westminster Wednesday night, with more demonstrations slated over the weekend.More than a million have also signed a petition appealing for parliament not to be prorogued.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 03:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/30/3883408/3883408_1B3B5331342748648E9D415A5142A6D3_190830_3883408_Prorogation_in_the_U_K__and_what_it_means_for_Br_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F32/F78/F32F78B98EEED7E7FF25D5DCB11578FF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, prorogation, UK, paused parliament, proroguing parliament, suspended parliament, boris johnson, brexit, no deal brexit, brexit deadline, UK parliament]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3883398</guid>
      <title>NASA attaches Mars helicopter
to Mars 2020 rover</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA  NASA's Mars 2020 rover will carry a small helicopter that will be deployed over the Red Planet to conduct test flights and capture photos of the Martian surface.NASA's engineers have connected a small helicopter to the bottom of the Mars 2020 rover.A cover will shield the mini helicopter from debris as the rover lands on Mars' surface, according to NASA. The aircraft will be deployed over the Red Planet once the Mars rover finds a suitable area to conduct test flights. The helicopter will be carrying a camera to capture photos of the Martian surface for transmission back to Earth.NASA's website explains that the main body of the Mars helicopter will be the size of a softball and weigh under four pounds. The helicopter will use two sets of rotor blades that are four feet long. These will spin at 2,400 rotations per minute to allow the helicopter to fly as high as 15 feet above the Red Planet.The Mars helicopter will include a solar array to recharge its batteries that are to be used to rotate the blades and keep the vehicle warm throughout the night.If the test flights are successful, second-generation helicopters could be used for future Mars missions.The Mars 2020 rover will be launched in July next year from Cape Canaveral Air Force Station in Florida.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/08/30/3883398/3883398_108E1B5275B9410190D597711799002C_190830_3883398_NASA_attaches_Mars_helicopter_to_Mars_2020_rover_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E69/DCA/E69DCA92EF09D06F0A0EE26DAE48C6BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Mars helicopter, Mars 2020, Mars rover, Mars mission, NASA helicopter, NASA, helicopter on Mars, Mars, NASA Mars mission 2020, nasa helicopter mars, nasa helicopter to mars, nasa is sending a helicopter to mars, nasa plans to send a helicopter to mars in 2020, mars helicopter, marscopter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
