<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3956962</guid>
      <title>Chinese people making DIY coronavirus helmets, masks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  As the Wuhan virus continues to fan out across all parts of China, the number of confirmed cases is already over 9,400, with another 12,000 plus suspected cases and over 200 dead.  And these are numbers coming out of China, so clearly the actual numbers are obviously higher than what's being reported. Amongst all the madness, Chinese travelers have started to take matters into their own hands and have started to think outsideREAL outside the mask.  People have been spotted in and around China with all types of do-it-yourself coronavirus helmets and masks.One popular type appears to be the plastic water jug helmet. Chinese people have been spotted on planes, trains and automobiles sporting the stylish not-so-protective gear.This guy appears to be going for a Kylo Ren-esque look with his water jug and water bottles. For those that can't spring for the water jug, don't worry, a motorcycle helmet will suffice. Probably not, but what the hell. Then there are the more eco-friendly masks made from fruit. But what if you can't find or make any of these masks yourself? Here's one way you can stop the flowof contaminated air you breathe.  So are any of these methods effective? Probably not. Are they safe? Well, one of the first things you learn as a child is to never put your head in a plastic bag. Guess that doesn't apply in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 15:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956962/3956962_097EAB4495834D22912D15EEA4033541_200131_3956962_Chinese_people_making_DIY_coronavirus_helmets__m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Wuhan coronavirus, DIY coronavirus mask, homemade coronavirus mask, coronavirus helmets, China Wuhan virus, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956917</guid>
      <title>SpinLaunch will slingshot rockets into space with giant centrifuge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONG BEACH, CALIFORNIA  A U.S. aerospace company is building a huge centrifuge to launch spacecraft into orbit.Wired.com reports that the SpinLaunch's centrifuge, or the kinetic launch system, has an internal vacuum chamber with a diameter of 100 meters.The SpinLaunch rocket is about the size of an SUV and the vehicle's design will allow it to carry a satellite payload of about 200 pounds.The centrifuge's electric motor will spin the tethered rocket for an hour to build up speed.Once the rocket is ratcheted up to a speed of over 5,000 miles per hour, the release mechanism will cut the vehicle loose and let it fly through the 35 degree launch tunnel.When the vehicle reaches the edge of the stratosphere, the rocket's internal propulsion will fire and push the spacecraft through the final stretch to space.Citing SpinLaunch, Wired reports that the centrifuge could launch up to five small satellites a day and reduce launch costs by a factor of almost 20.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956917/3956917_C49F0D50BB174D7295F8F6B6231588AF_200131_3956917_SpinLaunch_will_slingshot_rockets_into_space_wit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Centrifuge, space launch, throwing rockets into space, slinging rockets into space, giant centrifuge, launch rockets, kinetic launch system, spinlaunch, U.S., space, aerospace, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956857</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus might infect people faster than Ebola</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  Chinese Researchers find that the novel coronavirus epidemic doubled in size every 7.4 days during the initial outbreak from December last year to early this month.The statistical study published in the New England Journal of Medicine suggests human to human transmission occurred early in the outbreak's beginning.Examining the first 425 confirmed cases of coronavirus infection, the scientists estimate that the mean incubation period was 5.2 days.Before January 1, 2020, 55 percent of the symptomatic cases were linked to the Wuhan wet market, but just 8.6 percent of the subsequent cases were connected to the market."The authors say that it is clear that human-to-human transmission is occurring and that the epidemic has been spreading in recent weeks.MedPage Today reports that virus' reproductive number of 2.2 means a carrier will infect two people on average, which is more than Ebola.Citing Infectious Diseases Society of America, the outlet reports that the reproductive number is situational and quarantining a patient could reduce the number to zero.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 11:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956857/3956857_41A5D997CBC54B4CB917F35CE10DE612_200131_3956857_Wuhan_virus_might_infect_people_faster_than_Ebol_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china virus outbreak 2020, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, wuhan virus, china pneumonia, faster than the Ebola, faster than ebola, reproduction number, 2019-ncov, 2019 ncov, novel coronavirus, new coronavirus,  TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956763</guid>
      <title>Harvard professor charged with hiding illegal ties to China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS   A Harvard professor is in big trouble with the feds for lying about his ties with China.According to court documents, Charles Lieber headed Harvard University's Lieber Research Group, and got over $15 million in grants from the U.S. National Institutes of Health and Department of Defense.What he failed to mention was that he was also on another country's payroll. The BBC reports that in 2011, Lieber was recruited by China into its Thousand Talents Plan, which is designed to lure foreign scientists and research specialists to China.He joined the Wuhan University of Technology as a scientist, and was paid a salary of $50 Gs a month and up to $158,000 in living expenses to set up a research lab, apply for patents, and publish articles on the Chinese university's behalf.Lieber was arrested at his office on Tuesday for concealing his Chinese funding, and remains in federal custody.Prosecutors also announced charges for Boston University robotics researcher Yangqing Ye, who sent documents and information to China and hid the fact that she was a lieutenant for the People's Liberation Army.Just last month, authorities also nabbed a Chinese cancer researcher for stealing specimen vials from a lab and attempting to smuggle them back into China inside a sock in his luggage.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 09:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956763/3956763_266CED41CBA74BE0A7CC258C430DCC22_200131_3956763_Harvard_professor_charged_with_hiding_illegal_ti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Harvard professor arrested, Harvard professor China ties, thousand talents plan, China spy, China espionage, China intellectual property theft, Charles Lieber, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956708</guid>
      <title>Pentagon says 50 soldiers were injured after Iranian missile strike</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRAQ  The Pentagon now says that 50 U.S. troops stationed in Iraq have been diagnosed with traumatic brain injury after an Iranian missile strike earlier this month.The agency previously said that 34 troops had been injured in the Iranian attacks.In an earlier statement, the Department of Defense explained that Iran launched more than a dozen ballistic missiles that targeted U.S. military and coalition forces in Iraq on January 7.The attack was an act of retaliation against the U.S. after the killing of Qassem Soleimani, an Iranian Revolution Guard general.Thirty-one of the soldiers were treated in Iraq and have since returned to duty, Reuters reports, citing a statement. Eighteen troops have been sent to Germany for further treatment while one was sent to Kuwait and has since returned to duty.According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, symptoms of traumatic brain injury include headaches, dizziness, nausea, and sensitivity to noise or light.The Trump administration has been criticized for taking so long to reveal the extent of casualties caused by the Iranian missile attack, reports BBC News. U.S. President Donald Trump had initially said that no U.S. soldier had been injured right after the attack before raising the number of casualties to 34 and now 50.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 07:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956708/3956708_E22778C17085487AA9D01E0C4CEFC3D2_200131_3956708_Pentagon_says_50_soldiers_were_injured_after_Ira_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[iran vs usa, iranian attack on us airbase, iranian attack on us airbase in Iraq, US troops injured in Iraninan attack, Ain al-Asad air base, iranian attack 2020, US troops traumatic brain injury, iran strike US troops, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956702</guid>
      <title>The Wuhan coronavirus has spread to every region in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  China has confirmed its first case of novel coronavirus in Tibet. This means the Wuhan virus has now spread to every single region across China, bringing up the total number of confirmed cases to nearly 9,800 as of Friday, according to the New York Times.According to CNN, the number of coronavirus cases has already surpassed the number of SARS cases, which was 5,327, inside China back in 2003. The virus has taken the lives of 213 people in China.The novel coronavirus has spread to at least 19 other nations including Japan, South Korea, Vietnam, Cambodia, Malaysia, Singapore, the U.S. and Canada, reports BBC News. Since the outbreak, countries including Japan and the U.S. have rushed to evacuate their citizens out of the Chinese city of Wuhan, where the virus is believed to have originated.The New York Times reports health officials in the U.S. reported its first human to human transmission of the coronavirus. A woman who had traveled to Wuhan had spread the virus to her husband who had not been to China. Both of them have now been hospitalized for treatment.According to CNN, other countries including Australia, Germany, Italy and Spain said that they are working with local authorities in China and are expected to repatriate their citizens out of Wuhan later this week.On Thursday, the World Health Organization declared the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak a global health emergency.A large number of countries are advising their citizens to avoid all non-essential travel to China, BBC News reports. Symptoms of the coronavirus include severe coughing, fever and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.The coronavirus is believed to have originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there are now documented cases of the virus being transmitted between humans.The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention advised the public to wear facemasks and cover the mouth when coughing or sneezing to prevent the spread of the coronavirus. The CDC also advised the public to avoid using unwashed hands to touch their eyes, nose and mouth, and to avoid sharing items that could easily be infected.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 07:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956702/3956702_76D84EDAD66D4354B0A53B3BAB6EC1B6_200131_3956702_The_Wuhan_coronavirus_has_spread_to_every_region_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[china virus outbreak 2020, china virus outbreak, chinese virus, coronavirus mystery virus, chinese disease, wuhan pneumonia, china pneumonia, china wuhan virus outbreak, wuhan outbreak,  TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956590</guid>
      <title>Starbucks shuts 2,000 Chinese stores over coronavirus fears</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Starbucks has shut down half of its stores in China amid the coronavirus outbreak in order to protect its staff and support government containment efforts.NPR reports that the coffee behemoth has temporarily shut more than 2,000 outlets as the number of infected have skyrocketed throughout the country.    According to the BBC, Starbucks warned that the latest epidemic could affect its financial performance. Which is all anyone really cares about, right? The Beebs reports that the coffee chain has almost 4,300 stores in China, making it the company's biggest market outside the U.S. Starbucks CEO Kevin Johnson said the company was "navigating a very dynamic situation." As the Wuhan coronavirus threatens to spiral out of control, Chinese authorities have tried all types of measures including the locking down of a bunch of cities with tens of millions of people. According to Business Insider, other fast food chains such as McDonald's, KFC and Pizza Hut have also been shutting down stores in response to the virus.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 03:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956590/3956590_BB48B2ECDB4A49118519D3D48326FDC2_200131_3956590_Starbucks_shuts_2_000_Chinese_stores_over_corona_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Starbucks shuts China stores, Starbucks shuts 2,000 stores China, Starbucks coronavirus, Wuhan coronavirus, China coronavirus outbreak, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957678</guid>
      <title>World's first cheese-themed hotel opens in London</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMDEN, LONDON  Can you brie-lieve it! The world's first 'cheese-themed' hotel has opened in London, with cheese-themed wallpaper, artwork, bedding, and even cheese-scented soap.The Cheese Suite in Camden will be open until the 6th of February; the room is a part of a promotion by restaurant chain Café Rouge to celebrate its new 'cheesy menu'.Guests will also have access to a 'cheese hotline', at the push of a button you'll be provided with 'melted cheesy goodness' straight from Café Rouge.Stays are limited to one night and are free, guests are selected at random but are encouraged to donate to the restaurant chain's charity, the Prince's Trust.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 23:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957678/3957678_01F1BB1A00384BE99980F265226FFEAC_200203_3957678_World_s_first_cheese_themed_hotel_opens_in_Londo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cheese hotel, U.K cheese hotel, cheese-themed hotel, TomoNews, satire, cheese room, Cafe Rouge, Cafe Rouge cheese hotel, funny hotels, strange hotels]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957959</guid>
      <title>A dwarf star's giant mass twists the fabric of space and time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA  In a new study published in Science, astronomer writes that a dwarf star in the Musca constellation has so much mass that it measurably distorts space and time.According to OzGrav, the dwarf star's stellar companion, an exotic pulsar, courses around the bigger star in a speedy five-hour orbit.Space.com reports that the white dwarf is the size of the Earth, but according to OzGrav, the star's mass and density is hundreds of thousands of times greater than our planet.According to Space.com, the pulsar is the corpse of a star that had gone supernova and the dead star crushes protons and electrons to emit neutrons.The white dwarf's powerful gravity and rapid spin cause frame-dragging, or distortions in space-time.Frame-dragging imparts a wobbling effect on the pulsar and makes the neutron star twirl on its axis about 30 times an hour.The drift in the pulsar's orbit is then picked up by Australia's telescopes, including Parkes, which allowed astrophysicists to corroborate Einstein 's theory of general relativity.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 11:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957959/3957959_57CE6767A56747FBBBA136669681B981_200203_3957959_A_dwarf_star_s_giant_mass_twists_the_fabric_of_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[White dwarf, giant stars, giant star, twisting space and time, distorting space and time, space-time continuum, space time, pulsar, space-time distortion, frame-dragging, frame dragging, gravity, binary stars, albert einstein,  general theory of relativity, general relativity, relativity, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957950</guid>
      <title>Bird flu outbreak kills thousands of chickens in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHAOYANG, CHINA  China has confirmed the latest outbreak of the highly pathogenic H5N1 bird flu in Hunan province."On Sunday, China's Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Affairs reported the discovery of an H5N1 cluster on a farm in the province's city of Shaoyang[d].The incident occurred on a farm with about 7,900 chicken, where 4,500 of the birds have died. Local authorities have responded by culling the infected birds.According to the WHO, H5N1 is an influenza virus that is highly contagious among birds and can cause severe respiratory disease in avians.The virus does not infect people easily and human to human transmission is rare.However, the WHO reports that people associated with close contact with dead or live birds could contract the H5N1 and that the infection is fatal to humans 60 percent of the time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957950/3957950_F8DB2F8827E24F8D88177B3FBB8620E2_200203_3957950_Bird_flu_outbreak_kills_thousands_of_chickens_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bird flu, avian flu, H5N1, flu, Chinese bird flu, China bird flu, China bird flu outbreak 2020,  Chinese bird flu outbreak 2020, highly pathogenic, chicken, health, chicken farm, shaoyang, hunan, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957884</guid>
      <title>China claims herbal medicine will cure coronavirus then backtracks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  As a certain country continues to battle against you-know-what, herbal remedies are also being enlisted in the fight.  Chinese state-owned speakerbox Xinhua reported on Friday that scientists in China recommended a traditional Chinese medicine called Shuanghuanglian [b]to help "alleviate fever" and "contain the progression" of the latest virus spreading across the country.Apparently, the concoction is made with honeysuckle and flowering plants, which is said to "inhibit" the latest epidemic.  Xinhua was encouraging the public to use traditional Chinese medicine along with western medicine to get better results.Chinese people were quick to storm their nearest drugstore. Images and videos shared on social media show long lines of people geared up waiting to get a hold of the miracle drink. Shuanghuanglian quickly sold out online and in actual stores.Though not everyone was thrilled about the product. Some on Weibo expressed skepticism about the effectiveness of herbal medicine.In response, The China Daily and the People's Daily then began to discourage people from buying the herbal concoction as it is still in its early stages of research.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957884/3957884_4645779E2EBF4174B3755D202DBDC625_200203_3957884_China_claims_herbal_medicine_will_cure_coronavir_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[双黄连,Shuanghuanglian, Shuanghuanglian china, china herbal remedies, china herbal remedies, herbal concoction, herbal medicine, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957876</guid>
      <title>United Nations networks targeted by hackers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA  Leaked documents from the United Nations reveal that the body's networks had been compromised by hackers last year.Thirty-three servers were compromised at the United Nations Geneva headquarters while at least four were infected at the agency's Vienna office. The United Nations Human Rights Geneva office also had three of its servers compromised.Hackers exploited a flaw in Microsoft's SharePoint software to infiltrate the United Nations' networks, the Associated Press reports, citing the report. Hackers were able to exfiltrate roughly 400 gigabytes of data.According to the New Humanitarian, which had access to the documents, hackers may have been able to access internal documents, emails and databases from the United Nations.The publication says staff records, health insurance and commercial contract information were also compromised. Staff members were asked to change their passwords but were not informed of the breach.A UN official told the Associated Press that it was possible the cyber attack was state-sponsored as it appeared "sophisticated."Technicians isolated the agency's data center from the internet and rebuilt its infrastructure and replaced keys and credentials to ensure network systems were protected, the Associated Press reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957876/3957876_E98BA5096C624A5789520F0FAEEE98DA_200203_3957876_United_Nations_networks_targeted_by_hackers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[United Nations, United Nations hacked, United Nations networks hacked, hacking operation, United Nations breach, United Nations security breach, UN hacked, UN hacking operation, UN networks infiltrated, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957815</guid>
      <title>Wuhan coronavirus symptoms clarified in new study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  A study published in The Lancet examined 99 of the earliest cases of the 2019 novel coronavirus, which first emerged in the Chinese city of Wuhan.Science News reports that coronaviruses are one of a variety of viruses that can cause the common cold, as well as deadlier infections like SARS and MERS.According to the Lancet study, the average age of infected patients was 55. Sixty-eight percent were male, half already had a preexisting chronic disease, and 49 percent had a direct connection to the seafood market where the virus is believed to have originated.Fever and cough were the two most prominent and consistent symptoms of the virus, with most of the infected displaying these symptoms on admission to a hospital. Other patients exhibited shortness of breath, muscle aches, and headaches.According to University of East Anglia Professor of Medicine Paul Hunter, the features and epidemiology of the Wuhan virus outbreak is similar to SARS.The one big difference is a lack of upper respiratory symptoms like runny nose, sore throat, and sneezing, which can spread the infection.By January 25, 31 of the patients in the Lancet study had recovered and been discharged, while 11 had died from the virus.Most of the deceased were over 60 with pre-existing medical conditions, and died primarily from a critical form of respiratory failure called acute respiratory distress syndrome.The study also found that similar to the SARS and MERS outbreaks, the virus had a higher infection risk to men than women.Scientists hypothesized that women's reduced susceptibility to the virus could be due to protection from the X chromosome and sex hormones, which play a role in immunity.According to China's National Health Commission, the novel coronavirus is contagious during its incubation period, before patients start showing visible symptoms. This incubation period lasts up to 14 days.A case study recently published in The Lancet describes how a family in Shenzhen became infected with the virus after travelling to visit relatives in Wuhan, which verifies person-to-person transmission. A child in the family remained without symptoms despite being diagnosed with the virus, which also suggests asymptomatic transmission is possible.Because of this, researchers in the family study believe that to control the outbreak, patients need to be isolated, and those they came into contact with traced and quarantined. It's likewise paramount that health workers comply with infection control, and the public be educated on proper food and personal hygiene.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 07:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957815/3957815_06102D0E21644D4BA846FAF152C3AD17_200203_3957815_Wuhan_coronavirus_symptoms_clarified_in_new_stud_2600_v1580802336.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[nCov, 2019 ncov, epidemic, contagion, China contagion, Chinese pneumonia, China pneumonia, ncov symptoms, contagious, SARS, MERS, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957794</guid>
      <title>Super-long smuggling tunnel found at U.S.-Mexico border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO  Authorities have found what they are calling the "longest" smuggling tunnel ever discovered on the U.S.-Mexico border.In a statement on January 29, the U.S. Customs and Border Protection agency announced that it had uncovered the cross-border tunnel along the U.S. border with Mexico.The underground tunnel has a total length of 4,309 feet, making it the longest smuggling on the southwestern border found to date.Officials said that the tunnel was concealed by a small industrial building in Tijuana, Mexico, and stretched over three-quarters of a mile to San Diego, California.Images shared by the U.S. border officials show that the tunnel is narrow, only two feet wide and roughly five and a half feet high. Officials said they discovered hundreds of sandbags at the end of the tunnel blocking what is suspected to be an old exit to the city of San Diego.U.S. authorities also uncovered an incomplete offshoot from the main cross-border tunnel leading into the U.S.The tunnel housed an extensive transport system including an elevator at the entrance and a rail system. The cross-border tunnel was also found to contain an air ventilation system, a drainage system and high voltage electrical cables.U.S. officials have yet to make any arrests regarding the discovery of the tunnel.Previously, authorities had found a 2,966-foot-long tunnel in San Diego in 2014.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 06:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957794/3957794_A9D759A10E074BAFBACE842D89B0F083_200203_3957794_Super_long_smuggling_tunnel_found_at_U_S__Mexico_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[US mexico border, US mexico tunnel, US mexico border wall, smuggling tunnel, mexican smuggling tunnel, longest smuggling tunnel, longest cross-border tunnel, cross-border tunnel, US mexico cross border tunnel, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958687</guid>
      <title>Some people don't have an internal monologue</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S.  Do you hear your own thoughts? Then chances are you have what's called an 'internal monologue.' Normal, right? Actually, there are loads of people out there that have no inner voice.While this isn't exactly news, people are only just realizing this thanks to a post on social media.The tweet said: "Fun fact: some people have an internal narrative and some don't as in, some people's thoughts are like sentences they 'hear', and some people just have abstract non-verbal thoughts and have to consciously verbalize them and most people aren't aware of the other type of person."Russell Hurlburt, a professor of psychology at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas says that an internal monologue might not necessarily even be with words; it can also be done with images or any other symbols. Netizens shared their experiences or non-experiences with an internal monologue. One user said, "I don't have an internal monologue. I think if I had to listen to myself talk in full sentences all day I would stick a whisk up my nose and scramble my brains until there was nothing left."Which one are you?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 23:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958687/3958687_F87967399FB44A05A780094956826C56_200205_3958687_Some_people_don_t_have_an_internal_monologue_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, inner thoughts, internal monologue, think to myself, voice in my head, talk to myself, chat to myself, think sentences in my head, thoughts, thinking, psychology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958520</guid>
      <title>Vampire star unleashes blazing light while eating its companion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Astronomers have spotted a strange white dwarf star that devours its captive companion and blazes intense light in a rare event called a "super-outburst."NASA published the study in Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society.NASA says that the retired Kepler telescope, which revolved around the sun to search for exoplanets, had captured the archival footage that made this discovery possible."According to NASA's news release, the brown dwarf circles around the stellar vampire every 83 minutes at a distance of 400,000 km.The white dwarf is about the size of the Earth, but its mass is equivalent to the Sun.The little star's huge mass creates a powerful gravitational pull that sucks in matter from the brown dwarf which forms an accretion disk.According to NASA, current theory speculates that when the accretion disk reaches a critical mass, its outer edge experiences gravitation resonance with the orbiting star.The resonance heats up the accretion disk, raising the temperature from a normal high of 5,300 degrees Celcius to a peak of 11,700 degrees.The study says that the enormous heat build up results in the blaze known as the super-outburst in a repetitive process."NASA further states that current theory does not explain why there is a long delay between each outburst.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958520/3958520_24C2F212571242E09D8E1D048D24F9C1_200204_3958520_Vampire_star_unleashes_blazing_light_while_eatin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Vampire star, white dwarf star, white dwarf, brown dwarf star, brown dwarf, dwarf nova, eating stellar companion, devouring stellar companion, dwarf nova super-outburst, super-outburst, super outburst, binary star system, NASA, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958514</guid>
      <title>Chinese man takes out 2,257 feet of guardrail with one kick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LINFEN, CHINA  Guardrails and fences around the world fear this man. In an amazing testament to human strengthor shoddy Chinese constructiona guy in the city of Linfen in Shanxi province was caught on camera taking out a whopping 2,257 foot chunk of guardrail with just one kick.According to United Daily News, the incident happened around 2 p.m. on January 29 at the Shili Promenade, a 5 km long riverside trail.That's when the two men surnamed Shi and Chang decided to film a TikTok video of them kicking a stone pillar. Unfortunately for the stone pillarit was made in China. Thankfully for us the stone pillar wasmade in China.    One of the guys then unleashes the kick heard round the world, which sets in motion a hilarious CHAIN of events. After the first pillar falls, because they are all connected by an iron chain, they all begin falling like a massive chain of dominos218 stone pillar dominos to be exact.  Wonder how the TikTok video turned out?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958514/3958514_34723C38A28B4CAFAE1A1782808911F5_200204_3958514_Chinese_man_takes_out_2_257_feet_of_guardrail_wi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Man kicks over guardrail, man kicks over 688 meter guardrail, man kicks over waterside guardrail, cheap construction, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958505</guid>
      <title>Trump hat tips wrong state after Kansas City Chiefs win Super Bowl</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  President Donald Trump apparently watched the Super Bowl on Sunday night with the rest of the United States to see the Kansas City Chiefs come from behind to win an exciting Super Bowl against the San Francisco 49ers. After the game was over, Trump hopped on Twitter to congratulate the Chiefs and the great state of Kansas. In a since deleted tweet, the commander in geography wrote, "Congratulations to the Kansas City Chiefs on a great game and a fantastic comeback, under immense pressure. You represented the Great State of Kansas, and in fact, the entire USA, so very well. Our Country is PROUD OF YOU!"Only one problem...the Kansas City Chiefs are located in Missouri. Cue the memes. Social media immediately pounced. Former Missouri Sen. Claire McCaskill tweeted out, "It's Missouri you stone cold idiot."Trump's erroneous tweet was then put in timeout, while a new one was put up congratulating the correct state. Wellgood thing Trump didn't take Air Force One to congratulate the Chiefs. Otherwise he'd still be flying over Kansas somewhere.Obviously what Trump should have done is just made a new map. It's not like most Americans would actually miss Kansassorry Missourisame difference.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958505/3958505_C2877CE788C049EBB174EA1B78FF6C86_200204_3958505_Trump_hat_tips_wrong_state_after_Kansas_City_Chi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Trump Super Bowl Tweet, Trump Super Bowl, Trump Super Bowl Kansas state, Trump Kansas City Kansas, Kansas City Chiefs, Chiefs win Super Bowl, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958428</guid>
      <title>Claw machines in Taiwan offer masks, hand sanitizers as prizes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Claw machines in Taiwan are now offering face masks, hand sanitizers and antibacterial hand wipes as prizes amid the latest you-know-what.Local authorities have found at least 40 such claw machines in Taipei alone, reports the Liberty Times.  A Taipei city councilor has accused the claw machine vendors of violating fair trade laws by hawking and hoarding these medical supplies during this time. An official from Taipei's Department of Health said that these vendors may face fines of up to $66,000 if the products inside contain a medical equipment license number. This would mean they're in violation of Taiwan's Pharmaceutical Affairs Act.Face masks, hand sanitizers have been in high demand in Taiwan recently, with stores now routinely running out of supplies at record speed.As a result, the government has announced plans to ration face masks. Taiwanese people will be allowed to only purchase two face masks per week while showing their national health insurance cards starting this Thursday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958428/3958428_1B64E8D3B7E248D09AADEF9C86E449EB_200204_3958428_Claw_machines_in_Taiwan_offer_masks__hand_saniti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Face masks, face masks taiwan, hand sanitizers claw machine,  claw machine face mask prize, taiwanese claw machines, taiwan claw machine, taiwan claw machine craze, weird claw machine prizes, crazy claw machine prizes, claw machine medical prizes,   TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958418</guid>
      <title>How plants are slowing down global warming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON  Researchers from Boston University have found that increased vegetation growth, or greening, has effectively slowed global warming. Greening usually involves intensive land use for farming, planting trees at a large scale or natural reforestation of lands that have been abandoned. The study found that roughly half of Earth's vegetated land has been greened due to this technique.For the study, scientists analyzed satellite images from the 1980s to the 2010s. They noticed an increase of greening in China and India over the decades due to afforestation efforts.As green leaves convert sunlight to sugar, carbon dioxide in the atmosphere is replaced with water vapor which cools Earth's surface. In the study, researchers explained that global greening may have slowed the rate of global warming by roughly 0.2 to 0.23 degrees Celsius.Study authors Shilong Piao and Xuhui Wang, explained in a Boston University news release that this provides "credible evidence" that human activities are dramatically impacting Earth's climate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958418/3958418_EB969C02445F43DEBA9CBC4B36C3D067_200204_3958418_How_plants_are_slowing_down_global_warming_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Global warming, climate change, plants slowing global warming, global warming plants, effect of plants on global warming, impact of plants on global warming, plants and global warming, greening our planet, impact of greening our planet, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958216</guid>
      <title>Greece plans to build sea barrier to keep migrants out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LESBOS, GREECE  Greece wants to put up a sea barrier to stop boatloads of refugees and asylum-seekers from reaching its islands.According to the BBC, migrants fleeing persecution and violence in countries like Afghanistan and Syria often try to reach Europe by travelling through Turkey to Greece.Migrant camps on several Greek islands are now overcrowded, but plans to create new ones have only angered residents, who took to the streets to protest them.With arrivals proving hard to manage, Greece is planning to install a floating barrier near the island of Lesbos on the Aegean Sea.According to the Guardian, the 2.7-kilometer long netted barrier will rise from pylons 50 meters above water, and will be equipped with flashing lights.Greece's defense ministry said the budget for the project is 500,000 euros, which includes around four years of maintenance costs.The BBC reports that such barriers rising above sea level will make it difficult for small boats to pass, and may present a problem for propeller-driven vessels.Greek authorities believe a sea barrier will be able to curb flows in a similar manner to the barbed-wire fence built in Evros, along the northern land border with Turkey, in 2012.Amnesty International, meanwhile, criticized Greece's plan, warning that it would only add to the dangers refugees are already facing in their quest for safety.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 03:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958216/3958216_C87653B878D347A3A4E088046C8CB614_200204_3958216_Greece_plans_to_build_sea_barrier_to_keep_migran_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Greek sea barrier, sea barrier, sea fence, Lesbos sea fence, floating sea barrier, floating barrier, EU refugees, Greek refugees, asylum seekers, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958192</guid>
      <title>Man gets socked for calling out pharmacy over face mask prices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOMEWHERE  A pharmacy employee is in a world of trouble after going rock 'em sock 'em at a customer complaining about face mask price gouging.According to Beijing News on Miaopai, the incident happened in Donggang, in China's Liaoning province. On January 27, a male customer at a Kangyi Medicine store filmed himself confronting staff about a too-expensive 35 yuan face mask. He reminded them that there were government regulations against jacking up face mask prices amid the Wuhan outbreak.A female employee offers to refund his money, but the man insists he wants to buy it at its regular price.Eventually, a male staff member got aggressive, telling the customer to scram and then punching him right in the moneymaker.Wth China in the middle of an epidemic, raising face mask prices is about one of the worst, most shameful things anyone can do. That plus the violence, and sure enough – the Chinese internets got absolutely livid.By that evening, the Donggang City Market Supervision Bureau announced in a statement that it would impose penalties on the store.According to the Shanghaiist, the male employee has also been detained by the cops.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958192/3958192_4A6432DCB2D94B6795AA5219F1398170_200204_3958192_Man_gets_socked_for_calling_out_pharmacy_over_fa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, pharmacy, Chinese customer, Chinese customer unhappy, Chinese, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958167</guid>
      <title>Drones are being used in China to help battle Wuhan coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOMEWHERE  As the you-know-what continues to spread around the country that will remain nameless, authorities are now enlisting the help of drones to make it look like they are doing something. According to video posted to Weibo, traffic police in Shuyang county in Jiangsu province have enlisted the help of drones to yell at pedestrians walking around the streets without face masks. At one point, the drone can be heard squawking at one guy, "the gentleman with a pink coat riding a motorcycle. Yeah, you! Please put on your mask."In another exchange the drone blurts out, "Hey, guy on the phone! Where is your mask? Wear your mask!"And in other parts of the country that will not be named, videos from provinces like Jilin, Shandong and Zhejiang have been posted onto social media showing drones crop dusting the air with disinfectant. Apparently the unmanned aerial machines are more effective at dispersing cleaning solutions than on foot or by car.  Police in the Sichuan province were also using drones to disinfect areas harder to reach like people's roofs. But here's the thing, does your roof really need disinfecting? Can all these drones make a difference? What do you think?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 01:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958167/3958167_78A1A35314CC4D3386A4BAE1582CF149_200204_3958167_Drones_are_being_used_in_China_to_help_battle_Wu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, drones, China drone usage, China authorities use drones, drones remind Chinese citizens, Chinese drones, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958161</guid>
      <title>Chinese health officials clueless on coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Chinese health officials are struggling to answer questions about recent developments in the country. On January 29th, two senior health officials were asked a set of basic questions about the virus during an interview in Huanggang, a city to the east of Wuhan. State broadcaster CCTV sat down with Tang Zhihong, chief of the city's health commission, and Chen Mingxing, director of the city's Center for Disease Control and Prevention. However, they either couldn't answer the questions or couldn't agree. The Huanggang government announced that Tang had been dismissed from her position the following day. But they're not the only ones to suffer a media mishap, Sheng Wenjun the Communist Party Secretary of quarantined Chibi City was caught wearing his surgical mask incorrectly during an inspection of his city's response to the virus.Worst of all, at a press conference on the 26th of January, the governor of Hubei Province didn't even wear a mask; the Hubei secretary did, however, he too didn't cover his nose and the mayor wore his inside out. On January 29th, Zeng Guang, the chief scientist of epidemiology at China's CDC, made a rare and honest admission about why Chinese officials cannot tell people the truth, saying that they, "need to think about the political angle and social stability" in order to keep their positions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958161/3958161_ABD48894B748403D9AC993C4AC2B2199_200204_3958161_Chinese_health_officials_clueless_on_coronavirus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, health officials, Chinese health officials, Chinese health officials confused, Chinese officials, TomoNews, satire, Chinese illness]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959035</guid>
      <title>Iowa Democratic caucuses were a complete and utter debacle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IOWA  Wow that was embarrassingand we haven't even started yet. After way too much fanfare and pregame hype, the Iowa caucuses turned out to be an utter disaster from beginning todid it even end yet?The failing New York Times reported that a "quality control" issue with a new system of reporting results led to mass confusion, which then turned into massive delays in tabulating results. Across the state, precinct chairmen and volunteers at more than 1,600 caucus sites reported widespread disarray, with a ton of people having problems with a new app for reporting results. This forced them to call in the results using the party hotline, where some people were left on hold for over an hour.  The Iowa Democratic Party also said another reason for the trainwreck was that the caucus leaders were required to report three sets of numbers to party HQ, instead of just onethe delegate count.After spending way too much money and entirely too much time in Iowa, the campaigns demanded results. When they didn't get those, they all just kind of declared victoryespecially Peteand then all bounced to New Hampshire. What was even funnier was all the live-streaming and interactive graphics of the results by all the major outlets and papers literally showing nothing but a bunch of zeros after every candidate's name all day long. On Tuesday, Iowa's Democratic Party said preliminary results from 62 percent of precincts show Pete in first, followed by the Bern, then the Native-American woman, and then hands-on Joe in fourth. But don't worry folks, this is just the beginning of a long, drawn out primary race to pick the next candidate to lose to Donald Trump.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 13:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3959035/3959035_9399771EF2844B80BF52D42E50661CA0_200205_3959035_Iowa_Democratic_caucuses_were_a_complete_and_utt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Iowa caucuses, Iowa caucuses debacle, Iowa Democratic caucuses, Iowa Democratic caucuses app, Iowa caucuses delays, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959019</guid>
      <title>U.S. creates first ever coupled quantum dots</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GAITHERSBURG, MARYLAND  Coupled quantum dots  which act like artificial atoms that share an electron  could potentially form a robust qubit to revolutionize computing.According to a study in Physical Review B, scientists have created the first ever pair of this substance.The U.S. National Institute of Standards and Technology says that classical computers are made of binary bits that store information as fix values of either one or zero.Qubits can take on multiple values simultaneously, which enables quantum computers that utilize qubits to perform larger and more complex tasks.To create the coupled quantum dots, NIST researchers hovered a scanning tunneling microscope above a sheet of graphene with an underlying layer of boron nitride.The STM's electrical charge penetrates the graphene and releases electrons from the boron nitride, which the graphene then captured. Afterward, the team applied a magnetic field on the microscope's tip and forced the electrons to take up residence in two concentric rings.This process leads to the creation of the coupled system, but the research team states that they are unable to explain their success with the current state of quantum theory.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3959019/3959019_F67C9ED0F788483EB0988CFB9608F2CA_200205_3959019_U_S__creates_first_ever_coupled_quantum_dots_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Coupled quantum dots, quantum dots, quantum bits, qubits, qubit, quantum computers, quantum computing, computer science, quantum physics, U.S., TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958993</guid>
      <title>Discrimination could make people feel more physical pain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, FLORIDA  A study published in Nature Human Behavior suggests that discrimination can change how different ethnic groups perceive and respond to pain. The University of Miami says scientists gave pain stimuli to the participants' arm, then gauged their pain via MRI.Researchers learned that when the same pain is applied by a heating device, African Americans reported more pain than Hispanic or non-Hispanic white American participants.Scientists found that two areas of the brain  the ventral striatum and ventromedial prefrontal cortex  responded to pain more strongly in African Americans.Those brain areas have been linked to chronic pain."Since stressful experiences are correlated to chronic pain later in life, the researchers believe that stress from racial discrimination may cause increased pain sensitivity.Yet data suggests that doctors tend to believe African Americans to be more pain tolerant, which might make them less inclined to alleviate black pain.The research team writes in a statement: 'Understanding why these pain biases exist, therefore, is a key step toward ... eliminating racial and ethnic disparities in pain and its treatment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 11:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958993/3958993_7FF467B461BA43D6BB10BBEC6096D9A2_200205_3958993_Discrimination_could_make_people_feel_more_physi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ethic pain disparity, pain, racial discrimination, discrimination, minorities, African Americans, ethnic minorities, stress, chronic pain, brain, neurology, neurobiology, neuroscience, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958942</guid>
      <title>Video shows Wuhan's new hospital looking like a prison</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China announced the completion of a 1,000-bed hospital that will accommodate patients infected with the dreaded you-know-what.The Associated Press reports that the first patients arrived Monday at Huoshenshan Hospital, which was assembled in 10 days.Satellite images released by the China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation shows a field at the site back in October 29. Construction was in full swing by January 30, a mere seven days after it broke ground, and was complete by February 2.A new video posted to Twitter by Himalaya Global claims to show the inside of the Huoshenshan facility. The footage was supposedly shot by a contractor, who shows a sick ward with the ominous warning that "once you are in, you can't get out" and says "you'd better quarantine at home than here."He then proceeds to walk around the facility, showing windows welded shut, a small window opening to deliver food, and doors that can't be opened from the inside. It's supposed to be a hospital, but looks more like a prison.Folks online chimed in that hospitals don't usually have doors opening just one way, and commented that this was more a "medical" internment camp than anything else – a jail for sick people, basically.A second 1,500-bed "hospital" called Leishenshan began construction on January 27 and is meant to be ready this week after 12 days of construction work.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 10:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958942/3958942_00083AF9D3DC47A4AFE544190BD0F27B_200205_3958942_Video_shows_Wuhan_s_new_hospital_looking_like_a__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China hospital, instant hospital, hospital construction, huoshenshan hospital, China construction, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958901</guid>
      <title>Google admits sending users' private videos to strangers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA   Google has admitted that a few of its users had their private videos on Google Photos sent to complete strangers because of a tech glitch. This is because the search giant allows its users to download their data through a service called Google Takeout, the Verge reports. The problem was discovered after users who downloaded their data discovered private videos from other users that didn't belong to them. Google says 0.01 percent of users were affected. The company did not specify the exact amount of people affected by the breach.Users who had their videos compromised were in for a rude shock when Google sent out an email this month informing them that some of their videos were "incorrectly exported" to other users between November 21 to November 25 last year.According to 9 to 5 Google, the company asked users who downloaded their data from Google Takeout to delete their previous export and to request new ones. The search giant also stated in the email that the issue has since been identified and resolved.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958901/3958901_0D4818328BF64B0B835365C321D0A9D0_200205_3958901_Google_admits_sending_users__private_videos_to_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Google, Google Photos, Google Takeout, videos saved on google sent to strangers, google photos private videos, google controversies, google scandals, private videos saved on google sent to strangers, google share private videos, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958890</guid>
      <title>Red and processed meat linked to heart disease, early death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EVANSTON, ILLINOIS  A new study published in the journal JAMA Internal Medicine has found that eating two servings of red meat or processed meat every week is linked to a 3 to 7 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease and premature death.The study included more than 29,000 participants who were asked about their dietary habits.One of the study's authors said that it's worth trying to cut down on red meat and processed meat such as pepperoni, bologna and deli meats.Scientists also found those who consumed two servings of poultry a week had a 4 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease. Though researchers noted that this might be related to the cooking method of the chicken which may have been fried or due to consumption of chicken skin rather than chicken meat itself.The study did not find any association between eating fish and cardiovascular disease or early death.The researchers recommended consuming fish, seafood and plant-based protein sources such as nuts, legumes, beans and peas as healthier alternatives.The study's findings are in stark contrast to a meta-analysis published just a few months ago which claimed that there was no need for people to reduce their intake of red meat or processed meat for good health.Nutritionists at NutriRECS said at the time that their analysis did not find "any certainty that eating red meat or processed meat causes cancer, diabetes or heart disease," CNN reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958890/3958890_513C686D79C54BB695D862189DF7D8F3_200205_3958890_Red_and_processed_meat_linked_to_heart_disease___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Red meat, processed meat, processed meat health, processed food, red meat bad for you, red meat study, processed meat study, red meat heart disease, processed meat heart disease, red meat diet, cutting red meat from diet, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958725</guid>
      <title>Four passengers collapse on Ryanair 'flight from hell'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUDAPEST / EDINBURGH  What was supposed to be an uneventful 3-hour plane ride to Edinburgh turned hellish after passengers started collapsing mid-flight.Passenger Shaun Pinkerton told the Scottish Sun that the fire alarm on the plane was going off during boarding, but the Ryanair flight still took off as planned. An hour into the January 31 trip, a 17-year-old girl collapsed in the cabin, and had to receive CPR. A second passenger also fainted, followed by Pinkerton, and then a fourth and final person.Cabin crew had to perform CPR and bust out huge oxygen tanks for the fallen passengers.Pinkerton himself needed an oxygen mask, and claimed he went into shock and started shaking.The 27-year-old says passengers feared there was something wrong with the plane – that there wasn't enough oxygen. He blames the airline for the "flight from hell" and is demanding compensation. But in a statement to the Independent, Edinburgh Airport denies any fault with the aircraft, and confirmed that cabin crew called ahead to request medical assistance upon landing.The plane touched down in Edinburgh normally and was met by medics, who provided treatment for the four victims of the fainting spells.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958725/3958725_186B87A3F91244C28095B3B8C2CEA052_200205_3958725_Four_passengers_collapse_on_Ryanair__flight_from_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Flight from hell, Ryanair flight from hell, Ryanair, plane passengers fainting, Ryanair flight, passengers collapse on flight, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958718</guid>
      <title>Fend off Chinese mask hoarders with Taiwan flag face masks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  It's trying times in China with the you-know-what causing a global pandemic and prompting everyone and their Great Aunt to wear protective face masks.As folks went into a frenzy of panic buying and mask hoarding, a photo popped up on Reddit showing face masks embellished with the Taiwan flag.It came with text saying: "Taiwan printed its national flag on face masks so that any mainland Chinese who buys them will have to wear the Taiwanese flag on his face."Ooooh, yes please!According to Taiwan News, the Japanese got wind of the photo after blogger Rie Ogasawara posted it on social media site Ameba. Some commented that the presence of the dreaded flag would keep any card-carrying follower of the CCP from buying it, which only means more for the rest of us!They also mistakenly assumed someone in Japan had started the trend. But eagle-eyed Taiwanese netizens were quick to claim that the manufacturer, Champ Mask, was Taiwanese, and the price in the photo couldn't be in yen.It's unlikely that the face masks were made specifically to troll Chinese, but hey, if it's there why not use it?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958718/3958718_B2E1D18EFCB3404EB4B5ED8F2F195422_200205_3958718_Fend_off_Chinese_mask_hoarders_with_Taiwan_flag__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taiwan, Taiwan flag face mask, face mask, surgical mask, Taiwan face masks, Taiwan numba one, Taiwan number one, face mask hoarders, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959551</guid>
      <title>Shadow Inc. CEO apologizes for Iowa caucus tech woes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IOWA  The 2020 Iowa Caucus was supposed to start off this year's presidential election cycle with a bang. Instead, it got royally screwed over by an app.Shadow Inc. CEO Gerard Niemira, whose tech company made the app, has come out to apologize for the embarrassing snafu, saying "we feel terrible" about it.Niemira told Bloomberg that the app, which cost the Iowa Democratic Party 63 Gs to develop, was meant to help compile results quickly from the state's 1,765 precincts.He claims all the data and calculations done by the app were legit, but there was a glitch in the transmission process. Apparently, there was a bug in the code that transports results data to the party's main database, and that made all the catastrophic impact.Theoretically, someone should've caught the glitch in the code during testing, but it was a rush job – put together in just two months, and according to the New York Times, not adequately tested.Still, that's a pretty big gaffe, and it's already costing the company. CNN reports that on Tuesday, the Nevada Democratic Party said it won't be using the same app or vendor used in the Iowa caucus.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959551/3959551_E8104EB5C6CE45F29EA751FDD933653A_200206_3959551_Shadow_Inc__CEO_apologizes_for_Iowa_caucus_tech__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Iowa caucus, Shadow Inc, 2020 Iowa caucus, Shadow app, Iowa caucus fail, Iowa caucus chaos, app chaos, Democratic caucus, Iowa Democratic Party, 2020 election, 2020 presidential election, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959524</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's three effective responses to Wuhan virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN  Taiwan has drawn from lessons learned during the SARS epidemic to mount an effective and immediate response to the 2019 novel coronavirus outbreak, using three major steps. According to a report by Mirror Media, Taiwan's first response to the novel coronavirus came on December 31, when China reported 27 cases of a mysterious Wuhan pneumonia to the WHO.Direct flights from Wuhan became subject to onboard health screening, and passengers had to declare their health status.It wasn't until January 21 that the island nation reported its first confirmed case. A 55-year-old businesswoman who returned to Taiwan from Wuhan was brought directly to the hospital upon arrival.Taiwan's second step was made on January 15, when the country's Centers for Disease Control listed the Wuhan pneumonia as a Category 5 communicable disease.According to Focus Taiwan, this made it mandatory to report suspected cases within 24 hours. Quarantining those who exhibited symptoms also became compulsory.When a man in Kaohsiung neglected to report viral symptoms after returning from Wuhan, the government fined him NT$300,000, or about US$10,000.On January 16, Taiwan's CDC raised the travel alert for Wuhan, after a Taiwanese expert team sent to the city to observe the epidemic suspected the possibility of human-to-human transmission.As of February 6, Taiwan has 13 confirmed cases of the virus. According to a CDC press release, patients are being treated in isolation wards and are in a stable condition.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959524/3959524_5DD19CFFED0E4511A840F5C23213CB29_200206_3959524_Taiwan_s_three_effective_responses_to_Wuhan_viru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taiwan epidemic prevention, Taiwan outbreak, Taiwan outbreak response, epidemic prevention, epidemic, outbreak, Taiwan, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959511</guid>
      <title>Boeing breaks apart after skidding off runway, killing three people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISTANBUL  The crashed airplane, a Pegasus Airlines Boeing 737-800 on Flight 2193 from Izmir to Istanbul, arrived at the Sabiha Gokcen[e] airport at 6:19 p.m. on Wednesday.The plane was carrying 177 passengers and six crew.According to International Flight Network, weather conditions were poor with heavy rains and a powerful tailwind that may have caused the plane to touch down too late.The Boeing overshot the runway and had trouble slowing down on the rain slicked surface.Flight data indicates that the Boeing's last recorded speed was dangerously fast at 117 km per hour.Speaking at a news conference, Istanbul Governor Ali Yerlikaya said the plane was dragged 50 meters before falling down a 30-meter slope, the New York Times reports.The jet broke into three pieces and social media footage apparently shows passengers fleeing the wreckage after the crash.The New York Times reports that three people were killed and 157 were hospitalized.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959511/3959511_8E773F25C8E84C88B7D1E50650CF3026_200206_3959511_Boeing_breaks_apart_after_skidding_off_runway__k_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Plane crash, air crash, airplane crash, Boeing 737, Boeing 737-800, Boeing, Pegasus Airlines, Pegasus, Flight 2193, overshooting runway, PC2193, Instanbul, Turkey, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959504</guid>
      <title>Pluto's frozen heart pumps out nitrogen wind</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  According to a study in the Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets, Pluto's frozen heart of nitrogen ice may be the main driver of the dwarf planet's winds. Pluto's heart shaped Tombaugh Regio is a vast structure made of nitrogen ice and its left lobe Sputnik Planitia contains 1,000 km of ice sheet within its 5 km basin.During the day, a thin layer of the frozen nitrogen evaporates in relative heat; at night, the gas condenses and returns to icy form.The sequence pumps nitrogen wind through Pluto's atmosphere like rhythmic heartbeats.As nitrogen in Tombaugh Regio vaporizes in the north and freeze into ice in the south, the process triggers a westerly wind.Citing the study's authors, Phys.org says this behavior is unique in the entire solar system with perhaps the exception of Neptune's moon Triton.The study's other discovery is that Sputnik Planitia's high cliffs trap winds within the basin before releasing the strengthened currents to the west.The atmospheric movement is similar to certain wind patterns on Earth, such as the Kuroshio in Eastern Asia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959504/3959504_3596A0D465A7460D9260DC75F095C0B8_200206_3959504_Pluto_s_frozen_heart_pumps_out_nitrogen_wind_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Pluto, nitrogen, Tombaugh Regio, Sputnik Planitia, atmospheric circulation, dwarf planet, retro-rotation, American Geophysical Union, AGU, space, science, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959444</guid>
      <title>Global Times spreads hoax that infrared cameras see your farts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  As China continues to tell the world that everything is A-okay when it's clearly not, the uber pro-government Global Times has been trying to pass off a story about infrared cameras picking up when you let one go. Using their official Twitter account, the Chinese tabloid posted a Tik Tok video from a television station in Enshi located in Hubei province on Monday. They included the caption, "Can't help farting? Well, better try harder, because infrared temperature sensors recently installed in airports and train stations to monitor temperatures of passengers amid" the latest outbreak can screen them all. Seems legit. Actually...it's fakewhich in China passes the test of a hard hitting news story. According to Gizmodo, the video is actually from 2016 with the noxious gas clouds digitally added.  Gimozo reports that the video was first LET GO in 2016 by an online group called Banana Factory, who later came out and said the video was a hoax. And now thanks to the Global Times, you have Chinese people worried about fevers and holding it in when they pass through security.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959444/3959444_ABBCDAA5F329490EB35FEACAAA64DECB_200206_3959444_Global_Times_spreads_hoax_that_infrared_cameras__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Global Times, China Global Times, China Global Times spreads hoax, Global Times thermal camera hoax, Global Times infrared camera hoax, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959418</guid>
      <title>Anonymous create pro-Taiwan page on United Nations website</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN  Anonymous successfully hacked into a United Nations webpage and created a page that supports Taiwan.Taiwan is not a member of the United Nations because Chinawho is one of the permanent members of the UN security councilwon't allow it. China also forces the U.N. to deny Taiwan membership into the WHO, which is of vital importance especially at a time like this.   Hackers at Anonymous had created a UN page that had a black background with the logo of the hacking group, the words "TAIWAN NUMBAH WANNNN!!," the Taiwanese flag, the Kuomintang's party emblem and the flag of the Democratic Progressive Party, representing the two main political parties in Taiwan.As we scroll further down, we see two videos. One is a video playing Taiwan's national anthem and another is a soundtrack titled, "It's Been a Long, Long Time," from the Marvel movie "Avengers Endgame."The hacked page was shared via a link by a Reddit user. Interestingly, 14 hours after the link was shared on Reddit, the UN had yet to take the page down, though it has since been removed.Users on a Taiwanese subreddit praised the hacking group for standing up for Taiwan. One user said, "Okay, this is epic," while another said, "Awesome. Fully support taking advantage of the confusion of the virus crisis."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959418/3959418_A9A11E1AA50C48C185DC3BDFB25BFB4A_200206_3959418_Anonymous_create_pro_Taiwan_page_on_United_Natio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Anonymous, Anonymous hacking group, UN website hacked, pro-taiwan page on UN website, United Nations website hacked,  UN website pro-Taiwan page, taiwan number one, taiwan number 1, pro taiwan, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959332</guid>
      <title>Fireflies threatened by artificial light, habitat loss: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEDFORD, MASSACHUSETTS  A joint study by Tuft University and the International Union for the Conservation of Nature has found that fireflies are being threatened by habitat loss, light pollution and pesticide use.Researchers surveyed 49 firefly experts from around the world in order to get a better understanding of prominent threats faced by roughly 2,000 different firefly species.Habitat loss was believed to be the largest threat to fireflies worldwide as their habitats are shrinking due to loss of land. Artificial light pollution is the second largest threat to fireflies globally as it interferes with their natural light which is used for communication and mating purposes. The use of pesticides was regarded to be the third largest threat as it is harmful to insects that fireflies consume for survival.Study author Sara M. Lewis, told the Washington Post that this was the first time a comprehensive list of threats, based on expert opinions, has been written about fireflies from around the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959332/3959332_15F5CD16E26E41CA9FC1C3B57A56075A_200206_3959332_Fireflies_threatened_by_artificial_light__habita_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fireflies, fireflies bioluminescence, bioluminescence, fireflies light show, fireflies light, fireflies light vs artificial light, fireflies light pollution, how fireflies are threatened, fireflies threatened, fireflies threatened with extinction, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959222</guid>
      <title>63-year-old actress Chen Meifen dubbed "Taiwan's Hottest Auntie"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  A Taiwanese actress is turning heads all across the internet for her age-defying looks.If you didn't know any better, you'd think Chen Meifen was in her 30s. She's actually 63, because ladies and gentlemen, Asian don't raisin!Back when she was still 36, an influential Taiwanese TV presenter called her the "hottest obasan of Taiwan", obasan being the Japanese term for aunt or older woman. 30 odd years later, she's still fresh-faced and living up to that monicker.Next Shark reports she's been quoted as saying obasans don't have to look dowdy and ugly, adding that "we can grow beautiful as we age."Her most recent outing was in a pre-recorded Lunar New Year show for a local broadcaster, which saw her showing off her toned physique in this revealing number.Most of us can only dream about being this genetically blessed, though according to Next Shark, Chen attributes her assets to a diet of "ginger and soup", and working out.Chen is a household name in Taiwan. As a 19-year-old in 1975, she was crowned Knitwear Beauty and has been in the limelight for over four decades. The stunning 63-year-old is fairly active on Facebook and Instagram, where she's got over 500,000 likes and 83,000 followers respectively.And in case there's any hot uncles watching this – she's also still single!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959222/3959222_7D3A36AEDF834525907EFBBBF3F88041_200206_3959222_63_year_old_actress_Chen_Meifen_dubbed__Taiwan_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chen Meifen, hottest auntie, taiwan's hottest auntie, taiwan hottest auntie, hot auntie, taiwanese celebrity, taiwan actress, obasan, celebrity TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959193</guid>
      <title>Couple receives 55,000 pieces of post in a massive mailing mistake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CLEVELAND, OHIO  An Ohio couple were left shocked after receiving 55,000 copies of the exact same letter.Twinsburg resident, Dan Cain was highly suspicious when the post office clerk told him he would not be able to get his mail through the front door; Cain then drove around the back of the office and saw a couple of postal workers wheeling out two huge bins of mail and it was all addressed to him. What did he receive? 55,000 statements for the student loan, he and his wife Dee had taken out for their daughter's college fees.Cain opted to not only accept the mailing mistake but to also make two trips in his truck to get all the letters home, letters that he says are incorrect; apparently, the company had used the wrong interest rate to calculate the payment.The loan company apologized to Cain and his wife for the mistakes and blamed a computer glitch for the mailing mishap; the company also said that they would send another statement, this time for the correct amount.Cain said with a chuckle, "I just may start a fire, a bonfire and burn it all."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 02:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959193/3959193_8A3882634FA44441B829569BF5F0FE30_200206_3959193_Couple_receives_55_000_pieces_of_post_in_a_massi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, mail mistake, coupe receives 55,000 letters, mail mishap, mail fail, funny mail video, massive mail mistake, student loan mail mistake]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959186</guid>
      <title>An Air Canada Boeing 767 has close call in Madrid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRID  On Monday, Air Canda's Toronto-bound Flight 837 had to request an emergency landing almost immediately after taking off from the Barajas International Airport in Madrid.The Associated Press reports that the Boeing 767 had a ruptured tire and that one engine had failed.Citing a Spanish civil aviation official, AP reports that the landing gear did not fold up properly and a piece of it may have been ingested by the engine, causing damage.According to the Spanish edition of The Local, the Spanish air force scrambled an F-18 to escort the Boeing and help assess the damage.AP reports that the commercial jet circled over Madrid for nearly four hours to burn off fuel until it was light enough to attempt a landing.Shortly after 7:10 p.m., the Boeing 767 made a safe landing back in Barajas with no injuries to the 128 passengers and eight crew on board.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959186/3959186_A73D430096A24D069D407FD9354C6BAB_200206_3959186_An_Air_Canada_Boeing_767_has_close_call_in_Madri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Air Canada, AC837, Flight 837, Boeing 767, Boeing 767-300, landing gear, engine failure, emergency landing, safe landing, Barajas, Madrid, Spain, Toronto, Canada, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960125</guid>
      <title>China quarantines negative coronavirus news coverage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  As cases continue to skyrocket within the country, Xi Jinping and his pals in Beijing have decided to clamp down on negative coverage over news media and online.According to the failing New York Times, the Communist party is struggling to control the narrative about the crisis that has slammed the leaders like a serious case of the mexican beer thing. The party was caught off guard by the flu's ugly cousin, which handled the initial outbreak in typical fashionby shoving it under the rug.     And then when it blew up in their faces, when it was already too late, they put around 60 million people on total lockdown. Now that Chinese citizens are getting increasingly pissed off, China's leaders are once again putting the screws on information.This after a short spell where news outlets were able to be quite straightforward about the tense situation, and negative comments about the clumsy official response were left uncensored online. The failing Times reports that in recent days, both state-run media and more commercially minded outlets have been ordered to focus on positive stories. Internet platforms have removed numerous articles criticizing the lazy-footed response by the Chinese government or painting the current situation in a negative light. Unfortunately less actual information and more positive propaganda isn't going to make this problem go away. With thousands of new cases each day, many Chinese fear the spread is not being adequately containedand they're dead right.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 14:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3960125/3960125_3A5525BFE86A431A81437A5EF2AA4EC6_200207_3960125_China_quarantines_negative_coronavirus_news_cove_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Main keyword or keyword phrase you are targeting, a few variations of your main keyword, two to three tags that describe video's overall category, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960041</guid>
      <title>Why cruise ship passengers are falling to diseases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YOKOHAMA, JAPAN  Thousands of travelers are stranded on cruise ships after coronavirus cases were discovered on board.CNN reports that the World Dream cruise ship is quarantined at the port of Hong Kong, while the Diamond Princess is kept at bay in Yokohama by Japan.According to Live Science, the confined spaces of a cruise ship provide almost the ideal environment for viruses that rely on person-to-person contact to thrive.Coughing and sneezing, contaminated water and shared food onboard are all potential paths of infection."For instance, a trace amount of feces in the food or water can infect any passenger that dined in the buffet.Some pathogens can linger on surfaces that an infected person touched and transmit to the next victim.Not only that crews have limited time to sterilize the ship between cruises, but certain viruses including the norovirus can survive  bleaching even by a 10 percent solution.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3960041/3960041_11B40482D41940D79F27DE9F8F6D65C4_200207_3960041_Why_cruise_ship_passengers_are_falling_to_diseas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cruise ships, cruise liners, diamond princess, world dream, quarantine, hygiene, public health, China news, Yokohma, Japan, Hong Kong, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960018</guid>
      <title>China's coronavirus containment strategy is not working</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  China continues to struggle. On Thursday, China's number of confirmed novel coronavirus infections grew to 28,000 cases or a 15 percent increase over the previous day.According to CNN, reported deaths have spiked, which increased the death toll to 600 fatalities.The contagion continues to spread rapidly despite population control and quarantine protocols Beijing imposed in central China.BBC reports that the new coronavirus has infected about 28,300 people worldwide, compared to SARS's 8,100 cases and MERS's 2,500 cases.Citing an epidemiologist, BBC reports that the Wuhan pneumonia appears to have lower mortality rates than the two other viruses.Al Jazeera reports that China has built hospitals at a frantic pace in Wuhan, including the Huoshenshan Hospital built over 10 days with 1,000 beds, which opened Monday.CNN reports that a second new hospital named Leishenshan opened on Thursday.The CNN reports that common symptoms include headache, malaise, coughing and muscle pains.Complications include fever over 39 degrees Celsius, troubled breathing and pneumonia, and sepsis that could result in death.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3960018/3960018_6EFCD80338AB4521B354F389E33D88F3_200207_3960018_China_s_coronavirus_containment_strategy_is_not__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China news, public health, sanitation, hospitals, hospital construction, huoshenshan hospital, leishenshan hospital, China, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959887</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus impacting cruise ships, airlines, car manufacturers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  As the Wuhan virus continues to spread at an alarming rate, it is starting to impact cruise ships, airlines and other international companies.Two cruise ships traveling in Asia have been forced to quarantine thousands of passengers. One of the ships is anchored off of Japan while the other is in Hong Kong, Reuters reports. According to Bloomberg, Japanese health workers said 61 passengers on one of the ships were found to test positive for the novel coronavirus.Air travel has been disrupted, with more than 73 airlines around the world either suspending or restricting flights to China, as reported by Business Insider. This includes airlines such as Japan Airlines, Air Canada, Air France, Cathay Pacific and American Airlines.Hong Kong's Cathay Pacific has gone a step further and asked staff members to take three weeks of unpaid leave to cope with the impact of the Wuhan virus. The company says that it plans to cut roughly 90 percent of its flights to China over the next two months, BBC News reports. Global car manufacturing firms have been forced to shut down factories for an extended amount of time in China following the outbreak of the coronavirus. Car companies that have closed down their Chinese factories include Hyundai, Tesla, Ford and Nissan among others.Airbus SE is halting one of its assembly lines in China, while Boeing and French company Safran SA are both closing plane making facilities in China in order to minimize workers' exposure to the virus, Bloomberg reports. The coronavirus has already spread to 28 countries and regions outside of China. More than 31,000 people in China have been affected with the virus so far. The virus has caused 636 deaths in China, with two additional deaths from the virus in the Philippines and in Hong Kong.The World Health Organization had declared the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak a global health emergency at the end of last month.Symptoms of the coronavirus include severe coughing, fever and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3959887/3959887_5B8A08E41BAF4F93A26A1EF163B17A49_200207_3959887_Wuhan_virus_impacting_cruise_ships__airlines__ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China virus, china virus economic impact, wuhan virus, coronavirus, coronavirus outbreak, coronavirus economic effect, coronavirus china economic impact, coronavirus china economy, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959869</guid>
      <title>China is sealing people in their homes amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  As new cases continue on an upward climb, respect for human lives has gone right out the window as footage appears to show how some are being treated amidst the latest outbreak.    In a video shared on Chinese social media, a door of a house is seen totally blocked by a massive pile of coal ash, commonly used in furnaces. It's unclear how many people live in the house, or what their condition is, but it's safe to say they won't be leaving anytime soon. In another video, health officials are seen using a welding machine to seal the door of a residential house in order to prevent those under quarantine from leaving their house.Chinese police officers are also seen in another disturbing video nailing in wooden planks to block the front door of an apartment with people inside who had just returned home from Wuhan.Afterwards, officials are seen sticking a red sign beside the front door which reads, "The people in this house have just returned from Wuhan, don't be in contact with them." The poor people inside are heard desperately screaming, "Open the door!"Chinese officials did the same to other residences as well, but this time they used metal bars instead of wooden ones.How will those sealed inside their houses get access to food, medicine and other essential supplies?And this comes after rumors that China has woefully underreported the number of those who have been sickened and those who have unfortunately succumbed to it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 07:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3959869/3959869_7271EEFF25914A3186B0DDD232A9EBA8_200207_3959869_China_is_sealing_people_in_their_homes_amid_viru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China precaution, creative chinese people, china disease, china quarantine, china confinement, in house confinement, china locking people in their houses, china locking people indoors, how china is making sure people stay locked in, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959696</guid>
      <title>Did Tencent just leak real data on Wuhan coronavirus epidemic?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA  Tencent may have accidentally posted the real numbers of infections and deaths from the coronavirus, figures astronomically higher than what the Chinese government has been telling everyone. On February 1st, Tencent's homepage, titled "Epidemic Situation Tracker" showed confirmed cases of the coronavirus in China as 154,023, ten times the official figure at the time. It also listed the number of suspected cases as 79,808, four times the official figure.The number of cured cases was a mere 269, well below the official claim of 300. Most worryingly, however, was the death toll which stood at 24,589 which was tremendously higher than the 300 officially listed for that day.Tencent then wiped the numbers and updated them to reflect the government's 'official' ones. According to Taiwan News, netizens noticed that Tencent has on at least three separate occasions posted extremely high numbers, only to quickly change them to adhere to the government-approved numbers. This jump or swap of numbers has led netizens to believe Tencent has two sets of data, the real data, and 'processed' data.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3959696/3959696_6F6D2E72053A4069ABC24CBE6FD665B1_200207_3959696_Did_Tencent_just_leak_real_data_on_Wuhan_coronav_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Chinese illness, Chinese disease, China sickness, Tencent, Tencent leaks data, leak, data leak, Beijing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961234</guid>
      <title>A Boeing 747 broke speed records during New York to London flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  A British Airways Boeing 747-400 set the record for the fastest ever subsonic flight across the Atlantic on Sunday. Flightradar24.com reports that BA112 flew consistently at Mach 0.86.  CNN reports that the overnight flight from New York coincided with Storm Ciara, which boosted the Boening's speed and allowed it to arrive at London in 4 hours and 56 minutes.FlightRadar 24 reports that the jet stream gave eastbound flights including BA112 a significant increase in airspeed and reduced their fuel consumption.Citing the online outlet, CNN reports the plane reached a top speed of nearly 825 miles per hour.CNN reports that the jet landed nearly two hours ahead of schedule at Heathrow airport at 4:43 am.The plane was faster by one minute than a Virgin Airways A350 that also took advantage of the jet stream.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 13:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961234/3961234_C827E6B7CE2C43DFAE4344B53E6656D9_200210_3961234_A_Boeing_747_broke_speed_records_during_New_York_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[British Airways, Boening, Boeing 747-400, transatlantic, speed record, subsonic, New York, London, BA 112, Flight 112, ciara, storm ciara, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961200</guid>
      <title>Soldier kills 29 in Thailand's deadliest ever mass shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NAKHON RATCHASIMA, THAILAND  A Thai soldier went on a shooting rampage over the weekend, killing 29 people in the country's deadliest ever mass shooting.Sergeant Major 1st Class Jakrapanth Thomma[m][n][o] made his way to his commanding officer's house in Nakhon Ratchasima, Thailand on Saturday, February 8 at 3:00 p.m. local time, where he shot his commander and a woman believed to be a relative of the commander after a dispute, Reuters reports. An hour later, he went to the Surathampithak army base where he was stationed and killed an army guard before stealing assault weapons, at least one machine gun and roughly 800 rounds of ammunition.The gunman drove off in a stolen Humvee and stopped at a Buddhist temple as authorities chased him. He killed around nine people before driving away. A Thai police officer was also killed during the shooting spree.The shooter posted updates to Facebook during the shootings, with messages such as "No one can escape death," at 6:30 p.m.The Thai soldier also live-streamed part of his shooting rampage on Facebook, though the video has since been deleted. It's unclear which part of the shooting was streamed on the social media platform.Around 5:30 p.m., the soldier made his way to Terminal 21 shopping mall in Nakhon Ratchasima, where he began to open fire on frightened shoppers in the vicinity. At least 12 shoppers were shot dead, while dozens were injured.Twenty minutes after the shooting, the police cordoned off two kilometers of the area around the mall. A few hours later, Thai security forces stormed the mall and helped hundreds of shoppers escape.The gunman escaped to the basement of the mall at 12:30 a.m., Sunday. Authorities continued to search for the soldier throughout the night. He was located in the basement in the morning at 9:05 a.m., when he was promptly shot dead by security forces.At least two victims died at the hospital during surgery, while others remain hospitalized, CNN reports, citing Narinrat Pitchayakamin, a Thai public health ministry official.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961200/3961200_440BF7E74F4A4CB28E5768FF014125D7_200210_3961200_Soldier_kills_29_in_Thailand_s_deadliest_ever_ma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Thailand shooting, thailand mass shooting, thai soldier, Jakrapanth Thomma, soldier in thailand, thai soldier attack, shooting rampage thailand, rare thai shooting, thailand news, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961190</guid>
      <title>Doctor's death sparks anger toward government in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  The passing of the Chinese doctor who tried to sound the alarm about China's grave situation has sparked public anger and grief. BBC reports that Li Wenliang is no longer around after contracting the same illness he was treating his patients for in the city where the latest incident began. Last December Li sent a text in a group chat with other physicians of a SARS-esque cousin. For his troubles he was told by police to "stop making false comments" and was put under the magnifying glass for "spreading rumors"  aka telling people THE TRUTH.    According to Forbes, after conflicting reports last Thursday the Li was no longer around, then critically ill, then indeed no longer around, Chinese citizens stormed onto social media voicing sorrow and extreme displeasure toward Xi and his pals.   Li has become a hero to Chinese people for his attempts to warn the public about the crisis in the early days, when the government was trying to cover it up. He was hospitalized January 12, 2020 and officially diagnosed with the you-know-what on February 1, 2020, before his passing was confirmed on February 6.According to the failing New York Times, #WeWantFreedomOfSpeech had at least 2 million views and 5,500 posts before fun-loving Chinese censors completely wiped them out of existence. But in the meantime, China will continue to keep hush hush at the expense of its citizens, all because saving face remains more important than saving ACTUAL lives.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961190/3961190_51E997DF9ABA4C3D8D1373B2C293256B_200210_3961190_Doctor_s_death_sparks_anger_toward_government_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China whistleblower, China doctor Li Wenliang, Li Wenliang, doctor Li Wenliang, China #WeWantFreedomOfSpeech, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961117</guid>
      <title>7-Eleven trials cashier-less convenient store</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRVING, TEXAS  7-Eleven has announced a trial of a cashier-less store in Irving, Texas starting this week. During the trial period, the store will only be open to 7-Eleven employees.Customers shopping at the store will need to download and sign up for an app then use it to check-in at the cashier-less store, according to a press release from the company.The convenience store will offer an array of products including beverages, food, groceries and also over-the-counter drugs.Once the customer has finished shopping, the app will be used to make payments and customers can view their receipt once they have exited the store.7-Eleven did not mention in its press release how long the trial is expected to last.The company had previously launched a Mobile Checkout feature which allowed customers to skip waiting in line and instead pay for products using their smartphones in selected stores.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 10:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961117/3961117_2354B19A86F645489947631C70380159_200210_3961117_7_Eleven_trials_cashier_less_convenient_store_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[7-11, cashierless 7-11, cashierless 7-eleven, 7-11 USA, cashierless stores, convenient stores, cashierless convenient stores, stores without cashiers, cashierless checkout, ai retail stores, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961084</guid>
      <title>Asteroid will fly very close to Earth this Saturday: NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  NASA warned that asteroid 2002 PZ39 will approach Earth on Saturday.This asteroid is moving at a speed of nearly 55,000 km per hour relative to Earth and has a diameter of between 440 meters to 990 meters.According to NASA, should a rocky asteroid bigger than 25 meters but smaller than 1 km were to hit Earth, the meteorite would likely cause local damage to the impact area.A meteorite larger than one or two kilometers in size would be capable of worldwide effects.Business Insider reports that most asteroids occupy orbits between Jupiter and Mars, so they pose little danger to the Earth.The outlet adds that 2002 PZ39 is one of the rare exceptions.NASA considers this asteroid a near Earth object and estimates that it will miss earth by a margin of 15.2 lunar distances  or 5.8 million km  at 11:00 pm on February 15.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 09:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961084/3961084_52EB46003B8A4382B9BDC0DEB4F89946_200210_3961084_Asteroid_will_fly_very_close_to_Earth_this_Satur_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Asteroid, asteroids, meteor, meteors, near earth object, near miss, neo, impact, 2002 PZ39, NASA, space, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960976</guid>
      <title>Driver wears 12 face masks at once during Wuhan coronavirus scare</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA  As China continues to struggle with all the negative news swirling around the Mexican beer sickness, stockpiles of many things are running low, especially face masks, so it's good to see people needlessly wasting them. Video footage posted to Miaopai, shows one driver from the city of Dongguan located in Guangdong province wearing a ridiculous 12 masks at one time. The clip shows the driver being pulled over by traffic cops for a quick temperature check. The police then ask the man how many masks he has on, so he starts taking them off. The guy methodically removes all 11 superfluous masks, while the police kindly wait for him. Authorities then let the man know that he only needs to wear one. What they should have told him is that if he's really that paranoid about catching the dreaded you-know-what, then you also need to protect your eyes. Great, now this guy is going to start driving around wearing 12 sets of goggles on his face.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 05:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3960976/3960976_964FF076A99540C5B1883D94719AD871_200210_3960976_Driver_wears_12_face_masks_at_once_during_Wuhan__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China driver, China traffic cops, Chinese social media, China Miaopai, China Miaopai video, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961648</guid>
      <title>U.S. charges four Chinese military officers over Equifax hack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (check dateline)  A federal grand jury charged four Chinese military officers on Tuesday for the massive hack of the credit rating giant Equifax that occurred in 2017. The four are alleged members of the People's Liberation Army's 54th Research Institute.Speaking at a press conference in Washington, U.S. Attorney General William Barr called the hack 'one of the largest data breaches in history.' Barr said the hackers stole personal information and trade secrets including data compilation and database designs.BBC reports that the hackers allegedly routed traffic through 32 servers in nearly 20 countries to conceal their location as they conducted the cyber attack, which occurred from May to June in 2017. The U.S. Department of Justice named three of the four suspects, but their whereabouts are unknown. The Washington Post quotes FBI Deputy Director David Bowdich as saying, "We can't take them into custody, try them in a court of law, and lock them up  not today, anyway."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961648/3961648_959C9A3F1EE146EFB728139F5BD46345_200211_3961648_U_S__charges_four_Chinese_military_officers_over_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Equifax, Equifax hack, Equifax breach, department of justice, fbi, people's liberation army, hackers, cyber warfare, cyber, trade secrets, 54th research institute, personal data, personal information, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961624</guid>
      <title>Melting Arctic ice might make Europe colder</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GREENBELT, MARYLAND  A NASA study says that human caused climate change is rapidly melting arctic ice and disrupting ocean currents, which could make Western Europe cooler.The new study was conducted over 12 years and published in Nature Communication.""The Beaufort Gyre is a current that previously kept the Arctic waters cold and protected sea ice.However, the glut of cold fresh water is making the gyre spin stronger and faster, and the natural reversal of the spin's direction has not happened for over 10 years.Researchers say that if the westerly wind guiding the current should reverse its direction now, the cold water build up could be unleashed at all once.The cold tide may well slow down the Atlantic currents that bring warmth to Western Europe.Citing the researchers, NASA says in its news release that disruptions to the Gulf Stream would have a negative impact on ocean life and the communities that depend on them.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961624/3961624_B3F4B1418E06457182E12107C8C2277D_200211_3961624_Melting_Arctic_ice_might_make_Europe_colder_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Global warming, climate change, sea ice loss, ice melt, beaufort gyre, gulf stream, the arctic, arctic ocean, atlantic, ocean currents, Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation, AMOC, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961601</guid>
      <title>Locust plague threatens Somalia and eastern Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GAROWE, SOMALIA  The U.N. has warned that Somalia and the rest of east Africa may soon be facing a severe locust plague.A report by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations says that young locusts are threatening pastures and crops in Somalia. The insects are said to threaten more than 10 million people in the region.These young locusts are expected to mature and develop wings in the coming weeks. They are then expected to make their way to Ethiopia and Kenya.Somalia has become the first country in east Africa to declare an emergency over locust infestation, BBC News reports. Kenya and Ethiopia are already taking precautionary measures by using planes to spray pesticides to prevent a locust outbreak.The locust outbreak follows a period of unusually heavy rains and a powerful cyclone off the coast of Somalia at the end of 2019, the Associated Press reports, citing climate experts. According to the report, more rains are expected in the next few weeks. This means that the number of locusts could increase.Dominique Burgeon, the Food and Agriculture Organization's emergency and resilience director, explained another generation of the insect could now even be born in regular moisture conditions due to the high density of locusts.He said that without enough planes spraying to stop the locust swarms, the outbreak may even turn into a plague, which could take years to control.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961601/3961601_384B1EF78CA9459CB18C8160505E47F3_200211_3961601_Locust_plague_threatens_Somalia_and_eastern_Afri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Locust plague, locust plague somalia, locust plague africa, locust plague africa 2020, locust plague in east africa, somalia declare emergency over locusts TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961588</guid>
      <title>China goes into further lockdown as Wuhan coronavirus spreads</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  As China continues to struggle with their grave situation, some of its biggest cities are partially hanging up the "We're Closed" sign.  Taiwan News reports that according to the Beijing Daily, Chinese officials said on Sunday Feb. 9 that Beijing was being locked down under "closed off management" measures. Authorities said the city would be strictly implementing "closed community management," under which vehicles and people from outside a community will be prohibited. Those coming to Beijing from other areas are required to report their health status and register their personal information. According to the new regulations, the first 14 days while in lovely Beijing, people visiting from affected areas or have a history of recent contact with those in affected areas must undergo inspection and observation in their homes. People must also actively provide health status updates and cooperate with relevant authorities. Oh yeahand they are not allowed to leave their quarters.  If people refuse to accept hospital confinement, home confinement and other prevention measures, they get to be FORCED to accept it. All public areas in residential communities, like recreation rooms and sports areas are now off limits, and all businesses and government agencies must constantly monitor people's temperatures. In addition, there will be checkpoints at entrances and exits of residences, where people coming and going on foot and in vehicles must be masked up and have their temps checked.  Shanghai followed Beijing's lead on Monday, Feb. 10 and also said it would be introducing similar lockdown measures across the city's 13,000 residential complexes.   Beijing is home to more than 20 million people, while Shanghai is close to more than 24 million people. Can locking these cities down slow the spread?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961588/3961588_1D9A08AB699D425D9071BA82AB33EB37_200211_3961588_China_goes_into_further_lockdown_as_Wuhan_corona_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, Beijing, Shanghai, Beijing and Shanghai, Beijing lockdown, Shanghai lockdown, lockdown measures, closed off management, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961423</guid>
      <title>Rise in sulfur dioxide could be sign of mass cremations in Wuhan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Do you smell that? Data from Windy.com on Feb. 9 showed a massive increase in levels of sulfur dioxide around the city which will remain nameless, causing some to speculate it could be a sign of mass cremation. Images from Windy.com shared over Twitter appear to show unusually high levels of sulfur dioxide being released, with no other city in China showing similar levels besides Chongqing. High levels of sulfur dioxide in the air is commonly associated with the burning of organic material. According to Taiwan News, as the number of no longer living continues to rise, there have been accounts and anecdotal evidence that crematoriums have been working in overdrive. On Sunday, Intelwave shared an image showing sulfur dioxide levels as high as 1,300ug/m^3 around the city.  For reference, the WHO recommends that a dosage of 500ug/m^3 should not be exceeded for more than 10 minutes. Intelwave then went through some possible explanations for the increased emissions, with the first being a power plant. Unfortunately, none of China's other power plants were displaying such high levels. A second possibility is that a lot of refuse and animal carcasses were being burnt. Yeah ok, maybe.The third possibility? Evidence is being disposed of on the outskirts of the city so that China can keep telling everyone that the flu is worse. Hmmmmmmm.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 04:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961423/3961423_08F5EBE8A3A246CF88D7EEFEBDCB9CE7_200211_3961423_Rise_in_sulfur_dioxide_could_be_sign_of_mass_cre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China crisis, China sulfur dioxide, China sulfur dioxide rise, sulfur dioxide levels, Chinese news, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961383</guid>
      <title>China silences whistleblowers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  After the death of a whistleblower doctor that led to hundreds of thousands of Chinese netizens demanding freedom of speech, little did they know, another unsung hero was about to go quite. Chen Qiushi, a citizen journalist who had been doing critical reporting from the center of China's epidemic went missing on Thursday. When friends and family could not locate him, they later learned from police that Chen had been forced into quarantine. Chen's disappearance didn't go unnoticed and by Sunday netizens on Weibo began pleading for his release. Chen had been in the outbreak epicenter since January the 24th, a day after the city was put under lockdown. Chen had visited hospitals that were overwhelmed, funeral parlors and temporary isolation wards and filmed it all. He uploaded videos of what he saw to offer us a glimpse into the reality of the situation and reveal China's struggle to control the situation.Fearing he could be detained at any moment for his reporting, friends checked in with him multiple times per day; but when Chen stopped picking up his phone they began to panic. The following day, a message from his mother was posted to his Twitter account pleading for help.  Chen was believed to have been in perfectly good health when he was forcibly detained. CNN contacted the Wuhan city police for information about Chen, however, they claim they had no information on him. The latest incident is pushing China's censoring machine into overdrive; they're desperate to shape the narrative and it is through this desperation that its methods of suppression are being forced into the light. Xi Jinping's government is getting reckless and will do anything to maintain the party's rule by iron fist, they fear free speech and will silence all whistleblowers and the house arrest of a nearly 90-year-old man illustrates that. This is Dr. Jiang Yanyong, an 88-year-old retired military surgeon who became a national hero when he exposed the government's cover-up of the Sars epidemic back in 2003. This so-called 'national treasure' was then detained and forced to undergo brainwashing sessions, or what China calls 're-education' when he wrote a letter to the government asking them to acknowledge that the 1989 student movement was a "patriotic movement."Jiang's wife said, "He is not allowed to be in contact with people outside. He is at home. He has no means of communication with the outside. His health is not good. He is not in a good mental state either. He is not very well. I am sorry, it is not convenient to say more." The free flow of information is the best weapon we have to stop this, so we have to ask ourselves, what exactly is China doing?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961383/3961383_EF2E824F90D14BB4AFE5E597BC764A82_200211_3961383_China_silences_whistleblowers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Chinese illness, China illness, Chen Qiushi, Chinese journalist, Chinese censor, censorship, whistleblowers, Chinese whistleblowers, Dr. Jiang Yanyong, 2013, outbreak, 1989 Hong Kong, Chinese government]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962229</guid>
      <title>Russian spacecraft are stalking an advanced U.S. spy satellite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARLINGTON, VIRGINIA  Two mysterious Russian spacecraft have been shadowing a U.S. reconnaissance satellite since November, coming to as close to 100 miles at times, U.S. Space Force commander General John Raymond confirmed to Time in a report dated to Feb. 10.[e]Citing outside experts, Time reports that the U.S. KH-11 satellite is about the size of a bus and its spying sensors are believed to be as powerful as the Hubble Space Telescope's.Citing General Raymond, Time reports that the Russians launched a Soyuz rocket in November with a payload that separated into the two stalking satellites. General Raymond says he believes the bigger satellite acted as a carrier for the small one.Satellite watcher Michael Thompson  who first broke the story in January  tweeted that the Russian orbit was cleverly designed. The orbit the pair of satellites holds allows the two to observe KH-11 from one side during daytime and the other at night.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 13:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962229/3962229_E16A2823790C4BED8FA591CB6C353BC4_200212_3962229_Russian_spacecraft_are_stalking_an_advanced_U_S__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[KH-11, spy satellite, reconnaissance satellite, surveillance, soyuz, russian satellites, russian spacecraft, u.s. space force, u.s., russia, space, defense, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962134</guid>
      <title>China has a coronavirus 'close contact detector' app</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China has apparently launched an app that allows people to check whether they have been at risk of catching you-know-what. The BBC reports that the "close contact detector" tells users if they have been near a person who has been confirmed or suspected of having the thing that will remain nameless. Those identified as being at risk are advised to seal themselves up in their homes and notify local authorities, so they can come and lock you up. The technology is just another example of how invasive the Chinese government is with its 1984-esque surveillance of its population. To see if you're about to join the land of the not living, users just scan a QR code on their smartphones. After the new app is registered with a phone number, users are asked to enter their name and ID number. Every registered phone number can then be used to check the status of up to three ID numbers. According to state-run speakerbox Xinhua, the app was designed in a fun-filled collaboration with government departments and the China Electronics Technology Group Corporation and supported by data from health and transport authorities. Here's a question though, how exactly is this app supposed to function properly when the Chinese government is obviously lying about how many people have been infected and how many are now pushing up daisies?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 10:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962134/3962134_CFC256C8E8944F3CA7719A6AEA451751_200212_3962134_China_has_a_coronavirus__close_contact_detector__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China close contact detector app, Chinese close contact detector app, close contact detector, Chinese health app, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962130</guid>
      <title>New MRI tracer could make cancer much easier to spot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA  Researchers claim that a new MRI contrast agent could be a "game changer" for the early detection of metastasizing cancers, especially liver cancer. This study was published in Science Advances on Feb. 5.The paper focused on a form of eye cancer that can migrate to the liver during the early stages of metastasizing. Georgia State University's news release states that current tests often do not detect liver cancer before advanced stages.The research team applies the metal element gadolinium to the contrast agent's protein. This allows the MRI to accurately detect overexpression of receptors called CXCR4 in cancerous organs, even during early stage metastasis.According to the paper, the contrast agent has been tested in mice, but the university says that the substance can identify multiple types of cancer cells and the FDA is fast tracking human trials, which could begin in 18 months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 10:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962130/3962130_141E87384A694A1CB5E3E62B08CABA3E_200212_3962130_New_MRI_tracer_could_make_cancer_much_easier_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[MRI, contrast agent, tracer agent, imaging agent, cancer detection, metastasis, metastasizing cancer, early stage metastasis liver cancer, eye cancer, metal element, gadolinium, receptors, health, science, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962074</guid>
      <title>Native American burial sites are being blown up for Trump's wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARIZONA  Trump is blowing up Native American burial sites to build his wall.The Washington Post reports that construction crews have begun controlled blasting within Arizona's Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument, which is a UNESCO recognized natural reserve.According to the BBC, the project is being done to prepare for the construction of Trump's border wall system, which will see a 30-foot tall steel barrier run across 43 miles of national park land.The blasts are occurring on Monument Hill, on ground considered sacred to Native American tribes, which include the burial site for the Tohono O'odham Nation."It also includes an area that is believed to contain artifacts dating back 10,000 years."Democratic Congressman Raul D. Grijalva described the project as 'sacrilegious' and says the Tohono O'odham Nation was not consulted by the government beforehand.Under the 2005 REAL ID act, the federal government has the right to waive laws that get in the way of national security. The Trump administration has since used this to waive dozens of laws, in order to construct the wall.Environmentalists are also concerned about the damage being done to the local underground aquifer, as well as to migrating wildlife in the region.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 09:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962074/3962074_63C49461D56E4C56895AAADF3582352D_200212_3962074_Native_American_burial_sites_are_being_blown_up__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Native American burial ground, Trump wall, Trump, Trump border wall, US border wall, Native Americans, Donald Trump, border wall construction, wall construction, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962035</guid>
      <title>North Korea is still making bombs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA  North Korea has continued development of its nuclear and missile programs, according to a confidential United Nations report seen by Reuters.The country conducted 13 missile tests last year and launched roughly 25 missiles. This included new short-range and submarine-launched ballistic missiles, according to the report. It mentioned that North Korea has continued to "develop infrastructure and capacity" to enhance its missile program.The U.N. report says that the country also exported tons of commodities such as coal using Chinese barges, even though North Korea has been banned from doing so since 2017. DPRK-flagged vessels would transfer over the commodities to local Chinese barges, a method known as ship-to-ship transfer, which would then deliver the goods to ports in Hangzhou Bay and the Yangtze River in China.In a statement, China called the accusations "baseless," and said that it is implementing U.N. sanctions against North Korea.According to the report, North Korea also continued to illegally import refined petroleum using the same method.The country has been allowed to import 500,000 barrels of refined petroleum under current sanctions, but the report found that North Korea exceeded the limit "many times over," between January 1 and October 31 of last year, reports Reuters. North Korea's allies, Russia and China, have both raised concerns saying that the U.N. sanctions are causing harm to civilians in North Korea, according to Reuters. The United States, France and Great Britain have all said that sanctions should not be lifted.North Korea has been sanctioned by the United Nations since 2006, Reuters reports. Members of the U.N. security council have imposed harsher sanctions against the country over the years to deprive the country of funding for its nuclear and ballistic missile programs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 08:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962035/3962035_296F01A607184A7F8F45CC587DE4A646_200212_3962035_North_Korea_is_still_making_bombs_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[North korea, north korea sanctions, north korea breach sanctions, north korea UN report, north korea nuclear missile program, north korea missile test, north korea enhanced nuclear program, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961910</guid>
      <title>Chinese couple suspected to have virus rounded up like strays</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  As pretty much all of China remains on edge, authorities are taking increasingly fewer chances when handling new or suspected cases. Video posted to YouTube by Epoch Times on Feb. 6 shows how one amazingly unlucky couple was rounded up because they might have been sick. The footage starts out with the couple hugging each other while the woman cries loudly. They are surrounded by Chinese officials in pink hazmat suits and some dude with an umbrella. The camera then pans toward a pickup truck with a metal box in back reminiscent of something stray animals are tossed into.The next thing we see is the couple climbing up into the pickup and getting inside the box.After getting sealed in, the woman is heard screaming at the top of her lungs as the hazmat guys prepare to drive off. According to the Liberty Times, last week another Chinese man suspected of having the you-know-what outside the Shanghai airport was also kindly introduced to the box.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3961910/3961910_312DB473D5EB4E5688FAABD538E77B75_200212_3961910_Chinese_couple_suspected_to_have_virus_rounded_u_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, Chinese couple, Chinese couple pickup truck, Chinese couple in truck, stray animals, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961895</guid>
      <title>Whistleblower who filmed coronavirus corpses arrested</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China continues its mission. China has silenced the whistleblower who posted the now viral video showing the not living piling up outside a local hospital.The Epoch Times reports that citizen journalist Fang Bin was arrested by police officers around 3 p.m. on February 10.He had refused to come out of his apartment, so officers surrounded his home and blocked possible escape routes before firefighters eventually broke down his front door.Netizens suspect his phone and home wifi were cut off before his arrest, which rendered him unable to post another video.Fang, a traditional clothes seller, had been spurred to citizen journalism by a lack of reliable information. He visited local you-know-where hospitals and recorded what he saw.  One video, where he spots 8 no-longer-around in a span of five minutes, went viral and caught the attention of Chinese authorities. Masked men in hazmat suits came to his house later that day wanting to take his temperature and possibly put him in quarantine. He refused to open the door, but they barged in anyway.Fang told the LA Times in a phone interview that he was detained by police and interrogated about the videos. He was told to stop "spreading rumors" before being released.But Fang continued with his crusade, and told his followers that he would be posting a video every morning so people would know he was alright.Plainclothes police officers, he said, were monitoring his every move, and he speculated that the only reason they haven't broken in is because his videos were attracting the world's attention.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 03:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3961895/3961895_BC598F62AE72435A99D2BFFED347B8CC_200212_3961895_Whistleblower_who_filmed_coronavirus_corpses_arr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fang Bin, whistleblower, China citizen journalist, China censorship, China censors, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961845</guid>
      <title>Queen sends disgraced Andrew to meet with Chinese Ambassador</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Britain's Queen Elizabeth sent her son, Prince Andrew to offer her condolences to the Chinese government for those affected in the latest crisis.Prince Andrew made headlines last year for a disastrous BBC interview that saw him fail to defend himself against allegations of sexual assault; the Prince also couldn't explaion his relationship with Jeffrey Epstein which led Andrew to announced he was stepping back from public duties.The meeting was met with mockery and shock, with one netizen calling out the Queen's decision, "You know this is a veiled insult, right?"]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3961845/3961845_6CC75FCDAE04426A99DDB967E004EF60_200212_3961845_Queen_sends_disgraced_Andrew_to_meet_with_Chines_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Prince Andrew, Royal Family scandal, British royals, royals, Queen of England, Queen Elizebeth, Chinese ambassador to U.K., harry and meghan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962830</guid>
      <title>Crew of Diamond Princess ship at greater risk of COVID-19 infection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YOKOHAMA, JAPAN  As quarantine on the Diamond Princess cruise ship continues, crews may be facing a greater risk of coronavirus infection.The New York Times reports that at least 219 people aboard the Diamond Princess cruise ship currently docked in Yokohama port have been infected with the novel coronavirus, or COVID-19.Those who tested positive for the virus have disembarked and been sent to local hospitals.CNN reports that passengers and crew have been quarantined on the ship since February 4.Passengers are asked to wear masks and stay in their cabins. Meals are delivered to their rooms. They are also permitted to walk the decks for a few minutes each day, but must keep a distance of at least six feet from other passengers.The ship's crew, meanwhile, continue to live and work in close proximity to each other and the passengers, which can mean potential contact with those who are infected.Harvard University professor of immunology Eric Rubin told CNN that keeping everyone on the ship poses a greater infection risk for the crew. 10 crew members who recently tested positive for the virus stayed in shared cabins and ate meals in the mess hall alongside other employees.According to the New York Times, it isn't clear how many people on the ship have the virus, because Japanese officials have only tested 439 of the 3,700 passengers for infection, reasoning that there is a shortage of testing supplies. The current quarantine period is scheduled to end on February 19, unless there are any "unforeseen developments."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 16:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3962830/3962830_7BB2FEC58A6548BC90F66B80458FD610_200214_3962830_Crew_of_Diamond_Princess_ship_at_greater_risk_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Diamond Princess crew, cruise ship crew, Diamond Princess, Diamond Princess quarantine, cruise ship quarantine, ship quarantine, quarantine, COVID-19, Diamond Princess cruise, Diamond Princess ship, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962808</guid>
      <title>Woman jailed for trying to open plane door mid-flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHELMSFORD, UNITED KINGDOM  A lady who tried to open a plane door mid-flight is set to spend the next two years in the slammer.The BBC reports that last June 22, Chloe Haines had been drunk as a skunk on both alcohol and medication while travelling with her wheelchair-bound nan aboard a Jet2 flight to Dalaman, Turkey.Prosecutors say she lunged at a door handle on the emergency exit door, bellowing "I want to die!" and "I'm going to kill you all!" as cabin crew and passengers tried to restrain her. She was kicking and punching, and even scratched up a cabin crew member named Charley Coombe.Haines' antics sparked a hijack alert, which then prompted two Royal Air Force fighter jets to scramble up there and intercept the plane, guiding it back to Stansted for an emergency landing.She later claimed she had blacked out and didn't really remember anything after downing her unholy cocktail.Haines pleaded guilty to two charges: endangering the safety of a passenger plane and assault by beating.Jet2 has also banned her for life after her little air rage incident cost them £86,000.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 15:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962808/3962808_6B998C8D63594BF988C509553700E487_200213_3962808_Woman_jailed_for_trying_to_open_plane_door_mid_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chloe Haines, air rage, woman opens plane door, woman opens plane door mid flight, emergency exit door, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962678</guid>
      <title>Wendy's worker fired for taking bath in kitchen sink</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRENNVILLE, MICHIGAN  A worker was filmed enjoying a nice bubble bath in a sink at a Greenville Wendy's joint while other employees watched on in enjoyment. According to WXMI, a version of the now viral video was originally shared on video-sharing app TikTok, but has since been deleted. But before that happened, it was also shared on Facebook.The 23-second video shows a worker submerged in a big old industrial sink used to wash kitchen items laughing and joking with other Wendy's workers. Another worker is seen throwing something into the sink and saying "Wash yourself!"The bather responds by saying, "It feels like a hot tub," while he scrubs himself down. He doesn't have a shirt on, but with all the bubbles it's unclear what's going on down below. According to Team Schostakthe company that owns the Wendy's restaurantall the workers involved in the video have been given the boot. In a statement from the vice president of Team Schostak said, "This egregious behavior is completely unacceptable and counter to our safety, training and operational standards. Upon learning of this situation, all employees in the video were terminated immediately and the restaurant is being completely sanitized." The Wendy's in question has since re-opened for business. Anyone else need a bath?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962678/3962678_B3EFC5109C2048CDA52D173ECC5A2D91_200213_3962678_Wendy_s_worker_fired_for_taking_bath_in_kitchen__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Wendy's, Wendy's worker bath sink, Wendy's worker fired, Wendy's worker bath TikTok, Wendy's worker takes bath, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962635</guid>
      <title>NASA's Mars 2020 rover will sport a laser that vaporizes rocks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  First 150 characters of description should repeat as many keywords from title as possible. Do not exceed 150 characters in first graf. This is so that the subscribe link appears above the dropdown bar.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 10:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962635/3962635_42709C6281A84C05B2B05FBF9655E21A_200213_3962635_NASA_s_Mars_2020_rover_will_sport_a_laser_that_v_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA, mars 2020 rover, mars rover, new mars rover, laser, lasers, minerals, fossils, microbes, microbial life, water, sulfates, sulfur, carbon, carbonates, SuperCam, mars, space exploration, science, technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962601</guid>
      <title>New coronavirus might spread through sewage pipes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  A Hong Kong woman fell victim to the new coronavirus after a man residing 10 floors directly above her unit became sick. The South Morning China Post reports on Tuesday that the new cases suggest building pipes could be a path for the virus.Citing the WHO, Live Science reports that the coronavirus which causes SARS could get into feces and infect people through leaky pipes because compromised sewage pipes could allow pathogens to move into the surrounding air.Toilets have a u-shaped drain to trap fluids and odor. However, the Washington Post reported in 2003 that faulty plumbing can cause backwash from toilets, which led to a SARS outbreak at another residential tower in Hong Kong.Citing an infectious disease expert, Live Science explains that the new virus, now named COVID-19, could in fact transmit via feces, although aerosols from coughing and sneezing are still believed to be the main infection mechanism.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 09:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962601/3962601_44F4E06CB25347BABCAC7C72006A75A2_200213_3962601_New_coronavirus_might_spread_through_sewage_pipe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Health, china, china news, hong kong,  hong kong news, transmission, water pipes, pipes, drainage, sewage, epidemiology, science, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962538</guid>
      <title>Global CO2 emissions plateaued last year: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  A new report by the International Energy Agency has found that global carbon emissions flattened in 2019, following two years of increased emissions. The U.S. also decreased its carbon emissions by 2.9 percent last year.This is because advanced economies, such as Australia, Canada, Japan and South Korea, increased their use of renewable resources such as wind and solar power, according to the report. The report also found that a rise in nuclear power and a weaker demand for electricity resulted in lower carbon emissions.In comparison, usage of coal-fired plants in advanced economies last year had declined by nearly 15 percent.The report also found that carbon emissions rose sharply in southeast Asia due to an increased demand of coal. China and India were found to have moderate emissions growth in 2019 due to slower economic growth and an increase in usage of renewable energy.In a statement, Fatih Birol, the International Energy Agency executive director, said that the halt in carbon emission growth provides optimism that climate change can be tackled this decade.A separate report from the United Nations stated that global emissions would have to be reduced by 7.6 percent every year until 2030 to prevent temperatures from rising to dangerously high levels which would "increase the frequency and intensity" of climate change.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 08:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962538/3962538_AD8437BFCD464A94A5C9A51DC8BFEDFC_200213_3962538_Global_CO2_emissions_plateaued_last_year__Report_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Climate change, global warming, carbon emissions, global carbon emissions, US carbon emissions, carbon dioxide, CO2, world's CO2 emissions, carbon dioxide emissions, International energy agency, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962449</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus can survive on surfaces for up to 9 days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GERMANY  New analysis shows that many human coronavirus strains can stay infectious on inanimate surfaces for up to 9 days.The 2019 novel coronavirus is a droplet-based infection that can be spread through direct person-to-person transmission or by touching contaminated surfaces. These include door knobs or handles, bedside tables and chairs, call buttons, and other objects around an infected patient.A report published in the Journal of Hospital Infection looked at 22 studies on different coronaviruses and found that human coronaviruses such as SARS and MERS can survive on glass, plastic, and metal surfaces for up to 9 days.According to Professor Gunter Kampf, from the Institute of Hygiene and Environmental Medicine at Germany's Greifswald University Hospital, low temperature and humidity can increase the viruses' lifespan.Fortunately, the research also found that disinfectants such as ethanol, hydrogen peroxide, or sodium hypochlorite can easily kill the viruses within just one minute.While the study focused on other types of coronaviruses like SARS and MERS, researchers predict the findings may also be applicable to the 2019-nCov.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962449/3962449_6334987814A849C789693D1785D3382F_200213_3962449_Coronavirus_can_survive_on_surfaces_for_up_to_9__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Coronavirus, SARS, MERS, nCov, novel coronavirus, contaminated surfaces, disinfectants, coronavirus transmission, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962410</guid>
      <title>Massive flock of crows take over Chinese city during outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINING, CHINA  This could be the end of days as we know itno seriously. Video footage posted online by Epoch Times from the city of Xining located in the fantastic Qinghai province could be a sign that the apocalypse is right around the corner.As China continues to try and get a handle on the situation, cities around the country have turned into virtual ghost towns.And now with everyone hunkered down at home and most vehicles off the roads, the birds have come out to play. All of them it seems.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 04:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962410/3962410_6CD040F3A5834FFEB4708A7B6930AE40_200213_3962410_Massive_flock_of_crows_take_over_Chinese_city_du_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Crows, flock of crows, massive flock of crows, crows take over city, crows take over intersection, crows, china, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962403</guid>
      <title>Dog takes itself on bus ride to get some exercise at the park</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  Eclipse is a black Labrador Retriever-cross-Mastiff and she's a hit with the local community because she rides the bus alone. Her owner, Jeff Young used to walk her down to the bus stop, and then get off at Belltown dog park. Eventually, Eclipse knew exactly where she was going and if Jeff was taking too long, she'd just jump on the bus without him. The bus driver would recognize her and drop her off at the dog park with Jeff catching her up later. After several trips, Jeff let Eclipse go on her own, and now amazingly she rides the bus alone, plays at the dog park and then catches the bus back; she even has her own bus pass attached to her collar.She's got 83,000 plus followers on Facebook and everyone wants to ride along with her.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 03:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962403/3962403_91212C459A47493489A293A9B9370CB8_200213_3962403_Dog_takes_itself_on_bus_ride_to_get_some_exercis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, dog takes bus, dog walks itself, dogs, dog videos, funny dog videos, dog rides bus, Eclipse Seattle bus riding dog, bus riding dog, eclipse rider, dog on bus, funny animal videos, cute dog videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962396</guid>
      <title>Jussie Smollett indicted on six counts for faking attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Former Empire actor Jussie Smollett is facing a new six-count indictment for filing false reports last year that he was the victim of a hate crime. According to USA Today, Smollett had told police that he was beaten by two masked men while walking near his Chicago apartment on January 29, 2019. He said the attackers shouted racial and anti-gay slurs, poured a chemical substance over him, and wrapped a noose around his neck.CNN reports that while Chicago police initially investigated the incident as a hate crime, prosecutors later claimed Smollett paid the two men – brothers Abel and Ola Osundairo – to stage the attack for publicity.    Court documents indicate that on January 22, 2019, Jussie Smollett received a threatening letter at the studio where the show 'Empire' is filmed. It came with a white powdery substance that was later determined to be ibuprofen."  Disappointed by the studio's handling of the letter, the actor met with the Osundairo brothers three days later, and asked them to stage an attack on him.According to prosecutors, Smollett wanted the assault to happen the night of January 28 near his Streeterville apartment. He told Abel to hurt him, but not too badly, and Ola to put a rope around his neck, pour gasoline on him, and yell, "This is MAGA country!"He then gave the brothers $100 to buy rope, gasoline, ski masks, gloves, and red MAGA baseball caps needed for the attack.On January 27, Smollett drove the brothers to the scene where he wanted the assault to take place, pointing out a surveillance camera that would capture the incident. He instructed them to pour bleach instead of gasoline, and not to bring their cellphones, then gave a $3,500 personal check payable to Abel.A flight delay on Smollett's part pushed the plan back to 2 a.m. on the 29th. The actor called Abel at 12:49 a.m. once his plane landed. Minutes later, the brothers hailed an Uber, switching to a cab midway that took them three blocks from the scene. The attack took place on 2:04 a.m. as instructed, though out of view of the camera. The brothers fled the scene afterward, taking a taxi home.ABC News reports that the actor had initially been indicted in March 2019 for 16 counts of felony disorderly conduct, before charges were all dropped just weeks later. Prosecutors said Smollett had forfeited his $10,000 bail and done community service.Following backlash from the dismissal, a judge assigned special prosecutor Dan Webb to look into why the original charges were dropped.After weighing the extensive nature of Smollett's false police reports and the resources expended by Chicago PD to investigate his allegations, Webb determined there are reasonable grounds to further prosecute the actor, adding that it is "in the interest of justice."Another factor that contributed to this decision is that the Cook County State Attorney's Office could not provide evidence of similar cases that showed Smollett's received no special treatment. Smollett is due in court on February 24.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 03:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962396/3962396_D2F4AF0E211540748C8A58773F0428C3_200213_3962396_Jussie_Smollett_indicted_on_six_counts_for_fakin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Jussie Smollett, fake crime, fake attack, Empire actor, Chicago special prosecutor, false reports, Jussie Smollett indictment, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963269</guid>
      <title>Using old mattress foam to grow plants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZAATARI, JORDAN   Researchers from the University of Sheffield have found a way to use foam from abandoned mattresses to grow plants and vegetables for those living in the Zaatari refugee camp in Jordan.In a news release from the university, researcher Tony Ryan explained that the mattress foam supports the plant while water and nutrient solution are pumped into the foam to allow the plant to grow. This system is called hydroponic farming and involves plants that are supported artificially and do not use soil.According to Jordanian law, refugees aren't allowed to grow plants in the ground or build permanent structures while living in these camps.In order to allow large-scale farming, researchers built a plastic piping system and put it on a rack. The piping system has numerous openings in which recycling yogurt pots holding the mattress foam and plants are put inside. Nutrient solution is added and flows through to the plants, helping them to grow and produce crops.This gives the refugees the opportunity to grow fresh vegetables which can be used for cooking their own meals, according to the researchers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 12:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963269/3963269_BC6F42CA11954BA2BE0BF325E9D86797_200214_3963269_Using_old_mattress_foam_to_grow_plants_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Old mattresses, discarded mattresses, mattress foaming, mattress foam plants, growing plants with mattress foam, mattress foaming for planting, using old mattresses to grow plants, growing plants in refugee camp, Zaatari camp, recycled mattress foam, refugee gardens, hydroponic farming system, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963152</guid>
      <title>Mars formation may have taken a lot longer than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN ANTONIO, TEXAS  The early solar system was a chaotic place with many large-scale collisions. A new study in Science Advances argues that such collisions involving Mars could be why scientists are underestimating the red planet's age.According to the Southwest Research Institute, Martian meteorites' tungsten content are highly varied. Since tungsten migrates from a planet's mantle to its core during formation, scientists are led to believe that Mars formed rapidly in 2 to 4 million years.However, the institute's researchers say Mars is known to have experienced large collisions in its early formative history. According to their models, this would have scrambled Mars's mantle and created a heterogeneous, marbled structure.Subsequently, when later collisions on Mars sent meteorites to Earth, the debris would have contained an uneven quantity of tungsten. Using the new models, the paper's authors claim that Mars may have taken 20 million years to become fully formed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963152/3963152_CC5C5F2521C14023A1D1A1E11ECBE940_200214_3963152_Mars_formation_may_have_taken_a_lot_longer_than__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mars, collision, collisions, timescale, formation, asteroids, tungsten, core, mantle, Southwest Research Institute, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963131</guid>
      <title>Lying about Wuhan virus will kill your social credit score</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  With all the things Chinese people are worrying about with the you-know-whatthat's now being called you-know-whatever-19destroying your social credit score is now another one.According to state-run Xinhua, a bunch of Chinese provinces and cities are tossing people on the social credit blacklist for lying about symptoms and sneaking out of quarantine. If you're lucky enough to live in Anhui, Jiangsu or Jilin provinces, or the cities of Shanghai, Chongqing and Hangzhou, officials there have also approved guidelines to punish those concealing travel history to key hit regions or history of contact with confirmed or suspected patients. Apparently if you're caught, not only will you have to deal with Chinese legal consequences, but you'll also be blacklisted on the local credit information platform. On February 12, Hangzhou did just that to nine completely appreciative residents for one year. Those nine people also got the privilege of being publicly shamed online with their full names and part of their ID card numbers posted, along with a full list of all the trouble they'll soon be in. Some Chinese have been forced to think outside of the seat like one woman who was caught at a Shanghai highway checkpoint hiding in the trunk of a car, so she could dodge quarantine. Let's just say she was unsuccessful. Maybe it's time for China to build a really big and really long wall to keep everyone from moving aroundoh wait.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963131/3963131_8310E2548F814D58AD27B7C3B854F4FB_200214_3963131_Lying_about_Wuhan_virus_will_kill_your_social_cr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China social credit score, Chinese social credit score, Chinese social credit blacklist, China blacklist social credit, Shanghai TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963128</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus misinformation as epidemic continues to grow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  TomoNews effed up. We here at TomoNews would like to apologize for publishing two stories that after further investigation were found to be untrue. On February 7, we published a story, "Tencent may have just leaked the truth," where it said a screenshot from Tencent's "Epidemic Situation Tracker" webpage appeared to show much higher estimates of those infected and killed by the Wuhan coronavirus. According to New Bloom Magazine, upon closer examination, Tencent's epidemic tracker has a link to a public database that anyone can access. New Bloom reports that hundreds of Chinese web developers have been scraping data from the Tencent website to generate their own charts, taking screenshots of the main Tencent dataset at different times, and sharing them along with their source code. A search of all available datasets did not reveal any of the inflated figures appearing in the screenshot used for the original story.  A second story published on February 11 titled, "Sulfur dioxide cloud could be sign of cremations" was also found to be incorrect. In the story, we said data from Windy.com on February 9 appeared to show high levels of sulfur dioxide, which could be a sign of mass cremations. However, Windy.com does not display real-time empirical data. It is a forecasting tool which relies on projections from datasets like those at NASA's GEOS-5 model.  Historical trends can be plugged into the underlying model, but it cannot predict individual events. Both stories have since been removed. We apologize again for not doing our proper due diligence.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963128/3963128_E0B5E7F19DA2415983D191E3F20673E2_200214_3963128_Wuhan_virus_misinformation_as_epidemic_continues_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Wuhan virus misinformation, Wuhan Tencent numbers, Wuhan sulfur dioxide levels, misinformation, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962920</guid>
      <title>Tyra Banks set to open 'ModelLand' theme park</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA MONICA, CALIFORNIA  Tyra Banks reveals that she's set to open 'ModelLand' later this year. Almost a year ago to the day, the creator of America's Next Top Model revealed that she was going to open up a model-themed theme park called 'ModelLand'Speaking on an episode of The View earlier this week, Banks said she wanted to bring "modeling to the masses." She described ModelLand as "a story-driven attraction where you can come and celebrate your own beauty." Late last year, Banks labeled ModelLand as her "baby which has not yet been born." She said that the park will be a "location-based attraction where you can be a model for a day." Speaking to Variety last year she revealed, "Modelland is going to be a place where the modeling world meets fantasy, meets entertainment, meets technology, meets retail, meets dining, meets your fiercest best self you could ever imagine."She noted Wakanda, the fictional country from Black Panther as inspiration for the project; she also lists her own young-adult novel 'ModelLand' as an influence.When will it open?No one knows exactly, details are lacking, all we do know is that it is set to open in Santa Monica sometime in winter this year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 02:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3962920/3962920_5CB1E6CB0E3E4BC4AFFAFE2D04B0D590_200214_3962920_Tyra_Banks_set_to_open__ModelLand__theme_park_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Tyra Banks, america's next top model, modelland mall, themepark, modelland book, modelland theme park, wakanda, black panther]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964431</guid>
      <title>China's makeshift Wuhan virus hospitals aren't even full yet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  As China's latest saga was in its early daysbut already out of controlto take the focus off their foot-dragging, the boys in Beijing decided to slap together a few prefabbed hospitals. At first, the Chinese boasted the first one, Huoshenshan, would be finished in a mere 6 days, leaving many westerners to complain that it often took 6 years just to get a simple road built in their home countries. But then 6 days, turned into 10. According to Business Insider, Chinese state media livestreamed frantic construction efforts with a bunch of aerial drone shots of excavators everywhere pushing around a lot of dirt paired with patriotic CCP-style tunes. The second makeshift hospital, Leishenshan, was completed in 12 days. And if you're wondering what kind of quality construction went into building these facilities? Here's a little taste. Anyways, Chinese officials claimed the two hospitals would have 2,600 extra beds for a health care system clearly stretched over its limits.Official speakerbox Xinhua even went so far as to call the quick construction, "Mission Impossible made possible."However, Business Insider reports that official Chinese data shows that as of Feb. 12, the facilities were running at less than half their projected capacity.  While Huoshenshan is now full, Leishenshan only had 416 patients out of a possible 1,600 capacity.  But let's be honest folks, would you want to stay at one of these places?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 23:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964431/3964431_24A3AC0B2F394F9697B5A4FC46F8BF2B_200218_3964431_China_s_makeshift_Wuhan_virus_hospitals_aren_t_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China construction, China fast construction, China hospitals, China makeshift, China temporary, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964237</guid>
      <title>China says plasma of recovered patients may help treat COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Could this help?Chinese researchers say blood plasma from recovered patients may help other COVID-19 patients to survive.China National Biotec Group said it is taking plasma taken from recovered COVID-19 patients to treat those who are critically ill. The state-owned pharmaceutical made those remarks in a news release dated Feb. 13.The group claims a round of the treatment improved the patient's condition significantly after 12 to 24 hours, including reduced inflammation and improved blood oxygen levels, lymphocyte counts, and reduced viral load.Citing an unnamed expert, the group states that this plasma contains special antibodies which were used to treat COVID-19 in the critically ill.The group says the procedure was tested successfully in over 10 patients and asserts that it is the best available option for reducing mortality rates. China Daily reports the president of Wuhan's Jinyintan Hospital called for plasma donations on Feb. 13.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964237/3964237_661FC413E76C4664AB571C0EC32DF00A_200217_3964237_China_says_plasma_of_recovered_patients_may_help_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Antibodies, blood plasma, china national biotec group, china, china news, health, science, technology, medicine, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964185</guid>
      <title>Using lasers to communicate with robotic spacecraft, astronauts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  NASA has announced that it is building a new satellite dish as part of the Deep Space Network that would be able to communicate with far away robotic spacecrafts.The dish, named Deep Space Station-23, is expected to be completed in two and a half years.The satellite dish will be 34 meters wide and will use advanced technology, such as lasers, to transmit data to and from space. Deep Space Station-23 will operate as a radio antenna and will also be equipped with mirrors and include a special receiver for laser beams.NASA officials say this technology can be used for communicating with astronauts once they are sent to places like Mars.According to Suzanne Dodd, director of the Interplanetary Network, which manages the Deep Space Network, lasers will be able to transmit roughly 10 times more data than radio antennas from Mars to Earth.NASA currently has deep space networks in Goldstone, California; Madrid, Spain; and Canberra, Australia. This is to allow spacecraft to have continual contact with Earth while our planet rotates.As part of the Artemis program, NASA plans to launch three lunar missions by 2024 which will eventually pave way for astronauts to make their way to Mars and make human exploration of the red planet a reality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 08:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964185/3964185_8262251AB3274ECDAB62BD9BB7ED4254_200217_3964185_Using_lasers_to_communicate_with_robotic_spacecr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[NASA, space, space exploration, NASA mars mission, NASA deep space network, NASA robotic spacecraft, Artemis program, moon mission, artemis 2024, lunar mission, space, astronauts, moon, space mission, artemis mission nasa, artemis nasa, artemis 2, artemis 3, Deep Space Station-23, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964133</guid>
      <title>How the Nevada caucus works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEVADA  After Iowa and New Hampshire comes the third nominating contest for the Democratic presidential contenders in Nevada, the "First of the West."Here's all you need to know about the upcoming Nevada caucus.The Nevada Independent reports that early voting for the Nevada caucus is from February 15 to 18 at over 80 sites.Voters must first check in with volunteers, whose party-purchased iPads are loaded with a PDF voter roll. After filling out a Google form and being given a voter pin, they rank their preferences on a scannable paper ballot, which is then dropped into a ballot boxDuring caucus day on February 22, voters sign in at their local precincts and must then separate into groups based on which candidate they support.Candidates who receive less than 15% of the vite are deemed 'non-viable' and disqualified. Their supporters can either go to a different candidate or remain uncommitted.Instead of the failed Shadow Inc. app used in Iowa, Nevada will use a Google Forms-based caucus calculator on the iPads.According to ABC, this will calculate totals by combining caucus day and early voting data, although precinct chairs will still be required to fill out back-up paper reporting sheets. Should the state deem it necessary to conduct a recount, these sheets will serve as their paper trail.'As required by the DNC, three sets of results will be reported on caucus day: raw votes from the first alignment, raw votes from the final alignment, and county delegate results.A Nevada Democratic Official told ABC that the reporting process will include a two-source verification, with data first reported through 'a secure hotline to a trained operator.' Either the calculator or the reporting sheet will serve as an additional source.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 07:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964133/3964133_A9B305ECB7764903A071CE9BD34235A1_200217_3964133_How_the_Nevada_caucus_works_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Nevada caucus, caucus explained, Nevada caucus explained, Nevada caucus 2020, caucus 2020, how the Nevada caucus works, Nevada caucus explainer, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964077</guid>
      <title>Space engineer makes her own rotary cell phone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A woman in New York invented an insanely awesome old school rotary style cell phone. With all the variedand often times uselessfunctions on today's modern not-so-smartphones, finally a device that won't suck the life out of your day. According to Wired, Justine Haupt works as an astronomy instrumentation engineer at Brookhaven National Laboratory in New York.  On Feb. 12, Haupt posted an article detailing how she made the DIY phone, which became so popular it caused her website to crash. On her website, she details how she took a rotary dial from an old Western Electric Trimline telephone, paired it with a microcontroller and an Adafruit Fona 3G cell transceiver. She then just 3D-printed a casing and was good to go. The phone comes with a 10-LED signal meter, a power switch, quick dial buttons and a curved e-paper screen that displays incoming or missed calls. Along with photos of the whole process, Haupt also shared raw schematics and links to all of the original design files, released as open-source materials, so anyone with the know-how can build their own.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 05:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964077/3964077_81F4FAF0CA404C02828B47CFFE03D6AC_200217_3964077_Space_engineer_makes_her_own_rotary_cell_phone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Rotary cell phone, DIY rotary cell phone, Justine Haupt rotary cell phone, Justine Haupt space engineer, rotary style cell phone, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964038</guid>
      <title>Vessel with Iranian-made weapons onboard seized in Arabian Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARABIAN SEA  The U.S. has seized yet another vessel containing Iranian-made weapons that was apparently bound for Houthi forces in Yemen.The USS Normandy was conducting maritime security operations when it stopped a stateless dhow in the Arabian Sea on Sunday, February 9, according to a statement from the U.S. Central Command.Sailors from the missile cruiser boarded the vessel in accordance with international law.They found and seized weapons onboard including 150 Dehlavieh anti-tank missiles, three surface-to-air missiles, thermal imaging weapon scopes, and components used for unmanned aerial and surface vessels.In a statement, the U.S. Central Command explained that these weapons were deemed to be of Iranian origin. These were seized as they were determined to be for Houthi fighters in Yemen, which would violate a UN Security Council Resolution. The resolution prohibits the sale, supply and or transfer of weapons to these fighters.The weapons are now in U.S. custody waiting for final disposition.The statement, which was released on Thursday, also noted that the seized weapons were "identical" to weapons seized by the USS Forrest Sherman in the Arabian Sea in November.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964038/3964038_6F657B571F4C4DA5A5B33FE697C263B3_200217_3964038_Vessel_with_Iranian_made_weapons_onboard_seized__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[USS Normandy, arabian sea, Iranian-made missiles, iranian dhow, US warship seizes iranian weapons, USS Normandy seizes Iranian weapons at sea, iranian made weapons, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964033</guid>
      <title>New Horizons probe of Arrokoth reveals how planets are formed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  New Horizons' flyby of the most distant object ever visited has revealed the secrets to how planets are formed.MIT Technology Review reports that there have been two theories for planet formation. The first more prominent theory, hierarchical accretion, is when smaller objects collide at high speeds until they form a larger structure.The second theory, called cloud collapse, is when concentrations of matter collapse or gently clump together at low speeds.NASA's New Horizons spacecraft ventured to Kuiper Belt in the outer reaches of our solar system, it conducted a flyby of an ancient planetesimal named Arrokoth.Three studies published in the journal Science analyzed the high-resolution photos of Arrokoth taken by New Horizons  and found no evidence of violent impact, indicating that there was instead a gentle accumulation of matter.Simulations based on the new data suggest that Arrokoth's two parts formed independently from the collapse of the same cloud, and eventually gently merged together.More data collected during the Arrokoth flyby has yet to be downloaded and analyzed – a task which scientists say may take another year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964033/3964033_AD45FB07B5804FEC975F6C5E2CACA2C5_200217_3964033_New_Horizons_probe_of_Arrokoth_reveals_how_plane_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[New Horizons, planet formation, hierarchical accretion, cloud collapse, planet formation theory, Arrokoth, planetesimal, Kuiper belt, space, space exploration, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964022</guid>
      <title>Quarantined North Korean official executed for public bath visit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA   That's some swift justice. A North Korean official has been introduced to the 'land of the not living' for going to a public bath when he was supposed to be under quarantine after coming back from China.The trade official was quarantined under a policy that isolates anyone who has been to China or had contact with Chinese people; the country has taken measures to almost completely shut China off, with flights being reduced and road and rail links either closing or being heavily restricted.North Korea's supreme ruler, Kim Jong-un has vowed to "rule by military law" against anyone who leaves quarantine without approval.According to a South Korean outlet, the trade official was promptly arrested and then immediately dealt with. World Health Organisation officials based in Pyongyang have not confirmed any cases; despite this, some South Korean media outlets have reported multiple cases and even possible deaths in the North.State media report that the country's Red Cross Society has been deployed to monitor people with possible symptoms. North Korea's KCNA report that the Red Cross Society is conducting 'information activities' in public places to introduce common medical knowledge. They say they want to encourage people to "give fuller play to the noble moral traits of helping and leading each other forward."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964022/3964022_1CA06507618D4C0AB5C3FB84CCBBDB38_200217_3964022_Quarantined_North_Korean_official_executed_for_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, North Korea, North Korean official, official public bath, health official, world health organization, North Korea public bath official]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964759</guid>
      <title>SETI will scour the sky for alien signatures with 27 giant scopes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA The SETI Institute says that National Radio Astronomy Observatory will turn the Very Large Array's 27 telescopes to scan for signs of alien life in 75 percent of the night sky, in a Feb. 14 news release announcing the collaboration.According to the institute, the VLA's 25 meter radio telescopes are the most productive in the world. While scientists utilize scopes to study black holes and the formation of the universe, the project will be the first time the VLA is used to look for technosignatures."SETI's contribution will be building and installing a system dubbed COSMIC SETI that establish Ethernet links for VLA telescopes. This system will allow the instruments to scan for alien signatures at all hours of the day.According to the NRAO, COSMIC SETI will allow parallel data processing with VLA's other analytical systems in real time, enhance analytical efficiency and detecting fast radio bursts.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 11:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964759/3964759_79889F38383D48BE89BB59515A5EA1F4_200218_3964759_SETI_will_scour_the_sky_for_alien_signatures_wit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Technosinature, technosignatures, SETI, COSMIC SETI, radiotelescope, radiotelescopes, VLA, Very Large Array, National Radio Astronomy Observatory, NRAO, alien life, intelligent alien life, alien intelligence, signals, signatures, space, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964740</guid>
      <title>YouTuber fakes vacation to Bali with Ikea photoshoot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IKEA  Even influencers need a vacation. It's tough for influencers out there busting their butts to influence as many people as possible with their influencing skills. Which is why YouTube personality Natalia Taylor went on a vacation to Bali and posted the snaps on her Instagram. Or did she? Taylor posted a few pictures on her IG saying that she was in Bali on February 7. But instead of actually going to Bali, she just hopped over to her local Ikea and had herself a photoshoot. According to Fox News, the first set of photos was captioned, "The queen has arrived." Her followers then started leaving the usual IG comments. We'll spare you from those. Then a few days later, Taylor posted a video on YouTube telling everyone how she faked her Bali vacay in a nearly 14 minute-long video. In the video Taylor explains, "It's been said life on the internet isn't always what it seems, especially in today's day and age when it's so easy to pretend to be anyone you want to be." "So many influencers nowadays have actually been caught in the act of pretending to be at a particular destination when they really weren't and it's either Photoshop or it's not even them.""The point of this video is to see if you can fake it 'til you make it." She said it was tough lying to her followers, but that she was happy that she could lift the veil on social media and then warns people not to believe everything they see on the internet. Wowour species really is doomed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 10:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964740/3964740_BD33A9E596D04FA9B6B2B65E26F6BF67_200218_3964740_YouTuber_fakes_vacation_to_Bali_with_Ikea_photos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Natalia Taylor fakes Bali vacation, YouTube fakes Bali vacation, YouTuber Natalia Taylor, Natalia Taylor Ikea vacation, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964718</guid>
      <title>Airbus unveils prototype of futuristic plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LEIDEN, NETHERLANDS   Airbus unveiled a prototype for a new aircraft called MAVERICK at the Singapore Airshow on February 11.MAVERICK is an acronym for Model Aircraft for Validation and Experimentation of Robust Innovative Controls.The prototype is two meters long and 3.2 meters wide, according to a press release from the company. Airbus has yet to unveil the dimensions of a full-sized MAVERICK.The company states in the press release that MAVERICK will have a "blended wing body design," which would allow the aircraft to potentially burn up to 20 percent less fuel in comparison to traditional planes. The press release explained that MAVERICK will also have a shielded engine above its central body that will reduce aircraft noise significantly.Its design would also allow the plane to utilize different types of propulsion systems, though Airbus has yet to specify what these might be.Airbus explained the unique design will allow the aircraft to have a wide cabin layout, which would provide passengers with extra legroom and larger aisles.According to WIRED, the aircraft may accommodate fewer window seats than traditional airplanes due to its design, though this may lead to more creative seating arrangements than what are usually present in traditional planes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964718/3964718_318A8CF1F7F94D3BB967DCBDE9D35B92_200218_3964718_Airbus_unveils_prototype_of_futuristic_plane_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Airbus, airbus prototype, airbus maverick, maverick, new airbus maverick, airbus next generation plane, airbus blended wing body, airbus maverick model, prototype flying wing, airbus flying wing, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964499</guid>
      <title>Big Chinese developer slashes prices in Feb, March due to virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  One of mighty China's biggest developers is offering massive sales around the country on all of its properties in February and March. Reuters reports that China Evergrande Groupthe third-largest builder by sales in the countryannounced that they were offering a 25 percent discount for the rest of February.According to Reuters, the discount will then go down to 22 percent for the month of March. The SCMP reports that the scale and amount they're slashing prices makes this a much larger campaign than Evergrande carried out last year. According to Evergrande's latest annual report, the company currently has 811 projects on sale. According to the SCMP, the company is trying to get a hold of some cash to help ease their finance crunch as home sales plunge across lovely China. Citing the China Real Estate Information Corporation, the SCMP said more than 110 cities in 12 provinces have told developers to shut down property sales offices. Many developers are getting hammered by tanking home sales, shrinking cash flow and a ton of loan repayments piling up. Reuters reports that an Evergrande official, who declined to be named because he or she isn't allowed to talk to the media, said the measures, "are routine marketing and there is  no specific reason for the price cut this time."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 04:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964499/3964499_BC30B13D895A4ADF95CF4B3D8F744A7A_200218_3964499_Big_Chinese_developer_slashes_prices_in_Feb__Mar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, China developer, China Evergrande Group, China Evergrande Group sale, China Evergrande cuts prices, home sales, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964441</guid>
      <title>China implements new restrictions in Hubei province</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  Beijing has now tightened restrictions across Hubei province amid the growing threat of the Wuhan virus.Residents of Hubei province have been ordered to stay at home and aren't allowed to leave unless there is an emergency, BBC News reports. The government will allow one person from each household to leave their house once every three days in order to purchase food and other essential products.Only one entrance will be kept open in residential buildings. The buildings will be guarded and only those residing in the building will be allowed to enter or leave.Pharmacies, hotels, grocery stores and medical services will be open while other businesses in Hubei province will remain closed.China has also banned the use of private cars on the streets of Hubei, though delivery vehicles carrying essential goods will be exempt from the ban.Separately, the New York Times reports, Beijing has now ordered everyone returning to the capital city to quarantine themselves for 14 days in an attempt to contain the novel coronavirus.According to CNN, the virus has already killed 1,775 people and has infected more than 71,000 people globally. 70,548 of these cases are in China. Outside of China, only five deaths have been reported: one in Hong Kong, Taiwan, Japan, the Philippines and France.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 01:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964441/3964441_2527D2190D9D457AB7020E26B22BD179_200218_3964441_China_implements_new_restrictions_in_Hubei_provi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, china virus, china virus 2020, china news, china virus spreads, wuhan virus, china hubei, china hubei lockdown, china hubei restrictions, china tightens restrictions on hubei, china coronavirus, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964434</guid>
      <title>Chinese netizens compete in 'earphone wire waist' challenge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Chinese netizens have taken to wrapping their abs in earphone wires to demonstrate their fitness in an all-new bizarre internet trend. The challenge comes as people are forced to isolate themselves during quarantine over fears of COVID-19; netizens have taken to the trend to deal with being cooped up. The hashtag for the new internet craze has wrapped up some 76million views and plenty of submissions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964434/3964434_B990F1E11F764004B0B232397C6F8B98_200218_3964434_Chinese_netizens_compete_in__earphone_wire_waist_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Headphone wire waist, headphone waist, Chinese headphone waist, Chinese trend, Chinese wire waist trend, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965339</guid>
      <title>U.S. designates China's fake news media as government operatives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. State Department on Tuesday designated five Chinese fake news media outlets as official government entities under the Foreign Missions Act, which means they will be treated as diplomatic outposts of the Chinese government and subject to the same constraints.In plain English, the U.S. is calling Xinhua News Agency, CGTN, China Radio International, China Daily and Hai Tian Developmenta U.S. company linked to the People's Dailywhat they actually are, STATE-SPONSORED-PROPAGANDA.The failing New York Times reports that the move is the latest by the Trump Administration to counter Beijing's influence and intelligence operations in America. According to the Times, in the past month alone, prosecutors have brought cases against Chinese spy operations involving scientific research at Harvard and the 2017 hacking of Equifax. The U.S. has also charged Huawei and two of its subsidiaries with federal racketeering and conspiracy to steal trade secrets. U.S. State Department officials said the new designation would not impede the five Chinese fake news outlets from reporting, broadcasting or carrying journalistic activities. The officials said the 5 Chinese puppet organizations will be required to provide names, personal details and turnover of staff to the State Department. They would also need to report if they own or lease property in the U.S. According to the Washington Post, the U.S. decision was likely more symbolic than punitive, but either way, it's a move in the right direction.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965339/3965339_DAD5A3FD86D246CB9FB39DAB7C53ACB2_200219_3965339_U_S__designates_China_s_fake_news_media_as_gover_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[US designates China media operatives, US China media foreign operatives, Xinhua News Agency, CGTV, China Daily, People's Daily, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965277</guid>
      <title>Why January 2020 was the warmest in history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO  The past month was the hottest January in weather history, according to the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.Citing climate researchers, NBC reports that a jet stream trapping cold air over the Arctic might be responsible for the warm January." NOAA data shows that the US and Hawaii region, Russia, Europe, South America and Australia experienced abnormally hot weather in January. Meanwhile, sea ice has retreated in the Arctics and Antarctica.Citing the National Ice and Snow Data Center, NBC reports the jet stream over the Arctic is called the Arctic Oscillation. The jet stream is wavy during a negative phase of this. This allows cool air to go south, taking cold temperatures and rains with it.Citing the center's director Mark Serreze[d], NBC reports the AO is having a positive phase with a flat jetstream circle, which entraps the cold air over the Arctic region. Serrez says this weather phenomenon is possibly the cause of the high temperatures.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 12:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965277/3965277_5C13A5B51B644EDA95EFD861DDB712BB_200219_3965277_Why_January_2020_was_the_warmest_in_history_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Arctic, jet stream, flat jet stream, wavy jet stream, arctic oscillation, January 2020, hottest January, warm winter, National Ice and Snow Data Center, National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, U.S., TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965179</guid>
      <title>The Sun's violent death will destroy the asteroid belt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Billions of years from now, the Sun will exhaust its hydrogen fuel and enter what astronomers call the 'giant branch' phase. The Sun will grow bigger by hundreds of times, while its luminance and radiation output increase by thousands of times.Writing in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, researchers say this energy will heat up the asteroid belt and cause the asteroids to spin faster and faster until they are torn to pieces, which will happen in six billion years.Since most big asteroids are a loose collection of rocks called rubble piles, they are susceptible to this heat induced spinning, or the YORP effect. Most asteroids will be reduced until they become small homogeneous fragments.The scientists' model predicts that the Sun will collapse into a white dwarf and absorb the smashed asteroids, which pollutes the star and changes its spectra. This would explain why many white dwarfs' spectra suggest the dead stars contain asteroid elements.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 09:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965179/3965179_5049240393764684BF39E5E86F73DFB5_200219_3965179_The_Sun_s_violent_death_will_destroy_the_asteroi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Sun, death, asteroid belt, yorp, yorp effect, giant branch, white dwarf, white dwarf star, rubble piles, monthly notices of the royal astronomical society, university of warwick, science, space, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965073</guid>
      <title>Iran-backed Hackers target VPN servers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN  A new report by cyber security firm ClearSky has found that hackers backed by the Iranian government have been exploiting bugs in corporate VPN servers.Over the past three years this campaign has targeted numerous companies around the world ranging from the IT sector to the oil and gas, aviation, government and security sectors. In some cases, the hackers were able to exploit vulnerabilities in a short period of time.The hackers developed and used infrastructure that would allow them to control and access their targets in the long-term, according to the report. They were able to use this technique to steal valuable information from targeted companies.Researchers said that this could also be used to spread malware such as ZeroCleare and Dustman. Both of these malware are designed to delete as much data from hacked devices as possible, according to ZDNet. ZDNet points out that the report 'dispels the notion' that Iranian cyber hackers aren't as sophisticated as hackers in Russia, China or North Korea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965073/3965073_8AFABEF28ED8437B8655F5BE3BB73D02_200219_3965073_Iran_backed_Hackers_target_VPN_servers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Hackers, iranian hackers, VPN servers, VPN servers hacked, iran hacking VPN servers, iran hacking campaign, iranian APT groups, iran breaching VPN servers, iranian cyber hack, iran cyber breach, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965039</guid>
      <title>SpaceX launches another 60 Starlink satellites to orbit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA  SpaceX successfully launched another batch of 60 Starlink satellites with a Falcon 9 rocket. Space.com reports that the mission lifted off at an airbase in Florida at 10:05 a.m. on Friday.According to SpaceX, Falcon 9 is a reusable first stage booster with nine Merlin 1D engines that put out more thrust than five Boeing 747s at full power. The payload of 60 small satellites rides atop the rocket into orbit.According to SpaceX, Starlinks are telecom satellites that feature ion thrusters for maneuvering into position and articulated solar arrays. Space.com reports the latest launch brought the Starlink constellation up to nearly 300 satellites.The launch marked the fourth time the company used a booster four times. This rocket's earlier missions include a satellite launch and two runs to replenish the International Space Station last year.However, the rocket apparently missed the drone ship Of Course I Still Love You and made a soft landing in the seas near the robotic vessel. Space.com reports that the company is hopeful that the rocket can still be retrieved, citing SpaceX.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965039/3965039_21E9E3E4AB294A9A94B23D15CDC5214D_200219_3965039_SpaceX_launches_another_60_Starlink_satellites_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[SpaceX, falcon 9, reusable rocket, falcon 9, rocket, first stage, dragon, starlink, satellite, satellites, constellation, megaconstellation, drone ship, elon musk, space, science, technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965002</guid>
      <title>China deploys remote tanks and drones in the fight against virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE MIDDLE COUNTRY  Technology is being called up to duty as you-know-where continues to deal with its little situation.According to Pear Video, officials in the Shanxi city of Taiyuan have dispatched a couple of remote controlled mini tanks to spray a bunch of disinfectant in the streetswhich apparently keeps the road from catching a case of the sniffles. Community workers say the mini tanks had originally been used to spray pesticides in the orchards before they got the repurposing call.Sure, the tiny tanks can roll around down the streets, but they can also climb up onto the sidewalk and make sure the walkways also stay in good health. Each tank can carry 400 liters of disinfectant spray. Officials say the little guys can cover a lot more of the city than just hoofing it. Here's the thing. It probably makes a lot more sense to be disinfecting inside homes and apartments, rather than outside. But then of course, you don't get the nice photo op to show the people you're doing everything you possibly can to keep them safe.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 04:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965002/3965002_C72AFEA1B0C1409B8F679630239CA8DB_200219_3965002_China_deploys_remote_tanks_and_drones_in_the_fig_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Remote mini, mini tanks, mini tanks disinfectant, mini, tiny, health, Pear Video, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964946</guid>
      <title>Uighurs detained for beards, veils and internet browsing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A leaked document that details the lives of thousands of Muslims currently detained in so-called 're-education' camps across China is just another example of how Beijing is punishing Uighurs for their religious beliefs. A 137-page PDF file was allegedly leaked by a source inside Xinjiang. According to CNN, the document included information of more than 3000 individuals and listed details such as how often they pray, how they dress, whom they engage with and even how their own family members behave. CNN sent a copy of the document to both the Chinese Ministry of Foreign Affairs and the local government in Xinjiang to see if either could verify its authenticity, however, neither responded. The Chinese Foreign Minister, Wang Yi said that these  "concentration camps" are "fake news" and that he would gladly welcome any "international diplomat or media" to visit Xinjiang for themselves and see how harmoniously everyone lives together.CNN attempted to visit the detention centers in Xinjiang but was blocked by the local government. What other information can be found on these documents?One row listed the case of a 38-year-old woman who was sent to one of these camps for one main reason, she was known to have worn a veil some years ago. In another, a 28-year-old man was incarcerated for, "clicking on a web-link and unintentionally landing on a foreign website."One man's father is shown to have been sentenced to five years for "having a double-colored thick beard and organizing a religious studies group." The BBC details how a series of rows were dedicated to a 65-year-old man. His records show that his two daughters "wore veils and burkas in 2014 and 2015." He even had a verdict,  "continued training." Do we trust the document? One of the world's leading experts on China's policies in Xinjiang, Dr. Adrian Zenz, believes, yes we can."This remarkable document presents the strongest evidence I've seen to date that Beijing is actively persecuting and punishing normal practices of traditional religious beliefs." The BBC claim that much of the evidence they uncovered during a tour of one of these camps last year is, in fact, corroborated by this new document. What is the biggest justification for a person's internment?In the eyes of communist China, having too many children is the clearest sign that Uighurs put their traditions above their absolute obedience to the Chinese state.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 02:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3964946/3964946_0B63900557044EA79C0F2E3A19317FC7_200219_3964946_Uighurs_detained_for_beards__veils_and_internet__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Uighurs, China Uighurs, Chinese Muslims, re-education camps, Xinjiang camps, Xinjiang people]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964939</guid>
      <title>Tourist takes risky shot on the edge of Rio cliff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIO DE JANEIRO  How far would you go for the perfect Instagram shot?A video taken last November 2019 in Brazil is giving people the heebie jeebies after it showed a female tourist posing on the edge of a cliff – perilously close to a 3,000-foot drop.The nerve-wracking display was taken atop Rio de Janeiro's Pedra de Gavea mountain, which the unnamed woman had to take a demanding two-and-a-half-hour hike to get to.She managed to get to the top of what the Brazilian Tourist Board calls the world's largest coastline monolith, which is a victory in and of itself. But you know what they say – photo or it didn't happen.The woman did one better by having herself filmed as she shuffled her bum closer to the edge of the rock. The dude taking the video gets her to move forward even more, and the foolishly fearless lady complies, before posing with both arms raised. It's a cool shot for sure, but one wrong move and off the cliff you go. Fortunately, and shockingly, the woman didn't fall off, and came away from the whole experience completely unscathed.The internet reacted as it does, criticizing the lady for risking her life and the lives of people on the ground below, who could've been seriously hurt had she fallen.But it's not like she's the first one to do this. Search Pedra de Gavea on social media and you'll see a whole lotta folks risking life and limb to do exactly what this woman did.That's just how the cookie crumbles in this Instagram-obsessed world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 02:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3964939/3964939_0BB7B064055B48E5BCB212CA0CC1E79B_200219_3964939_Tourist_takes_risky_shot_on_the_edge_of_Rio_clif_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Risky tourist shot, risky instagram shot, Pedra de Gavea, instagram shot, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964932</guid>
      <title>Chinese farmer uses chickens to write out message of support</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GANSU PROVINCE, CHINA  A farmer in China used his chickens to send out a message of support for the fight against you-know-what.Shang Yukang is relatively famous on the Chinese web, having turned into an internet star after showcasing his daily life as a chicken farmer in rural Gansu province. He's also known for making his chickens come together to form various characters and patterns, such as this cute display of "I love you."Shang's latest video saw him using over a thousand of his feathery buddies to spell out "Zhong guo" – China – and "jiayou", which literally means "add oil" but is used as an expression of support or encouragement. Shang told pear video he didn't have enough chickens to spell out all the characters at the same time, so he did "China" one day, and "jiayou" the next day.As we all know, China is going through rough times these days with the-thing-Youtube-doesn't-want-named wreaking havoc all over, so this was Shang's way of cheering people on.He has also very generously donated over 3,000 eggs from his own farm to medical workers on the front line.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 02:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3964932/3964932_CAA90648CA164A54B0B2CE211A0EB3BC_200219_3964932_Chinese_farmer_uses_chickens_to_write_out_messag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chicken farmer, chickens, China, message of support, Chinese chickens, egg donation, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965911</guid>
      <title>India builds wall to hide poor people during Trump visit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AHMEDABAD, INDIA  Ahead of President Donald Trump's visit to India next week, Indian authorities decided to build a wall to welcome the big American cheese. No just kidding. They built it to hide a bunch of poor people and slums, so Trump won't have to look at it when his motorcade wizzes by it during his visit. Oh, how thoughtful of Prime Minister Narendra Modi.The Associated Press reports that a half-kilometer (1,640-foot) brick wall was thrown up in an awful hurry in India's Gurjurat state.According to the AP, Trump plans to hop over to Ahmedabad in Gujarat during a two-day India trip to attend an event called "Namaste Trump," which translates to "Greetings Trump" at a cricket stadium.  Trump and his motorcade accompanied by Modi are planned to drive along a road next to the slum.  Apparently, the wall was originally supposed to be 6 or 7 feet tall, but was chopped down to 4 feet after the government got blasted in public after widespread media coverage. Senior government official Bijal Patel told AP that the wall was built "for security reasons" and not to hide the slum. She also said, "apart from security reasons, the wall is also part of a beautification and cleanliness drive."   Here's the most important question though. Is Mexico going to pay for this wall too?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 23:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965911/3965911_39EC2B642E46453097F0352ADCED7FBC_200221_3965911_India_builds_wall_to_hide_poor_people_during_Tru_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Trump India visit, India builds wall Trump, India builds wall Trump visit, India builds wall to hide slum, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965800</guid>
      <title>Utah Senate supports bill decriminalizing polygamy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY  Something is rotten in the state of Utah. Utah's state Senate has actually voted unanimously to decriminalize polygamy amoung consenting adults. The BBC reports that under current laws, anyone found to have multiple spouses could face up to five years in the slammer. Supporters of the billso all 29 Utah Senate memberssay the bill would remove the secrecy surrounding the morons, sorry Mormons, who feel the more the merrier and would also allow victims to report abuse.According to the Beebs, the bill still needs to be approved by the states House of Representatives. The new proposal would mean that if you're really dumb enough to want more than one spouse, it would be considered a misdemenour, similar to a traffic violation. More serious crimes, such as forced or coerced bigamy, would be treated as a felony. According to the Associated Press, about 30,000 people in Utah live in polygamous communities. Utah is home to the Church of Jesus Freaks of Later-day Suckers, also known as the Mormon Church. If your Mormon history is a bit hazy, check out the South Park documentaries to get you up to speed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 13:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965800/3965800_90B82C62B27C4B2FBEA5841E071E5929_200220_3965800_Utah_Senate_supports_bill_decriminalizing_polyga_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Utah Senate polygamy, Utah Senate decriminalizing polygamy, Utah Mormons, Church of Mormon, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965744</guid>
      <title>Get ready for 3D printed chocolates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZURICH  Barry Callebaut, a Swiss-based chocolate manufacturer, has announced that it will start producing 3D printed chocolate at scale in its new studio called Mona Lisa.The 3D printing studio will be able to create personalized chocolates for customers, according to a news release from the company. Clients can choose which design, shape and size they want for their chocolate.Once a design has been chosen, studio designers will then make a digital 3D prototype of the chocolate. The news release explained that the technology is capable of printing thousands of chocolate pieces at a time while retaining a "hand-made appearance."The service could be used for desserts, confectionery or pastries.The company says that the service will be available to chefs, hotels, coffee chains and restaurants in select European countries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965744/3965744_329CFCEE10F043E2B15AD7DC1EEDB2C8_200220_3965744_Get_ready_for_3D_printed_chocolates_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chocolate, 3D-printed chocolate, Barry Callebaut, 3D-printed chocolate Barry Callebaut, 3D printing, Swiss chocolatier, Swiss chocolatier 3D printing, 3D printing food, printing chocolate, chocolate printing machine, 3D chocolate, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965707</guid>
      <title>Coral reefs may lose nearly all habitats by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO  A new study presented to the American Geophysicists Union says that global warming and rising acidity will kill off nearly all coral reef habitats by 2100.Warming and rising acidity bleach coral reefs by making corals eject their symbiotic algae.Scientists expect 70 percent to 90 percent of coral reefs to disappear in the next 20 years. While some groups are trying to regrow bleached corals with transplants, the study's model shows that almost none of these projects will remain viable in 2100.The study shows that small portions of Baja California and the Red Sea will be some of the last viable sites for growing reefs in 2020, but these locations are too close to rivers to be ideal habits.Researchers say climate warming and rising acidity are the main culprits for shrinking coral habitats because plastic pollution is so extensive that there are few places left for plastics to affect.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965707/3965707_445C69BA53A847CB9CF8E672E2A6FFD2_200220_3965707_Coral_reefs_may_lose_nearly_all_habitats_by_2020_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Coral, coral reefs, habitats, habitat, habitat loss, climate change, climate warming, climate, warming, acidity, ocean, coral bleaching, coral restoration, coral transplant, coral transplants, environment, science, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965690</guid>
      <title>MasterCard makes biometrics push for public transit users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARRISON, NEW YORK  Market Watch reports CCTV and gait analysis may come to US public transit to allow commuters to pay without using cards or passes, citing MasterCard officials working on biometric technologies with transport firms.Speaking to the outlet, MasterCard's cyber solutions president Ajay Bhalla said facial features and gait could be linked to databases for cardless payment. Those methods are less vulnerable to hacking than password authenticated accounts.MasterCard is also exploring other biometric solutions, such as using wrist bands to identify a commuter's unique heartbeat patterns, EEG, and veins on the surface of their skin to authenticate payments.Bhalla is cited as saying the way a person holds a phone, which ear they use and the manner their fingers touch buttons on their devices are all potentially useful methods for authentication.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965690/3965690_23CC845E05694392936864B6B5B67722_200220_3965690_MasterCard_makes_biometrics_push_for_public_tran_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mastercard, biometrics, public transit, bus, subway, payment, authentication, identification, commuters, commuter, gait, facial recognition, EEG, heartbeat, vein, science, technology, U.S., TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965487</guid>
      <title>Chinese authorities humiliating people for not wearing masks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Where's your mask? As China's government desperately scrambles to show the world they can manage this new threat, local police forces are implementing some ruthless and quite frankly archaic orders from Beijing.Shocking videos have emerged that show local authorities within China humiliating people for not wearing face masks.  In response to these videos, the editor-in-chief of China's Global Times offered a some-what audacious response by claiming the videos, "gave the public a very bad impression" and meant the "personal rights of citizens… have been severely violated."While the Chinese government is attempting to suppress negative coverage of its response to the threat, the masses of content flooding the internet of videos like these can not be stopped. China's control of the narrative is slipping.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 04:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965487/3965487_BA2F4E7CF42B4A45A0457B12EAEDAE3B_200220_3965487_Chinese_authorities_humiliating_people_for_not_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Chinese authorities humiliate, face masks, China, Beijing, Chinese police videos, humiliation, Chinese viral videos, weibo videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965460</guid>
      <title>Largest Chinese COVID-19 study shows elderly, sick most at risk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  Chinese authorities have published a study of COVID-19 patients across China – the largest one done on the disease so far.According to data released by the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention, 80.9 percent of COVID-19 cases have been mild, with patients exhibiting only mild pneumonia or none at all.Thirteen point eight percent of infections were classified as severe, and 4.7 percent as critical, with the sick and elderly found to be most at risk.The study also pointed out the high risk the outbreak presented to medical workers, 1,716 of whom have been diagnosed with the disease.While men are more likely than women to get infected, children and teens aged 0 to 19 are not as affected, making up just 2 percent of those who contracted COVID-19.Of the 44,672 confirmed cases used in the study, 1,023 had died as of February 11, which puts the crude death rate for the virus at 2.3 percent.Hubei province was found to have a much higher rate at 2.9 percent, compared to 0.4 percent for the rest of China.Patients with cardiovascular disease were found most likely to die of complications from the virus, followed by those suffering from diabetes, chronic respiratory disease, and hypertension.The report finds that the epidemic peaked in January, and that a 'downward trend' in the overall epidemic curve since February 11 suggests China's aggressive containment measures have paid off.It's important to remember though, that the CDC is a Chinese government entity, and that with people returning home from their long holidays, there may be a possible rebound of the epidemic.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 02:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965460/3965460_8AAA2E1B53C94684B2F6423811496A88_200220_3965460_Largest_Chinese_COVID_19_study_shows_elderly__si_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[COVID 19, coronavirus, China CDC, China CDC study, patients at risk, COVID-19 fatality rate, Coronavirus statistics, COVID-19 statistics, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965456</guid>
      <title>Russian lieutenant proposes to girlfriend with 16-tank display</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  A platoon commander in Russia decided to propose to his girlfriend in a most unusual way – with the help of military tanks. According to RT, Lieutenant Denis Kazantsev got permission from his commanders to carry out his big proposal at the Alabino testing grounds southwest of Moscow.On the morning of February 13, 16 T-72B2 tanks rolled onto the range and proceeded to maneuver around until they lined up in a heart formation.23-year-old Kazantsev can be seen leading girlfriend Alexandra Kopytova to the middle of the heart, making sure to keep her eyes all covered. Lover Boy then gets down on one knee and pops the question while holding out some flowers and a shiny ring.Unsurprisingly, Kopytova said yes. It'd be awkward if she said no, because as it turns out, she and Kazantsev have already been married for a year.He told Metro News that his first proposal was in December 2017. But seeing as how they lived in different cities then, it probably wasn't THAT romantic and needed a round 2.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 02:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965456/3965456_ECFF854FF33D429BA76568BB115B50AC_200220_3965456_Russian_lieutenant_proposes_to_girlfriend_with_1_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Russian tank proposal, Russian lieutenant proposal, Romantic tank proposal, romantic proposal, marriage proposal, Valentine's day proposal, vday proposal, military tank proposal, tanks forming heart, 16 military tanks, Russian defence ministry, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966460</guid>
      <title>Far-right extremist kills 9 in Germany shisha bar shootings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANAU, GERMANY A gunman in Germany opened fire on two shisha bars in what police suspect is a racially-motivated attack.The BBC reports that around 10 p.m. Wednesday, a 43-year-old man began shooting inside the Midnight shisha bar in the city center of Hanau in Germany. He then fled by car to the Kesselstadt neighborhood about 2.5 kilometers away, and continued his attack at another shisha bar, called Arena Bar and Cafe. According to CNN, nine people were killed in the attacks, with both German and Turkish nationals being among the victims. Six others suffered injuries.The BBC reports that following the shootings, police carried out an hours-long manhunt that lasted through the night.According to the Guardian, special police force officers stormed the suspect's home at 5 a.m. local time and found the suspect dead along with another body. Police say the gunman, later identified as Tobias Rathjen. had shot his 72-year-old mother and then himself.The Bild newspaper reported that the suspect left a letter of confession, in which he expressed "extreme right wing views. He also put up a video explaining his motives, but it has since been taken down from social media sites.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/22/3966460/3966460_8C9D551656274DE0B53FB0432BC2686C_200222_3966460_Far_right_extremist_kills_9_in_Germany_shisha_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Germany shooting, Germany attack, Germany far right, Germany far right shooting, far right shooting, Germany terrorism, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966455</guid>
      <title>Cop couple on date night foil armed robber</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOUISVILLE, KENTUCKY  Of all the fast-food joints in all of Kentucky, one supremely unlucky criminal had to try and rob the one with the off-duty cops in it.According to WHAS11, the incident occurred at a Raising Cane's Chicken Fingers store in Louisville around 10 p.m. on February 15.Married Elizabethtown officers Nicole McKeown and Detective Chase McKeown were inside for date night when a masked suspect sauntered in.According to the Louisville Metro Police Department, the perp, later identified as Justin Carter, flashed his gun at an employee and demanded cash.The McKeown were seated at the very back of the store, but it didn't take long for them to figure out what was happening.Slowly, they get up from their sears and draw their weapons, splitting up as they beeline toward the suspect.When Carter sees the armed pair, he drops his weapon and runs outta there.The officers follow after him, eventually detaining him about a block later.WHAS11 reports that Carter has been charged with possession of a handgun by a convicted felon, receiving stolen property, and robbery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/22/3966455/3966455_A48552A240354D85A9D4414A0E1DD985_200222_3966455_Cop_couple_on_date_night_foil_armed_robber_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Attempted robbery, robbery fail, off duty cops, date night adventure, date night bust, robber foiled, armed robber foiled, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966318</guid>
      <title>Google just removed 500 Chrome extensions containing malware</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  Google has removed hundreds of extensions for their internet browser Chrome after they were found to have malware.A joint investigation by cyber security firm Duo Security, and Jamila Kaya, an independent security researcher, has identified roughly 70 chrome extensions that contained malicious codes. The researchers notified Google after which the tech giant conducted its own analysis and found more than 500 chrome extensions that were infected with malware.According to the report, the chrome extensions would inject malicious advertisements while users are browsing a website or lead users to specific websites such as Macys, Dell, or BestBuy.In some cases, the extension would take users to a phishing page or a malware download site.Researchers said that if users weren't regularly checking their chrome extensions, the plugins were able to collect extensive data and generate revenue through the user's device.Google has since removed the malicious chrome extensions and deactivated them for users who had installed the extensions on their browser, according to ZDNet. The website reports that Google also marked these extensions as "malicious",  so users would know to not reactivate them and to get rid of them from their browser.Google did not mention how many people had been affected by the breach.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 12:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3966318/3966318_0BBAD57DF9464AB49B4DCC4E9A9A5FF6_200221_3966318_Google_just_removed_500_Chrome_extensions_contai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Google, google chrome extensions, google chrome extensions malicious, malware chrome extensions, malicious extensions online, Duo Security, google security TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966249</guid>
      <title>Scientists say they may figure out why the universe exists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA  Scientists may have figured out  why matter outnumbers antimatter in our universe. According to the researchers, had the two substances been created in equal amounts, they would have annihilated one another and the universe would not have existed.In a study published in Physical Review Letters, researchers say that after the big bang, the early universe must have gone through a phase that allowed neutrinos to create more matter than antimatter. This period would also have created the cosmic strings.Citing the authors, Live Science reports that cosmic strings are thin bands of energy that still thread through the universe and that the strings' formation in the early cosmos can be proven by the ripples in space time they created.Although the ripples are faint, the research team says that if their models are correct, future instruments such as NASA's future Laser Interferometer Space Antenna will be able to detect the ripples and confirm their theory.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 10:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3966249/3966249_E258BE4141084AC0A49E259AF0BFC49A_200221_3966249_Scientists_say_they_may_figure_out_why_the_unive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Big bang, cosmic strings, cosmic string, space time, space time ripples, matter, antimatter, laser interference space antenna, LISA, NASA, universe, science, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966204</guid>
      <title>China created youth anime influencers, then deleted them</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE BEST COUNTRY  With everything on the up and up in the fantastic Middle Kingdom, the Communist Youth League decided to introduce a pair of patriotic anime mascots on Feb. 17. According to the failing New York Times, the youth wing unveiled the two new anime influencers, but then got so pathetically hammered and criticized online that they quickly deleted them out of existence. The Times reports that the new, super short-lived avatars were styled like Japanese anime characters and were named Hong Qi Man and Jiang Shan Jiao, names derived from fun-loving dictator Mao's poetry.Apparently Jiang Shan Jiao, whose name translates into "lovable country," and her younger brother Hong Qiman, aka "fluttering flag," were meant to encourage patriotism among younger Chinese. After introducing the tag team on Twitter's ugly cousin Weibo, netizens immediately started criticizing the pair. Reuters reports that a lot of the negative comments were getting thousands of "likes," so they had to be removed by censors during the day on the 17th. By the end of the day, the post with the avatars was given the old Beijing bye-bye. Well, better luck next time guys.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 09:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3966204/3966204_1B7395B96A3F42FDA5A242335ACD6FA0_200221_3966204_China_created_youth_anime_influencers__then_dele_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Communist Youth League China, anime influencer, anime youth idols, anime idols, China creates anime idols, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965988</guid>
      <title>Police force mahjong players to carry table down the street</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE BEST COUNTRY  So what do you do when you're stuck in your house for a couple of weeks with nothing to do in the greatest country on earth? You play mahjong of course. The only problem is, getting caught by the authorities means some good old fashioned Cultural Revolution style public shaming. Footage from Twitter's illegitimate cousin Weibo shows four people from the town of Hexin in Chongqing prefecture having a pleasant stroll down the middle of the street. Oh yeah, they're also lugging a mahjong table over their shoulders while being followed by a police car. And to get everyone pumped up and in the proper mood, an officer is kind enough to hope on the loudspeaker and scream super annoyingly that playing mahjong and cards is a no no. Naturally people were thrilled when the footage was leaked online, so a local government worker had to explain that it was not an example of "parading through the streets" but of "disciplinary action"  by parading them through the streets. The fun police have actually cracked down on mahjong all over the country amid their latest struggles. Will it work? Wouldn't bet on it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 04:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965988/3965988_395F3A51EA3C42628F66C0EC75487593_200221_3965988_Police_force_mahjong_players_to_carry_table_down_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mahjong, mahjong table, playing mahjong, carrying mahjong table, mahjong players, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965944</guid>
      <title>Queen blocks Harry and Meghan using brand 'royal'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM / CANADA   The Duke and Duchess of Sussex, Harry, and Meghan have been told they won't be allowed to use the 'Sussex Royal' label after quitting the royals.Harry and Meghan spent tens of thousands of pounds building a website that was based on the brand which started from their Instagram account which boasts 11.2 million followers.The couple has also registered 'Sussex Royal' as a trademark internationally on items including clothing, stationery, books, and teaching materials.However, The Queen has claimed that the two should no longer be using the term 'royal' if they no longer carry out royal duties. A royal source has since stated that the future use of the term 'royal' by the abdicated couple "needed to be reviewed."Harry and Meghan first used the 'Sussex Royal' name when they created their own household with the intention of being financially independent; however, now they may now have to re-name their website and start again from scratch.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965944/3965944_5E3A3017BF90474B9B3FFBB8827C2B0D_200221_3965944_Queen_blocks_Harry_and_Meghan_using_brand__royal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Prince Harry, Meghan Markle, Harry and Meghan, Duchess of Sussex, Royals, Royal family, Sussex Royal, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965940</guid>
      <title>Shanghai lady breaks quarantine, nabbed for boozy behavior</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  A woman in Shanghai got herself in a whole lot of trouble after not only breaking quarantine, but also getting into a boozy fight with some security guards.According to a Miaopai video, the lady had been under self-isolation in her Shanghai apartment, and sneaked out one night for a drink...or seven.She came back totally sloshed and sans face mask, and began to get into a skirmish with the neighborhood guards over getting her temperature checked. In footage of the incident, the lady is seen being loud and aggressive, and ends up pushing one of the guards, who was REALLY not happy with her.Cops were called to the scene, and the unruly woman was arrested and hauled off.The best part is that once she got her bearings back, she realized she'd been trying to get into the wrong 'hood.Shoulda stayed home, lady.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965940/3965940_708D2C6096274079A7EAEC8977F5FEFD_200221_3965940_Shanghai_lady_breaks_quarantine__nabbed_for_booz_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Shanghai, Shanghai woman, China, Shanghai isolation, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965937</guid>
      <title>Plane passengers spotted traveling in full-body plastic suits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  With the C thing infecting people all across the world, folks these days have taken to sporting protective gear to keep it at bay. For most, that means donning a face mask, maybe even gloves if you're a bit more paranoid. But these two people took it up several notches when they decided to get on a plane while in a mask, latex gloves, AND fully covered in plastic.Who needs a hazmat suit, amirite?Twitter user Alyssa423 had spotted the pair on her flight, which according to the Dailymail, was going from Sydney to Hamilton island. She shared a video clip of the duo on the platform, which has since racked over 90,000 views.Twitter users had mixed reactions to the full-body plastic suit: some were impressed at the lengths to which the pair were willing to go and could totally relate. But a lot of folks thought it was a dumb idea, since not only was it a suffocation hazard, but such extra precautionary measures may not be all that effective anyway.But hey, whatever gives you peace of mind.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965937/3965937_EC6C31C2AD034CB080A5249607602271_200221_3965937_Plane_passengers_spotted_traveling_in_full_body__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Virus protection, makeshift hazmat suits, plastic suits, full body plastic, plane passengers, nervous flyers, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967425</guid>
      <title>Earth formed a whole lot fast than previously thought: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK  Scientists say the early Solar System's cosmic dust gave rise to primitive Earth over just five million years. If the Solar System's existence is compressed into 24 hours, then the proto-Earth's creation did not take more than a minute.According to the study published in Science Advances, the research team found that a type of meteorites known as CI chondrites are the closest iron isotope match to our planet and the bulk composition of the solar system itself.In a news release, the University of Copenhagen says that the Sun once possessed an accretion disk. After the young star cooled, the CI dust in the disk was allowed to settle on proto-Earth.The university says the process would not be not possible unless the earlier iron had already migrated into the proto-Earth's nascent core. That our planet's composition is similar to only one meteor type suggests it is not created from random collisions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967425/3967425_4A01B25AA11349928FAC0A76B5DE66E3_200224_3967425_Earth_formed_a_whole_lot_fast_than_previously_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Earth, proto-Earth, proto Earth, Earth formation, Earth's formation, iron isotope, iron isotopes, cosmic dust, CI chondrite, CI, meteorite, meteorites, accretion disk, Centre for Star and Planet Formation, StarPlan, University of Copenhagen, Denmark, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967414</guid>
      <title>Increased methane emissions linked to human fossil fuel usage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCHESTER, NEW YORK  A new study published by the University of Rochester in Nature magazine has found that human activity has been contributing significantly to the rise of methane emissions via the use of fossil fuels.For this study, scientists collected ice cores from Greenland and melted them to measure the amount of carbon-14 isotopes that were trapped in the ice cores.Fossil methane does not contain carbon-14 as it has been trapped underground for millions of years and the isotope has decayed. Biological methane, which comes from living sources such as animals, contains carbon-14. This chemical signature allowed researchers to distinguish natural emissions from man-made emissions over a period of 200 years, from before the Industrial Revolution started in the early 18th century to the present day.Researchers found that almost all methane that was emitted to earth's atmosphere until 1870 was biological in nature.After 1870, researchers found a roughly 25 to 40 percent increase of human-produced methane emissions. This coincides with a sharp increase in the use of fossil fuels such as coal, oil and natural gas around the same period of time.Scientists linked the study to today's climate crisis and said that a reduction in fossil fuel use could lessen the threat of global warming.A separate study from Princeton University found that methane emissions are roughly 30 times more potent than carbon emissions.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967414/3967414_3428FC1DED2A40B7ADDD098384ADB81A_200224_3967414_Increased_methane_emissions_linked_to_human_foss_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Methane emissions, human methane emissions, methane emissions natural gas, atmospheric methane, potent greenhouse gases, CH4 emissions, methane fossil fuel emissions, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967399</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How North Korea uses the Internet to prop up its regime</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOMERVILLE, MASSACHUSETTS  North Korea is turning to cryptocurrency as a means to circumvent sanctions. In a published report, analysts at Record Future say the regime is investing in high end machines for mining Monero and the activity has increased tenfold since May 2019.Recorded Future, which has ties to the CIA, says North Korea heavily regulates internet access and allows only elite military officials to use the Web. This makes Pyongyang's cyber traffic easier to sample and analyze. North Korea also engages in cyber theft and espionage, including cryptocurrency theft, hacking enabled bank theft, and financial cybercrimes. Over the past four years, those activities generated $2 billion, a sum equal to 7 percent of North Korea's annual GDP.According to the report, North Korea has three main ways to connect to the Internet, which is via its normal allotted IP, China-based Unicom, or Russia's satellite company SatGate Holdings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967399/3967399_0BB00C01BCAB44069D3FAF83AD5B0185_200224_3967399_Explainer__How_North_Korea_uses_the_Internet_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Cybercrime, Internet, cryptocurrency, Monero, sanctions, cryptocurrency mining, hacking, hackers, Insikt Group, Insikt, Recorded Future, North Korea, China, Russia, U.S., TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967272</guid>
      <title>Daredevil 'Mad Mike' Hughes killed in homemade rocket crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BARSTOW, CALIFORNIA  Self-proclaimed daredevil "Mad Mike" Hughes is sadly no longer around after he crashed in his homemade rocket shortly after take off near Barstow on Saturday. Hughes was well-known for his belief in a non-round Earth, and was hoping to prove it by launching himself up into space.  According to a Space.com, Hughes had planned to shoot himself up into the sky for a Science Channel series called "Homemade Astronauts." According to Discoverywhich owns The Science Channelthe series is supposed to follow people looking to "explore the final frontier on limited budgets." Discovery's website said Hughes and Waldo Stakes built the steam-powered rocket with the intent of getting Hughes 5,000 feet into the air. Video posted to social media shows the rocket flying up and a parachute ripping off at launch. According to witnesses talking to the LA Times, the rocket went straight up in an arc and then came straight down. None of Mike's backup parachutes worked either.According to the San Bernardino County Sheriff's Office, deputies responded to the crash off highway 247 in Barstow on Saturday afternoon. A sheriff's aviation unit is now investigating the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 09:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967272/3967272_BE4508E728014F9AA0D477AF32A64EF6_200224_3967272_Daredevil__Mad_Mike__Hughes_killed_in_homemade_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Mad Mike Hughes, Mike Hughes, Mad Mike Hughes rocket launch, Mad Mike Hughes homemade rocket, Mad Mike Hughes rocket launch fail, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967250</guid>
      <title>Here's how endangered blue whales are coming back</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH GEORGIA  Researchers from the British Antarctic Survey have found an increase of blue whales around the island of South Georgia near Antarctica.The whale population in South Georgia declined due to extensive hunting in the early 20th century, according to BBC News. The researchers embarked on several missions to the waters of South Georgia from January 1, 2018 to January 1, 2020 and spotted roughly 55 blue whales.Researchers used advanced acoustics to locate different whales and attached satellite tags to identify them. They also collected skin samples and flew drones over the whales to assess their body conditions.The report suggests that the whales may be returning to South Georgia waters for feeding purposes which is, in turn, impacting the reproductive rate of the whale population.According to British Antarctic Survey's website, South Georgia may have been an important place for many whale species in the past due to its influx of Antarctic krill and immense seasonal productivity.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 08:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967250/3967250_6C3D7E1164E341C2A453834D6B6F6EBC_200224_3967250_Here_s_how_endangered_blue_whales_are_coming_bac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Endangered blue whales, Blue whales, blue whales antarctica, blue whales south georgia, blue whale sighting, blue whale population, endangered blue whale population, blue whale population increases, blue whale population, blue whale conservation, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967205</guid>
      <title>Australian train runs off rail and kills two on a troubled track</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WALLAN, AUSTRALIA  An Australian XPT train travelling from Sidney to Melbourne derailed on Thursday, February 20, resulting in the deaths of the train driver and co-driver. Citing Australian officials, the BBC reports that 153 passengers were on board at the time.Australia's ABC reports the rail firm found track faults in the days before the accident. Citing passengers, BBC reports the driver had announced that he would try make up for earlier delays. At 7:50 p.m., the train derailed near Wallan, a township about 45 km from Melbourne.Citing Victoria Police, ABC reports the impact killed the train driver, a 54-year-old Australian Capital Territory man, and the pilot, a 49 year old Castlemaine woman. The crash turned the engine and the first carriage on their sides.Footage and images of the aftermath show that the engine and four passenger carriages left the rails. ABC reports that 12 passengers were hospitalized, including 11 with minor injuries and one person who suffered upper torso wounds.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967205/3967205_3A04AC7E1E254B998EE02B6A8A5D9F69_200224_3967205_Australian_train_runs_off_rail_and_kills_two_on__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Train crash, train wreck, derails, derailment, express train, XPT, SIdney, Melbourne, Wallan, faulty track, faulty tracks, track faults, Australia, accident, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967113</guid>
      <title>Burger King uses moldy Whopper to promote its signature product</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S.  Hungry?Burger King is promoting the 'beauty of no artificial preservatives' with its new moldy burger ad. The ad begins with someone making a fresh burger to the sound of Dinah Washington's song 'What Difference A Day Makes', and then uses a time-lapse showing it rotting over 34 days. The fast-food juggernaut says the campaign is highlighting its decision to remove artificial preservatives from the product.On Burger King's Twitter account they said: "The beauty of real food is that it gets ugly."It plans to get rid of preservatives from the burger served in all of its restaurants this year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 02:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967113/3967113_04EA05080785468B902A28F731413965_200224_3967113_Burger_King_uses_moldy_Whopper_to_promote_its_si_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Burger King advert, moldy burger, 20-year-old McDonald's burger, old McDonald's burger, Burger King ad, disgusting Burger King ad, burger that doesn't get old]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967913</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover parasite blobs that do not breathe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Henneguya salminicola is a species of parasitic blob that lives inside and feeds on the flesh of fish. The creature is the first multicell animal discovered that does not breathe, according to a study in Proceedings of the Academy of Natural Sciences.The parasite has no mitochondrial DNA, which enables other animals to respirate. Citing the authors, Live Science reports the parasite possibly absorbs ATP energy molecules directly from infected hosts to acquire energy without using oxygen fuel.Science Live reports that H. salminicola is mostly innocuous, but related parasites have wiped out whole fisheries stocks.H. salminocla is a distant relative of the jellyfish and the microscopic parasites have evolved to lose nerves, muscles and tissue. This genetic simplicity allows the creature to reproduce quickly, an evolutionary advantage for parasites.Study co-author Dorothee Huchon is cited as saying the parasite's spores are the only part of H. salminocla that shows any complexity. The spores are able to swim with two tails, and their eye-shaped stingers can latch on to the host when needed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 13:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967913/3967913_3424825BF8AB4A5786ADAF4378CC1015_200225_3967913_Scientists_discover_parasite_blobs_that_do_not_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Henneguya salminicola, h salminicola, parasite, parasites, animal, aninals, breathe, respiration, mitochondrial genome, mitochondrial dna, dna, mitochondira, multicellular animal, multicellular animals, microorganism, multicell, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967855</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy deploys its first laser-equipped destroyer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. Navy has put its first laser-equipped destroyer to sea. In a news release dated Feb. 20, Sea Systems Command says the Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, or ODIN, is designed to help ships counter enemy surveillance drones.Citing the command, Military.com reports the ODIN was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer Dewey in November. An image published by the Drive shows that the laser dazzler appears to be mounted in a turret atop the deckhouse."ODIN's predecessor  the Laser Weapons System  is a 30 kilowatt laser that had been tested but never operationally fielded.Military.com reports that Iranian drones had shadowed the carrier George H.W. Bush in the Persian Gulf and the laser will stymy hostile drones' attempt to gather intelligence on U.S. warships.The outlet reports that ODIN is only one of the laser weapons planned by the service. Another weapon, a 60 to 150 kW laser which has a range of five nautical miles will likely be installed on another destroyer by 2021.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 10:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967855/3967855_B08B2EDF00B2440EB7338645F0A6DFA2_200225_3967855_U_S__Navy_deploys_its_first_laser_equipped_destr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[ODIN, laser, lasers, directed energy weapon, directed energy weapons, anti-drone, drone, drones, UAV, UAVs, unmanned aerial vehicle, unmanned aerial vehicles, U.S. Navy, Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, defense, military, technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967761</guid>
      <title>Misleading recycling labels found on plastic products: Greenpeace</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  A new report by Greenpeace published on February 18 has found that several companies in the U.S. are misleading consumers by adding incorrect recycling labels onto their plastic products.This includes companies such as Target, Walmart, Procter & Gamble and Nestlé.After surveying 367 material recovery facilities across the U.S., Greenpeace identified only two types of plastics, PET #1 and HDPE#2, that can be processed in the U.S. These are the only types of plastic allowed to be labeled as recyclable.PET #1, or polyethylene terephthalate, includes plastic water bottles, soda bottles or peanut butter jars while HDPE#2, or High-Density polyethylene, refers to milk jars, shampoo bottles or laundry detergent containers.Researchers noted that many PET #1 and HDPE#2 plastic bottles or other containers consist of full body shrink sleeves which makes the products non-recycle too.The report found that plastics labeled PVC#3, LDPE#4, PP#5, PS#6 and others cannot be classified as recyclable as they have low acceptance by material recovery facilities and are typically sent to landfills or incinerators. These include plastics such as plastic cups, bags, plates and cutlery.Greenpeace has called for companies to eliminate single-use plastics and to invest in reusable, refillable packaging or go package-free instead.The organization has said that they will file a complaint with the Federal Trade Commission if the companies do not correct their labeling.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 08:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967761/3967761_AFE0F3A2F6C74BBE856FB026D67119D9_200225_3967761_Misleading_recycling_labels_found_on_plastic_pro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[misleading recycling labels, Plastic products, recycling labels, misleading recycling labels on plastic products, plastic products mislabeled,  TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967643</guid>
      <title>Russian mom set to marry her stepson after divorcing his dad</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUSSIA  A 35-year-old popular Russian blogger is gearing up to marry her 20-year-old stepson after her 10-year marriage to his father ended in divorce.On her Instagram page which boasts 406,000 followers, Marina Balmasheva said, "You never know how life will turn out and when you will meet a person who makes you smile. I know that some will judge us, others will support us, but we are happy and wish you to be as well."Marina said she is very happy with her stepson, Vladimir and that he is helping to raise three of his five siblings. She went on to say that the couple will have more children and that wedding bells are on the horizon, however, no date has been reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 05:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967643/3967643_D6243C15FB4C471D9CB4F8B2D47E3266_200225_3967643_Russian_mom_set_to_marry_her_stepson_after_divor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, in soviet Russia, Russian blogger, Russian blogger marries stepson, Marina Balmasheva, mom marries stepson, meanwhile in Russia, Russian mom marries stepson]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968549</guid>
      <title>China is hunting down Wuhan coronavirus critics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  As the Middle Kingdom continues to struggle controlling the narrative behind their latest gift to the world, it's now going after critics. The more things change, the more they stay the same. According to Vice, 28-year-old Chinese entrepreneur Joshua Left, from the city that shall remain nameless, arrived in San Fran in mid-January as the you-know-what was just blowing up. Worried about his family back home, he started sharing information most likely not available in lovely China over his WeChat. Left told Vice that he then received a warning message from WeChat administrators. Then he started getting really specific messages from four WeChat friends, all asking him for his location, what hotel he was staying at in S.F., what his room number was, and what his U.S. phone number was.He then said his phone got a warning message that someone in Shanghai was trying to log into his account. When he refused, the same four WeChat friends then simultaneously began telling him to immediately come back to China. According to Left, he thinks his friends were probably forced by agents from the Ministry of State Security to try and get Left to give up his location.It appears to be a part of a much wider effort by Beijing to crack down on people sharing real information about the you-know-whatever-19. Well, that's comforting.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 23:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968549/3968549_DA517F35E7A84DB083C6931844523BBC_200227_3968549_China_is_hunting_down_Wuhan_coronavirus_critics_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[WeChat, WeChat administrators, text messages, WeChat friends, Ministry of State Security, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968387</guid>
      <title>Archeologists complete first-ever laser survey of ancient Mayan road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COBA, MEXICO  Archeologists have used laser scanning to chart an ancient 100 km long Mayan highway built 13 centuries ago. They say Coba, a powerful city-state, may have built the road to invade its neighbor Yaxuna. The study was published in the Journal of Archeological Science.The University of Miami said in a news release that the study used light detection and ranging technology lasers to penetrate thick jungle vegetation and reveal the ruins beneath. The LIDAR survey mapped out the road and uncovered 8,000 structures on its path.University professor Traci Ardren is cited as saying the road did not run straight as supposed. Instead, Coba's warrior queen K'awiil Ajaw may have built the winding road to control settlements across the Yucatan Peninsula and to attack Yaxuna.Arden, who is a co-author, says the Mayan roads were an engineering marvel. Giant limestone boulders were utilized to fill uneven ground, then white plaster was applied to make the road surface. This substance is similar to Roman concrete and gave the road its name Sacbe, which comes from the Mayan word for "white way."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968387/3968387_623226BBF02B4A4E865A54946B8D8E55_200226_3968387_Archeologists_complete_first_ever_laser_survey_o_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Maya, road, roads, highway, highways, Sacbe, white road, white roads, Coba, Yaxuna, K'awiil Ajaw, Yucatan Peninsula, Yucatan, Mexico, University of Miami, archeology, history, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968375</guid>
      <title>Japan plans 2024 space mission to explore Martian moons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Japan is set to launch a robotic mission to the Martian system in 2024. The MIT Technology Review reports the mission will visit Phobos and Deimos, and recover dust samples from the former Martian moon, citing Japan's space agency JAXA.According to JAXA, the Martian Moon Exploration spacecraft, or MMX, will enter into a stable orbit to observe the two moons for a year. The MMX will utilize a NASA-funded neutron and gamma-ray spectrometer to determine the composition of these moons.The MMX will also land on Phobos and send out a small rover. The vehicle will use its equipped geological core sampler and dig 2 cm deep into the dust to retrieve samples weighing 10 grams.The mission's main goals are to investigate the two moon's origins, to find evidence that water had been present on Deimos and Phobos, and gather data on the gravitational stress that is expected to tear Phobos apart 30 to 50 million years from now.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968375/3968375_C6240E662CF548858DFB1307BE835C80_200226_3968375_Japan_plans_2024_space_mission_to_explore_Martia_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Martian Moon Exploration, MMX, space mission, Martian system, Martian moons, Mars moons mission, Mars' moons, Mars, Phobos, Deimos, rover, JAXA, Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency, NASA, 2024, space, space exploration, science, technology, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968260</guid>
      <title>China's wildlife consumption ban explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China announced on Monday that the country has banned the consumption and trade of wildlife with immediate effect amid the ongoing Covid-19 outbreak.Hunting or transporting wild animals for eating purposes will also be prohibited under the ban. Scientists in China suspect that the new coronavirus has spread from wild animals to humans, but this has not been proven yet.This includes wild animals protected by law, terrestrial animals and terrestrial wild animals that are being raised in breeding farms, the South China Morning Post reports, citing the People's Daily. Animals such as civet cats, wild boars, deer, blue peacocks and pigeons will all be protected under the ban.According to Reuters, these wild animals can be used for medical or scientific purposes but will be subject to inspection and strict examination.Aquatic animals, livestock, poultry and other animals are exempt from the ban.China's wildlife protection laws, which was brought into effect in 1989, included loopholes that allowed consumption of wild animals and captive breeding of wildlife for commercial purposes, the South China Morning Post reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968260/3968260_CB92BFEC74AB4DE190467D48A4CBE0DC_200226_3968260_China_s_wildlife_consumption_ban_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China wildlife ban, wildlife in china, covid-19, china covid-19, consumption of wildlife banned in china, chinese wildlife industry, china wild animals, eating wild animals in china banned, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968178</guid>
      <title>Wuhan's blood curdling screams will haunt your nightmares</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE MIDDLE KINGDOM  That doesn't sound good. Video posted to Chinese social media from the city on lockdown that shall remain nameless on February 22 is pretty bone-chilling.  Just listen.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 05:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968178/3968178_ECDCEF6EDCB14342AD2E61BAA2541409_200226_3968178_Wuhan_s_blood_curdling_screams_will_haunt_your_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Screams, screams at night, city at night, city residents scream night, city residents scream, screaming, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968088</guid>
      <title>Surfer punches shark in the eye and tells it to "F*** off!"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PAUANUI, NEW ZEALAND  A 60-year-old surfer fought off a Great White shark by punching it in the eye repeatedly after it took hold of his arm and clamped down on his surfboard. Aucklander, Nick Minogue says he was "quite a long way out" at Pauanui Beach, and at around 11:30 am his elbow, forearm and then board were all attacked by what experts believe to be a three meter-long Great White. Minogue instantly remembered that sharks hate being punched in the eyes and nose; he shouted, "f**k off!" and went to strike it, but missed.He said, "then I pulled my fist back and shouted 'f**k off!' again and got it right smack bang in the eye. It's quite a big eye, about three knuckles across."According to Minogue the shark disengaged its teeth from his board and swam off. Desperate to get out of the water, Minogue said it was only him and a German surfing at the time. After Minogue started screaming, both he and the German started paddling back to shore as fast as they could with Minogue adding, "The German guy was kind of screaming the whole way which probably made me paddle even faster."Fleeing the open water, Minogue was "bumped" into again by what he says was probably a Great White; he sat up on his board and punched that one too. With his fingers intact and one small puncture wound to his arm, Nick Monuge is looking ahead to a surfing trip later next week.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968088/3968088_F89A018A621C4A6AB37D4D6E4129A179_200226_3968088_Surfer_punches_shark_in_the_eye_and_tells_it_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Shark attack, surfer, surf, sharks, surfing in New Zealand, sharks in New Zealand, Pauanui Beach, Nick Minogue, shark man, New Zealand shark man, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968075</guid>
      <title>Shanghai police now using WeChat to handle car accidents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  Shanghai traffic police announced last Friday that they will now be using WeChat to handle car accidents. According to the Shanghai Daily, let's say you are lucky enough to be able to drive at a time like this and you happen to get into a little fender bender. The cop in charge of the accident will set up a WeChat group with everyone that was involved and their insurance agents. Traffic authorities say evidence collection, exchanging of information and compensation will all be carried out in the chat group. If the police have any questions, the head officer will get in touch with relevant parties via video call on WeChat. If you don't have WeChat, you get sent to a campthat's not true. When WeChat isn't available, the police officer will make recorded calls.   Police will then take a picture of any court decision and send it over in case anyone wants to appeal. Chinese authorities say the reason for going online is to try to discourage citizens from face-to-face gatherings. That should be pretty easy for a city of 24 million people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 03:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968075/3968075_350E5006C0AA456D90842C513E1A9C49_200226_3968075_Shanghai_police_now_using_WeChat_to_handle_car_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Shanghai, Shanghai traffic police, Shanghai traffic police WeChat, WeChat traffic, We Chat accident Shanghai, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968062</guid>
      <title>China SWAT team practices using nets to nab COVID-19 victim</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TONGBAI COUNTY, CHINA  China's got a new tool to take down uncooperative citizens suspected of being infected with you-know-what: fishing nets.According to Storyful, footage of a mock drill was uploaded to Weibo by the Tongbai County Municipal Public Security Bureau.The staged incident starts off with a masked driver being given a temperature check at a checkpoint in Henan province.After presumably failing the temp check, two SWAT team members, one of whom is carrying a riot shield, are called in. They ask the man to get out of the vehicle and cooperate with the investigation, but he refuses and begins to drive off.He's subsequently stopped by a police van, and when he gets out and strips off his face mask, more SWAT team members descend and pull him in with a net over the head.The man is restrained, and the net over is head quickly replaced by what appears to be a black bag. After he's taken away, those at the scene are sprayed down with disinfectant.In a post accompanying the video, the Tongbai security bureau wrote that the armed exercises were conducted in order "to win the epidemic defense."Since Henan borders Hubei province, whose capital Wuhan is the epicenter of the outbreak, Sky News reports that authorities are on particularly high alert.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 02:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968062/3968062_131C5C757EA347AF9EC9132D82293E9D_200226_3968062_China_SWAT_team_practices_using_nets_to_nab_COVI_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Chinese SWAT training, China SWAT, China SWAT drill, viral video, China video, China checkpoint, temperature check, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968058</guid>
      <title>WHO warns COVID-19 could become a pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA  The World Health Organization has warned that the world should prepare for a potential coronavirus pandemic.Outbreaks of COVID-19 have emerged in South Korea, Italy, and Iran, causing concern and prompting the WHO to say countries should be in 'a phase of preparedness' for a possible pandemic.The BBC reports that a pandemic occurs when an infectious disease easily spreads from person to person across many parts of the world.Thus far, the outbreak has been centered in China, where the virus originated. Over 77,000 people have been infected, and 2,600 have died.South Korea currently has 830 confirmed cases – the largest number outside China. Eight have died, and 7,700 troops are now quarantined after at least 13 in the military were found to be infected.Most of the country's cases are in Daegu, where clusters have been linked to a hospital and a secretive religious group.The largest number of cases in Europe – at least 229 – are in Italy. To contain the outbreak, authorities have locked down several towns in the Lombardy and Veneto regions.Iran also has 61 confirmed cases, the majority of which is in the holy city of Qom.According to the BBC, cases have also been reported in Iraq, Afghanistan, Kuwait, Oman, and Bahrain, all of which involve people who came from Iran.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 02:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968058/3968058_D16B7DD0CE324C5B8EDBF82139830F8A_200226_3968058_WHO_warns_COVID_19_could_become_a_pandemic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[WHO, pandemic, global pandemic, South Korea, Iran, Italy, cases outside China, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968859</guid>
      <title>Explainer: how coronaviruses spread from animals to humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  The WHO reports the COVID-19 outbreak as of February 25 has infected 80,000 people and resulted in about 2,700 deaths, mostly in China's Hubei.Writing in a column for Quanta Magazine, U.S. epidemiologist Tara C. Smith says that SARS-CoV-2 probably transmitted from bats to pangolins to humans.However, Smith, who is a public health professor at Kent State, notes other coronaviruses are known to jump the species barrier.SARS-CoV, which caused the SARS outbreak in 2003, originated from a civet cat. A decade later, MERS-CoV would emerge from a camel to infect humans.Coronaviruses rely on surface glycoproteins for binding themselves with the receptors on the cells of their hosts to cause infections.The part of the protein that binds is called the S1 subunit. Coronaviruses possess highly varied S1s that allow them to bind with many mammalian cell receptors, including those found on the surface of human air passageways.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 10:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968859/3968859_9CEBCAC168CA47ED92A2FABC798B4D39_200227_3968859_Explainer__how_coronaviruses_spread_from_animals_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Health, public health, science, China news, U.S., species barrier, species leap, protein, proteins, glycoprotein, glycoproteins, mammals, S1, Kent State University, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968602</guid>
      <title>China sentences HK bookseller to 10 years in prison</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Hong Kong bookseller Gui Minhai has just been sentenced to 10 years in Chinese prison, in what some say is a warning from Beijing that acts of resistance will be strictly punished.CNN reports that 55-year-old Gui was put on trial by a court in Ningbo for "providing intelligence" overseas. According to a court statement posted online, he pleaded guilty to the charge and will not appeal.Back in 2015, Gui, a naturalized Swedish citizen, disappeared from his holiday home in Thailand. Around the same time, four other Hong Kong-based booksellers went missing. All were connected to Mighty Current Media, which published salacious books on President Xi Jin-pooh and the rest of China's ruling elite. They later surfaced in Chinese police custody.In 2016, Gui appeared on Chinese state television claiming he returned to China voluntarily to face justice over a drunk driving incident over a decade earlier. Chinese police announced he'd been released from custody a year later, but was not allowed to leave the county.He was taken for a second time by 10 plain clothes policemen in 2018, while traveling on a train to Beijing with two Swedish diplomats.Sweden has repeatedly called on China to free Gui, on the grounds that he is a Swedish citizen. But China warned Sweden not to interfere, and despite having a law that bans dual citizenship, officials claim Gui is "a Chinese national first and foremost."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 03:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968602/3968602_1F26F66EF3D9473C8D016082210EFE32_200227_3968602_China_sentences_HK_bookseller_to_10_years_in_pri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[HK bookseller, hong kong bookseller, gui minhai, china dissent, beijing dissent, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968585</guid>
      <title>Why COVID-19 infections surged in South Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DAEGU, SOUTH KOREA  Coronavirus infection cases have surged in South Korea, with more than half linked to a religious cult whose secretive nature is said to have helped the virus spread undetected. The Korean Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported 1,146 confirmed COVID-19 infections in the country as of February 26. Majority are located in the city of Daegu and neighboring Cheongdo county, where they are centered around a hospital and the Shincheonji church of Jesus.The New York Times reports that the link to many of the cases is a 61-year-old woman known as Patient No. 31. Despite presenting a fever and sore throat, she initially refused to be tested for the virus, and attended several Shincheonji church gatherings before testing positive.Church members sit packed together on the floor during services and are not allowed to wear glasses or face masks. Citing South Korean health officials, the BBC reports that any gathering in such a confined space attended by Patient No. 31 would likely have led to more infections.Another cluster at a hospital in Cheongo has also been associated with the church. According to the New York Times, a large number of followers attended a funeral at a hall owned by the hospital. Over 100 patients and staff have since tested positive for the virus.Health officials learned that Patient No. 31 had also been in Cheongdo in early February. She told Newsis she hadn't visited the funeral or the hospital, only a public bathhouse.Shincheonji is considered a cult by many in South Korea, so members typically hide their membership from non church members. This, along with the belief that being sick is a weakness, has made it more difficult for authorities to track down those who have been infected, according to the BBC.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 03:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968585/3968585_097E52ED5B4842FCAD453AB5831EA485_200227_3968585_Why_COVID_19_infections_surged_in_South_Korea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[South Korea infection surge, South Korea infections, South Korea virus, Daegu, Shincheonji church of Jesus, religious cult, shincheonji church, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968553</guid>
      <title>600 Ibs sea lion takes a stroll, ends up on Washington road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CASTLE ROCK, WASHINGTON  A 600-Ibs sea lion was found wandering a "significant distance" on a road in Washington on February 23rd.According to the Cowlitz County Sheriff's Office, the sea lion was caught in a wooded area in the city of Castle Rock.They believe the sea lion wound up there after traveling up Delameter Creek from the Cowlitz River.  Video footage of the capture shows the sea lion fluster as officials attempt to get the animal into a cage on the back of a trailer. The Department of Fish and Wildlife triumphed and managed to remove it from the area, but only after local officials waited with the animal for several hours until wildlife staff could arrive with a trailer.Fortunately, the wayward sea lion was returned to the Columbia River.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968553/3968553_9410D50E03634318943D6228AB0841DC_200227_3968553_600_Ibs_sea_lion_takes_a_stroll__ends_up_on_Wash_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Washington sea lion, lost sea lion, sea lion found on road, Cowlitz sea lion, when animals escape, sea lion gets lost on Washington road, castle rock Washington]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3969075</guid>
      <title>Eyeball tattoo leaves alt-model blind for 3 weeks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA  24-year-old alt-model, Amber Luke has spent more than $25,000 on modifying her body, and she recently revealed that she went blind for three weeks after inking her eyes late last year.Dubbed 'Blue-Eyes White Dragon' by friends, Amber claims, "I can't even begin to describe to you what the feeling was like, the best thing I can give you is once the eyeball was penetrated with the ink, it felt like the tattoo artist grabbed 10 shards of glass and rubbed it in my eye."Amber, who developed an addiction to tattoos at the age of 16, said, "unfortunately, my artist went too deep into my eyeball  If your eyeball procedure's done correctly, you're not supposed to go blind at all. I was blind for three weeks. That was pretty brutal."Amber, who has had her tongue split, a silicone implant in her eye, a boob job, cheek and lip fillers and pointed implants placed in her ears says the eye tattoo was totally "worth it." She said every morning she wakes up, looks at her eyeballs and is happy because blue is her favorite color. Before you judge, Amber has one request, "We should all try and take a step back and wonder how creative and passionate that person must be to express themselves like that  instead of shunning someone, look at their beauty – I mean come on, it's 2020."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 02:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/28/3969075/3969075_04D24940B1BB4DB7872839350319B931_200228_3969075_Eyeball_tattoo_leaves_alt_model_blind_for_3_week_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire, Amber Luke, Blue-Eyes White Dragon, tattoo girl, tattoo woman, dragon tattoo woman, tattoo girl goes blind, eyeball tattoos, crazy tattoos, funny tattoos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
