<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 19:31:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3622578</guid>
      <title>Roseanne tries blaming her racism on Ambien, Ambien says hold up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TWITTERLAND  Roseanne Barr is reeling from her not-so-nice Twitter tirade telling her fans, "I'm not a racist, just an idiot who made a bad joke."Barr lost her hit show on ABC after firing off a tweet about former Obama aide Valerie Jarrett where she compared Jarrett to "Planet of the Apes" and the Muslim Brotherhood on Tuesday morning. After stumbling through multiple apologies over the Twittersphere, she actually blamed Ambien for the outburst. Roseanne tweeted, "guys I did something unforgiveable so do not defend me. It was 2 in the morning and I was ambien tweeting  it was memorial day too…" Barr brought ambien back into the mix in a later excuse when she tweeted, "Not giving excuses for what I did(tweeted) but I've done weird stuff while on ambien…" According to CNN, Sanofi  the maker of Ambien  clapped back in a statement saying, "While all pharmaceutical treatments have side effects, racism is not a known side effect of any Sanofi medication."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 13:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622578/3622578_BFF3C76F037B44D7AF562ADE931FF54E_180531_3622578_Roseanne_tries_blaming_her_racism_on_Ambien__Amb_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CA2/FFF/CA2FFF84FE9E41A6ABD78CE26018ABD6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Roseanne, ABC cancels Roseanne, Roseanne Barr rant, Roseanne Barr twitter rant, Roseanne Ambien, Roseanne Barr Ambien]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622535</guid>
      <title>What is Manhattanhenge?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  It's an exciting time of the year for residents of the Big Apple, who get to witness the unique urban phenomenon known as Manhattanhenge.CBS reports that the term, coined by astrophysicist Neil deGrasse Tyson, is a callback to Stonehenge, where the sun rises in perfect alignment with the stones during summer solstice.Manhattanhenge occurs around the dates framing the summer solstice, and is contingent on the exact position of the Earth on its orbital path around the sun.Manhattan's city grid is tilted 29 degrees east, with streets set at 90 degree angles. When the sun's path is at 29 degrees north of due west, it aligns with streets on the grid.The setting sun can be seen simultaneously on all streets heading east and west. It's an unusual event that happens four times a year in May and July, twice with a half sun and twice with the entire disk visible.This year, Manhattanhenge went down around Memorial day, on May 29 and 30, and will be seen again on July 12 and 13.Experts say the sunset alignment isn't just limited to NYC. Gridded cities like Chicago or Toronto experience similar phenomena, just on different dates.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 12:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622535/3622535_F4B13A8FD532472EB252C8957B0521B0_180531_3622535_What_is_Manhattanhenge__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8D4/654/8D4654D304BE45FC80BEE02BE8066DD8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, manhattanhenge, manhattan solstice, sunset, manhattan sunset, what is manhattanhenge, new york sunset, city grid, perfect sunset, stonehenge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622379</guid>
      <title>Nintendo's new joypad is a pokeball</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Nintendo this week announced a new Switch Pokemon game that'll be released in November 2018 along with a Pokemon-themed controller.According to Gamespot, the Pokeball Ball plus joy-con works pretty much like current joy-cons except you can mimic a throwing action at one in game. Gamespot reports it'll light up, vibrate and even play sounds. And the best part, for Nintendo's coffers is that it'll be sold separately from the new Pokemon Let's Go games at launch.  It'll be Pokemon Go compatible and also reportedly have the same features as the $35 Pokemon Go Plus device. The new games, as we previously reported, will be based on 1999's Pokemon Yellow and feature Pikachu and Eevee editions. The wrist-worn plus device basically let Pokemon Go players pocket their devices and notifies them about nearby monsters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 09:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622379/3622379_6D2478FE4A6747E69B5D6B59DA2A7964_180531_3622379_Nintendo_s_new_joypad_is_a_pokeball_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/845/650/845650AD7CF84834A8A2C20DA272B0C5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, pokemon, pokemon lets go, evee, pikachu, pokemon, nintendo, pokemon quest, shigeru miyamamoto, mario, legend of zelda, gaming, videogames, gaming news, nintendo news, new pokemon news, pokemon go]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622316</guid>
      <title>Skeleton of unlucky man crushed by stone uncovered in Pompeii</title>
      <description><![CDATA[POMPEII, ITALY  Here lie the remains of one supremely unlucky fella, who managed to survive an initial volcanic blast, but ended up getting squashed by a rock.Archaeologists in Pompeii have unearthed a skeleton that had been pinned underneath a 300-kilogram block of stone during the eruption of Mount Vesuvius in A.D. 79, according to a Facebook post by the Pompeii Parco Archeologico.The decapitated remains are believed to be that of a 30-year-old male. Lesions on the tibia suggest a bone infection, which would have hampered the man's ability to flee.The bones were found on the first storey level, over a thick layer of volcanic fragments called lapilli. This suggests he survived the first phase of the eruption.Scientists think the man had been hit by hot pyroclastic flows while fleeing. A massive rock thrown by the volcanic cloud then collided with his upper body, crushing his head and thorax.The unfortunate man's skeleton is the latest discovery out of Pompeii. Excavations in the past few months have unearthed the remains of a horse and a young child.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 08:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622316/3622316_4F0EDF53D8E4433A85A32E72AD5EF04B_180531_3622316_Skeleton_of_unlucky_man_crushed_by_stone_uncover_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/20B/433/20B433759BCD42EABEBE67A5289B9E29.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, pompeii, skeleton, mount vesuvius, excavation, volcanic eruption, stone block, man crushed by rock, ancient rome, pyroclastic flow, volcanic blast, lapilli]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622287</guid>
      <title>Airline asks mom to prove
biracial son is hers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DENVER  Southwest Airlines asked a woman to prove her relation to her biracial son while they were at the Denver airport on May 28, the BBC reports.Lindsay Gottlieb, who is white, was traveling with her African American fiance Patrick Martin and their son, when they showed the official their child's passport at the airport.However, the official asked for further evidence to prove they were a biological family, asking to see a Facebook post or a birth certificate.Gottlieb said "being pushed further to 'prove' that the child was her son felt disrespectful," the Washington Post reports.Gottlieb claimed in a tweet that she has flown with her son "approximately 50 times," and this type of an incident has never occurred.The airline was quick to apologize in a statement and said they were going to launch an investigation into the incident, CBS News reports.Gottlieb claims the officials told her that the airlines would treat the incident as a "coaching" moment for their employees, referring to Gottlieb who coaches the Women's basketball team at the University of California at Berkeley, CBS News reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 07:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622287/3622287_B1DE024F91A64F2985FE138B482DB33B_180531_3622287_Airline_asks_mom_to_prove_biracial_son_is_hers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/74B/3F7/74B3F73935D3471BBFE8688F0119AA08.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Travel, Flying, Airlines, Biracial, Airline asks mom to prove relation to son, mixed race,biracial son, US, Southwest Airlines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622237</guid>
      <title>Labrador gives birth to 8 pups at Tampa airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAMPA, FLORIDA  A Philly-bound dog gave birth to eight puppies at Tampa airport earlier this week.Service labradors Ellie and Nugget were waiting to board their flight to Philly along with their humans when suddenly their travel party got unexpectedly bigger.  Ellie was pregnant at the time, but her humans had no idea she was about to pop. The mama-to-be went into labor in the concourse and soon started pushing out puppy after puppy. Medical staff from Tampa Fire Rescue were on hand to help welcome the baby labs into the world.  Ellie gave birth to seven boys initially and then finally their sister, Fox 13 reported.Needless to say, the 10 canines and their humans missed their flight. Fox 13 reports they'll have to find a new means of travel as airlines don't allow newborn pups to fly.According to the Miami Herald, all 10 labs and their two humans will be driving 1,000 miles to Philly instead.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 06:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622237/3622237_A6BFFA3889EE4B4381B8A42689E3D533_180531_3622237_Labrador_gives_birth_to_8_pups_at_Tampa_airport_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A4D/EDC/A4DEDC1CBA6948D58061BBF7E007040B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, dog, puppies, labrador, lab puppies, newborn puppies, puppy birth, tampa airport, animals, aww animals, labs, lab wins, dog stories, dog stories 2018, happy news, positive stories, uplifiting]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622193</guid>
      <title>De Beers plans to sell lab-grown diamonds at a cheap rate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERKSHIRE, UK  British diamond maker De Beers said on Tuesday that they are going to sell diamonds that are "grown" in laboratories. The lab-grown diamonds are made from a carbon seed placed in a microwave chamber and superheated into a glowing plasma ball.This process then creates particles that can crystallize into diamonds in weeks.Unlike imitation gems such as cubic zirconia, lab-grown diamonds have the same physical characteristics and chemical makeup as mined stones.Despite being able to produce these diamonds in three weeks, De Beers has refused to use lab-grown diamonds to compete with mined stones, as they would not grade them in the traditional way. De Beers's CEO Bruce Cleaver said that these diamonds are not special, they are all the same. De Beers plans to launch the lab-grown diamonds under their new brand, Lightbox, with  plans to charge $200 for a quarter-carat, $400 for a half and $800 for a carat.Cited by Bloomberg, analyst Paul Zimnisky says man-made gems currently make up a small part of the diamond market, but demand is increasing. Global diamond production was about 142 million carats last year. Bonas & Co reports that compares with lab production of less than 4.2 million carats.De Beers's shift to lab-diamond jewelry comes at a sensitive time, as the British diamond makers will soon negotiate a new term with with Botswana, the source of three-quarters of De Beers's diamonds.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 05:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622193/3622193_84C18B59DF3F401D8F1B07719B06CCC0_180531_3622193_De_Beers_plans_to_sell_lab_grown_diamonds_at_a_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FD3/EBD/FD3EBDF03A89420FB373B15693E944CE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, De Beers diamonds, lab diamonds, de beers lab grown diamonds, de beers lab created diamonds, laboratories diamonds, diamonds laboratories, diamonds made in laboratories]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622116</guid>
      <title>Pregnant 71-year-old woman soon to become the world's oldest mom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MAZATLAN, MEXICO  A 71-year-old woman from Mazatlan, Mexico, claims that she is six months pregnant and will soon give birth to a baby girl.If so, that would make her the oldest mother to give birth in history. But who's the father?!The woman, named Maria de la Luz said that she was aware of her pregnancy since three months ago. She started feeling fatigued and had symptoms like dizziness and nausea.She also said she has ultrasound checkups 10 times and the results showed that that she will be a mother to her baby girl. Doctors who examined her was also surprised by the results.Despite the good news, Maria's children aren't too happy with the news of their mother being pregnant again, especially for a woman of her age.Regardless, Maria is scheduled to give birth on July 18 via C-section.Her pregnancy story quickly went viral in Mexico. One of the local politicians even expressed the desire to be the godfather for the miracle baby.Several hospitals in town have invited Maria for a checkup to see if she really is pregnant, so far, the one and only ultrasound photo is the one Maria has shown to the reporter.Currently, the oldest mother being pregnant is Maria del Carmen Bousada, in 2006 she gave birth to a twins at the age of 66 years and 358 days.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 03:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622116/3622116_A58499FCD02043E4883F35319B6A8C85_180531_3622116_Pregnant_71_year_old_woman_soon_become_the_world_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3B0/314/3B03148BC99341A5A23679F600F7E885.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,oldest pregnant woman,oldest pregnant woman in the world,oldest pregnant woman ever,oldest pregnant woman in history,pregnant woman mexico,pregnant guinness world record,guinness world record oldest pregnant woman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622099</guid>
      <title>Woman laughs when she sees other people being tickled</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO, CALIFORNIA  Researchers at the University of California, San Diego, found a strange case on a woman who laughs hysterically when she sees people being tickled. Referred to only as TC, the woman laughs uncontrollably when she sees someone getting tickled.Researchers concluded that the woman suffers from mirror-touch synaesthesia,  it's a condition caused by mirror neurons, connectors in the brain that react the same way when an event is experienced or observed.To make sure TC suffered from mirror-touch synaesthesia, researchers tested the her reactions in various circumstances, like seeing other people touch different surfaces. They also tested her reactions to funny video clips and jokes. It turn out she has a normal sense of humour. Researcher found that her uncontrollable laughter comes from watching people getting tickled as if she were experiencing the tickling herself. The sensation was so realistic that she would rub her armpits in an attempt to neutralize itResearcher found approximately 2 percent from population experience mirror - touch synesthesia. Researchers say in observing those with mirror-touch synaesthesia, they they can also learn more about human empathy toward each other.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 02:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622099/3622099_509E9810E7AE4EE2AAB816B33FE59466_180531_3622099_Woman_laughs_when_she_sees_other_people_being_ti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/234/F84/234F846B8D594896838760C8FCC9CE4E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, laughing out loud, laughing hysterically, laughing uncontrollably, tickle laughs, mirror-touch synaesthesia, can't stop laughing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622094</guid>
      <title>Couple's dinner ruined after liquid  drips from a dead rat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHANGSHA, CHINA  A woman and her boyfriend who were on business trip in southern China on May 14 had quite the disgusting dining experience. Guangdong native Ms. Yu and her boyfriend were having dinner in Changsha, China when suddenly something started dripping into their dinner from the ceiling, Xiangtan News reported.Thinking it was a leak from the air conditioning unit in the ceiling, they called the waiter over. Turns out the liquid was coming from a dead rat lying on a metal grille.Afraid the couple might have been poisoned from the dead rat juice, the restaurant's manager took the pair to hospital for a checkup. Lucky for him, they were both fine.The manager also paid for their accommodations as they had to extend their stay in Changsha. He also paid 2,000 RMB to cover their medical expenses. However, the restaurant still received a letter of complaint and was ordered to sterilise the restaurant to meet standards of hygiene.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 02:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622094/3622094_C365EA49A9054F76B7A17ADC0F431B59_180531_3622094_Couple_s_dinner_ruined_after_liquid__drips_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0D4/190/0D4190574399401F892B2CCDA9B27C5E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, rat in restaurant, rat in restaurant video, report rat in restaurant, dead rat in restaurant, liquid from rats, rats ruin dinner, rats in china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622091</guid>
      <title>Cockroach milk is the gross new superfood you didn't know existed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  You may think cockroaches are the spawn of Satan, but new research has found that the little buggers can produce a whole lotta nutrients.The Washington Post reports that unlike most insect species, the Pacific beetle cockroach is viviparous. This means it gives birth to live offspring instead of eggs,which it nourishes with a yellow, liquid substance from her brood sac.Instead of simply being digested, the liquid milk is deposited in the embryo's midguts and forms into tiny crystals. Analyses revealed the crystalline milk is a complete food containing proteins, lipids, and carbohydrates, and with three times more energy than buffalo milk.It's apparently one of the most nutritious substances on the planet, but does that mean we should be guzzling the stuff?Eh … not quite. Milking a roach is hard, but even without the eww factor, there's no telling if roach milk is safe for human consumption. Fortunately, science is on it.Scientists are now reverse bioengineering the milk and working on using yeast to produce the beetle roach crystals in larger quantities.It may take a while, but someday people might hoard roach milk instead of kale and avocado.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 02:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622091/3622091_24651B22196E4231A049A1446AEF5601_180531_3622091_Cockroach_milk_is_the_gross_new_superfood_you_di_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/21C/525/21C525700D004EB8903AAEBDBB182C4D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cockroach milk, superfood, cockroach, pacific beetle cockroach, roach, baby roach, lili mip, superfood trend, milk, non dairy milk, milk alternatives, dairy alternatives, crystal protein]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622082</guid>
      <title>Televangelist seeks charity for $54M jet to share the gospel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOUISIANA  A televangelist based in Louisiana is seeking money from his followers for a $54 million jet for "the Lord's work," reports The Times-Picayune.Reportedly, the jet can "go anywhere in the world in one stop."Televangelist Jesse Duplantis is asking money to purchase a Dassault Falcon 7X, a three-engine jet with a range upto 5,950 nautical miles and with customizable cabins which can hold 12 to 16 passengers, The Times-Picayune reports.Duplantis stated in a video posted to his ministries' website that he has owned three different jets in his life, his most recent purchase being in 2006, and has "used them and burning them up for the Lord."He apparently believes that the Falcon 7X will allow him to save money and not pay "those exorbitant prices with jet fuel all over the world."When asked about his use of private jets, Duplantis defended himself saying that commercial airlines are filled with "a bunch of demons" which "get in the way of their busy schedules."Duplantis mentioned that God himself asked him to believe in Him for a Falcon 7X, and not purchase it himself, according to The Christian Post.Duplantis added that he believes that if "Jesus was physically on the earth today, he wouldn't be riding a donkey. He would be in an airplane preaching the gospel all over the world."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2018 02:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/05/31/3622082/3622082_CA566F2E3DA94F5DB1E94D6C0E8CDF07_180531_3622082_Televangelist_seeks_charity_for__54M_jet_to_shar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4CA/6B7/4CA6B7200CAE49BBB933876BD5F2C9AF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Televangelist, Louisiana, Private jet, God, Jesus, Gospel, the Lord's work, Televangelist asks followers for money to buy private jet, donations, money, $54 million]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3623550</guid>
      <title>Badass K9s take down ruthless criminals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[1. After a high-speed chase through Grand Prairie, Texas, cops cornered a suspect pretending to wield a gun. Officer Jeff Payne deployed K9 Jurek, who quickly took down the man, his flashlight and his gun.1. A Florida Deputy and his canine partner Shep were the epitome of teamwork, splitting up to catch two criminals who stole and crashed a Ford Expedition.1. Indianapolis police and their brave K9 Tipster apprehended a wanted man who led police on a lengthy chase. He later admitted to shooting heroin during the car chase. Crazy!1. Pasco K9 Knox successfully tracked a speeding suspect who fled on foot into a densely wooded and swampy area, and then proceeded to celebrate his victory by attacking the bad guy with licks to the face. Now that's a takedown!1. An Ohio driver who refused to leave his vehicle and comply with police had to be forced out by a K9, who jumped into the vehicle and latched onto his arm.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 18:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/02/3623550/3623550_8291393DFFDA4BF6B5183E3CAAFCDB45_180602_3623550_Badass_K9s_take_down_ruthless_criminals_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F25/552/F25552A4012C723131E9355F90B0F119.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, k9, k-9, police k9, police dogs, canine unit, k9 suspect takedown, k9 unit, top 5, best police dogs, brave dogs, compilation, epic takedowns]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3623159</guid>
      <title>New Bethesda game isn't a Skyrim sequel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCKVILLE, MARYLAND  Game developer Bethesda dropped a trailer for a new entry in the Fallout franchise.If Kotaku's reported rumors are right, the new game will be an online survival RPG. According to Gamespot, the game will focus on Vault 76, an area that's been mentioned in other games in the franchise.The Fallout games are RPGs set in a post-apocalyptic USA. The player typically wakes up in an underground bunker called a vault 200 years after a nuclear war laid waste to the world. Fallout 76 however is rumored to take place 20 years after the planet went kaboom.The game will reportedly be released on Playstation 4, Xbox One and PC. No release date yet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 09:52:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/01/3623159/3623159_22CB88173A0D4BCBA7E2747076E33C05_180601_3623159_New_Bethesda_game_isn_t_a_Skyrim_sequel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/09E/98A/09E98AB4156D4641AF50F11A57FBEF51.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Fallout 76, Fallout games, Fallout, bethesda, elder scrolls 6, elder scrolls, skyrim, skyrim sequel, online rpg, rpgs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3623142</guid>
      <title>Chinese minority woman forced to marry Chinese man</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A post from Facebook account "Talk to East Turkestan" claims the Chinese government is forcing Uyghur women to marry Chinese men.  They claim that the Uyghur men are locked up and are put in "re-education" camps. They also claim that Uyghur women are then forced to marry the ethnic Han majority men in order to rescue their relatives. The Uyghurs are a Turkic ethnic group with their own distinct language and culture separate from China's ethnic Han majority.The page also claims that forced marriage is a part of the Chinese government's program to assimilate ethnic minority groups with the Han majority to reduce tensions between the different ethnic groups. In the video included with the post, a host is seen asking an apparently Chinese man how long he has known a Uyghur woman standing before him. He says "two months".In 2014, a local county government in Xinjiang, where the majority of the Uyghur people live, announced a "Uyghur-Han Marriage and Family Incentive Strategy", reports The RFA.The local government is reportedly encouraging intermarriage between the ethnic minority Uyghur and China's ethnic Han majority by offering 10,000 RMB, which is around US$1,500 to promote ethnic unity.The Chinese government is also offering incentives to children born from intermarriages, such as subsidies for medical aid and not having to pay for their education from kindergarten to high school, reports The Chinese New York Times.A Chinese official commented that intermarriage brings about "positive energy" and is a way to "realize the Chinese Dream," The Chinese New York Times reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 09:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/01/3623142/3623142_541B61B18EDF4CA980CD3639C3CC80A4_180601_3623142_Chinese_minority_woman_forced_to_marry_Chinese_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/686/A39/686A3967864E4D1398003C0548A4F5BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, Chinese minority, Uyghur woman, Uyghur minority, forced marriage, Uyghur woman forced to marry Chinese man, Ethnic groups in China, Chinese minority forced to marry Han Chinese]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3623100</guid>
      <title>Bomb joke causes chaos on Lion Air flight as passengers flee</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PONTIANAK, INDONESIA  An Indonesian flight from Pontianak [b]to Jakarta on Monday was delayed after a flight attendant reported a threat from a passenger. A flight attendant on flight JT 687 reportedly found a bag on the floor of the plane and asked who the owner is, with a smile, passenger Frantinus Nirigi said it was his and that there was bomb in it. The man was apparently joking, but the flight attendant immediately reported the incident and the man was immediately being questioned about what's inside the bag.Most people panicked after hearing the word bomb, with one desperate passenger then opening one of the emergency exits.Flight attendants were busy instructing the passengers to exit the plane properly, but weren't able to control the crowd from trying to rush through the doors.Here is a translation of what the flight attendants said about the incident: "I asked everyone to exit the plane quickly and calmly. Some were desperate to get out, some just stood where they were. Everything was chaos and I was unable to prevent people from exiting through the emergency exit."Ten people were injured, with eight of them being taken to hospital. Only two who sustained minor injuries were able to continue with their flight.Indonesian media reports the jokester has been charged with breaching civil aviation security law, and he could face up to eight years behind bars.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 08:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/01/3623100/3623100_3BC8307754CA4890B968263C24637EA9_180601_3623100_Bomb_joke_causes_chaos_on_Lion_Air_flight_as_pas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/624/00D/62400D237D4B42D8BEFB4BAB858B1977.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,lion air indonesia,lion air emergency,emergency exit lion air,lion air incident,lion air threats,lion air delayed,indonesia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3623028</guid>
      <title>Submarine discovers shipwreck with treasures worth $17 billion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLOMBIA  The shipwreck of a 300-year-old Spanish ship discovered off the coast of Colombia was found to have treasures that may be worth up to $17 billion.The ship was found with the help of an underwater robot submarine. The Remus 6000 went 2,000 feet below the surface, and was equipped with a long-range sonar that scanned the sea floor. The drone also took pictures of anything that seemed unusual, CBS reports.When researchers revisited the site recently, they found cannons engraved with dolphins. The researchers claim that this is a sign the ship was the San Jose, without a doubt.The exact location the shipwreck is still kept a secret, but it was found off the coast of Cartagena, Colombia in 2015. It supposedly has a cargo full of gold, silver and emeralds that could be worth nearly $17 billion, CBS reports.Since the treasure has been discovered, both Spain and Colombia are claiming that they are the rightful owner of the ship.The researchers have mentioned that since they "are explorers, not treasure hunters," they would not be involved in the dispute between Spain and Colombia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 06:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/01/3623028/3623028_59EC98BE27054C1EA2A1A43BF84CADD3_180601_3623028_Submarine_discovers_shipwreck_with_treasures_wor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DA1/878/DA18787A4EC4DFD9B4EA933D46A21900.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Colombia, Spain, Shipwreck, wreckage, Treasure, Treasure hunters, Caribbean Sea, Remus 6000, Spanish galleon San Jose, holy grail of shipwrecks, 300-year-old ship, cargo of gold, silver, emeralds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622990</guid>
      <title>Woman dies after doctor removes her ovaries during surgery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRISTOL, ENGLAND  One of Britain's most well-known doctors is now under investigation after removing a woman's ovaries during a surgery without her consent.Reported by the Telegraph, in 2016, Lucinda Methuen-Campbell, 58, was experiencing a bowel problem and sought help at Spire Hospital in Bristol, England.The woman eventually had to go through a surgery, which was carried out by Dr. Anthony Dixon, who was internationally renowned for using mesh to fix bowel problems.The woman later learned something shocking  her ovaries had been removed during the surgery, but without her permission. Dixon told her that he did her a favor.In an interview with the BBC, Methuen-Campbell said Dixon defended his decision by telling Methuen-Campbell that her ovaries were in the way.Despite the follow-up operation, Methuen-Campbell was still experiencing excruciating pain constantly.After telling her ex-partner that there didn't seem to be a solution for her pain, Methuen-Campbell was later found dead, hanging in her attic of her home in the village of Three Crosses, near Swansea.Methuen-Campbell's ex-partner and son told the media that while she was alive, she was in a great deal of pain after the operations and was very upset that her ovaries had been removed, and no one was able to solve the problem. Swansea assistant coroner Aled Gruffydd ruled the death a suicide, and cited that the operation made the pain worse and affected the woman's mental health.Since the incident, Dixon has been suspended by both Spire[g] Hospital and Southmead Hospital, he's currently under investigation by England's National Health Service. In a response to the surgery, Dixon admitted that all operations have potential problems but they were done in good faith and most of them were successful.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 05:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/01/3622990/3622990_B734FB9127EF40EBB57264C757086668_180601_3622990_Woman_dies_after_doctor_removes_her_ovaries_duri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9B7/063/9B7063D79E33489DA7BD49A66D5E6A4E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,surgery gone wrong england,ovaries removed,ovaries removed surgery,operation ovaries removed,both ovaries removed,surgery without consent,surgery without informed consent]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3622951</guid>
      <title>Whatsapp bans millions of Brits as new privacy law comes into play</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS/LONDON/SAN FRANCISCO  Millions of Brits are now reportedly without access to the world's most popular chat app thanks to new legislation.Basically, anyone under 16 years of age who didn't verify their age has been dropped Whatsapp thanks to the European Union's new General Data Protection Regulations. That's GDPR for short. Now that law  incase you live in a cave and haven't been spammed by companies you've long forgotten about over data for the last 6 months  is meant to enforce privacy EU wide. But what about Brexit? The UK's still subject to EU law until March 2019 at the earliest.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 04:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/01/3622951/3622951_5C7F114790B8455CA2DACB2EAB15BB70_180601_3622951_Whatsapp_bans_millions_of_Brits_as_new_privacy_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9A0/988/9A098849656857E11C750273BFEAEEB9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, whatsapp, whatsapp uk ban, whatsapp gdpr, facebook, mark zuckerberg, technology news, privacy, online services, electronic services, British and EU law]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624984</guid>
      <title>FBI agent backflips, drops gun, and accidentally shoots someone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DENVER  An off-duty FBI agent can know convincingly claim to be the deadliest on the dance floor, but not because he can dance, because he capped someone by accident. A hilarious only because no one bit the bullet  well, technically someone kind of did  video that has since gone viral on Twitter.  The clip shows Agent So-You-Think-You-Can-Dance wiggling around in front of an impressed crowd of rhythmically challenged bar goers. Since there was no one else around to get served, Agent Pop & Lock dropped a back flip on the audience. It was all set to be an instant IG story, when the his piece dropped out of his hostler onto the ground. When Agent Dancing with the Stars went to pick it up, he accidentally popped one off right into some guy's leg. The man was taken to the hospital and is okay  well aside from being shot. According to the BBC, it's unclear if Agent Just Dance will face charges or disciplinary action. At the very least, some dance battle etiquette training might help.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 11:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624984/3624984_B76422C5FEBC4BF4BBA055171A59BAD8_180604_3624984_FBI_agent_backflips__drops_gun__and_accidentally_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0FC/209/0FC20936ED6A4AE59576D2889DA3D9EC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, FBI agent back flip, FBI dancing, FBI agent drops, FBI agent dancing accidentally, FBI fail]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624978</guid>
      <title>China's developing a new space station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  China Is working on a newly planned station dated for a 2019 launch.Beijing expects the "China Space Station" to be operational by 2022. The space station will be able to host up to six astronauts over 180-day periods.This is around the same time span that astronauts will spend on the International Space Station.China says their planned space station will orbit Earth at altitudes of between 340 kilometers and 450 kilometers. The ISS orbits at around 400 kilometers.China's space station may outlast the ISS, as that craft's future is unclear after 2025. Reportedly, the U.S. government is considering pulling its funding or privatizing it. According to Yahoo News, the U.S. has banned China from using the ISS since 2011.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 11:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624978/3624978_B7A0DCDC34C24EDD8A9D04E7E072D03C_180604_3624978_China_s_developing_a_new_space_station_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5EE/DBF/5EEDBFB8D44545DC8A0966D630E0B374.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,china space station,css space station,iss,iss css,nasa,china space,china in space,astronauts,science,technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624945</guid>
      <title>Teacher charged for feeding sick puppy to snapping turtle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PRESTON, IDAHO  An Idaho teacher is in hot water after allegedly serving up a sick puppy as a meal to a snapping turtle in front of several students. Robert Crosland, a science teacher from Preston Junior High School, was charged last Friday with misdemeanor animal cruelty, according to CBS News. Crosland is now facing up to six months behind bars and a $5,000 fine if convicted. According to parents that snitched, Crosland served the puppy up to the turtle on March 7.  The turtle was then seized a few weeks later by state officials, who euthanized it because it was an invasive species.  Petitions have been started on both sides of the argument, those calling for Crosland's dismissal and others supporting the teacher.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 10:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624945/3624945_FD9B944460B44EC68878D8CFE3CC3FD8_180604_3624945_Teacher_charged_for_feeding_sick_puppy_to_snappi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/816/D42/816D42E0D3B24C40A39A35439C695C0D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, snapping turtle, puppy, sick puppy, teacher feeds sick puppy, teacher feeds snapping turtle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624923</guid>
      <title>How landfill meat is recycled as food for the poor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANILA, PHILIPPINES  In the Philippine capital of Manila, the poorest of the poor are forced to eat 'pagpag'  washed and re-cooked landfill meat  to relieve their hunger.Reuters reports that the term means "to shake or dust off" in Filipino, in reference to the act of cleaning dirt off the leftover food scraps to make it edible.When food is discarded by restaurants, it ends up at dump sites where scavengers sort through the waste for hours, picking out chicken bones and other scraps of meat. These leftovers are later separated, bagged, and then sold to families or eatery owners for a few pesos.Those who prepare pagpag first wash or boil it in water, to get rid of the germs, before re-frying or cooking it in some type of sauce.Eateries sell a pagpag meal for as little as 20 pesos or 38 U.S. cents a portion. For those who live hand-to-mouth, this is a day's wage, and the only thing they can afford.Slum-dwellers who eat the recycled meal say it's delicious, and claim no one has died from eating it.Despite warnings from health experts and the Philippine National Anti-Poverty Commission that it can cause stomach and other food-related illnesses, most say they will continue to eat it  not that they have a choice.To them, food from the garbage is better than no food at all.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 10:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624923/3624923_9E115CE3E7914777A0DC8337C12EAAC9_180604_3624923_How_landfill_meat_is_recycled_as_food_for_the_po_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/559/704/5597041029AB4B2EA97B67A5A1E53955.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, pagpag, recycled meat, recycled food, landfill meat, trash meat, garbage meat, garbage chicken, food scraps, poverty, poor, poor people, filipino poor, landfill, manila]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624815</guid>
      <title>Crayfish makes daring escape by cutting off its own claw</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  In a video gone viral on Chinese social media, a crayfish is seen sacrificing its claw in order to escape death by boiling hot pot.The video was posted on Weibo, aka Chinese Twitter on May 28, Taiwan News reports.Jiuke (九可), the person who posted the video, said that they had ordered a big serving of live crayfish, which was supposed to be boiled in a giant bowl of spicy hotpot.He commented that one of the crayfish caught his attention when it slowly crawled out of the boiling hot cauldron, determined to survive.In the video, it appears the crayfish uses its right claw to detach its left claw in order to successfully make its escape.Comments on social media were overwhelmingly sympathetic to the poor crustacean.Jiuke assured social media users that he took the crayfish back home and is now raising him in an aquarium.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 08:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624815/3624815_E20AAFB194AD4EDE91A9A721A7473F1E_180604_3624815_Crayfish_makes_daring_escape_by_cutting_off_its__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E10/11F/E1011F74764041D2B46AD98748826942.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Animals, seafood, China, Crayfish, pet, Crayfish escapes boiling hot pot and gets taken home as a pet, miraculous animals, cute animals, smart animals, animal escapes, marine life, brave crayfish]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624782</guid>
      <title>Pet dog dies during flight layover in Michigan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MICHIGAN  A man and his girlfriend were devastated when they found their dog that had been placed on a Delta flight had passed away during a layover.Michael Dellegrazie and his girlfriend were traveling from Phoenix to Newark, New Jersey, and had decided to put their pomeranian, Alejandro, on a plane. They planned to pick the pooch up at Newark Airport, CNN reported.There was a layover in Detroit, where the 8-year-old dog was held in a cargo facility.Evan Oshan, Dellegrazie's attorney, claims Alejandro was alive when he arrived in Detroit, but a little while afterward he was dead when someone went to check on him, Fox News reported.Delta officials say the pet was discovered in a cage with vomit and fluids, according to a CNN report.Oshan said the family is very upset and added that "this is essentially their family member who died. To say they are upset is a gross understatement."In a statement, Delta Airlines said, "We know pets are an important member of the family and we are focused on the well-being of all animals we transport."Delta added that they are conducting a thorough review of the situation and are working with Alejandro's family to make sure this doesn't happen again.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 07:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624782/3624782_ADBDC690AA7A445997E8C3921E98161A_180604_3624782_Pet_dog_dies_during_flight_layover_in_Michigan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/804/262/8042621FF18740D99C241399A2208B27.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Dog, Pomeranian,  Michigan, US, Delta Airlines, layover, Dog dies, Dog dies during flight layover, pets, pet,  family, pets are family, airplane, flight, plane]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624767</guid>
      <title>Whale dead after chowing down on 80 plastic bags</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTHERN THAILAND  A whale perished in Thailand last week after eating over six dozen plastic bags.According to AFP,  the male pilot whale was found struggling to stay alive in a canal in southern Thailand near the Malaysian border.A team of veterinary staff tried to help the wounded creature but its condition got the best of him last Friday afternoon The AFP reports that officials found 80 plastic bags inside the whale's belly  weighing a combined 8 kilograms. Those chunks of plastic were likely consumed by the whale, which probably thought they were squid or other fish.A marine biologist told AFP it's a huge problem, explaining that 300 marine animals die in Thailand each year after eating plastic. That number not only applies to pilot whales, but also sea turtles and dolphins.According to nonprofit organization Sea Turtle Conservancy, over 100 marine animals are killed annually due to plastic debris in the ocean. The conservancy says that there's 100 million tons of plastic in the world's oceans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 07:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624767/3624767_5116DF8D61BB4F8DA15FCA7753F0F3FC_180604_3624767_Whale_dead_after_chowing_down_on_80_plastic_bags_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4CB/B51/4CBB519B26EE4DF5AF847CA24492A2C1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, plastic ocean, sad whale story, sad fish story, plastic bags, plastic bags in Thailand, plastic bags and fish, plastic, plastic waste, pollution, climate change, human waste]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3624754</guid>
      <title>Taiwan maybe hit two typhoons in this month</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  A European weather forecast model predicts Taiwan may get hit by two typhoons at the same time this month.According to Taiwan News, a model from European Centre for Medium-Range Weather Forecasts predicts twin cyclones could interact with each other and bring storms to the island-nation. This kind of weather event is rare. Though the European model predicts this will occur, others do not.Taiwanese meteorologist Wu Der-rong[c] told Taiwan News that weather simulations from Taiwan, Europe and the U.S. differ. He also said it in it's too early to draw conclusions on whether it will happen.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 06:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/04/3624754/3624754_DC3D325B5A4143CD84BAE8653E94A6FF_180604_3624754_Taiwan_maybe_hit_two_typhoons_in_this_month_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1AD/136/1AD13661001B404591DB722FAAF35F9F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, fujiwhara, fujiwhara effect explained, taipei, weather, storms, cyclones, typhoons, hurricanes, tropical storms, fujiwhara explained]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3625690</guid>
      <title>Dying cockroach leaves egg in Florida man's ear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, FLORIDA  A Florida man lived out everyone's worst nightmare after a creepy crawly burrowed into his ear and left a nasty surprise.The Tallahassee Democrat reports that Blake Collins and husband Samuel McGee had been battling a serious roach infestation in their Tallahassee apartment for over three years.The couple says dozens of German cockroaches would often pour out of light bulb sockets, crawling all over the bed and pretty much any surface in the house.  Last week though, things took a turn for the really gross.Collins woke up horrified at 5 a.m. one morning to a roach in his ear. The pest had crawled right into his ear canal, and was burrowing deeper inside.He panicked and rushed to the hospital, where a doctor used a syringe and the numbing agent lidocaine to kill the intruder.But the now-dead roach still had one surprise left: it had laid an ootheca in the 25-year-old's ear. Had doctors not pulled it out, a whopping 40 baby roaches would have burst from the one egg. Gross!Collins was later discharged from the hospital. He and McGee were let out of their lease and are now moving into a new, hopefully not roach-infested home.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 10:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/05/3625690/3625690_93E882E3DE0145B0AD34D1261E43AAD1_180605_3625690_Dying_cockroach_leaves_egg_in_Florida_man_s_ear_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7CE/853/7CE853AD69124B08AF98C11369BE91E2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cockroach, roach, roach in ear, cockroach in ear, roach infestation, roach egg in ear, dying roach, cockroach extermination, pest control]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3625664</guid>
      <title>Worldwide 24-hour boycott on plastic packaging begins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EARTH  To fight ocean pollution, a campaign group is hoping to get everyone to stop using plastic-packaged products.The organization is supported by groups in Europe, Asia and the Americas.Reported by the Telegraph, more than 300 million tons of plastic are produced globally each year, and 10 percent of that ends up in the ocean. By 2050, plastic will most likely outweigh the population of fish.Campaign group "A Plastic Planet" is starting the world's first 24-hour boycott on plastic-packaged products to mark World Environment Day on Tuesday. Inspired by the world's first plastic-free aisle supermarket in the Netherlands, A Plastic Planet demanded supermarkets to have non-plastic aisles, an idea strongly supported by British Prime Minister Theresa May.Backed by celebrities, the event "One Plastic Free Day" encourages people to share photos of the plastic products they forgo on social media by using the hashtag #passonplastic.Sian Sutherland, co-founder of A Plastic Planet told the media that plastic has no place in food and drink, and there's no logic in wrapping food in something as indestructible as plastic. Sutherland also described the use of plastic products in this day and age is equivalent to smoking addiction as we have unknowingly damaged the ocean and environment by using plastic packaged products.So what can we do to make Earth a better place? According to Plastics Oceans Foundation, there are five things you can do: use paper bags instead of plastic bags; choose products wrapped in paper instead of plastic; leave the plastic bags at the cash register; if you smoke, use matches instead of plastic cigarette lighters; use a steel bottle to fill and drink water. The organization claims, by stopping the use of plastic-packaged products or plastic products, we can increase the chances of making Earth a better place and give ourselves a more sustainable future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 10:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/05/3625664/3625664_61B5245800D14624ABFF183CFBDCDF5B_180605_3625664_Worldwide_24_hour_boycott_on_plastic_packaging_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/796/D70/796D708F568B4DE981F3969330B7829C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, plastic packaged products, plastics in ocean, plastics in ocean pollution, plastic bags in the ocean, ocean pollution plastics, plastics pollution in the ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3625555</guid>
      <title>Guatemala Mt. Fuego eruption kills at least 62, dozens missing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUATEMALA  At least 62 people have been killed with dozens more missing after Mount Fuego erupted on Sunday in Guatemala, according to officials.Villages located along the mountainside were buried in volcanic ash, mud and rocks during the 16-hour eruption, the BBC reported.Mt. Fuego is a stratovolcano, which are classic-cone shaped peaks built up from layers of ash and lava rocks, according to Smithsonian Magazine. Stratovolcanoes have violent eruptions that launch columns of ash and scorching rock miles into the air. When these clouds collapse, they form deadly pyroclastic flows  avalanches of hot rocks, gas and volcanic ash.    According to the BBC, around 1.7 million people have been affected by the eruption in four regions. According to the head of the National Disaster Management Agency Sergio Cabañas, the town of El Rodeo was completely "buried."The towns of Alotenango and San Miguel Los Lotes were also affected. Temporary shelters have been set up for around 3,000 evacuated residents.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 08:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/05/3625555/3625555_107F25E38A514A6DB08C5852C019628B_180605_3625555_Guatemala_Mt__Fuego_eruption_kills_at_least_62___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EEF/204/EEF204E844D073F8F3864B836D286C7C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, volcano, volcanic eruptions, Guatemala Mt Fuego eruption, Mt Fuego eruption, Guatemala volcano, Mt Fuego volcano]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3625509</guid>
      <title>LINE partnering up with blockchain project ICON</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CRYPTOWORLD  Japan's largest messaging app LINE announced around mid-May a partnership with the South Korean blockchain project ICON.According to Bitcoinist, the joint venture is called "UNCHAIN" and will see the LINE development team create a wide range of decentralized applications, dApps, and deploy its blockchain central net on the ICON blockchain protocol. As of May 31st, the ICON blockchain network had a market cap of around $1.4 billion. According to an ICON blogpost, "Unchain will create a blockchain ecosystem fueled by a token economy, where the users are rewarded for their contributions to the network."LINE is a popular messaging app in many countries throughout Asia, with over 200 million active monthly users.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 07:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/05/3625509/3625509_967D8FDD53D3401BA00DBE2652E9809E_180605_3625509_LINE_partnering_up_with_blockchain_project_ICON_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6B0/31E/6B031EF501D9461996522FD49C668F6B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,LINE,ICON ICX,LINE ICON partnership,LINE blockchain,Unchain,blockchain technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3625410</guid>
      <title>China needs AI and facial recognition in classes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China needs to keep its 1.3 billion citizens in check, especially now some of them have found the real world beyond the Great Firewall.To take Chinese control into the 21st century, Beijing is now shoving facial recognition and A.I. into the classroom. The West worries about things like individual privacy, while in China it's about as prevalent as clean air. According to a state-media, a high school in Eastern China is testing facial recognition to see how engaged  aka bored  students in the classrooms are in real-time. They claim the system can pick up seven moods, including happy, sad, afraid and angry by scanning a student's face. A camera in front of the classroom also can track six types of behavior such as reading, writing, raising your hand, standing up, listening to the teacher (listening!?) and leaning on the desk.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 05:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/05/3625410/3625410_54ABCC61B9AF4F76BD4D68249AD633A7_180605_3625410_China_needs_AI_and_facial_recognition_in_classes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CCB/ACE/CCBACE7A11094BD396243C4B59F36C28.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China A.I., China A.I. classroom, China classroom facial recognition, China social credit score, China suppression]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626542</guid>
      <title>Crocodile kills Ethiopian pastor during lake baptism</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAKE ABAYA, ETHIOPIA  A Protestant pastor unfortunately on his way to meet up with God after he had a run in with a crocodile during a lake baptism in southern Ethiopia. According to the BBC, Docho Eshete  was performing the ceremony for around 80 people at Lake Abaya in Arba Minch on Sunday morning. The pastor had just finished baptizing the first person, and was about to move onto the second, when the croc suddenly leapt out of the water and attacked Eshete. Fisherman and residents frantically tried to save the pastor. But In the end, the pastor went up to the pearly gates after being bitten on his legs, back and hands.Locals were able to save Eshete's body from being taken by the crocodile, but were unable to catch the croc.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 15:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626542/3626542_E31D78F0CF534D218787024A986ED272_180606_3626542_Crocodile_kills_Ethiopian_pastor_during_lake_bap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/095/FDE/095FDEF0D0B0E6FCADCDF5D364A2A8B7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, crocodile, croc, crocodile attack, lake baptism, crocodile pastor baptism, crocodile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626537</guid>
      <title>Woman claims human feces fell out of sky and into her eyes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KELOWNA, CANADA  A Canadian woman is claiming that human feces fell from the sky and into her eyes last month, the Canadian Press reports.Susan Allan, 53, says she and her son Travis Sweet, 21, were in their car returning from having lunch with her mother when something smelly fell through the sunroof of their car and onto their faces, the CBC reports.According to Allan, the substance appeared to have fallen from a plane that was flying overhead, with the icky stuff covering their car. She added the substance fell right into their eyes.Allan says she and her son went to a car wash, where they sprayed themselves off before calling Kelowna airport to report what happened, the CBC reports.An administrator reportedly told her Transport Canada would be investigating, but it was possible the goo falling from the sky was frozen lavatory waste, otherwise known as "blue ice."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 14:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626537/3626537_88C5D309A8C54DD19A61D361D310A96A_180606_3626537_Woman_claims_human_feces_fell_out_of_sky_and_int_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/219/14A/21914A4727963894579519EB743A720B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, blue ice, plane lavatory, gross stuff, falling from the sky, falls from the sky, human waste, human feces]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626382</guid>
      <title>Free-range chicken busted for jaywalking in Portland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON  A chicken looking for fun outside the coop had its freedom cut short after it was picked up by a Portland cop.According to the Portland Police Bureau, the wayward, free-roaming bird had been spotted crossing the road at a busy intersection, and was picked up by Officer Daniel Trummer, who managed to get the grumpy jaywalker into his patrol car with the help of a bystander.Needless to say, feathers were ruffled.It's unclear if Portland Police formally charged the fowl or just let it off with a stern warning.They legendary jaywalker had to be turned over to animal control when they couldn't find its owner, though she did eventually come after seeing her pet's escapades on social media.The chicken, whose name turned out to be Edie, is now back at home and safe, and hopefully won't be crossing any streets for a good long while.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 11:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626382/3626382_00682411E7224242BE6526D2EF6B799F_180606_3626382_Free_range_chicken_busted_for_jaywalking_in_Port_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A09/106/A091067E55414F42A08EC69539785FB7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, jaywalking chicken, free range chicken, chicken crossing the road, why did the chicken cross the road, pet chicken, runaway chicken, chicken road, arrested chicken, chicken jokes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626373</guid>
      <title>Patient stays conscious during CPR in distressing medical case</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK  A new Danish study is raising awareness of the rare but disturbing phenomenon of patients being awake during CPR.At the Euroanaesthesia congress in Copenhagen, anaesthesiologist Dr. Rune Sarauw Lundsgaard presented the case of a 69-year-old man who went to the hospital after three days of indigestion symptoms, but suffered cardiac arrest while being admitted, CNN reports.A medical team immediately began chest compressions. CPR was administered over the next 90 minutes, with the patient reportedly showing signs of conscious awareness.A high level of awareness during CPR is extremely rare, according to experts, since blood flow to the brain is often insufficient.Strangely, the man's heart remained non functioning and without electrical activity, which caused him to lose consciousness each time doctors held off on CPR.Despite being given several shots of epinephrine, his heart failed to restart on its own. The man eventually died after compressions were stopped for good.An autopsy later revealed that the patient had suffered a complete aortic dissection, a lethal condition in which blood is forced between the inner and outer aorta layers.Since the decision to terminate CPR happened while the man was still conscious, it raised serious ethical questions, including the use of sedation when resuscitating patients.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 11:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626373/3626373_D01CD652EEC84F5CA6F25F3F48B0D494_180606_3626373_Patient_stays_conscious_during_CPR_in_distressin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9E8/1AC/9E81AC5278754E53B44FBCE260663417.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, CPR, cardiac arrest, CPR awareness, emergency response, rare medical case, strange medical case, heart problems, indigestion, nausea, aortic dissection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626293</guid>
      <title>Little girl's 'imaginary friend' will haunt your dreams</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UK  This went viral after Women's Magazine Oh Comely asked kids to illustrate and write about their imaginary friends. A girl named Ruby drew a picture of her imaginary friend "Grateful", who has yellow eyelashes so she can see in the dark and she has two babies in her belly.Ruby said Grateful only visits her at night, which at first she was quite afraid of this new friend, then as Ruby got to know her special friend more, she began to enjoy the time they spent together.However, what's terrifying is the fact that Ruby said her imaginary friend is 14 years old, but can never have a birthday. Twitter user Natalie Morales tweeted the picture of the drawing with the caption "Ruby, you have a ghost. This is straight up terrifying." The Twitterverse agreed as the post instantly went viral and was retweeted more than 26,000 times]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 09:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626293/3626293_9881715BADAF478889AD7D19747EB5C5_180606_3626293_Little_girl_s__imaginary_friend__will_haunt_your_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/227/A74/227A74F072804CB3A57EB167F3764F54.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, imaginary friend, imaginary friend child, child imaginary friend, a child having an imaginary friend is an example of, why does my child have an imaginary friend, imaginary friend ghosts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626174</guid>
      <title>Samsung and theloop to develop CHAIN ID blockchain identification</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  Samsung is partnering up with theloop to develop CHAIN ID in order to incorporate the blockchain identification technology into its Samsung Pass service.According to decrypto.net, Samsung Pass is an identity management service that utilizes biometric authentication. CHAIN ID is a blockchain identification system that lets people use the same certificate at any bank or securities company that belongs to the Korea Financial Investment Blockchain Consortium, according to Medium. According to Medium, CHAIN ID is the first blockchain based joint authentication system designed from theloop's 'loopchain' blockchain engine. It is currently being used by 11 securities companies in South Korea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 06:56:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626174/3626174_4C089CE8896D48DE8EDB4CD01B4314D0_180606_3626174_Samsung_and_theloop_to_develop_CHAIN_ID_blockcha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A02/174/A02174398A834A9390F5E413D555E99A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, blockchain, blockchain technology, Samsung, Samsung Pass, loopchain, Samsung CHAIN ID, CHAIN ID]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626168</guid>
      <title>Body cam catches police officer striking man with patrol car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GEORGIA  A police officer in Georgia was fired after body camera footage showed he used his patrol car to strike a man, reports The New York Times.In a statement posted on Facebook, the Athens-Clarke County Police Department said the officers were on patrol on Friday around 7:30 p.m. when they saw Timmy Patmon, who they claim was wanted on a felony probation warrant.The officers said they attempted to confront Patmon, with one of the officers chasing him on foot and Officer Saulters chasing him in the police vehicle.In a video posted by the Athens-Clarke County Police Department, Patmon moves in front of the vehicle while Officer Saulters continues to drive and strikes him.The police claim that Officer Saulters was attempting to block Patmon's path as he tried to flee.An internal investigation by the Athens-Clarke County Police Department found Officer Saulters used too much force when he struck Patmon.A police spokesperson said that the crash is being investigated by Georgia State Patrol and added that Patmon suffered from scrapes and bruises and had been taken to a hospital. What do you think? Who's wrong here? Let us know in the comments below]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 06:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626168/3626168_1327488376674872B16843F26F2F894B_180606_3626168_Body_cam_catches_police_officer_striking_man_wit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C78/261/C7826165018A4A52BBF2A750F7969950.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US, Police officer, body camera, police officer strikes man with patrol car, patrol car, police brutality, body camera catches footage, footage of police officer striking man, police violence]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626137</guid>
      <title>Man poses for selfie in front of train accident victim</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ITALY  In a case sparking controversy in Italy and beyond, a man was photographed taking a selfie with a victim of a train accident.A young Canadian woman was hit by a train in Northern Italy on May 26, the BBC reports. Rescue workers arrived at Piacenza station soon after to help the victim. It is unclear how the woman came to be in the path of the train in the first place.Meanwhile, a man wearing white bermuda shorts was spotted at the scene with the victim and the rescue team in the background, all the while posing with a "V for Victory sign" and taking a picture with his other hand.Commenting on the situation, Antonella Boralevi, an Italian writer, said that the man had turned off his soul and has become an "automation of the internet."The picture has been posted across various Italian publications with most responding in a negative manner, the BBC reports.Local journalist Giorgio Lambri commented "we have completely lost our sense of ethics," referring to the man's lack of moral compass.Lambri photographed the man taking a selfie, captioning it: "The barbarism you don't expect: the 'selfie' in front of a tragedy."Other comments ranged from calling selfies a "cancer that corrodes the internet" to one Twitter user saying "Nothing surprises me anymore."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 06:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/06/3626137/3626137_600067DC47EA439DA2EF3722F3EEAD26_180606_3626137_Man_poses_for_selfie_in_front_of_train_accident__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/188/BD3/188BD379FF8845F4BA66C3F04631A12B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Italy, Italians, Selfie, Selfie Man, The Internet, Train Station, Piacenza Station, Northern Italy, Train accident, Man takes selfie with victim of train accident, Italian public appalled, Selfie in front of tragedy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627350</guid>
      <title>Foul-mouthed star Lil Tay goes dark on Instagram, YouTube</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  After blowing up the internet in February with her foul mouth, a rising online star has now gone dark on social media.The South China Morning Post reports that when trash talker Lil Tay burst into the Instagram scene, she did so flashing wads of cash, cussing up a storm, and calling herself the "youngest flexer of the century".The 9-year-old's online persona capitalizes on shock value. She's a puny Asian kid who talks and acts like a stereotypical black gangsta on camera.The girl made millions in Instagram followers thanks to publicized "beefs" with famous personalities like YouTuber RiceGum and rapper Bhad Bhabie, aka the cash me outside girl.But in recent weeks, the schtick has seen some real-world consequences. Mom Angela Tian was fired from her real estate job in Vancouver, and 16-year-old brother Jason has been outed as the mastermind behind the whole production.Rumor is, the luxury homes Tay had been filming in were agency listings, and a red Mercedes she claimed was hers was in fact owned by mommy's boss.The controversial family has appeared on Good Morning America, and was most recently seen in a video that appeared to show Lil Tay smoking hookah. Her Instagram and YouTube were scrubbed of all content soon after, supposedly for rebranding.Although well before the empire went dark, Lil Tay's Twitter tried to generate buzz by challenging people to act like the potty-mouthed preteen. Since then, the internet has seen a slew of flexing videos from people eager to hitch a ride on the Lil Tay wagon.It's both interesting and more than a little disturbing to see what people make of this pint-sized human who may or may not know what she's gotten herself into.Despite insisting on GMA that she manages herself, it's become abundantly clear that Tay isn't top dog behind the scenes.More distressing is the realization that even if the girl were to leave the biz, the internet would simply move on to the next shameless act. That's just the nature of the beast.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 14:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/07/3627350/3627350_24683DBC54564140BCB89FCB21FC4B07_180607_3627350_Foul_mouthed_star_Lil_Tay_goes_dark_on_Instagram_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/91F/718/91F718569B902C71B732B112823941C6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, lil tay, lil tay challenge, instagram, social media star, social media, fake it til you make it, lil tay moneyway, kids on instagram, trash talk, youngest flexer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627342</guid>
      <title>Guatemala volcano death toll rises, nearly 200 people still missing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUATEMALA  Emergency crews have resumed search and rescue operations in the surrounding areas affected by Sunday's Mt. Fuego eruption, which has killed at least 99 people, with around 200 people still missing.  Rescue work was stopped temporarily on Tuesday when a second eruption sent plumes of gas and molten rock down Fuego's south side, reported the BBC. Some places are still so hot that when rescuers poked metal rods into the ground, clouds of smoke came pouring out, reported The Guardian.Firefighters said the temperatures reached between 750 to 1,300 Fahrenheit under the surface at some locations.   Reuters reports the volcano had its most violent eruption in more than 40 years on Sunday when it sent ash 33,000 feet up into the atmosphere. No evacuation alert was given before the massive eruption on Sunday, said Guatemala's Disaster Relief Agency Chief Sergio Cabañas. More than 1.7 million people were affected by the eruption, with 3,319 people currently in shelters.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 13:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/07/3627342/3627342_C1AA5276500646908D2107EAF8DECF45_180607_3627342_Guatemala_volcano_death_toll_rises__nearly_200_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EDF/61B/EDF61B36989BCCFBFDC434FECF080111.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Guatemala volcano,Guatemala volcano eruption,Mt Fuego eruption,Mt Fuego search and rescue,volcano search and rescue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627276</guid>
      <title>Woman's advanced breast cancer cured with immunotherapy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCKVILLE PIKE, MARYLAND  A woman's advanced stage breast cancer that had spread to other parts of her body was cured using her own immune cells. Doctors say the treatment marks the first time a T-cell immunotherapy application for late-stage breast cancer was successful. The results were published in the journal Nature Medicine. Judy Perkins, a 49-year-old engineer, from Florida was selected for the new therapy after chemotherapy failed to stop the tumor in her right breast from spreading to her liver and other areas, according to the Guardian. She was told she only had three years to live. Doctors from the National Cancer Institute in Maryland first took biopsies from Perkins' tumors, looked at the DNA mutations specific to her cancer. Physicians then extracted immune cells called tumor infiltrating lymphocytes, TILs, from the biopsies. Billions of these immune cells were then grown in the lab. The researchers then injected 80 billion of the TILs into Perkins' body. The treatment was given in tandem with pembrolizumab, a standard cancer drug that helps the immune system. After 42 weeks, tests showed Perkins was completely free of cancer. According to the Guardian, researchers are now planning full scale clinical trials.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 11:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/07/3627276/3627276_E1AAFB35EA8840639054AFC108F321DD_180607_3627276_Woman_s_advanced_breast_cancer_cured_with_immuno_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FFB/672/FFB6728134926DFEC460BE537F1EA13D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, breast cancer, breast cancer cured, late-stage breast cancer cured, t cell immunotherapy, immunotherapy]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627168</guid>
      <title>Swimmer begins 6-month Pacific ocean challenge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHOSHI, JAPAN  A Frenchman this week set out on an epic journey this week to raise awareness of pollution caused by plastic trash  According to CNN, Benoit Lecomte began swimming from Choshi, Japan on Tuesday. His goal is to swim 5,500 miles to San Francisco in 6 months. That means Lecomte will have to average 30 miles daily.CNN reports if he accomplishes the feat, he'll be the first person in history to do so.Lecomte will swim 8 hours per day, before resting on a boat named The Discoverer. After that he'll begin swimming again from where he left off.To follow Lecomte's progress visit www.thelongestswim.com]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/07/3627168/3627168_9F77839955204AD6B3C84172F7BFA344_180607_3627168_Swimmer_begins_6_month_Pacific_ocean_challenge_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B60/7DE/B607DE88ACB711B1582345E51A66DCE5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, the longest swim, benoit lacomte, choshi, japan, longest swim, swim across ocean, swim across pacific, swim across atlantic, the discoverer, swimming, ocean swimming, plastic, plastic pollution]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3626947</guid>
      <title>Factory worker arrested for adding foreign objects into sausage links</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JOHNSONVILLE, WISCONSIN  A worker at Wisconsin's Johnsonville Sausage plant was caught placing strange objects into sausage links during his shift, and was arrested, reports Fox News.Jonathan Lane was apparently pretending to have done no wrong, by going up to his superiors and acting as if he found the items himself.But Lane reportedly placed cigarette paper and wire connector into different sausage links, Fox News reports.In factory surveillance cameras, Lane was seen as the one placing objects into the meat.Lane was arrested on Friday and was charged with two counts of tampering with a consumer product and acting with reckless disregard for risking the lives of others.He may face up to 10 years in prison and $250,000 in fines, for both counts, if he is convicted.Johnsonville was quick to react, commenting that none of the contaminated sausages made it out of the factory.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 06:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/07/3626947/3626947_0E86384E67054E599F04921B8A99A056_180607_3626947_Factory_worker_arrested_for_adding_foreign_objec_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7E8/BC7/7E8BC706094CF84237E09D37433CE843.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Factory, factory worker, sausage factory worker, sausage, sausage links, foreign objects found in sausage links, man arrested for putting foreign objects in sausage links]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3628193</guid>
      <title>Mt. Everest cryptocurrency PR stunt tragically cost a Sherpa's life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNT EVEREST  A cryptocurrency PR publicity stunt organized by a social networking site has reportedly cost a Sherpa's life who helped lead a team up Mount Everest.For their upcoming cryptocurrency offering, social networking site ASKFM thought they needed something different to draw attention from the public.On May 14th, the social networking site sent four cryptocurrency enthusiasts to climb Mount Everest to bury two hardware wallets containing $50,000 worth of their tokens, ASKT.And whoever's brave enough to climb the mountain and lucky enough to find the hardware wallets, get to keep them and the ASKT tokens. So why the audacious move then? According to the company's blog post, cryptocurrency offering isn't something fresh anymore, so AskFM being one of world's top 10 social networks and world's largest Q&A platform, can definitely afford to make symbolic statements and draw attention.However, the whole thing wasn't such a smooth climb as ASKFM's post mentioned that two of the climbers were stranded at above 7,000 metres with no reserve oxygen until they were rescued by air response on the second day.One Sherpa wasn't so lucky, he reportedly went missing at about 7,900 metres when the team was descending down the mountain, and he never made it down.In an interview with the Financial Times, ASKFm's CEO Max Tsaryk admitted the event was tragic and horrifying but said the company should not be blamed for it, instead the Sherpa's death should be directed to the company that represented him.The CEO was later asked if he had felt this campaign had gone too far, Tsaryk said he didn't think there's much difference between ICO marketing and standard marketing stunts, therefore his company should not be blamed for a stunt that went wrong.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 16:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/09/3628193/3628193_43339E21804444DAA111A02EB4FD1443_180609_3628193_Mt__Everest_cryptocurrency_PR_stunt_tragically_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E1A/7ED/E1A7EDCFA20C6907BB2BAE1AFCCEF48B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, public stunts that went horribly wrong, askfm pr stunt, cryptocurrency publicity stunt, mount everest summit, askfm 2.0, sherpa mount everest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3628175</guid>
      <title>Orangutan tries to defend jungle home from bulldozer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST KALIMANTAN, INDONESIA  A heartbreaking video shows an orangutan in Indonesia desperately trying to stop humans from destroying its home.The Independent reports that the footage was filmed in 2013 in Borneo's West Kalimantan, but only recently uploaded to Facebook by International Animal Rescue.In the video, the orangutan can be seen frantically running across a fallen tree trunk toward a large excavator. It grabs at the excavator bucket with its bare hands, seemingly in an attempt to stop it from wreaking more havoc in the jungle.When the machine moves, the animal fails to hang on, and instead tumbles off the trunk and onto the ground.Two men from the animal charity can be seen running after the distressed primate, and appear to shoot it with a tranquilizer dart. The organization claims on their post that they managed to rescue the poor animal and bring it to safety.Sadly, more and more habitats in Indonesia are being destroyed by loggers, leading to death and starvation in the orangutan population.Unless we stop the madness and start rebuilding, our future will look much like Borneo's forests: gone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 16:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/09/3628175/3628175_6906DBAF112C42F28F509E4347F4EA9A_180609_3628175_Orangutan_tries_to_defend_jungle_home_from_bulld_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1C9/589/1C9589EB82225EF3AC3BF53E5FC9D9A8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, animal rescue, orangutan, orangutan fights back, deforestation, logging, illegal logging, borneo forest, bulldozer, excavator, digger]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3628078</guid>
      <title>Soldier steals armored vehicle for a 2-hour drug-fueled joyride</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLACKSTONE, VIRGINIA  A soldier under the influence of drugs boosted an armored personnel carrier from a National Guard base on Tuesday and went for a short little spin around downtown Richmond. Joshua Philip Yabut, 29, jacked the M577 armored vehicle around 7:50 p.m. from Fort Pickett in Blackstone, police said. The vehicle was not equipped with any weaponry, but that didn't stop him from tearing down Route 460 and then towards Richmond on Interstate 95 at a cool 40 miles per hour. While all this was going on, a parade of police cars formed behind the personnel carrier as it was cruising around. Armed police officers protected the entrance to Capitol Square as a police chopper followed the armored vehicle from up above.  Yabut eventually drove onto a median at was surrounded around 9:40 p.m. He was tased and taken into custody. Luckily, no one was injured in the incident.  The soldier has been charged with driving under the influence of drugs, one felony count of eluding police and one felony count of unauthorized use of a vehicle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 13:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/08/3628078/3628078_3346A9BAEBE34DD3B06BAF7B1289645F_180608_3628078_Soldier_steals_armored_vehicle_for_a_2_hour_drug_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/335/3F5/3353F5083D721C4BCF55F14FEFDDDF04.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, soldier steals, soldier steals armored vehicle, armored personnel carrier, armored vehicle police chase, stolen armored vehicle]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627984</guid>
      <title>NASA Curiosity rover finds ancient organic matter on Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARS  After decades of searching for organic compounds on the Red Planet, scientists have finally been successful.NASA announced on Thursday that rock and soil samples taken by the Curiosity rover from Mars' Gale crater has yielded organic molecules believed to be 3 billion years old.Organic molecules refer to chemical compounds that contain carbon. They can come from both living and nonliving sources, and are the chemical building blocks for all life on Earth.Curiosity's Sample Analysis at Mars instrument, or SAM, heated the samples to over a thousand degrees Fahrenheit, releasing small hydrocarbons that may be fragments of bigger, more complex molecules.While the organics could have resulted from biological activity, NASA says they are just as likely to have emerged from geological processes, or from a meteor crashing into the planet.Still, the discovery of the molecules sheds light on the planet's history  painting a picture of an ancient Mars that had favorable conditions for life.It likewise spurs on future explorations, with both NASA and the European Space Agency developing new technologies to search for signs of life.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 11:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/08/3627984/3627984_6291B38E12CD4F90B730E6A0FDDBA6C7_180608_3627984_NASA_Curiosity_rover_finds_ancient_organic_matte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6D7/67B/6D767BF561B0A421A49BACDFF8DD7161.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Mars, NASA, curiosity rover, organic molecule, organic matter, life on mars, hydrocarbons, ancient mars, building blocks of life, red planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627930</guid>
      <title>Sonic attacks in China may be side effects from intrusive surveillance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGZHOU, CHINA  Alleged cases of "sonic attacks" in China and Cuba has raised the question of how sound can used as a weapon.U.S. diplomats in Guangzhou, and previously Havana, have been diagnosed with unexplained brain injuries following abnormal sensations of sound and pressure, prompting fears of a sonic weapon, The New York Times reports.Ultrasound is a possibility, but an unusual weapon choice: it loses power with distance more quickly than audible sounds, and requires precise alignment with a subject.University of Maryland researchers theorized that the illness may have resulted from surveillance gear being positioned too closely together.Ultrasonic devices can interfere with each other in a phenomenon known as intermodulation distortion, producing audible sound similar to what patients claimed to hear.When placed at too close range or combined with other ultrasonic emitters, these devices can cause cavitation damage, causing bubbles to form in body fluids, tissues, or cells.It's hard to say for certain what exactly triggered the diplomats' mystery ailments, but more than one expert has chimed in to say bad engineering or a bad spy job is more plausible an explanation than a sonic attack.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 10:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/08/3627930/3627930_090C9705124A4CE0A475C3286911A276_180608_3627930_Sonic_attacks_in_China_may_be_side_effects_from__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/751/3CB/7513CB77C4F70F40214A4D1BE8322BF7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, sonic attack, mysterious illness, mystery disease, brain injury, brain trauma, surveillance, ultrasonic, ultrasound, weaponized sound, sound as weapon, cavitation, us diplomats, china, cuba]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627620</guid>
      <title>Man swallowed up by malfunctioning escalator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISTANBUL, TURKEY  A Turkish man is lucky to still be alive after he was swallowed up whole by a hungry subway station escalator.The insane incident was captured on video at the Ayazaga Metro station in Istanbul on Feb. 27 at 5:30 p.m., according to the Mirror.The footage starts with busy commuters walking down an escalator that was not moving.But when Mehmet Ali Erik stepped on, the escalator suddenly came to life and started moving, that's when a section collapsed, opening up a large hole. Erik fell in the gap and can be seen disappearing from the CCTV view. The man was reportedly trapped under there for an hour, before firefighters were able to rescue him and transport him to the hospital for unspecified injuries. According to local news, the Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality had put a warning sign by the broken escalator.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 04:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/07/3627620/3627620_B22DA8CB542C437DBB14998CBB00DC14_180607_3627620_Man_swallowed_up_by_malfunctioning_escalator_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/01C/F26/01CF261233AB9DE0047071822CF317D2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, escalator malfunction, escalator fail, man swallowed by escalator, man swallowed up by escalator]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3627567</guid>
      <title>AA to have smaller restrooms for its North American flights</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  American Airlines is shrinking bathrooms for its North American flights, reports Miami News.Smaller bathrooms will be installed on the new Boeing 737-Max airplanes, which reportedly will be just 24 inches wide.American airlines also plans to decrease its front-to-back space between economy class by another two inches, reports KHON.American Airlines commented that the new airplanes will have 172 seats, compared to previously having 160 seats.The airline had previously been in the news for shrinking its overhead bins. American Airlines has also reportedly been receiving a lot of negative feedback from travel bloggers, frequent fliers and even flight attendants.For now, the new single-aisle aircraft will be in use starting later this year and will be flown mainly in North America.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/08/3627567/3627567_A15DC92444E740E6B7DC243F43F852F7_180608_3627567_AA_to_have_smaller_restrooms_for_its_North_Ameri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C86/5A8/C865A8A335C1EA308DA7FD7029EF381A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Flight,American Airlines,North American Flights,Flights,planes,airplanes,bathrooms,flight bathrooms,AA,US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3628442</guid>
      <title>Snake caught slithering out of air vent of woman's car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WARRENTON,VIRGINIA   A woman in Virginia was driving when she noticed a snake slithering through the air vent of her car, The Washington Post reports.Lora Goff was apparently in her car during her lunch break when she looked down and saw a snake slithering out of the air vent.She was quick to call 911, soon after, animal control arrived. Unfortunately, even the guy from animal control admitted that he was afraid of the snake.Goff then asked for advice from her colleagues who suggested that she use glue pads to trap the snake, reports Fauquier Now.After trapping the snake overnight, Goff and her husband went to check on it. The snake was reportedly stuck to the glue pad but it wasn't dead...yet.Goff commented that her husband threw it in the back of his truck..saying that she "doesn't know and doesn't want to know" what he did to it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 06:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/09/3628442/3628442_6C688615C7994885B695CD11947C64FE_180609_3628442_Snake_caught_slithering_out_of_air_vent_of_woman_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AEF/BA9/AEFBA91926485C10A2BDF2D577D7C837.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Animals, snakes, garter snake, snake slithers out of car air vent, US, car, driving, animal control, sneaky snakes, snake startles woman while driving]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3628437</guid>
      <title>Days on Earth are gonna get longer because of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  New research shows that days on Earth are getting longer as the moon slowly spirals away from us.Due to gravitational forces between Earth and its satellite, the moon moves away at a rate of 3.82 centimeters per year, causing our planet's rotation to slow, according to the study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.Earth currently completes a full rotation on its axis every 23 hours, 56 minutes, 4 seconds, according to NASA.But researchers using astrochronology on geological rock layers found that when the moon was closer to Earth 1.4 billion years ago, a day was just over 18 hours.The length of a day has grown one seventy-five thousandth of a second on average per year, and is expected to continue at this rate for the next millions or billions of years.The Guardian reports that the moon will eventually stop moving when it reaches a stable distance from Earth. When this happens, the two will be tidally locked- rotating at the same pace, with the moon visible from only one side of Earth.Of course, that's assuming either of them survive the Sun's destructive red giant phase.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 06:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/09/3628437/3628437_415675C42E1947B79875EF7BB5FA75F6_180609_3628437_Days_on_Earth_are_gonna_get_longer_because_of_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/23B/CF7/23BCF78286B79C95C44258F5F20BCD4A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, moon, earth, longer days, astrochronology, 24 hour days, 18 hour days, day length, day hours, hours in a day, astronomical theory, Milankovitch cycles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629989</guid>
      <title>Everything you need to know about the June 21 solstice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  The 2018 summer solstice will soon be upon us, marking the beginning of different seasons depending on where you live. The earth rotates on a tilted axis while orbiting the sun, which means different parts of the planet are pointed at or away from the sun depending on the time of year.During the solstice on June 21, the North Pole is tilted toward the sun, allowing it to shine at a 90-degree angle on the Tropic of Cancer, which sits at 23.5 degrees north of the equator.Anyone standing right on the Tropic of Cancer at noon on solstice day will see the sun directly overhead, and find themselves casting a very minimal shadow.Since the northern hemisphere faces the sun, it will experience the longest day and the start of summer. For the southern hemisphere, which tilts away from the sun, it is the shortest day and the start of winter.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 16:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/12/3629989/3629989_EE965C6E93B34F80AE0D8D4B2F788D7E_180612_3629989_Everything_you_need_to_know_about_the_June_21_so_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C49/700/C49700B79BE5813814ACE6964F67184F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, summer solstice, june solstice, 2018 solstice, summer solstice explained, summer solstice explainer, solstice explainer, earth, sun, tilted axis, summer, winter, why we have seasons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629799</guid>
      <title>How did Easter Islanders put 13-ton hats on moai statues?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EASTER ISLAND  Researchers say they have figured out how Easter Islanders transported 13-ton stone hats across the island and placed them on top of 33-feet tall moai statues.The study, published in the Journal of Archaeological Science, examined how ancient islanders were able to move the additional red stone cylinders, pukao, on tops of the statues, according to NPR. Easter Island has almost 1,000 moai statues spread across the island, with around 100 of them wearing the pukao hats. Researchers say the pukao were added later, but are unsure of the exact dates.  After constructing 3D models of the stone cylinders, scientists closely analyzed the details and features of each pukao.They developed a hypothesis that the hats were rolled up to the top of the statues using long ramps with a technique known as parbuckling.  Archaeologist Carl Lipo, co-author of the study, described the technique being similar to the way barrels used to be loaded onto cargo ships, saying "people would wrap ropes around the center of the barrel and then, from the top of the ramp, pull the barrel up the ramp. … All the attributes we saw match that model." Using the 3D models, the team was able to calculate how long the ramp would have to be, in addition to how many workers would be required to pull the pukao into place. With a ramp 75 to 328 feet long, with an incline of 5 to 20 degrees, a team of 15 people could maneuver a pukao into position, according to ArsTechnica.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 11:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629799/3629799_13145CE848B34D8CBDD2C0D8A30C7574_180611_3629799_How_did_Easter_Islanders_put_13_ton_hats_on_moai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D5F/D8B/D5FD8BFCE67E4121A62341989BFEA011.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Easter Island, Easter Island pukao moai statues, pukao, moai statues, parbuckling]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629789</guid>
      <title>Singapore on high alert for the Trump-Kim summit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE  Singapore has been busy preparing the city for the historic Trump-Kim summit to be held on June 12. Singapore Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong told the press on Sunday that hosting the meeting was costing the city-state US$15 million, mainly on enhanced security. According to the South China Morning Post, Interior minister K. Shanmugam said around 5,000 police officers and first responders will be on hand for the meeting. Singapore in total has 13,000 police officers and 2,500 first responders, the South China Morning Post reported. An unspecified number of military personnel have also been deployed, and with at least two warships on patrol off Sentosa island where the meeting will be held. The Singaporean government has also designated areas around the three hotels  the Shangri-La, St. Regis and Capella   to be used in the summit as "special event areas."Police in these "special event areas" have enhanced powers to stop and search vehicles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 11:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629789/3629789_CA282422B2E242E59272DD202095D29E_180611_3629789_Singapore_on_high_alert_for_the_Trump_Kim_summit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/119/033/119033E188AB326BD2DBCEC81CA80338.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Trump Kim summit, Trump Kim meeting, Trump Kim Singapore, Trump Kim Summit security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629744</guid>
      <title>Emirates leads the way to windowless planes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UAE  Emirates says it is planning to replace all of their windows in airplanes with virtual windows instead.Emirates Airlines President Sir Tim Clark told the BBC the "ultimate aim was to have no windows at all."Clark claims that the aircrafts will be lighter this way and could fly faster and fly higher while burning less fuel.Clark also claims that the projected images are "so good, it's better than with the natural eye."For now, the virtual windows are being used in Emirates' Boeing 777-300ER aircraft in the first class cabin. The virtual windows are supposed to look 'just like the real thing," reports ABC Net.Aviation expert Douglas Drury claims there aren't really any safety concerns. Though Drury says that there should be windows in critical places, such as the emergency exits, to have a clear view of the aircraft wings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 10:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629744/3629744_A03ABEA716604A908E6822290A6D5860_180611_3629744_Emirates_leads_the_way_to_windowless_planes_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F27/BC7/F27BC73E3B66C3C361BC8908BD2A48AE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Airlines, Airplanes, Emirates, windowless planes, virtual windows, first class suite without windows, airplanes without windows, flying without windows]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629712</guid>
      <title>Alligator kills Florida woman while she was walking dogs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DAVIE, FLORIDA  A Florida woman was killed last week by a massive alligator while walking her poodles.Officials told the Sun Sentinel that Shizuka Matsuki was with her two poodles last Friday morning when the reptile attacked in Silver Lakes Rotary Nature Park. There were no witnesses to the attack. The Sun-Sentinel reports one of her dogs was bit and a witness saw both animals barking near the water with Matsuki nowhere to be seen. Her pets were taken to a local animal center.Florida Fish and Wildlife, along with local police, searched the area for Matsuki. Officials later discovered one of her arms inside the stomach of an alligator. The park had been trying to trap it for the past two years, but the reptile always bested their efforts.Speaking to the Sun Sentinel, a local resident said some viewed the animal as a mascot and sabotaged traps set for it. A park official told the paper they hadn't heard anything about sabotaged traps.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 09:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629712/3629712_C31EC6213B5B42D5BBD76690395D538E_180611_3629712_Alligator_kills_Florida_woman_while_she_was_walk_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3A2/D9B/3A2D9B92078F94720DC27772B6CC2189.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, alligator, alligator attacks on humans, alligator florida, florida gator, gator incidents, alligators and humans, davie, alligator v dogs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629646</guid>
      <title>Rare condition makes 18-year-old student look like a grandpa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARBIN, CHINA  Xiao Cui is an 18-year-old high school student from Harbin, China, but you probably won't believe that, it's all due to his mysterious skin condition.According to China's People's Daily, Xiao Cui[e] first noticed the symptoms when he was in middle school, and his face has been getting saggier ever since, making him look a lifetime older than he really is.Doctors in China still have yet to figure out Xiao Cui's condition, let alone finding a way to cure him. The 18-year-old student said he has no option but to accept his condition and just try to look on the bright side of life. Luckily, Xiao Cui's condition does not give negative effects on his health.Xiao Cui isn't the only person who's suffering from his condition, Hu Juan[f], a 28 year old woman who looks like an grandma was diagnosed with an extremely rare connective tissue disorder known as Cutis Laxa[g], it's a group of rare connective tissue disorders in which the skin becomes inelastic and hangs loosely in folds. Also there was 30 year old Yuan Taiping[h], whose sagging skin made him look at least five decades older. Xiao Cui said people sometimes poke fun at his looks and he admits he does get upset from that but he still tries to stay positive, especially having supports from his friends and family, even his teacher rates him highly. Now Xiao Cui is currently studying hard to pass his exams and hopefully get accepted at Beijing University or Tsinghua University, two of the most prestigious learning institutions in China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 08:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629646/3629646_9BE97300A4BC4DE8892AB5CCBCDBC272_180611_3629646_Rare_condition_makes_18_year_old_student_look_li_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/187/984/187984A654F1BD2F7DAC2E35CBD50856.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, rare skin condition, rare skin condition makes you look old, cutis laxa, cutis laxa syndrome, rare condition makes you old, mysterious skin condition, harbin china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629543</guid>
      <title>Videos show police rescuing puppy, dog and owner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Check out these videos of cops from across the U.S. saving dogs.1. In March 2018, firefighters and cops in North Reading were called into save the life of a choking pup.2. Awesome cops from Atlanta Police Department rescued a dog they called "Smokey" from an apartment fire.3. Body cam footage from early May 2018 shows officers from Lancaster Police Department rescuing an elderly woman and her dog from a house fire.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 06:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629543/3629543_7E1E207544CB4315A0AA0484D4D852C0_180611_3629543_Videos_show_police_rescuing_puppy__dog_and_owner_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D37/35F/D3735FD4BE41365AC107832CAF00A32F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News,  k9, k-9, police k9, police dogs, canine unit, k9 rescue, k9 unit, top 5, best police dogs, brave dogs, compilation, police dog rescue, police dog video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629519</guid>
      <title>Teen drowns after hair clogs up the shower drain in freak accident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUTLER, PENNSYLVANIA  A Pennsylvania family is in mourning their teen daughter after she died in what is said to be a freak accident while taking a shower. CBS-affiliate KDKA reported that when Michael Rapp got a phone call early the morning of June 1st, his ex-wife informed him of the shocking news of their daughter Brianne's passing. In an interview with KDKA, Rapp said Brianne was in the shower, getting ready for school while his ex-wife was still asleep.Rapp said Brianne, who was later found by his ex-wife, probably blacked out in the bathtub and fell and hit her head, at which point her hair must have clogged the drain and caused the tub to overflow, consequently drowning her.Rapp added that his daughter had a thyroid problem and took medication for it, although he's uncertain if Brianne had slipped and fell or just blacked out. The coroner did not immediately release the official cause of Brianne's death.Rapp went on to say that he will miss his daughter's smile, her great personality, and how she wanted the best out of life. He added that he and his ex-wife are proud to have raised a daughter that people had great things to say about.A GoFundMe page has been set up to help the family finance their funeral expenses, and in just six days, more than the targeted amount was raised. The family added that any money left over would be placed in a college trust fund for Brianne's brother and sister, in her memory.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 05:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629519/3629519_3092F4A5E2AC42A585847D661314D9D5_180611_3629519_Teen_drowns_after_hair_clogs_up_the_shower_drain_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F34/2A4/F342A4A6E561DED52BA401FEF67F8746.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, drowning in shower, freak accident shower, freak accident bath, teen drowning, drowning in bathtub, girl drowning in shower, drowning in bathtub scene]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629496</guid>
      <title>Crocodile exacts revenge on dog that teased it for 10 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA  A saltwater crocodile has exacted its revenge on dog that had allegedly been teasing it for 10 years, ABC News Australia reports.Pippa, the dog, was reportedly known to frequently bite Casey, the crocodile.The gag was so popular that even guests were known to gather around to watch Pippa and Casey, CBS 17 reports.Pippa, also known as Dumb Blonde, would usually go straight to the crocodile's tail to bite it.This time, however, Pippa made a "dumb" move and decided to target Casey's head.Guests screamed as Casey snapped Pippa up and dragged it into the water.Pippa's owner responded by saying Casey just "did what crocs do," reports ABC News Australia.Many commenters on social media blamed Kai Hansen, Pippa's owner, for not stopping the dog from teasing the crocodile in the first place.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 05:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629496/3629496_ABD5D462458B4F50A6D99929123A0666_180611_3629496_Crocodile_exacts_revenge_on_dog_that_teased_it_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/81C/FBE/81CFBEE303A1E191240217E4F6973BB4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Australia,Reptiles,Crocodiles,Crocodile revenge,saltwater crocodile,Dog teases crocodile,crocodiles seeks revenge from teasing dog,small dog,aggressive small dog]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3629470</guid>
      <title>Woman fails to remove mascara for 25 years, almost goes blind</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  An Australian woman in her 50s risked blindness and serious injury to her eyes after not removing mascara for decades.Theresa Lynch had not removed her mascara properly for 25 years, News.com.au reports. The mother of two reportedly suffered pain in her eyes as well as some irritation and discharge. She claimed medication for this didn't help. Medical staff soon made a harrowing discovery inside Lynch's eyes. They found small bumps, specifically calcified concretions, underneath the woman's eyelids.Lynch told News.com.au that infection was so deep in her eyelid that the bumps were building on top of each other. Eye doctor Dana Robaei said everytime Lynch blinked, these bumps rubbed the surface of her eye. The doctor treated the infection during a 90-minute medical procedure, saying that Lynch was at risk of blindness.Robaei published details of the case in the Ophthalmology journal, in a study titled Subconjunctival Mascara Deposition.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 04:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/11/3629470/3629470_E04EE101D8B7447BA633586806FC920D_180611_3629470_Woman_fails_to_remove_mascara_for_25_years__almo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/14A/CE3/14ACE3672B8BAB47BE5EBD3E1CD09AFC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, mascara eye infection, mascara infection, mascara blindness, eye makeup infection, health, beauty, beauty stories, eye stories, makeup, eye makeup, bad makeup stories, health and beauty, remove mascara]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630666</guid>
      <title>EU copyright law could change the internet as we know it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS The European Union will on June 20 vote on a Copyright Directive that could effectively spell the end for memes and links as we know them.   If Europe goes ahead with the plans, everything from reaction GIFs, to fan fics and satire such as our own could be censored by by Europe's copyright Orwellian bots.Word from Brussels is that they're planning a 'link-tax' law for websites linking to news publishers. Any site using a thumb, link and preview text to link to a news site will have to pay the publisher to do use the content.EU lawmakers vote on the controversial directive next Wednesday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 14:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/12/3630666/3630666_888A6752FBC142B6AB416311128993A7_180612_3630666_EU_copyright_law_could_change_the_internet_as_we_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F83/51E/F8351E3E8AA0DE6AF568596CDF9A7532.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, eu, eu copyright, eu article 13, copyright, eu gdpr, eu article 11, crazy eu laws, eu overreach, brexit, axel voss, germany, spain, angela merkel, EU parliament]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630663</guid>
      <title>Is Rockstar's new game a Red Dead cash grab?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS SANTOS  Gamers are worried one of this years most anticipated games will follow a controversial gaming model called termed "Pay to win".Pay-to-win is controversial because it enables gamers to use real world cheddar to progress quickly in games and get ahead of others who are playing the game as normal.Red Dead Redemption 2, due out this fall, looks good, but as YouTuber Worth a Buy noted earlier this month, the game's single player and online multiplayer seem to follow a pay-to-win model.Red Dead 2 developer Rockstar Games also makes the Grand Theft Auto series. GTA5 has a fun online multiplayer, but players can also use real world money to get ahead in it.Some fans view this as a cash-grab, baiting players with expedited access to content they should earn. Others, apparently, seem to enjoy this model and are OK with it. According to GameDebate,com GTA5 has made Rockstar over half-a-billion dollars since 2013.As WorthABuy notes, Red Dead 2 will feature several editions, priced all the way up to $100. Playstation players will also get access to some exclusive content first, ahead of other platforms, reports GameSpot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 14:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/12/3630663/3630663_092A185D12EF4980A1DD9765FBECCA1A_180612_3630663_Is_Rockstar_s_new_game_a_Red_Dead_cash_grab__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0AE/0E3/0AE0E31D17196CCF0AAEA01102772484.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, rockstar, red dead 2, rdr2, red dead 2, red dead redemption, red dead redemption 2, multiplayer rockstar microtransactions,  rdr2 multiplayer, rdr2 special edition, rdr2 ultimate edition, rockstar games]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630488</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover new planet more than 600 light years away</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  A team of scientists in India have discovered a sub-Saturn sized exoplanet, reports the Financial Times.The planet, called EPIC 211945201b or K2-236b, is reportedly 600 light years away from Earth.The planet has a mass of around 27 Earths while its radius is six times that of Earth. Scientists used the PRL Advance Radial-velocity Abu-sky Search spectrograph, or PARAS, to measure the mass of a planet travelling around a star.The surface temperature of the planet is approximately 600 degrees Celsius, which makes it virtually uninhabitable. Distance-wise, it is seven times closer to its sun-like star in comparison to Earth and its sun.It takes around 19.5 days to complete one rotation around its Sun-like star.The scientists believe elements such as ice, silicates, and iron content make up around 60-70 percent of the total mass of the planet, based on the calculations of the mass and the radius, reports The Economic Times.This type of a discovery is crucial in our understanding of how these types of planets are formed, the Financial Express reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 09:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/12/3630488/3630488_2A74D8D7AA2D4023ACAD954846461993_180612_3630488_Scientists_discover_new_planet_more_than_600_lig_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8FF/FD0/8FFFD032A56A524921F22AA94BC3CD7C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, India, Space, Space Discovery, Planet discovery,  Planet, Exoplanet, sub-saturn size planet, Spectrograph, Observatory, Laboratory, K2-236b, K2-236, EPIC 211945201b, Sun-like star, Planet rotation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630372</guid>
      <title>Doctor pulls out live 4-inch leech from Chinese man's nose</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGXI, CHINA  A 51-year-old man in southern China who had been suffering from nosebleeds recently was horrified when doctors showed him the cause of his problem.Reported by New Straits TImes, the man from Beihai, Guangxi had been suffering from nosebleeds for 10 days and general discomfort in the nasal area.A doctor determined that some unusual activity going on in the man's right nasal cavity and was shocked to see what found. The doctor began to treat the problem, and decided to record the process.In the video, we see a light from a flashlight illuminate the man's right nostril as the doctor is poised with a tweezer. And what is in there is not for the faint-hearted.An 4-inch-long leech was eventually pulled from the man's nose, Reported by the Shanghaiist, the leech was much smaller when crawled into the man's nose while he was drinking "fresh" mountain spring water. Well, thanks to the doctor, the man is now in good condition and his nose isn't bleeding anymore, for now.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 08:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/12/3630372/3630372_BE040DB4372C4AF6BCF7E0281F99187D_180612_3630372_Doctor_pulls_out_live_4_inch_leech_from_Chinese__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3AA/BD2/3AABD2EED88795EA03EB36996DC35746.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bugs in nose, leeches in nose, leeches in your nose, leech nosebleed, leech nose, leech removal from nose, leech in nose of man, nosebleed problem]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630354</guid>
      <title>Nine-year-old girl so addicted to Fortnite, she doesn't get up to pee</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  A nine-year old girl is in rehab after becoming addicted to the game Fortnite. The girl was so into the game she would spend up to 10 hours a day playing. And what would she do when nature came calling while playing? Nothing. She just stayed put and did her business there. When her father tried to take away her Xbox, she hit him in the face. The long hours at night were awesome for her in class attentiveness as well. The girls parents are now seeking help for the girl.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 07:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/12/3630354/3630354_87F0B887A755407B86CD332695FD09FD_180612_3630354_Nine_year_old_girl_so_addicted_to_Fortnite__she__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/54D/553/54D553E6FE7531297C3BB0870457EC7E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, gaming addiction, fortnite, fortnite addiction, girl fortnite addiction, Xbox fortnite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631382</guid>
      <title>Chinese staff slapped and made to crawl at appraisal meeting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUBEI, CHINA  A video clip has hit the Chinese internet showing six male employees in central China standing in a line and being slapped in the face by their female manager.According to China News Service, the unnamed real estate company in Yichang, Hubei province defended themselves by claiming the six guys in the video all "volunteered" to be punished after failing to meet their work expectations.The real estate company also said that the female manager in the video was just "going through the motions."What's more jaw-dropping is that in the second part of the video, more than a dozen staff members are seen crawling around in a circle on the floor while chanting.Apparently, this isn't first time something like this has happened in China. In April, a real estate agent failed to meet his business target so his manager came up with this brilliant idea by having the guy to do 100 push-ups.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 14:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3631382/3631382_099DA954E2EA463B92FFCE25675608EF_180613_3631382_Chinese_staff_slapped_and_made_to_crawl_at_appra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/05E/9B5/05E9B57B307976774AB71546DC8F3E2E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, slapped in the face, slapped in the face china, chinese slapping, chinese slapping video, chinese company punishing, public shaming punishment, company shaming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631237</guid>
      <title>Little girl temporarily paralyzed from tick bite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRENADA, MISSISSIPPI  A 5-year old Mississippi girl was temporarily paralyzed after getting tick bite during one of her T-ball games. Kailyn Kirk was fine after her game, but when she woke up the next morning she couldn't walk.  When her mother Jessica Griffin  who posted about the incident over Facebook  started combing through Kailyn's hair, she noticed a tick in her scalp. After consulting with her husband, who is currently deployed in Iraq, she put the tick in a ziplock bag and rushed Kailyn to the hospital.At the University of Mississippi Medical Center, Kailyn had some blood work and a CT scan. Doctors later diagnosed her with tick paralysis. Tick paralysis is caused when female ticks bite someone on the scalp or at the nape of the neck, and release a toxin from their saliva. Tick paralysis is normally very sudden  within 24 hours. To treat tick paralysis, the tick only needs to be removed. People usually recover within a day. According to her mom, Kailyn was a champ through the whole ordeal. She even walked out of the hospital by herself later that evening.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 10:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3631237/3631237_5A199A75DF214F49A438978CF9A68A52_180613_3631237_Little_girl_temporarily_paralyzed_from_tick_bite_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/624/02F/62402FB302BAAA591A1A185E6647EBA0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, tick, tick bites, tick bite paralysis, tick bite temporary paralysis, girl temporarily paralyzed tick bite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631112</guid>
      <title>Dog hailed a hero for warning family about nearby blaze</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STOCKTON, CALIFORNIA An 8-month-old pit bull was outside the apartment when it realized their house was on fire on Sunday, June 3, CBS News reports.Sasha, the pit bull, was outside its owners' fourplex apartment when it realized the other half of the fourplex was consumed with fire. The pit bull started banging the door with its paws and barged inside the apartment when Chaichanhda, the pit bull's owner, answered the door. Chaichanhda said Sasha ran straight into their home and into the bedroom.She thought the dog was just behaving strangely, The Sacramento Bee reports.She then turned around and saw other half of the building on fire and rushed inside.Chaichanhda saw Sasha in their bedroom reportedly dragging her 7-month-old baby "off the bed by her diaper."The family got out of the fourplex unharmed, and is now staying with relatives for the time being.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 08:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3631112/3631112_B1158B8F199C4624B81ADF34B34CB3DB_180613_3631112_Dog_hailed_a_hero_for_warning_family_about_nearb_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5D3/5CE/5D35CEE784217F1C064F9F5EDDC9F348.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US, Dog, Hero Dog, Dog Videos, Dog saves family from fire, Family, House Fire, Baby, Baby in diaper, Dog drags baby to safety, Dog saves baby from fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631073</guid>
      <title>Man dies trying to save kayakers from sinkhole whirlpool</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEARCY, ARKANSAS  A man was killed Saturday in a fatal boating accident after a sinkhole created a dangerous whirlpool on the Spring River in Arkansas.Arkansas Online reports that authorities identified the victim as Donald Wright, who worked as the executive director of a halfway house in Searcy.According to the Arkansas Game and Fish Commission, a sinkhole opened around noon below the falls near Dead Man's Curve, resulting in a deadly whirlpool.While paddling in the area, Wright's residents were thrown off their kayak after it became caught in the whirlpool. Wright tried to help, but his own kayak capsized and got sucked into the whirlpool. The 64-year-old reportedly drowned within minutes.A spokesman from the Commission says one of the paddlers was able to swim to shore, while the other was injured and had to be medflighted out.Officials have installed buoys around the sinkhole, and warned visitors not to go into the area.Engineers are also set to assess the region within the week, amid worries that another sinkhole could open up in the area.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 07:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3631073/3631073_2C4F5D1B97D74AFA8F740C8F9A4D697A_180613_3631073_Man_dies_trying_to_save_kayakers_from_sinkhole_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9B3/3EE/9B33EEFDD1122E440F61D017B6DBFA42.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, sinkhole, whirlpool, hero, good samaritan, underwater sinkhole, boating accident, fatal boating accident, kayak accident, arkansas, spring river, dead man's curve]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631068</guid>
      <title>Venezuela hit by first case of polio in 30 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VENEZUELA  A young child is reportedly afflicted with polio in Venezuela  the first reported case of the crippling disease since it's eradication in the country in 1989.The Telegraph reports that according to the Pan-American Health Organization, the child lived in an impoverished indigenous community in the Delta Amacuro state.According to the CDC, poliomyelitis, or polio, is caused by the poliovirus, which enters through the mouth via contact with contaminated feces, or through droplets from a cough or sneeze.The virus multiplies in small intestine, before being carried through the bloodstream to the central nervous system, where it destroys motor neuron cells.The majority of infected don't get sick, while one in four develop non-paralytic polio with flu-like symptoms. Paralytic polio, though rare, can lead to muscle pain, paralysis, and even death.In some cases, those who contracted and fully recovered from the disease as kids can develop symptoms years later as adults.Young children, especially those who are malnourished an unvaccinated, are especially susceptible to polio. The disease has no cure, but is preventable through immunization.Venezuela has been plagued with economic and political crises in recent years. Local health authorities who were supposed to report cases of polio within 24 hours, took more than a month to do so.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 07:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3631068/3631068_0CA401233BA84D64AD6C4217D1FD720E_180613_3631068_Venezuela_hit_by_first_case_of_polio_in_30_years_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AC0/22D/AC022D1DEA1E5B29E7EEEA22558CDAE0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, polio, poliomyelitis, polio vaccine, what is polio, polio explainer, contagious diseases, polio virus, polio comeback, polio venezuela]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631049</guid>
      <title>Raccoon climbs 22 stories up high rise in St. Paul, Minnesota</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. PAUL, MINNESOTA  All eyes in America are on a restless raccoon that scaled up a skyscraper in St. Paul, Minnesota on Tuesday.Minnesota Public Radio's Tim Nelson noticed the animal had been stranded on the ledge of the two-storey Town Square building for two days without food or water.Maintenance staff tried to rescue it, but instead of coming down, it instead scampered over to the high-rise next door and climbed up. Next thing you know, trash panda is scaling up the side of the UBS tower like a Spider-ninja, and everyone is riveted.By Tuesday afternoon, the little hairball had made it more than 20 stories up. Employees from the Paige Donnelly Law Firm on the 23rd floor spotted it resting and grooming itself on a ledge.Since a rescue attempt might just spook the furry fella, animal control put live traps with food on the roof hoping to lure it up.But seems like Spider-raccoon won't be captured, and has instead begun the long laborious climb to the bottom. And since raccoons are nocturnal  it's gonna be a long night.As the whole nation waits in silent agony for a resolution, speculation abounds as to why the animal pulled a King Kong.More than a couple have suggested the raccoon is secretly Rocket, who can't deal with the heartbreak of Infinity War, and maybe wants to "Make America Groot Again."There's even a fake fan account on Twitter complete with elaborate backstory on how the critter got into its current predicament.Whatever it turns out to be, let's all just say a prayer, keep fingers, toes, and everything else crossed, and hope that raccoon makes it down safely.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 07:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3631049/3631049_3708DF528CE14943958FA307DF0495C8_180613_3631049_Raccoon_climbs_22_stories_up_high_rise_in_St__Pa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EC0/305/EC0305A48B5B528BEB2DF47E0FDF49E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, raccoon, mprraccoon, st paul raccoon, skyscraper raccoon, stranded raccoon, UBS tower, MPR, raccoon watch, trash panda, sky panda, rocket raccoon, make america groot again, st paul, minnesota]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631020</guid>
      <title>Woman attacked by bison in Yellowstone after getting too close</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YELLOWSTONE NATIONAL PARK  A bison attacked a woman in a crowd last Wednesday morning after it was approached by a crowd, USA Today reports.  The crowd was walking on a boardwalk, close to the bison and was apparently within 10 yards of the animal .... when it noticed the people lurking around. It was apparently agitated and decided to charge toward the crowd.A woman identified as Kim Hancock was gored by the bull, which reportedly left immediately after attacking Hancock.Hancock was then taken to the hospital by an ambulance after sustaining a hip injury, The Sacramento Bee reports.This is a third time in a week that animals from Yellowstone have attacked humans, reports The Sacramento Bee.Two women were reported to have been attacked by the park's female elks earlier this week.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 06:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3631020/3631020_09A108C6DDC145179882911705BD801C_180613_3631020_Woman_attacked_by_bison_in_Yellowstone_after_get_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1EB/328/1EB32850F30FF9509D41E236F9FF710E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US, Animals, Bison, Bison attack, Yellowstone, Yellowstone National Park, Yellowstone National Park Animal attacks, animal attacks, Woman, woman attacked by bison, crowd gets too close to animals, wild and unpredictable animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3630900</guid>
      <title>U.S. unveils world's fastest supercomputer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OAK RIDGE, TENNESSEE  The U.S. has unveiled its latest supercomputer which is twice as powerful as the world's current leader. The Summit supercomputer can process 200,000 trillion calculations per second  or 200 petaflops, the BBC reports.China's Sunway TaihuLight supercomputer had been the most powerful machine with 93 petaflops of processing power. Summit will be used first in the areas of astrophysics, cancer research and systems biology, the BBC reports. The computer was developed in tandem by IBM and NVidia, and is located at the Oak Ridge National Laboratory, ORNL, in Tennessee.The supercomputer has 4,608 compute servers and has more than 10 petabytes of memory. According to the BBC, the U.S. now has 143 of the world's top 500 supercomputers, while China has 202.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 03:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/13/3630900/3630900_0785F607F5E34B03A6F7D0B710808E34_180613_3630900_U_S__unveils_world_s_fastest_supercomputer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/336/8F2/3368F2E4AB7DBAA33E1CECE2F00DDE8C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Summit supercomputer, US Summit supercomputer, US fastest supercomputer, supercomputer, IBM Summit, NVidia Summit]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632149</guid>
      <title>Ancient Earth map lets you look up addresses across 750M years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Ever looked at a map of Earth millions of years ago and wondered where certain modern-day locations were supposed to be?The Ancient Earth globe is a cool little online tool curated by Ian Webster  the same genius who meticulously compiled the Dinosaur Database.Webster's interactive map allows users to see how the earth has evolved from 750 million years ago to the present. To do so, he adapted a software used by geologists to visualize plate tectonics, and overlaid his map with modern political boundaries. It's got the added bonus of an address search, so you can pin a location and see where it was during the ice age, the age of dinosaurs, or even post-extinction.The site has neat extras, like short descriptions on the bottom left hand side that lets you know exactly what the conditions are during any given time period.Alternatively, there's an option to jump through the stages of evolution, like when the first vertebrates appeared, or the first primates, or hominids.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 13:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3632149/3632149_BE0805C6F8AF456189D20C3638A32DAA_180614_3632149_Ancient_Earth_map_lets_you_look_up_addresses_acr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/87A/704/87A704160C93C233900DF51DE1E20340.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ancient earth map, ancient earth globe, interactive map, interactive globe, address search, map search, gplates, ian webster, dinosaur database]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632108</guid>
      <title>Apple to close iPhone security loophole used by cops, criminals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA  Apple is releasing a new software update that will make it much harder for police and criminals to crack iPhones to access data.The company said on Wednesday the update is called USB Restricted Mode and will close off data access through an iPhone's Lightning port if the device hasn't been unlocked in the past hour, CNET reports.The update is meant to close a security hole that left customers at risk to identity thieves.According to the company, "At Apple, we put the customer at the center of everything we design. We're constantly strengthening the security protections in every Apple product to help customers defend against hackers, identity thieves and intrusions into their personal data. We have the greatest respect for law enforcement, and we don't design our security improvements to frustrate their efforts to do their jobs."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 12:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3632108/3632108_13C22692E56E4D21B0090A2082D901FB_180614_3632108_Apple_to_close_iPhone_security_loophole_used_by__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1D0/0C0/1D00C01472FFCB7FE03FF301BAD4575D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Apple, Apple iPhone, Apple iPhone Restricted USB Mode, Restricted USB mode, Apple iPhone security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632013</guid>
      <title>Birdwatchers in India rescued bird with beak shut by plastic ring</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BASAI, INDIA  A bird in India with its beak clamped shut by a plastic ring was fortunately rescued by Indian birdwatchers who feared it would starve to death.Reported by The Times of India, the stork was rescued about 9 a.m. on Wednesday in Basai wetland, a suburb of India's capital.Luckily, the bird was rescued by birdwatchers and wildlife officials and was taken to a bird sanctuary for treatment. Surprisingly, the dehydrated bird was nibbling on a small fish and is in good condition despite living without food for at least seven days. Black-necked storks are classified as "near-threatened" on the Red List of threatened animals and are native to parts of India, Indonesia and Sri Lanka. But only 50-60 of the birds are found in the wetlands region outside Delhi.When the photo of the stork with its beak shut by the plastic ring emerged on the internet this week, it immediately captured attention from around the world. Pankaj Gupta, a bird watcher and member of the Delhi Bird Foundation, who was involved in the rescue mission said the plastic ring could have come from a bottle or can, and is likely to have slipped onto the bird's beak when it was hunting in the water, and then got stuck there.The stork is currently being looked after by officials of the Sultanpur National Park and bird sanctuary, they will put it back into its natural habitat once it's deemed fit. The BBC reported that environmentalists in India want the Basai area to be protected and are hoping to build a factory there to deal with the recycling construction waste.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 10:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3632013/3632013_DBC7B901F92940E082425B4DD117C8B3_180614_3632013_Birdwatchers_in_India_rescued_bird_with_beak_shu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/44C/D9E/44CD9E1AB3D4DCF5CBC20220ADA4700A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bird beak plastic, bird gets rescued, bird rescued india, bird rescued by people, animals trapped by plastic, birds trapped by plastic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631983</guid>
      <title>Insidious horror ads shown to kids ahead of YouTube Frozen clips</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  British kids were exposed to movie ads featuring a demonic monster attack ahead of videos showing Frozen and Minecraft clips.Britain's Ad-regulator the Advertising Standards Authority said kids had been shown adverts for the new Insidious movie, the BBC reports.Children were seeing these pre-roll ads in front of Lego how-tos, cartoons and the aforementioned Frozen and Minecraft videos.Columbia Pictures, a Sony company, said they were targeting adult audiences with the pre-rolls and had removed children and unknown audiences from their campaign targets.Google-owned YouTube says it lets advertisers control their campaigns and are responsible for their own content. The ads were apparently seen between December 2017 and January 2018 by kids and some adults, who complained they were distressing. The regulator claims it received five complaints in total. The pre-rolls for the movie, rated 15-years and older in the UK, showed women screaming, and a monster attacking a woman. The regulator told Sony to better target it's ads in the future, but according to the BBC, an investigation by the company found it to be YouTube's algorithms to be at fault.The BBC says in its report that it understands YouTube is "now limiting its ads for mature content to a pre-vetted list of safe YouTube channels." If true, that means less ad dollars for other creators through no fault of their own.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 10:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3631983/3631983_008B63FD8FE8491EACB3F68BE61A6B17_180614_3631983_Insidious_horror_ads_shown_to_kids_ahead_of_YouT_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/182/A48/182A4865B2B64E691EB13325CE40C4EE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,youtube ad fails,google ad sense,frozen insidious,frozen horror,minecraft insidious,frozen,lego how-to,asa,advertising standards authority,youtube scandal]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631970</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Episode 1 - knives vs taser</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured RAW by officers' body cams and dash cams from around the globe.THIS WEEK:1. Man attacks Welsh cops with two knives, gets tasered.2. Alleged drug driving carjacker leads pursued by Ocala, Florida cops through neighborhood.3. Vegan Seattle cop saves adorable little kitty thrown by "meth-addled" man.4. Car theft suspect's teary goodbye with Capuchin monkey.5. Police pursue impaired driver in Canada.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 10:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3631970/3631970_9871ECA83B2B478FB6BFCE0D4F16D71B_180614_3631970_LAWMAN_CAM__Episode_1___knives_vs_taser_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0F7/7E9/0F77E900B8AF11217250D70AE16B03E9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,latest police videos,new police videos,latest cop video,new cop footage,police footage,police body cam,police dash cam,police compilation 2018,cop videos,police chase 2018,latest police chase videos,crazy car chases,police pursuit,impaired driver,us police videos,cop camera,cop saves kitten,lawman cam,tomonews lawman cam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631956</guid>
      <title>Oakland 'Jogger Joe' throws out homeless man's stuff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OAKLAND, CALIFORNIA  Netizens are fuming after an online video captured a jogger throwing out a homeless person's belongings in Oakland.The incident occurred near Lake Merritt, close to where the now infamous BBQ Becky called the cops on two men for barbecuing while black, SFGate reports.On Friday, Henry Sintay, 30, was apparently so offended by a homeless man's things that he paused during a run and started dismantling the makeshift encampment.Bystanders confronted Sintay as he tossed stuff into the lake and a nearby garbage can. When asked to stop, he fired back that he was simply taking out the trash. JJ Harris, one of the bystanders, filmed the confrontation and put it up online. After video of his douchebaggery blew up, Sintay  now dubbed "Jogger Joe" by the internet  returned the next day to pull stuff out of the lake. While being asked questions by a community organizer, Jogger Joe attacked the man and stole his phone, not realizing it was live-streaming the whole thing.Sintay has since been nabbed by Oakland PD and is facing a felony charge of second-degree robbery, according to the San Francisco Chronicle.Supporters have also come together to help Drew, the homeless man whose belongings Sintay trashed. They gave him new blankets and clothes over the weekend and put up a GoFundMe page that has now amassed over $10,000.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 09:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3631956/3631956_A41F0E0D44C34793A191D90FE83B9763_180614_3631956_Oakland__Jogger_Joe__throws_out_homeless_man_s_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/207/DEE/207DEE0B6DD01EF8D42E17E5298FE7DF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, jogger joe, homeless man, lake merritt, oakland homeless, oakland, henry sintay, gentrification, bbq becky, barbecuing while black]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631746</guid>
      <title>Climate change maybe wiping out thousands-years-old trees</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AFRICA  Climate change maybe killing some of the world's most ancient and beautiful trees, according to new research. Writing in a new study in the journal Nature Plants, researchers detail how they tracked African Baobab trees using radiocarbon dating since 2000.According to Popular Science, the researchers looked at at 60 trees in total.Their findings report that nine of 13 oldest trees have began to perish, as have five of six larger ones. The deaths just began occurring in the last 12 years, scientists don't know particularly why.But they do have a guess and it's the usual suspect: climate change.Speaking to the Los Angeles Times via email, lead author Adrian Partut explained the trees were used to "drier and colder conditions, but possibly not to hotter conditions.Partut told the Times he and researchers suspect that the combination of "temperature increase and extreme drought stress were responsible for these demises."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 06:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3631746/3631746_5B06BB3935C44ED491A9FABFD7ADB902_180614_3631746_Climate_change_maybe_wiping_out_thousands_years__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A02/2EE/A022EE1F339579F45A0A57EA755080B2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, baobab trees, baobab climate change, baobab tree age, baobab tree size, global warming, nature]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631728</guid>
      <title>Trump has a bad case of dictator envy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Donald Trump made history this week as he met Kim Jong-un in Singapore.One thing that has become evidently clear is that Trump has a real affinity for dictators.While meeting with the G7, Trump proposed letting Vladimir Putin back into the G8, while at the same time just skipping over the invasion of Ukraine and annexation of Crimea. The problem is that as Trump gushes over dictators, he threatens the very democracy that protects the world from these evil douches. President Trump literally is the most powerful man in the world, yet he looks up to spineless autocrats and envies their "strength."  And with all this North Korea nonsense going on, Trump has once again been played, because it's not North Korea that is causing the problems in Asia  it's China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 05:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3631728/3631728_D13B01C3F5E34FE5A8A997E4600DF148_180614_3631728_Trump_has_a_bad_case_of_dictator_envy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D3C/140/D3C140D48DDEB1F4B4E6A2634F3DF9A0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Trump,Trump Kim Summit,Trump loves dictators,Trump Kim Jong-Un,Trump Putin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631694</guid>
      <title>Apple protects users by banning cryptocurrency mining apps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[US  Apple has set new rules for app developers which ban the creation of cryptocurrency mining apps on its mobile devices to protect iOS users, reports IT world.Apple is moving to stop the practice of hackers using a portion of the CPU power from thousands of different iPads or iPhones to mine cryptocurrency.Apparently, Apple has made several rule changes stating that any apps, "including third party advertisements..may not run unrelated background processes, such as cryptocurrency mining."ComputerWorld reports that the cryptocurrency-mining services "thrash your CPU, and  drain your battery."ComputerWorld also reports cryptocurrency services are known for spreading malware, reportedly being one of the top offenders of doing so.Apparently cryptocurrency services use a small piece of JavaScript it installs on websites, advertisements then uses the code to hijack part of the CPU power of the device to mine cryptocurrency. This practice is known as "cryptojacking."Cryptomining malware has been on the rise in the past year, following the rise of cryptocurrency, IT world reports. For now, Apple is the only one to ban cryptocurrency mining apps, however Google may soon join Apple in the decision.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 04:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3631694/3631694_8534D480E10C46DA8A23280568D17820_180614_3631694_Apple_protects_users_by_banning_cryptocurrency_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AC6/933/AC6933A4E3C294C630473045EB28348C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US, Cryptocurrency,Cryptocurrency News, Cryptocurrency 2018 Cryptocurrency Mining, Cryptocurrency Mining apps, Cryptocurrency Service, Cryptocurrency malware, Apple bans cryptocurrency mining apps]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3631587</guid>
      <title>Woman sues NASA just in case to keep her vial of moon dust</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KANSAS  A Tennessee woman is preemptively suing NASA in order to keep a vial of moon dust allegedly given to her by Neil Armstrong. The lawsuit was filed by Laura Murray Cicco on June 6 at the U.S. District Court in Kansas to decide who legally owns the dust, according to Cincinnati Enquirer.The woman is challenging NASA's 2011 court case declaration that private citizens cannot own lunar material.Cicco says in the lawsuit that her father was a friend of Neil Armstrong, and that when Armstrong was an aerospace engineering professor at the University of Cincinnati, he gave the vial to her as a gift. The lipstick-size vial also came with a note that said, "To Laura Ann Murray  Best of luck  Neal Armstrong Apollo 11."Well...good move Laura. Now the whole world knows that you have this moon dust  which you definitely could have kept no problem had you only kept your trap shut.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/14/3631587/3631587_0C1D1E89C8814750AE368E63C63364C3_180614_3631587_Woman_sues_NASA_just_in_case_to_keep_her_vial_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2CD/494/2CD49498FF1256779B5C9DC238F21354.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, moon, moon dust, woman sues NASA, woman sues NASA moon dust, Neil Armstrong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632694</guid>
      <title>Teen's head gets stuck in tailpipe of truck during music festival</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNESOTA  A young woman was attending the Winstock Music Festival in Minnesota when she apparently got her head stuck in the tailpipe of a truck, KARE 11 reports.Kaitlyn Strom, 19, commented saying she was just hanging out with friends and "having fun" when she "saw the exhaust pipe and thought she could probably fit in that."It was the first day of the festival when Strom got her head stuck in the tailpipe for around 45 minutes, reports Fox News.Strom told the Hutchinson Leader newspaper, she "was confused" and "didn't know what was going on."She also said she "trusted everyone who was around … to get me out safely."The Winsted Fire Department was called to "cut off the exhaust pipe" and free Strom's head, reports the Hutchinson Leader newspaper.After Strom's head was freed, she was taken for a medical test and "cited for underage drinking" by the McLeod County Sheriff's Department, KARE 11 reports.The video of Strom's rescue has gone viral on social media, having more than two million views.Strom later posted a picture on Facebook holding the exhaust pipe her head was stuck in and wrote, "Yeah I'm the tail pipe girl, whatchu know about it?"]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 09:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/15/3632694/3632694_5652E75EF8F04442BCA4924CAA0285E8_180615_3632694_Teen_s_head_gets_stuck_in_tailpipe_of_truck_duri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D0C/2B1/D0C2B1A87035A1A933AC7B05FE494E98.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Idiot, Teenager, Teen, Minnesota, US, Music Festival, Teens gets her head stuck, Teen gets her head stuck in exhaust pipe, tailpipe, getting stuck in a tailpipe, drinking, Teen drinking, Teen gets head stuck attending music festival, Video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632679</guid>
      <title>Porta-Potties in flight, afternoon delight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COMMERCE CITY, COLORADO  Winds were so strong in Commerce City the other day, they actual launched two porta-potties several stories up into the air.  The incident was captured and posted to Instagram by user Kingdemic and has already racked up over 3,000,000 views. The footage starts off with the two porta-potties placed by a parking lot. The strength of the wind can be heard on the man's phone. The wind then suddenly grabs both toilets and takes them airborne. One of the porta-potties reached an apex and then came be seen releasing its contents. No word on what type of injuries the porta-potties sustained from the flight.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 09:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/15/3632679/3632679_40273792BDB14F05941F11EFC331E7D7_180615_3632679_Porta_Potties_in_flight__afternoon_delight_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4FC/FBB/4FCFBBBB0A73F2025F48388B535D0ACB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, porta-potties, porta-potty, porta-potties take flight, porta-potties flying, porta potties in air]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632667</guid>
      <title>Dogs in BODYSUITS played Star Wars alien hounds in 'Solo'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[A KENNEL IN A GALAXY FAR, FAR AWAY  Monster alien canines in the film "Solo: A Star Wars Story" were actually played by real dogs wearing bodysuits.  A behind-the-scenes look at the film on this week's edition of the Star Wars Show on StarWars.com, gave fans a look at the planet of Corellia. Specifically, the show looked at the many practical effects employed, including the thick lycra bodysuits worn by dogs to portray the Corellian hounds.According to WOOKIE-pedia  no joke, real thing  these are "a fleet-footed, loud-barking, vicious species" that were "used for attack and hunting, but did not make good pets".StarWars.com writes that this canine named Saxon was specially trained to wear the lycra body suit. Saxon also played Nymeria, a Direwolf in season 7's Game of Thrones, where looking epic was all that was required.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 09:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/15/3632667/3632667_CF2649579C864AE8A96BA9BFA9B96A04_180615_3632667_Dogs_in_BODYSUITS_played_Star_Wars_alien_hounds__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7A0/D83/7A0D839060014A63ABA0C18F91272E85.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, star wars, solo, corellian hounds, star wars dogs, dog actors, acting dogs, got dog, game of thrones dog, dog in star wars, star wars dog, saxon dog, solo dogs, corellian hounds solo, star wars facts, sci fi, practical effects, behind the scenes, han solo, chewbacca, millenium falcon, movie magic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632615</guid>
      <title>NASA's Mars rover gets stuck in dust storm, agency loses contact</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE RED PLANET  NASA lost contact with their Mars-based Opportunity robot this week after a massive dust storm set about its position on Mars.That storm has, according to the space agency, made it almost completely dark, making it hard for the solar powered machine to operate. Curiosity, NASA's other Martian rover, is nuclear powered and not reliant on the sun. The space agency believes that the robot has entered low power mode where only a mission clock remains active. NASA reckons the large amounts of dust it has encountered will stop it from charging for some time. The dust storm, active since May 30, covers some 14 million square miles of Mars. For comparison, that's more than double the size of Russia  Earth's largest country.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 07:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/15/3632615/3632615_BD24F1C9D6754FF4A0FB1EAB6403B33D_180615_3632615_NASA_s_Mars_rover_gets_stuck_in_dust_storm__agen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4AE/2ED/4AE2ED00F910B48FAA92EEA7808BC4FA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, mars, mars rover, mars rover opportunity, nasa rover, nasa mars, mars videos, dust storm, mars dust storm, mars weather, martian landscape, alien weather, space videos, NASA, NASA opportunity]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3632389</guid>
      <title>Organization sheds light on the practice of eating dog meat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VIETNAM The World Dog Alliance is shining a spotlight on the hidden truth of dog meat consumption throughout Asia, especially in Vietnam.Reportedly more than 80% of the population of Vietnam consumes dog meat, with dogs being killed, burned, and grilled in open areas as well as restaurants.Some restaurants even emphasize the idea that "eating dog meat can change your fate," with dog meat often being served as a traditional dish.The dogs are put in tiny cages where they suffer from overheating, hunger and dehydration and are transported to different regions across Vietnam.Upon arriving at the slaughterhouse, the organization says dogs are force-fed to fatten them up, while dog meat traders hold the dogs down with a clamp while doing so. Locals even believe that the quality of the dog meat is better if "the dog was miserable before dying."The high demand of dog meat is a result of the Vietnamese belief that dog meat is "rich in protein" and "eating tough meat meat makes a tough man."The trade is lucrative in Vietnam because of high profits stemming from high demand.Dog traders can purchase a dog in Thailand for 5 to 7 US dollars and sell it in Vietnam for 100 US dollars.However because dog meat is so popular, dog traders often resort to stealing pets, street dogs, or even smuggling dogs in Vietnam or from other neighboring countries for a profit.This is a very pressing issue regarding the abuse and torture of these canines.Unfortunately YouTube often chooses to demonetize videos highlighting such atrocities, which ultimately does not help in shining a light on this issue.The World Dog Alliance claims it is the only organization dedicated to 'explicit legislation against dog meat' worldwide, and says it is working to expose the true nature and cruelty of the dog meat trade across the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 02:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/15/3632389/3632389_E6385ACE597649AD96D59E9782778B29_180615_3632389_Organization_sheds_light_on_the_practice_of_eati_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/199/69D/19969D3DF8ED945C37BD6F86CE1E7C5C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Dog meat, Practice of eating dog meat, Eating dog meat, Dogs in Vietnam, Vietnamese Dog meat,  Dog meat in Vietnam, Dog meat trade, Bringing attention to the practice of eating dog meat, World Dog Alliance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634584</guid>
      <title>Gamers are raging mad over Black Ops 4 season pass</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA MONICA, CALIFORNIA   The season pass for Call of Duty: Black Ops 4 will only be available with editions of the game costing $100 or more. The regular game will cost around 60 bucks, but in order to get access to the season pass gamers will need to shell out much more.Activision says it will be available separately but when and at what price is not known. According to Activision, the only way to get it at launch will be to buy one of three editions priced higher than the standard edition. Those are the Digital Deluxe version for around $100, Digital Deluxe Enhanced at $129.99 and the Pro Edition for $120.A season pass is something players can buy that typically provides players access to content beyond the original game. They're usually sold in a bundle or separately.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 09:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634584/3634584_178AAEAC01CB47118F1538C9C6D39BC5_180618_3634584_Gamers_are_raging_mad_over_Black_Ops_4_season_pa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1CE/364/1CE364E91FC3A9A64B990083293E5280.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, call of duty black ops 4, cod black ops 4, microtransactions, activision, gamers, fps, cod bo4]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634549</guid>
      <title>Deadly plant that causes burns, blindness spotted in Virginia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CLARKE COUNTY, VIRGINIA  Virginians are being warned to keep their eyes out for the giant hogweed plant, which can cause third-degree burns and even blindness.Thirty of the deadly plants were recently found at a site in Clarke County, according to the Massey Herbarium at Virginia Tech, though they've been known to grow in other states.Giant hogweeds are huge and invasive. They grow up to 14 feet and have sharply lobed leaves, umbrella-shaped white flowers, and hollow, hairy, purple-splotched stems, according to the New York Department of Environmental Conservation.Their sap contains toxins called furanocoumarins, which can make human skin hypersensitive to sunlight.If not washed and covered immediately, the skin can develop itchy burning blisters, with scarring, discoloration, and sometimes persistent sun sensitivity that can last years. The sap has also been known to cause temporary or permanent blindness when it comes in contact with the eyes.Experts strongly advise against taking out the plant with a weed whacker, since the sap could splatter and spread.Physical removal or the use of herbicides is a much more effective  not to mention safer  option. Or, just call it in and leave it to the pros.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 09:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634549/3634549_E7396060FFEB485EBE8862BD2AE87889_180618_3634549_Deadly_plant_that_causes_burns__blindness_spotte_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/973/51E/97351E16C5D74670A081382C2C2A0BBD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, deadly plant, dangerous plants, toxic plants, giant hogweed, poisonous plants, toxic sap, blisters, sunburn, sun exposure, photosensitivity, phytophotodermatitis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634500</guid>
      <title>Tourist center ceiling collapse on top of tourists in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUAYIN CITY, CHINA  CCTV footage shows a shocking scene where a ceiling collapsed on top of tourists who were riding down on an escalator in northwestern China on Saturday.At a popular Chinese tourist spot in Huayin City, Shanxi province, tourists on the escalator were seen looking up in fear as the ceiling suddenly collapsed on top of them.Spectators quickly ran over to help to remove the debris and escort the injured tourists away from the scene, luckily, no one was seriously hurt. Nine injured tourists were taken to Huayin People's Hospital for treatment while the tourist centre is working with local authorities to establish the cause of the collapse, the facility will remain closed for now.According to Hong Kong's Oriental Daily News, out of the nine injured tourists, three of them are still in the hospital for treatment, while the rest await medical checkups.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 08:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634500/3634500_5FC5B03E73864933AB58BDA2ED25BDC5_180618_3634500_Tourist_center_ceiling_collapse_on_top_of_touris_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B42/3A7/B423A7E9C2819A167F48924A58F9DAAA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, cctv collapse, ceiling collapse in china, tourist center collapse, ceiling fall off, ceiling fall off in china, tourist center china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634486</guid>
      <title>Dog saves missing baby girl by barking to alert the authorities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MISSOURI   A dog led a search team to a 3-year-old girl's rescue with a "weak bark," reports ABC News.Remy Merritt, the 3-year-old girl, had gone missing on Thursday around 8:30 p.m. with her dog, Fat Heath. A rescue team consisting of 150 volunteers were frantically looking for the pair that went missing Thursday night, reports WTOP.The search team wasn't able to find them during the night so they continued at dawn, where "everyone in the small farm town chipped in ..."The rescue team used a grid search through the cornfield "filled with 5-foot high stalks."One of the canines from the rescue team barked, which is when they heard Fat Heath respond with a "weak bark," WTOP reports.The search party swiftly followed the sound of the bark and found Merritt and the dog together.The two were reportedly in "good shape" and had "only been bitten by mosquitoes" and were "a little thirsty."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634486/3634486_1A8D58A0E0EC4CAEA560727F2C329F32_180618_3634486_Dog_saves_missing_baby_girl_by_barking_to_alert__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4F6/217/4F621760265AF6025D8F01B7F132F642.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News,US, Missouri, Dog, Yorkie, Yorkshire terrier,Yorkshire terrier bark,  weak bark, toddler, search party, weak bark, cornfield, dog alerts search party, dog leads rescuers to missing baby, missing child]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634449</guid>
      <title>Drunk woman says something racist on video, loses two jobs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS  A woman has been kicked out of the United States Air Force Reserve after she was filmed mouthing a racial slur.Missouri woman Tabitha Duncan was videod last week responding to question "So we going n-word hunting today or what?"  Duncan can be seen in the video saying, "You get them n-%^$!."She was a waitress and a Air Force reservist but after footage of her dropping an n-bomb went viral she's now lost both roles. Speaking to the New York Daily News, Duncan said she's sorry and has black friends and family.She explained she didn't know she was being recorded, adding was she was drunk, underage drinking said something stupid. Her employer, the Social Bar and Grill in Missouri said she was immediately fired for making a vile, disgusting and offensive video.According to Military.com, the U.S. Air Force is also kicking her out of the reserves.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 07:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634449/3634449_B7B6226E814549CB9370CDCD37A59C54_180618_3634449_Drunk_woman_says_something_racist_on_video__lose_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1FA/10F/1FA10FE93C698975111ECD64F6F2C957.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, tabitha duncan, waitress racist rant, drunk things, caught on camera,  air force, air force reserve, social bar and grill, st louis, missouri]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634388</guid>
      <title>Georgia grandma kills rabid bobcat with bare hands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HART COUNTY, GEORGIA  This may well be the world's most badass grandma, who managed to fight off and end a big wild cat with nothing but her bare hands.According to the Athens Banner-Herald, the attack went down around 6 p.m. on June 7. DeDe Phillips had just put a bumper sticker on her new truck that read, "Women who behave rarely make history", and wanted to snap a photo for her husband.While walking out of her Hart County, Georgia home with phone in hand and camera app at the ready, she spotted a bobcat in her yard and managed take a picture before it pounced.As the daughter-in-law of a bobcat trapper, Phillips knew the animal would go straight for her jugular, so she grabbed it by the shoulders and took it to the ground.The 46-year-old managed to get her hands on the feline's throat, and squeezed, not once screaming for help in case her 5-year-old granddaughter heard her and came running out.She shouted for help only when it stopped moving, and didn't release her grip until her son had stabbed the animal multiple times to make sure it was dead.Phillips sustained bruises, broken fingers, and puncture wounds on her hands and arms from her encounter with the bobcat, which she learned the next day was rabid.She's had to get treated for rabies, and has had the first round of painful shots, which cost an eye-popping $10,000. With no insurance and four more rounds to go, Phillips' cousin has set up a Fundly account to help raise money for her medical expenses.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 06:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634388/3634388_FBADF3280CB24FCEA57649BA9450315A_180618_3634388_Georgia_grandma_kills_rabid_bobcat_with_bare_han_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AB5/22D/AB522DFEE45F4EC673641C46CE4E1ACA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, grandma vs bobcat, bobcat, grandma strangles bobcat, grandma kills bobcat, wild animal attack, rabid bobcat, rabid animal, rabies, world's toughest grandma, badass grandma, dede philipps]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634376</guid>
      <title>Video shows Native American man struck by border patrol vehicle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOHONO O'ODHAM NATION, ARIZONA  Authorities are investigating claims of a Native American man who says a border patrol vehicle ran over him, reports CBS News.The incident apparently took place last Thursday night in a Native American reservation between the U.S. Mexico border in southern Arizona.In a video posted on Facebook, Paulo Remes, appears to be hit by a border patrol vehicle, which is then seen driving away. Remes recorded the entire incident, and told the Arizona Daily Star that he ran into the dirt road in front of his house, because he knew they would try and hit him.Remes was then taken to a hospital for minor bruising.Tribal leaders of the Tohono O'odham Nation, a Native American reservation, claim they often run into Border patrol agents as they are on the lookout for illegal immigrants and drug traffickers.Border Patrol released a statement saying they "do not tolerate misconduct on or off duty and will fully cooperate with all investigations."Remes' family commented saying they hope the video would "contribute to greater justice for … all victims of Border Patrol violence.."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 05:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634376/3634376_DC49AFEE44CF4B0E85542BF0078CCABD_180618_3634376_Video_shows_Native_American_man_struck_by_border_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3DF/8AA/3DF8AA69351D42D4E7ACD65941DA40D2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US, Native Americans, border patrol, Arizona, Native Americans Reservations, Border Patrol runs over man, Border patrol hits native american,Native American man hit by border patrol vehicle, border patrol agent]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3634307</guid>
      <title>Indonesian woman gets swallowed by massive python</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PERSIAPAN LAWELA, INDONESIA  An Indonesian woman who went missing last week was unfortunately discovered in the stomach of a 23-foot python. According to the AFP, 54-year-old Wa Tiba went missing Thursday night while taking care of her vegetable garden. When she failed to come back from her garden, around 100 villagers and family members went looking for her. They found the seven-meter long python about 30 meters from Tiba's sandals and machete. Residents killed the python and found Tiba had been swallowed head first and her body was discovered intact.  Giant pythons have been known to take down small animals, but attacks on people are rare. Guess that's not really important to Tiba.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 04:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/18/3634307/3634307_7C3DB07040414A28A3820521140A3052_180618_3634307_Indonesian_woman_gets_swallowed_by_massive_pytho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE1/529/CE1529E60C1283C6472EA368E767F189.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, python, giant python, huge python, massive python, python swallows, python eats, python indonesia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3635389</guid>
      <title>WAS THAT A UFO?! Weird cloud spotted over World Cup stadium</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST RUSSIA  An object travelling at speed in the Russian sky and the odd cloud left in its wake over a World Cup venue was not due to aliens.Citing ROSCOSMOS, the Russian space agency,  the Moscow Times reports the whole thing was the re-entry trail from a launch vehicle.According to the Metro, a woman who posted video of the event said she'd never seen anything like it. An object can be seen travelling at speed and then going so fast, a rocket trail forms behind it in the shape of an odd cloud.Onlookers, were quite naturally amazed, with some speculating it maybe aliens and another adding they've arrived for the World Cup.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 12:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/19/3635389/3635389_1F518F59A04342FAB0A8DCAB9EDDAC95_180619_3635389_WAS_THAT_A_UFO___Weird_cloud_spotted_over_World__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C90/808/C90808ED616D55D73A28EFA1B964B85D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, world cup, fifia world cup, world cup aliens, world cup aliens ufo, weird sky, russia ufo, russia aliens, aliens, weird clouds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3635297</guid>
      <title>ER doctor mocks patient who said he was having trouble breathing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS GATOS, CALIFORNIA  A Northern California emergency room doctor has been suspended for being an all around crappy human being.Cell phone video shows her mocking, ridiculing and cursing out a young b-ball player, who suffers from extreme anxiety attacks. According to ABC News, Samuel Bardwell, 20, suffers from anxiety attacks and takes the sedative Klonopin to treat the affliction. Samuel ran out of his prescription and hadn't had time to get it refilled, so that's why he ended up in the hospital emergency at El Camino Hospital in Los Gatos.Enter the 57-year-old human blob, Dr. Beth Keegstra. Keegstra proceeds to mock, yank and verbally spar with Samuel and his father Donald Bardwell.Keegstra then argues with Samuel and his father whether he's just trying to get drugs. When Samuel told her that he could not "inhale," Keegstra laughed it off saying, "He can't inhale. Wow! He must be dead.""Are you dead, sir? I don't understand. You are breathing just fine."El Camino Hospital has suspended Dr. Keegstra from all facilities connected to the hospital.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 10:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/19/3635297/3635297_1584A1DAC4F94407B1E4CD12C4AC64D4_180619_3635297_ER_doctor_mocks_patient_who_said_he_was_having_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/95F/59C/95F59CAECC411858F5B658DB5896C1BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ER doctor mocking patient, doctor mocks patient, Dr Beth Keegstra, Dr Beth Keegstra suspended, Dr. Beth Keegstra mocks patient]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3635208</guid>
      <title>Florida trapper saves gator from 10-foot-long python</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FORT LAUDERDALE, FLORIDA  An Everglades alligator would have been snake chow if not for a man who saved it from a suffocating death.The Miami Herald reports that Florida trapper Mike Kimmel and friend Jack Hubbard had spotted the python near some bushes, and realized as they approached that it was wrapped around a small gator.In a video posted to Facebook, Kimmel is seen grabbing the 10-foot-long snake by the head and lifting it up. The python is still coiled around its prey, but soon releases its grip.The 4-foot gator falls to the ground and quickly scurries away, but the snake isn't so lucky. Like all the others Kimmel's caught, it'll be euthanized and turned over to the state for study. Once it's given back, he claims its skin is sold and its meat used as well.As a contractor for the South Florida Water Management District's snake removal program, Kimmel says this is the third gator he's saved from a python in the past year.The invasive snakes were likely introduced to the Everglades via the exotic pet trade, and have since displaced gators as the top predator.In the last year alone, Kimmel and other contractors have removed over a thousand pythons  but the problem is persistent, and won't go away anytime soon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 09:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/19/3635208/3635208_D56F7738B00D433D8C1774862F78D1F5_180619_3635208_Florida_trapper_saves_gator_from_10_foot_long_py_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/72B/77B/72B77BD820E179DC79BE301D06469EAF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, gator vs python, gator, alligator, python eating gator, python, everglades, everglades python, everglades python problem, python problem, invasive species, burmese python, snake removal, snake trapper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3635164</guid>
      <title>Tesla Model S bursts into flames on Los Angeles street</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Tesla was on fire over the weekend after a video of Tesla Model S bursting into flames for no apparent reason went viral last Friday.According to the Washington Post, the clip was posted on Twitter by actress Mary McCormack, who said it was her husband's.In a since deleted tweet, McCormack said, "this is what happened to my husband and his car today. No accident, out of the blue, in traffic on Santa Monica Blvd." Tesla said the video looked like a battery fire and that car blazes are an "extraordinarily unusual occurrence."According to a Tesla spokesman, "our initial investigation shows that the cabin of the vehicle was totally unaffected by the fire due to our battery architecture, which is designed to protect the cabin in the very event that a battery fire occurs."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 08:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/19/3635164/3635164_7B82DA580CE9486A88610C9E332EBDC8_180619_3635164_Tesla_Model_S_bursts_into_flames_on_Los_Angeles__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F7E/8D2/F7E8D264AFC866EDB1B3DA2810F4DFE5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Tesla, Tesla catches fire, Tesla fire, Tesla Model S fire, Tesla Model S catches fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636330</guid>
      <title>Harvard sued over admissions bias against Asian Americans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  A group representing Asian-American students has filed a lawsuit against Harvard, citing discriminatory admissions practices.According to court documents, Students for Fair Admissions commissioned an analysis of applicant records from 2014 to 2019, and found that Asian-Americans were consistently rated lower than others on personality traits, despite having high SAT scores, GPAs and full extracurriculars.In the 1920s, Harvard and other Ivy League schools used the same subjective criteria to limit the number of Jewish students. Now Asians are getting the Jewish treatment and are being given low personal ratings to hurt their chances of getting in.Duke University economist Peter Arcidiacono, the expert who conducted the analysis for Students for Fair Admissions, says the low scores were from admissions officers who've often never even seen the students in the flesh. Meanwhile, alumni interviewers who actually met the applicants consistently gave top marks.Students for Fair Admissions alleges that Harvard knew what was up. The university's own internal investigation in 2013 revealed a biased system. But instead of addressing the issue, it axed the investigation and buried the reports.The school has denied the allegations, defending their process as "holistic" and claiming that Students for Fair Admissions cherry-picked variables from the admissions data to fit their cause.At the end of the day, it could be argued that Harvard admissions only wants what's best for the school, but if that involves racial discrimination, then obviously there's something wrong.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 13:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/20/3636330/3636330_D27F2AE9A0F04E4DA0487CC5659DE151_180620_3636330_Harvard_sued_over_admissions_bias_against_Asian__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/882/192/88219204A191531C90F5E768D6577916.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, harvard, harvard admissions, asian americans, discrimination, bias, racial bias, racial discrimination, school admission, university admission, ivy league, harvard demographic, jewish treatment, quota]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636309</guid>
      <title>U.S. expecting North Korea to return troop remains</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The United States is expecting North Korea to return up to 200 sets of remains believed to be troops who died during the Korean War.According to CNN, administration officials said arrangements are being made to accept the remains, although no set date or location have been yet been determined. The Defense Department says there are up to 5,300 sets of U.S. service member remains still in North Korea, with a total of 7,697 personnel still missing in action. Some of the remains were from downed pilots, others from ground troops, while others may be those who died as prisoners of war. When the transfer does occur, it is expected North Korean officials will give the remains to United Nations officials at the DMZ. The UN will then hand them over to U.S. military personnel. The remains will then be sent to a military laboratory in Hawaii for DNA identification and matching.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 12:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/20/3636309/3636309_14F374AFB4D541D4B037EEB06E3AE94B_180620_3636309_U_S__expecting_North_Korea_to_return_troop_remai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9E8/189/9E8189330FB0D7B51E00E90FCD49CB71.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Korean War, US troop remains, North Korea, North Korea US troop remains, US servicemember remains]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636299</guid>
      <title>Dad shows how easy kids can fall into pools in terrifying video</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATTLEBORO, MASSACHUSETTS  A Massachusetts dad is sending out an important warning on pool safety after seeing how easily his toddler could fall into a pool.CBS reports that Keith Wyman was shocked the first time he witnessed his son Cody climb up a locked pool ladder. The second time, he was ready with a camera.The Wymans' pool is above ground, with a small ladder and a door that closes over the steps to prevent access. But in a video posted to Facebook, Cody can be seen putting his feet in between the door slots and hoisting himself up.The 2-year-old makes it to the rim of the pool in less than a minute before being grabbed by mom and returned to the ground.The couple have since returned the ladder and are trying to get the manufacturer to change the design to make it really childproof.In the meantime, Wyman advises parents to watch their kids like a hawk, and be especially vigilant when there's a pool nearby.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 12:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/20/3636299/3636299_4A1F8C585A554FE4AFC99079CFE6C6E9_180620_3636299_Dad_shows_how_easy_kids_can_fall_into_pools_in_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3EF/4C9/3EF4C97623E0FBF212A6892BB6C2C66A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, pool safety, pool accidents, child lock, child proof, pool, pool ladder, pool lock, backyard pool, toddler falls into pool, child falls into pool, terrible twos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636161</guid>
      <title>Rescued pit bulls get their own cottages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EUGENE, OREGON  When you stop by most animal shelters, many of the animals are locked up in cages, however one Oregon shelter decided to go all out with their pooch palaces. The Luvable Dog Rescue is located in Eugene, Oregon and sits on 55 acres of trees, trails and the great outdoors. The shelter offers rescued pit bulls a home-like environment featuring cozy, colorful cabins, furnitures, and other creature comforts.Watching the pits interact in a home setting can help staff inform potential adopters. The shelter's executive director Liesl Wilhardt told PupJournal that the shelter is to make each dog's stay as comfortable and stress-free as possible. Wilhardt said she built the "pit bull palace" to make dogs feel more comfortable. She also hopes to build a maternity ward for doggie moms.The rescue is currently home to 10 pit bulls and 30 small breed dogs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 09:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/20/3636161/3636161_9E0B3F2C83964DCC8E51BCC34DDC595C_180620_3636161_Rescued_pit_bulls_get_their_own_cottages_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/009/713/009713F151A097FFE6877121E167EADE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, animal shelters, animal shelters animal rescue, animal shelters cages, animal shelter cottage oregon, luvable dog rescue, luvable dog rescue eugene, luvable dog rescue cottages, luvable dog rescue adoptable dogs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636107</guid>
      <title>WHO labels gaming addiction a disorder but experts disagree</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA  Video game addiction is now a disease, according to the Word Health Organization, and it's being called "gaming disorder."The WHO says the disorder can manifest in individuals who are obsessed with videogames, particularly those who game longer and do it in place of other activities.They also warn the disorder may hurt relationships with family and friends and activities in work and school. For a gaming disorder diagnosis an individual needs to show symptoms for around a year, according to the WHO.In a December 2016 paper, a plethora of experts from the world over refuted the WHO classification. Writing then, they argued that the gaming disorder definition "should be removed to avoid a waste of public health resources as well as to avoid causing harm to healthy video gamers around the world."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 09:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/20/3636107/3636107_910A14893E9F4652B6909108C4A2E153_180620_3636107_WHO_labels_gaming_addiction_a_disorder_but_exper_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6C3/2F1/6C32F10B4393AF3406AB060F30B8E56F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, who gaming disorder, gaming disorder, gaming addiction, video game addiction, gamers, video game news, united nations, who gaming disorder, who gaming disease, video game news, gaming news, technology, nintendo, sony, microsoft]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3635804</guid>
      <title>Sea creatures fall from the sky during powerful storm in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QINGDAO, CHINA  Sea creatures that were seen falling from the sky in Qingdao, a coastal city in China, on June 13.This was the result of having been picked up by a powerful storm, reports The Sun.Chinese local media reports the weather was erratic during those few days, resulting in powerful Hurricane-force winds that sucked up sea creatures and "spat them out" before hitting land.The powerful storm was reported to have caused widespread destruction throughout the city.Apparently, waterspouts were caused by the storm in the Yellow Sea, which resulted in sea creatures such as shrimp, octopus, starfish and mollusks being cast into the sky.Locals were reportedly "stunned" upon seeing the marine creatures falling from the heavens.The phrase "seafood rain" trended on Chinese social media as locals shared their pictures of the event online.The Mirror reports the city's meteorological service said wind speeds generated from the storm set an "new all-time record" for June, reports The Mirror.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 02:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/20/3635804/3635804_CAB07AAFDFEA4F59AA05012A41183ADF_180620_3635804_Sea_creatures_fall_from_the_sky_during_powerful__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5ED/F35/5EDF3515AF104FE1288D0670F8C4F504.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, Animals,China sea creatures, Sea creatures, Octopus, Starfish, sea creatures falling from the sky, seaport city, violent weather, sea creatures sucked by storm, marine life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3635792</guid>
      <title>Seals forced to dive off cliffs after teens throw rocks at them</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWCASTLE, ENGLAND  A group of teens in England's northeast were caught on camera throwing rocks at seals.Posted by St. Mary's Seal Watch, three teens moved a warning sign on St. Mary's Island Nature Reserve near Newcastle before approaching a seal, then began throwing rocks at the poor animal.The seal got so scared that it dived off a cliff to escape into the water. Once it got away, the group began to throw more rocks at other animals.One teen filmed the whole thing on her phone, and St. Mary's Seal Watch shared the video on their Facebook page, saying it happened at about 9 p.m. on June 9. The group stressed that this was not to shame anyone in the video but to highlight the problems the wildlife faces on the reserve.The Seal Watch group went on to explain that, without protection, St. Mary's Island Nature Reserve is not safe for the wildlife.St. Mary's Seal Watch also urged visitors to report anyone they see ignoring signs or causing similar harassment of wildlife.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 02:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/20/3635792/3635792_4CC4D62D35164E589C4410FD4DB84C4A_180620_3635792_Seals_forced_to_dive_off_cliffs_after_teens_thro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/805/4D0/8054D0125AAAFFB8F37152C82EEDC670.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, throw rocks at, throw rocks at seals, throw rocks at animals, british teens, animals dive off, seals dive off, newcastle england]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637032</guid>
      <title>Oh Canada is legalizing recreational buddha</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OTTAWA, CANADA  Prime Minister Justin Trudeau has announced that Canadians will able to blaze the stick-icky recreationally starting Oct. 17. Trudeau is giving the green light to brick and mortar shops, online sales as well as growers.The government estimated it would take eight to 12 weeks between the passage of the bill and full legalization to take effect to give provinces enough time to get everything set up and in place.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 12:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3637032/3637032_EB8301C09BFB46EBBA8DE62663BF9D06_180621_3637032_Oh_Canada_is_legalizing_recreational_buddha_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/465/824/4658246D6DD5E6632DECC7444547DAC2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Canada legalizes, Canada recreational, Canada passes legalization, Canada leaf]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637002</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Ep. 2 - WATCH OUT!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured RAW from cops around the globe.THIS WEEK: 1. Helicopters make a chopper sandwich in Pasadena, California.2. Female Florida Highway Trooper chases down suspect who struck her patrol car.3. Illinois cop saves toddler running on busy highway4. The NYPD scuba unit dive into action to rescue two downed kayakers]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 11:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3637002/3637002_EE292992544048A6A0CA4F88DEFEB433_180621_3637002_LAWMAN_CAM__Ep__2___WATCH_OUT__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D8E/18F/D8E18FAB6A133622EC991159179119E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, female cop, good cop, hero cops, cops doing amazing things, female cop takes down man, latest police videos, new police videos,  latest cop video, new cop footage, police footage, police body cam, police dash cam, police compilation 2018, cop videos, police chase 2018, latest police chase videos, crazy car chases, police pursuit, impaired driver, us police videos, cop camera, cop saves kitten, lawman cam, tomonews lawman cam, pit technique, police responding, police news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636832</guid>
      <title>American infants are basically black holes for processed sugar</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SUGARLAND  A new study by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention finds that U.S. infants are consuming excessive amounts of sugar that even exceed maximum levels recommended for some adults. The results were presented at the American Society for Nutrition's annual meeting on June 10, Quartz reports.Researchers focused on the sugar added during food preparation or processing such as cane sugar, high-fructose corn syrup and honey, not natural sugars found in fruit or milk.  The study looked at more than 800 children between six months and 23 months who had taken part in the 2011 to 2014 National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey. Parents were told to keep track of every item their child ate or drank during a 24-hour period. Scientists then calculated an average sugar intake from the sample.The results showed toddlers 12 to 18 months consumed 5.5 teaspoons of sugar per day, while toddlers 19 to 23 months ate 7.1 teaspoons a day.For comparison, the daily recommended limits for added sugar for children 2 to 19 years old and adult women is 6 teaspoons or less a day, and 9 teaspoons or less a day for adult men.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3636832/3636832_56A90CA84C1D407385FE3D543E9EF80D_180621_3636832_American_infants_are_basically_black_holes_for_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/447/F56/447F5607DE73DC228FAC9C91959380DA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, sugar, sugar consumption, toddler sugar consumption, baby sugar consumption, CDC study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636781</guid>
      <title>Woman gets eyeliner stuck in her eye while doing makeup in taxi</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BANGKOK, THAILAND  A woman in Bangkok, Thailand learned not to wear her makeup in a moving taxi the hard way after the vehicle slammed into a truck.The unnamed woman, in her 20s, was applying eyeliner in a slow moving traffic jam in Din Daeng[b] area of Bangkok. Suddenly, the driver crashed into a pick-up truck in front of them, and the impact was so strong that it forced the eyeliner pencil into her left eye socket.Paramedics came quickly. Luckily, the pencil missed the vital parts of her eye and her sight will be unaffected.The woman was taken to the hospital, where doctors were able to remove the pencil without further injuring the woman's eye.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 07:46:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3636781/3636781_B0B5FD3C6DB744C19FDB01236A3952DC_180621_3636781_Woman_gets_eyeliner_stuck_in_her_eye_while_doing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3E0/513/3E0513873830082E491D6A8EBE15E460.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, makeup horror, makeup horror stories, eyeliner pencil, in the eye, makeup horror stories, pencil in the eye, bangkok thailand]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636698</guid>
      <title>Body parts found in cracked nose of Japanese bullet train</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN  Human body parts were found in a cracked part of the nose of a bullet train in Japan, reports The Asahi Shimbun.According to Japan Times, the driver of the train heard a strange sound coming out of his train but decided to keep going without informing the control center.The driver "thought he had hit an animal" and decided it wasn't serious enough to report, reports The Asahi Shimbun.The train driver of another bullet train noticed the crack in the nose of the bullet train.He then notified the control center, who in turn quickly notified the police and halted the train.Officers examined the bonnet and shockingly found human body parts inside the crack.After the incident, the West Japan Railway Co. is encouraging drivers not to be reckless and halt the train if they suspect anything out of the ordinary.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 05:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3636698/3636698_DF9F84C503C844D88025C509063DEB12_180621_3636698_Body_parts_found_in_cracked_nose_of_Japanese_bul_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/00B/D45/00BD4514FF4BC9FCCFE1529A6FF1A655.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Japan, Bullet Train, Japanese Bullet Train, Bullet Train Japan, Human Body parts found, Human Body parts found in bullet train, body parts found in bullet train]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636658</guid>
      <title>Indian forest ranger strangled by python posing for selfie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INDIA   A forest ranger in eastern India was almost strangled to death by a python while trying to take a selfie with it. The locals had called for help in capturing the poisonous python, which had reportedly just offed a goat.Mr. Speaks-With-Snakes showed up and captured the slithering reptile. But that's not all.According to the Khaleej Times, he then decided to pose with the serpent while locals gathered around and took selfies.Then for some strange reason, the snake started twisting and turning around the man's neck. Fortunately, the locals saved the ranger's rear end. The snake was later released into the wild.The forest ranger commented to AFP saying his first instinct was "to rescue the snake." So was his second instinct to get strangled by the snake?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 04:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3636658/3636658_1A590E3150994C558526193863808506_180621_3636658_Indian_forest_ranger_strangled_by_python_posing__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C44/881/C4488182D52716BC03EF84B57300F6F2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, India, Python snake, Selfie, Forest ranger, man almost strangled to death by python while posing for selfie, Python attack, Python strangling man]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636581</guid>
      <title>Quebec realizes blockchains could fry their grid, ups rates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEBEC, CANADA  Access to Quebec's power grid is going to cost new cryptocurrency miners triple.This week Quebec increased energy prices for new blockchain companies by 300 percent to 15 cents per kilowatt hour, reports Bloomberg. The province is powered entirely by renewable energy sources, and most of this comes from hydropower. Bloomberg reports new blockchain energy requests would go beyond what Quebec can provide power for in the short and medium-term.  State-owned provincial power administrator Hydro-Quebec will keep the rate in place for several weeks until a new power limit and pricing model is calculated.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 02:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3636581/3636581_D40DFEC4E79B4E5199BAC11F5A64077C_180621_3636581_Quebec_realizes_blockchains_could_fry_their_grid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/90D/477/90D4779829AB3B378BD380C99BB9C500.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Quebec, Quebec energy, Quebec crypto currency, bitcoin mining, cryptocurrency, cryptocurrency power, blockchain, blockchain power needs, bitcoin mining power needs, bitcoin power consumption, bitcoin mining hardware, bitcoin mining hardware setup]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3636577</guid>
      <title>Ancestral bacteria of plague found on almost 4,000-year-old teeth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAMARA, RUSSIA  Scientists have unearthed findings that changes current thinking on how old the plague is. Research published in the journal Nature Communication describes how scientists found the bacterium Yersinia Pestis on the teeth of 3,800-year-old human remains in Samara, Russia.Researchers looked at the remains of nine people, two of them had the bacteria.Yersinia Pestis gave rise to the bubonic plague. The scientist used sequencing to analyze the samples and found that they pre-date current thinking on the plague's lineage  3,000 years  by around 1,000 years. Researchers suggest that there was at least two strains of plague lineage floating around at the time. Previously it was suggested to be one.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/21/3636577/3636577_F5A32482EEBA49CD8A2B192F8BA338C9_180621_3636577_Ancestral_bacteria_of_plague_found_on_almost_4_0_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ABE/A25/ABEA254EBD1B057951D6151CDC227BDD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, ancient findings unearthed, the bubonic plague, the plague, ancient findings, ancient research, ancient civilizations, Russia, Samara, Yersinia Pestis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637641</guid>
      <title>Airline pilot blasts AC to force passengers off plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INDIA    A video showing an airline cabin filling up with mist as passengers vomit has gone viral.The AirAsia flight was flying from Kolkata to a small town in West Bengal when it was delayed for four hours, reports The Express.The captain made an announcement for the passengers to get off the plane, giving no explanation.When the poor passengers refused as it was raining heavily outside, he decided to retaliate.The pilot reportedly blasted the ac on full, forcing the passengers to deplane.The video shows passengers protesting, screaming loudly, some even hurling as the mist filled the cabin.Passengers complained saying it was "suffocating," and very "unprofessional and rude."Air Asia released a statement apologizing for the inconvenience, however the airline claims the A/C was turned on because of 'high humidity conditions…."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 09:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/22/3637641/3637641_BBE928083A574082911A804C87DE145A_180622_3637641_Airline_pilot_blasts_AC_to_force_passengers_off__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8CF/127/8CF1278DE826F58D7C9A31DD289C5D4A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, India, Airplane, Airline cabin, airline cabin fills up with mist, passengers forced off a plane, passengers vomit as pilot blasts ac, airline pilot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637612</guid>
      <title>Drinking too much can lead to a whole bunch of nasty cancers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BETHESDA, MARYLAND  A new study finds that light drinkers have the lowest combined risk of developing cancer and dying prematurely, even when compared to people who did not drink at all. According to NPR, scientists looked at 100,000 adults in their mid-50s to early 70s, and had each complete a survey about their alcohol consumption. Researchers then tracked these people for nine years and found that the more alcohol consumed, the higher the risk of developing cancer and dying. The findings were published in the journal PLOS Medicine. Heavy drinkers were the most at risk. Scientists found that men who drank three or more drinks per day were three to four times more likely to develop esophagus or liver cancer. Other alcohol-related cancers were colorectal and breast cancer in women.According to NPR, a drink is a single shot of liquor, 5 ounces of wine or 12 ounces of beer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 08:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/22/3637612/3637612_23B9BD342AD74AE097B93E654BB3364F_180622_3637612_Drinking_too_much_can_lead_to_a_whole_bunch_of_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/78A/C88/78AC8851A586C39DB6CCA22B5648DBB0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, drinking, drinking excessive alcohol, drinking causes cancer, light drinker, heavy drinker]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637552</guid>
      <title>NASA outlines plan to protect the Earth from an asteroid strike</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  The chances of a space rock colliding with Earth in the near future may be slim, but here's good news for anyone paranoid about an asteroid armageddon: NASA's got a plan.Titled "National Near-Earth Object Preparedness and Strategy Action Plan", the document details the steps NASA and Federal Emergency Management Agency will take to prevent asteroids from hitting Earth, and to prepare the planet should such a catastrophic event take place.Large asteroids can obliterate life on Earth, but smaller ones may also cause serious damage. The 130 to 200-foot wide asteroid that hit Tunguska, Russia in 1908, for example, levelled over 700 square miles of forest, and would have been able to destroy the entire metropolitan New York area.The outlined plan involves five main goals. The first involves enhancing detection of near-Earth objects, or asteroids that pass within 28 million miles of Earth's orbit. The second goal is to improve modelling and prediction, to help determine when and where a potential asteroid strike will occur.The third objective is to come up with new ways to deflect an asteroid, such as the Double Asteroid Redirection Test that's set to be launched in 2021.Goal four aims to increase international cooperation, while the fifth and final goal calls for the U.S. to come up with an emergency plan should an asteroid ever crash with little to no warning.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 07:49:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/22/3637552/3637552_E7CFD5C5E7574C31AF7DD51B19B77690_180622_3637552_NASA_outlines_plan_to_protect_the_Earth_from_an__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B0F/2F1/B0F2F111950F9530AAB50CB5D9F715E6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, asteroid, asteroid strike, asteroid protection, emergency plan, NASA, armageddon, asteroid apocalypse, near Earth objects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637519</guid>
      <title>Mother must wash baby in bleach to keep him healthy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHATTAROY, WASHINGTON  In recent reports, an American mom talks about how she needs wash her baby boy in bleach to help protect him from disease.Alicia Barber's infant son Jamison suffers from Harlequin ichthyosis, a rare genetic skin condition and needs round-the-clock care.Because of this, Barber needs to bathe him in bleach two times per week to stave off infection.  According to Metro, Barber needs to use clorox while washing Jamison. That is painful for him, so he's on morphine while being washed. In addition to that, Jamison is also bathed twice for 45 minutes daily, and then rubbed with a sandpaper rag to help shed his skin. According to rarediseases.org, Jamison's condition causes thick layers of plate-like skin scale to form. If untreated, the skin can make it difficult for the child to breath and eat. Approximately one in half a million suffer with the condition.  Barber's trying to raise awareness of her son's condition and is hoping to attend a medical conference that addresses it specifically. It takes place in in Nashville, Tennessee and the family has set up a GoFundMe account to help with the cost. So far, they've raised closed to $10,000, blowing way past their $6,000 target. https://www.gofundme.com/please-help-us-get-to-nashville]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 07:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/22/3637519/3637519_2D03BD1060F54C039557A3109313FAC1_180622_3637519_Mother_must_wash_baby_in_bleach_to_keep_him_heal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A27/7CC/A277CC6C9E456559048007E101C014C3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Harlequin ichthyosis, Harlequin ichthyosis baby, Harlequin ichthyosis treatment, Harlequin ichthyosis survivor, jamison barber, alicia barber, rare skin conditions, Harlequin ichthyosis birth, amazing stories, amazing, skin, documentary, harlequuin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637449</guid>
      <title>Toxic black henna tattoos may scar you for life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANKARA, TURKEY  Holiday henna tattoos are a cute little souvenir of days in the sun, but they could also open up a world of pain if you're not careful.The BBC reports that Mary Bates found this out the hard way, after getting a dreamcatcher henna-tattooed on her ankle during a vacation in Turkey.After about an hour, the tattoo lines on the then 16-year-old's skin became raised. It got worse over time, resulting in blistering, oozing, and a lot of skin peeling.Bates would later find out that she was having a reaction to black henna.Natural henna is entirely safe and made from plant-based ingredients. It hardens and peels off, and should leave an orange stain that becomes darker over the next few days.But black henna, contrary to the name, isn't actually henna. It's a synthetic black dye that's chock-full of the chemical PPD, which is toxic to the skin.While not everyone will experience a reaction to black henna, the risks can be severe for those that do. Bates had to get steroid treatments, and was at the hospital every week for over a month before her ankle got better. Now 19, she is relieved the scar wasn't permanent.Many others though, have not been so lucky, and still bear the scars of a little holiday fun gone wrong.Experts are cautioning tourists to only use henna that's brownish or olive-green in color. Anything that's jet black and purports to dye instantly should be avoided.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 05:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/22/3637449/3637449_729794A354164E63937CF3ED3F88D091_180622_3637449_Toxic_black_henna_tattoos_may_scar_you_for_life_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/779/23D/77923DD1B88950C19C7190C5CA407D2D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, henna, henna tattoo, holiday henna, black henna, toxic black henna, henna reaction, allergic reaction, scarring, temporary tattoo, PPD, black vs natural henna, natural henna]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3637433</guid>
      <title>Phillies fan struck in the face with a flying hot dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CITIZENS BANK PARK, PHILADELPHIA  A Phillies fan left a game on Monday night with a black and blue face, but not from a fight with a fan from the other team. No, she was injured from regular baseball stadium snack food, reports CBS Sports.The Phillie Phanatic, beloved mascot of the Philadelphia Phillies, was driving in the field with its hot dog launcher during a Phillies Cardinals game ... and started launching the all-American treat into the crowd of fans sitting on the stands. Kathy McVay was in that crowd at Citizens Bank Park when she was struck squarely in the face by a flying weiner. Accidentally, of course.McVay was rushed to the emergency room where she had to undergo a CAT scan.Speaking to WPVI, McVay said the hot dog "came out of nowhere" noting that the injury would probably would get worse before it gets better."However McVay said she a "big fan of the team" and doesn't plan to take any legal action.The Phillies reached out to McVay and offered her tickets to a future game, reports ESPN.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 05:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/22/3637433/3637433_5B00699D3FE744FFBB62211CEE98A74D_180622_3637433_Phillies_fan_struck_in_the_face_with_a_flying_ho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AE9/183/AE9183131D6E433B6BA1D18224BA79C3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US, Philadelphia Phillies, Phillie Phanatic, woman hit in the face by hot dog, Hot dog, flying hot dog, hot dog launcher, hot dog hits woman in the face by phillie phanatic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3638178</guid>
      <title>Orlando airport to use face scans on all international travelers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, FLORIDA  Long, snaking lines may become a thing of the past for passengers travelling through Orlando's main air hub.The Orlando Sentinel reports that Florida's Orlando International Airport is set to be the first U.S. airport to use facial recognition to process passengers on all inbound and outbound international flights.The scans will be checked against passenger passport photos and travel information on a Department of Homeland Security database, to verify a travelers identity.Biometric screening is expected to speed up passenger processing, but concerns have been voiced over privacy and potential information theft.In response, the U.S. Customs and Border Protection says scans in the database are deleted after 14 days, but could be removed almost immediately in the future. Photos of foreign nationals, however, are also kept in the Automated Biometric Identification System for up to 75 years.The system currently claims to have a 99% accuracy rate, though officials can manually screen passports and fingerprints if a photo doesn't match or a U.S. citizen decides to opt out.Once fully implemented, facial scanners will be stationed inside the airport's 30 international departure gates and two CBP checkpoints. The technology is also being used in other U.S. airports, though to a lesser degree.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jun 2018 05:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/23/3638178/3638178_C6DBE13A5C334B2C80126F3DF54D799F_180623_3638178_Orlando_airport_to_use_face_scans_on_all_interna_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1E0/CF8/1E0CF8DDEB7E5D5D95AB6A6E59C0E60E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, facial recognition, facial scanner, face scan, face scanner, airport, biometrics, biometric screening, facial recognition tech, privacy, orlando airport, customs border protection, homeland security]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639612</guid>
      <title>Woman calls police on black kid selling water in viral video</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Permit Patty is the latest white person to cry cop over black folks doing the most mundane things.According to the San Francisco Chronicle, the subject of her outrage was 8-year-old Jordan Austin, who on Saturday was selling bottled water outside her San Francisco apartment to help finance a trip to Disneyland.Patty, whose real name is Alison Ettel, got ticked off that the girl was shouting loudly and disturbing her work, so she stormed down and called her out for illegally selling without a permit.When the child's mother intervened and argued with Ettel, she threatened to call the police, prompting mom to pull out her own phone and record the incident.In a video posted on Instagram, Ettel can be seen ducking behind a structure with a phone to her ear, but is followed and confronted by the elder Austin's camera.Once the post went viral with over a million views, karma came swiftly for Permit Patty. Internet sleuths found out she ran a company that made cannabis products for pets. So on top of getting hate online, she's also suffering financial repercussions, with several business associates cutting ties.Permit Patty later told the Huffington Post she only pretended to call the cops, and now feels "discriminated against"' Oh please.Little Jordan, meanwhile, might be retiring her cooler after a kind soul heard about her story and sent four tickets to Disneyland as a gift.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 11:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/25/3639612/3639612_5458933916D34BBA8EE58821E35B4FC2_180625_3639612_Woman_calls_police_on_black_kid_selling_water_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CDE/D35/CDED353C304BFAD43070C5DA6535235A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, permit patty, white woman calls cops, woman calls cops on kid, living while black, selling while black, white people, toxic white people, young entrepreneur, child entrepreneur, disneyland, alison ettel]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639470</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia finally lets women behind the wheel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAUDI ARABIA  Saudi Arabia is probably the most progressive country in the world, which is why it went ahead and finally lifted its ban on female drivers. The Saudi monarchy always listens to its people. Sure, it may have taken 30 years for them to hear it, but hey.  According to the AP, women will no longer have to rely on their hubbies, dads or brothers to run some simple errands, get to work, visit friends or drop kids off at school. According to CNN, the Ministry of Interior and Traffic Directorate officials said that more than 120,000 women applied for a driver's license on Sunday. Saudi Arabia really is blazing a trail. Spearheaded by Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman, the country has an ambitious plan to overhaul its economy in a project called Vision 2030. It includes a revolutionary and radically progressive new idea  hiring women. At this rate, Saudi Arabia will hands down be the best place to live right around the end of human civilization.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 09:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/25/3639470/3639470_DB014F4D471645568DDF005E38772A37_180625_3639470_Saudi_Arabia_finally_lets_women_behind_the_wheel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1E8/90A/1E890AD029E63F6118514F8B319FC285.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Saudi Arabia women driving, Saudi Arabia lifts women driving ban, Saudi Arabia women driving, Saudi women driving, Saudi Arabia women driver's license]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639348</guid>
      <title>Gene-edited pigs immune to deadly virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIDLOTHIAN, UNITED KINGDOM  Scientists have successfully made pigs resistant to a deadly virus by editing their genes.According to the study, published in the Journal of Virology, Porcine Reproductive and Respiratory Syndrome  or PRRS  causes breathing problems and death in young pigs, and stillborns in infected sows.To address this, researchers from the University of Edinburgh's Roslin Institute used gene editing to remove a small section of the pigs' CD163 receptor, which the PRRS virus attaches to. They then exposed the gene-edited pigs to the virus and found that the animals did not become infected.Scientists say the genetic edit is permanent, meaning the pigs' resistance to the disease will be passed down through natural breeding.The Edinburgh team stressed that unlike genetic modification, which is highly controversial, no foreign genes are added in during the editing process. But with no regulations in place, it may take years before the technology can be applied to commercially raised swines.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 06:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/25/3639348/3639348_3F5157384222412BB1472F08CD8977BC_180625_3639348_Gene_edited_pigs_immune_to_deadly_virus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A31/977/A319775C46EBE150D410A0E6FCAE05FA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, gene editing, gene edited pigs, porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, PRRS, gene modification, GM, farm animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639295</guid>
      <title>Norway's testing an electrical airplane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OSLO  Norwegian fliers may be travelling on electrical powered aircraft within the next decade.According to Norwegian government information, the Alpha Electro G2 aircraft has a range of 170 km and can fly for up to 1 hour.Manufacturer Pipistrel says the aircraft's motor has power of around 50 kilowatts, with a 21 kilowatt per hour battery.This is small compared to batteries used by electric cars. Pipistrel says the aircraft can be recharged quickly at customized charging stations. The plane was tested this month at Oslo airport. Carrying two passengers, it weighed 570 kg and was airborne for several minutes. Reuters reports that the passengers described the experience as cramped, but quieter than normal aircraft.The country plans to operate domestic flights electric by 2025, with a view to having all electrically powered come 2040.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 05:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/25/3639295/3639295_8524911E1D98415288CEBE66CA35E4E3_180625_3639295_Norway_s_testing_an_electrical_airplane_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4CA/7AE/4CA7AECF098F8612D665D5D9A15CC409.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, electrical airplane, norway, electrical airplane flight, electrical aircraft, electrical airplane project, electrical engineering, pipistrel, electrical technology, green technology, tesla, tesla model s, electrical batteries, clean technology, norwegian, electricity planes, awesome planes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639285</guid>
      <title>Koko the gorilla who knows sign language and raised kittens, dies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WOODSIDE, CALIFORNIA  Koko, the gorilla famed for her ability to communicate using American Sign Language and amazing friendships with pets, died in her sleep last week at age 46.  Koko was a western lowland gorilla born at the San Francisco Zoo in 1971. She soon formed a close bond with Dr. Francine "Penny" Patterson.The following year, Dr. Patterson started teaching Koko sign language as part of a Stanford University project.Koko was said to have an IQ of between 75 and 95, could understand 2,000 words of spoken English. The average IQ for humans is 100, with most people scoring somewhere between 85 and 115.Koko adopted several cats, and used sign language to give them names. She even grieved for one of her kittens when it was killed in a car accident. Koko's love of animals turned into a children's book called "Koko's Kitten" and her own line of toys. Due to her fame, Koko became the subject of many documentaries and was on the cover of National Geographic.Koko also met quite a few celebrities, from the late actor Robin Williams, Betty White, Leonardo Dicaprio, and her favourite celebrity Fred Rogers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 05:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/25/3639285/3639285_79283A97D3084BAA88399824C7572B4B_180625_3639285_Koko_the_gorilla_who_knows_sign_language_and_rai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D46/C93/D46C93D4E87163553D2D4244606A682F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, koko the gorilla, koko the gorilla, koko the gorilla dies, koko the gorilla sign language, koko the gorilla age, koko life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639277</guid>
      <title>New tech lets you use your smartphones for keyless car entry</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEAVERTON, OREGON  New technology may soon see traditional car keys being replaced by smartphones.The 'Digital Key', developed by the Car Connectivity Consortium (CCC), can lock and unlock cars, as well as start the vehicle's engine, according to Mashable. CCC members include several car and smartphone manufacturers, according to information on the consortium website.Mashable reports the technology would enable shared access to vehicles across different smartphones. It uses technology such as GSMA, Bluetooth, Near Field Communication and GlobalPlatform, according to information on the CCC website.Their aim is to standardize the digital key as a car key solution across the automotive industry.Mashable reports that the digital key currently requires manufacturer installation.The next version of the technology, called Digital Key 2.0, should enable users to set it up themselves. That's expected for release in 2019.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 05:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/25/3639277/3639277_76193229AA464309A915C5BC64112841_180625_3639277_New_tech_lets_you_use_your_smartphones_for_keyle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F54/56E/F5456E818C5E307C44EF3B11AAEFF2E1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, smartphones keyless car entry, car keys, digital key, car connectivity consortium, CCC car key, keyless car, keyless car security, keyless car technology, keyless car entry, smartphone car entry, smartphone, latest technology news, new car technology, smartphone apps, technology news, innovation, technological innovations]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3639265</guid>
      <title>Trump threw Starbursts candies at Merkel during G7 summit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANADA  Trump is no stranger to winning, and if there's a Starburst tossing title out there, it should have his name on it.Trump was kind enough to share his Starbursts with the big kids at the G7 meeting two weeks ago, reports CBS.Trump went into big boy mode when the other leaders were ganging up against him, reports The Metro.The world leaders were trying to get things done while Trump was his usual Trumptastic self.Apparently, Angela Merkel was pressuring Sunny Delight to sign a joint statement when he pulled out the candies from his pocket and said "don't say I never give you anything."Trump initially agreed to do so, but then pulled out by a series of tweets and lashed out against the G7.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 04:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/25/3639265/3639265_4BE4C64CE664461A96570F8E676F7AF8_180625_3639265_Trump_threw_Starbursts_candies_at_Merkel_during__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/547/EE1/547EE1776B3F45CBB78098E9D76C4B82.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, US, Trump, G7 Summit, starbursts, Starbursts candies,starbursts candy, Trump threw starbursts to Merkel, Trump G7 meeting, world leaders, Merkel, Trudeau]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640348</guid>
      <title>French jogger detained for accidentally crossing US border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLAINE, WASHINGTON  A French woman who went jogging on a Canadian beach was sent to a U.S. immigration detention for straying across the border.Cedella Roman, 19, was visiting British Columbia and running along the beach that leads to Canada's border with 'Murica on May 21. As the tide began to rise, she turned onto a dirt path, stopped to take a picture then started heading back, not realizing she had accidentally strayed into U.S. territory.That's when she was pounced on by two U.S. border patrol agents who slapped cuffs on her for crossing into Blaine, Washington. The officers then took Roman 136 miles south to the Tacoma Northwest Detention Center.According to the BBC, Roman was crammed into a room with about 100 other people. They were locked up the whole time with barbed wire and dogs.She called her mom in B.C., who brought Roman's passport and work permit, but U.S. officials wouldn't release her until Canadian immigration said it was okay for Roman to come back.Finally, after 15 days, Ms. Roman was allowed to put this ridiculous ordeal behind her.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 11:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/26/3640348/3640348_CC234E6AD2B74789BC27192B6894CEC6_180626_3640348_French_jogger_detained_for_accidentally_crossing_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3DF/801/3DF8015F506A5973B4D28C5DB65DB8D8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, french jogger detained, french teen detained US border, french jogger crosses US border by accident, US border patrol, french jogging teen detained border]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640206</guid>
      <title>Police dog performs CPR on officer wins over audience's hearts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPAIN   A video of a police dog in Spain rushing to perform CPR on an officer after he collapses to the ground has gone viral.In the video released by the Policia de Madrid, the police officer falls down to the ground and pretends to be unresponsive while Poncho, the police dog, runs over to him to perform CPR.Poncho quickly dashes over to the officer on the ground and starts jumping on his chest. He also places its head to the officer's neck to apparently check for his pulse.The crowd watching starts clapping as the dog continues to do so until the police officer gets up and gives it a treat.The Policia de Madrid tweeted out praise for Poncho for "not hesitating to save the life" of an officer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 08:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/26/3640206/3640206_6351D0C548E446A0B908A527639ACE7D_180626_3640206_Police_dog_performs_CPR_on_officer_wins_over_aud_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/70B/33B/70B33BEF95C4E4A69D56C13E01F04CE5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Spain, Police dog, Heroic police dog, police dog cpr, police dog doing cpr, police dog saves officer, officer, police dog performs cpr on officer, police dog quick to save lives]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640196</guid>
      <title>Longest lunar eclipse of century coming end of July</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  The longest lunar eclipse of this century will appear over Earth at the end of July, according astronomer Bruce McClure. Writing on EarthSky.org, astronomer Bruce McClure says the lunar eclipse on July 27 will also be an apogean moon   when the Earth is at its furthest point from the moon. McClure notes this will be the lengthiest lunar eclipse of the current century (2001 to 2100).According to data from NASA, the eclipse will last 1 hour 42 minutes and 57 seconds.The celestial event will be viewable from most of Africa, the Middle East as well as central, east and southeast Asia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 08:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/26/3640196/3640196_B2AE13C4512449BC96905B9C5DED1301_180626_3640196_Longest_lunar_eclipse_of_century_coming_end_of_J_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5CA/511/5CA511EA1BCF7024C7D025CE594F46FE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, longest lunar eclipse, lunar eclipse, moon, blood moon, moon eclipse, astronomy, science, NASA, total lunar eclipse, bloodmoon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640182</guid>
      <title>China forcing all cars to have RFID chips so they can be tracked</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  The Chinese Communist Party is planning to track all new cars using RFID chips in a voluntary program that begins on July 1, that will become mandatory by 2019.   According to the Wall Street Journal, China's Ministry of Public Security and the ministry's Traffic Management Research Institute is working on the new tracking system.Chinese officials claim that windshield RFID chips will help the government study and improve congestion, thereby reducing pollution. Officials claim another goal is to help combat the rise of vehicular terrorist attacks. The system will not be able to locate a car like GPS, and it is unclear how much citizen information will be stored on the chips beyond car color and license plate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 07:53:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/26/3640182/3640182_C8F837D7DA8F4F45941BA2E5CA42FA46_180626_3640182_China_forcing_all_cars_to_have_RFID_chips_so_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/41F/2A4/41F2A4D3FD2EFA03163B53A790C7D281.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China cars RFID, China tracking new cars, China surveillance programs, China car RFID chips, China tracking cars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640173</guid>
      <title>Woman's moving facial bumps turn out to be roundworm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  A woman used selfies to document bumps migrating around her face, and was horrified to discover what was actually inside.According to the New England Journal of Medicine, the 32-year-old spotted the first nodule just below her left eye. Five days later, it appeared as three small bumps above her left eye. After 10 days, it migrated again, this time to her upper lip, making it swell significantly.The nodules were itchy and caused a burning sensation, though no other symptoms were reported. Doctors suspected some sort of parasite after seeing the patient's selfies, and spotted a moving oblong nodule during the physical exam.They surgically removed the unwanted visitor using forceps, revealing it to be a 9-millimeter-long roundworm. The worm was later identified as Dirofilaria repens, which is more commonly found in dogs and spread through mosquitoes.The woman recalled being bitten by mosquitoes during a recent trip to a rural area outside Moscow, and likely got infected there.Doctors say she has recovered fully since being rid of the nasty worm.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 07:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/26/3640173/3640173_0D8DBC920DDA47B1A60F76BB5B76C67D_180626_3640173_Woman_s_moving_facial_bumps_turn_out_to_be_round_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE0/32D/CE032D82345AADADAA7E98597FB2F315.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, parasite, worm, worm in face, worm in eye, moving bumps, migrating bumps, parasitic infection, roundworm, dirofilaria repens, mosquito bite]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640049</guid>
      <title>Teen's random act of kindness for blind, deaf passenger goes viral</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  A California teen offered a helping hand when a blind and deaf man aboard an Air Alaska flight needed help communicating. According to CBS News, Clara Daly was flying on an Air Alaska flight with her mom on the way back to California. Shortly after takeoff, a flight attendant made an announcement asking if anyone knew sign language aboard the plane. They said they had a blind and deaf passenger who could only communicate by signing into his hand. Enter Clara, who's been studying American Sign Language. The teen walked and began signing into his hand to help him communicate with flight attendants. According to Clara's mom over a Facebook post, Clara helped him ask for water and how much time was left on the flight. After that, they were just chatting it up. The man's name was Timothy and he was flying to Portland. Clara and her mom were originally supposed to fly on a direct flight to L.A., but had to scramble after their that flight was canceled. Guess it was fate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 05:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/26/3640049/3640049_B36700D2761D4E539DB5E27835AC6F97_180626_3640049_Teen_s_random_act_of_kindness_for_blind__deaf_pa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D27/5DE/D275DE1AE6433E43D4F51C6203C26754.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, teen helps blind deaf passenger, teen helps blind passenger, teen helps deaf passenger, sign language, random act of kindness]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641252</guid>
      <title>Spanish church tries really hard to restore sculpture</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ESTELLA, SPAIN  The Church of San Miguel in Estella hired a crack local arts and crafts teacher to restore a priceless 16th-Century wooden statue of St. George.Images of the newly restored statue have now gone viral, but unfortunately for all the wrong reasons. St. George is now sporting a new bright, pink face with some really colorful body armor.For some odd reason, many are less than pleased with how things turned out.    The Guardian reported that the town's Mayor Koldo Leoz said, "they've used plaster and the wrong kind of paint and it' possible that the original layers of paint have been lost. This is an expert job it should have been done by experts."The group in charge of the restoration is called Karmacolor and even uploaded a Facebook video showing each step of the process. Too bad it's been deleted already.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/28/3641252/3641252_245BE3CD8B2146598BAB31E24544F4B7_180628_3641252_Spanish_church_tries_really_hard_to_restore_scul_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/331/3A1/3313A103642462F77D47BF1194CD083F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Spain St. George statue restoration, St. George statue restoration fail, Spanish church sculpture restoration, sculpture restoration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641249</guid>
      <title>Genetic genealogy helps police solve 25-year-old murder mystery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENNSYLVANIA   Officers have cracked a 1992 murder case by getting a hold of the suspect's chewing gum and water bottle, reports The Washington Post.Christy Mirack was a young teacher in Pennsylvania, excited for the Christmas holidays like anyone else.The next day when she didn't show up at school, the principal called and then drove down to her townhouse.He goes inside and finds Mirack on the floor, with Christmas presents for her students strewn around on the floor.The police reportedly investigated the case and determined she was beaten, strangled and sexually assaulted.Unfortunately, the investigators never could find who murdered the poor woman...until now.Twenty-five years after the case went cold, investigators turned to genetic genealogy, a new technique where investigators match publicly available genealogical information with DNA found from victims at the crime scene. The investigators matched the DNA to Raymond Rowe, a popular wedding and event DJ, who was also known as "DJ Freez."The investigators then went on an undercover investigation at an elementary school party where Rowe was the DJ and collected a piece of Rowe's chewing gum as well as a used water bottle, reports The Star.The suspect was reportedly taken into custody on Monday, without being officially charged yet.Genetic genealogy has helped solved a number of other crimes, however it has raised privacy concerns about DNA being publically available for everyone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/28/3641249/3641249_E36E13C5ED6C4DC98AA26F169736D93D_180628_3641249_Genetic_genealogy_helps_police_solve_25_year_old_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/064/C83/064C8314E14C4C37239F4DDAA9488F77.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Murder mystery, Undercover investigators, police, Genetic genealogy, DNA, police links DNA to suspect, teacher, 1992 murder, cold case investigations, teacher murdered]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641243</guid>
      <title>World Cup reporter tells off jerk for inappropriate kissing attempt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YEKATERINBURG, RUSSIA  A Brazilian sports reporter clapped back after a man tried to kiss her on-camera during the World Cup.The BBC reports that the incident went down in Yekaterinburg, while Julia Guimaraes was reporting on the Japan vs. Senegal match for Brazil's TV Globo and Sport TV.As the camera rolled, a man suddenly ducked into the shot and tried to give Guimaraes a peck on the cheek.The journalist dodged the kiss, and proceeded to confront the jerk, reprimanding him on his highly inappropriate behavior. She tells him to never do again, that it's not polite and not right. Off-cam, the man can be heard apologizing repeatedly.Guimaraes said that while she never experienced this in Brazil, it's happened to her twice during the World Cup in Russia.She hasn't been the only victim either. Days before, a Colombian Deutsche Welle reporter got kissed and groped on-cam by an entitled douchebag.She chose to continue the report despite the interruption, which DW later denounced as "blatant harassment" and an attack.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 16:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/28/3641243/3641243_0884157EDB394BEDB8232989CCA0E5AF_180628_3641243_World_Cup_reporter_tells_off_jerk_for_inappropri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E68/699/E68699C1F9F509BDFD9AD8F8323B7F92.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, 2018 world cup, world cup 2018, world cup, russia world cup, inappropriate kissing, world cup reporter, kissing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641230</guid>
      <title>HBO website blocked in China after John Oliver mocks Xi Jinping</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  The HBO website is the latest to be blocked by China's Great Firewall, after John Oliver had a bit of fun with its president.The New York Times reports that the British comedian did a 20-minute segment on China on his satirical news show "Last Week Tonight," critiquing the country's human rights record and dystopian surveillance tactics.What really did it though, was joking about Xi Jinping and Winnie the Pooh, his pants-less, pot-bellied 2D twin.Xi is especially sensitive about his cartoon doppleganger, so much so that images of the bear have been purged on Chinese social media. Like Pooh, Oliver's name and show have been censored on Weibo, with attempts to post either resulting in "Send failure!" or "Content is illegal!"HBO's website has also been inaccessible to Chinese netizens since Saturday, though HBO shows like Game of Thrones are still available on Tencent's streaming platform.The Great Firewall's kill list currently includes a whole slew of blocked Western media outlets, including Youtube, Facebook, Twitter, and the New York Times. But mainland internet users hellbent on accessing these sites have their ways.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 15:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/27/3641230/3641230_013460C37CD540FB9552F4784ED67607_180627_3641230_HBO_website_blocked_in_China_after_John_Oliver_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/058/633/058633C8BCA7D59BA6A0F0DD3B3F46D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hbo, john oliver, last week tonight, xi jinping, china sensors, great firewall, beijing censors, blocked, china, blocked by china, winnie the pooh, weibo, chinese internet, chinese social media]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641021</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Episode 3 - Cop accepts donut bribe in joke video</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured RAW from cops around the globe.THIS WEEK: 1. A hero K-9 police dog was awarded a steak dinner after disarming a strapped drunk.2. Officers in Texas stop a would-be bridge jumper.3. Furry thief yoinks an Alaska cop's donut.4. Seattle cops borrow a jet ski to save two kayakers in distress.5. Police officer accepts donut bribe in joke viral video.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 10:22:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/27/3641021/3641021_52B1EBC6EAD64E14BBEA7BB5FD95EA2C_180627_3641021_LAWMAN_CAM__Episode_3___Cop_accepts_donut_bribe__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/5F3/D26/5F3D2686AEA24436A4D1E64782D84719.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, good cop, hero cops, cops doing amazing things, k-9 cop takes down man, latest police videos, new police videos,  latest cop video, new cop footage, police footage, police dog, police dog good boy, police body cam, police dash cam, police compilation 2018, cop videos, police chase 2018, latest police chase videos, crazy car chases, police pursuit, impaired driver, us police videos, cop camera, lawman cam, tomonews lawman cam, police responding, police news, latest police video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640949</guid>
      <title>Child finds loaded heater in Ikea couch, squeezes off a round</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INDIANAPOLIS, INDIANA  A child found a loaded burner in a sofa at an Indiana IKEA store and even squeezed off a round inside the store. According to local authorities, earlier in the day, a customer who was packing at the Fishers, Indiana store sat down on the sofa to give it a try. Suburban commando then dropped his piece into the couch when he got up, having no clue it fell out.Enter a 6-year-old boy who later found the heater and decided to do his best good guy with guns impression. Fortunately, no one was hurt. According to CNN, the Hamilton County Prosecutor's Office is reviewing the case to see if any charges will be brought against the gun owner.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 09:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/27/3640949/3640949_5CAD881ED6EC4EA6A028A43693303ED7_180627_3640949_Child_finds_loaded_heater_in_Ikea_couch__squeeze_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C7F/FE6/C7FFE6B70AB23EAC53A669A2D51AFEB4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Ikea, Ikea sofa, Ikea couch, kid finds burner in Ikea couch, kid finds piece in Ikea couch]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640920</guid>
      <title>South Korea plans railway linking Korean Peninsula and Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  Following the successful inter Korean summit, South Korea is now planning to build an extensive network that will connect the Korean Peninsula to Russia via rail.AFP reports that North and South Korea have begun talks about connecting their railways, using existing lines that run from Seoul to Pyongyang, and on to the Chinese border city of Sinuiju.The project also plans to build a separate high-speed railway that would allow trains to go from Seoul to Sinuiju at speeds of up to 350 kilometers per hour, reports Donga.Current North Korea rail infrastructure only allows slow moving trains at less than 50 kph, and will need to be upgraded to handle increased speeds and heavier loads.The completed lines will later connect to Moscow and the rest of the Trans-Siberian railway, ultimately establishing a land route between Europe and the two Koreas.The railway plan is one of the trilateral infrastructure projects between South Korea and Russia, the other two being energy and electricity.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 08:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/27/3640920/3640920_BC1E2A6C146F4DBD943F493355CBD329_180627_3640920_South_Korea_plans_railway_linking_Korean_Peninsu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E15/658/E156585012A9BA6218514A674C5876A3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, korean rail, inter korean rail, high speed rail, railway, rail link, north korea, south korea, russia, korean peninsula, trans siberian railway, eurasia rail]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640907</guid>
      <title>82 chihuahuas found in dirty, chaotic condition in British house</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM, UNITED KINGDOM   More than 80 chihuahuas had been discovered in a Birmingham house that "looked like it had been hit by an earthquake," reports The BBC.Apparently the house was owned by a woman and her husband who had originally just brought two chihuahuas home, Blue and Tinkerbell.However, as they failed to get the first two neutered, the number of pups in the house quickly began to multiply and four years later they had 82 dogs!The case came to the attention of the British police when they were examining the cause of the woman's death.They went to her house and found a bunch of chihuahuas, some having "matted coats, fleas, or burns."The police were reportedly stunned when they arrived at the woman's home and found the house "filthy and cramped."The police called a vet who said the house was "too hazardous" for the dogs to continue staying there, The BBC reports.The dogs were taken to Newbrook Farm Animal Hospital in Birmingham for checkups, reports The Mirror.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 08:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/27/3640907/3640907_49962335707B4DD783BA26B729EFED28_180627_3640907_82_chihuahuas_found_in_dirty__chaotic_condition__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A6F/A6E/A6FA6E2F34E0DED69EA99D3176336423.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, UK, Dogs, chihuahuas, 82 chihuahuas found in cramped home, filthy home, couple owns 82 dogs, dogs living in filthy conditions, cramped conditions, bunch of chihuahuas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640878</guid>
      <title>NSA maybe snooping en masse via 8 AT&amp;T locales</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FORT MEADE, MARYLAND  The U.S. National Security Agency used eight AT&T facilities across the country as part of a mass surveillance program, according to the Intercept.According to the Intercept, the National Security Agency may be using AT&T buildings across the U.S. as part of a mass surveillance program called FAIRVIEW.The Intercept identified AT&T facilities in Seattle, San Francisco, Los Angeles, Dallas, Atlanta, Chicago, Washington and New York city. The website reports that these locations process AT&T customer data, as well as large amounts of information from other internet providers inside the U.S. and abroad.The FAIRVIEW program, in which AT&T is the sole member, reportedly gives the NSA access to international communications cables, routers and switches.  According to the New York Times, this provided the agency access to billions of metadata records, as well as texts, emails and phone calls.An AT&T spokesperson told the Intercept the company was "required by law to provide information to government and law enforcement."The NSA told the website they couldn't confirm or deny their reporting, but said they are "bound by both policy and law to protect U.S. persons' privacy and civil liberties."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 07:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/27/3640878/3640878_DADCFD8D49E64F42B7D4191B7A99C977_180627_3640878_NSA_maybe_snooping_en_masse_via_8_AT_T_locales_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2F6/19F/2F619F978D8F7D5D30D2839046804F37.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, nsa, mass surveillance, government surveillance, spying, secret, edward snowden, at&t, telecoms, privacy, national security agency, NSA AT&T, The intercept, intercept news, science and technology, police state, big brother]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3640863</guid>
      <title>Woman walks away after crashing car into gas station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRANDON MISSISSIPPI  A Mississippi woman is lucky to be alive and unscathed after a gas station car crash that's possibly one of the craziest ever caught on camera.Mississippi News Now reports that according to a deputy on the scene, the incident occurred after driver Shelby Lynn May got off work, where she'd had one too many drinks.Her compact white sedan was spotted speeding over 100 miles, going into oncoming traffic and nearly colliding with another vehicle before crossing back over.Surveillance footage from the Marathon Xtra Mile gas station shows the car skidding into an embankment and going airborne. It crashes through a brick sign before flipping and landing in between two fuel pumps.Miraculously, none of the gas pumps were hit, and May literally walked away with only very minor injuries.She wasn't lucky enough to escape the law though, and has been arrested and charged with driving under the influence. She posted a $1,500 bond on Friday and is scheduled for a day at court on July 10.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 07:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/27/3640863/3640863_2685315E2F604E74A9760DAEAFAD6994_180627_3640863_Woman_walks_away_after_crashing_car_into_gas_sta_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7AB/E54/7ABE54C4DD2A8D0A2C59401F6433E077.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, car crash, viral car crash, car crash video, airborne car, caught on cam, caught on camera, DUI, mississippi crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641977</guid>
      <title>Tanacon: Ballsy attempt to create the anti-VidCon ends in disaster</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANAHEIM, CALIFORNIA A YouTuber’s convention she created to rival popular event VidCon wound up failing spectacularly at the weekend.YouTuber Tana Mongeau got mad at Vidcon after they wouldn’t give her featured status at Vidcon 2018. That would’ve gave her extra security and a designated spot for her fans. So Tana thought decided to do her own and partnered with organizers Good Times. The con had a solid lineup, reportedly featuring dozens of YouTubers with everyone from Casey Neistat to Shane Dawson.In a ballsy move, they hosted it on the same day, time and place as Vidcon and in Anaheim, California. She expected about 5,000 people with tickets but 20,000 showed up.  She gave the tickets away for free, charging $65 for VIP access. A vidcon community badge costs $150.Problem was, Tana’s venue  the Marriott Suites  could hold a few thousand tops. Reportedly, the disorganization left some fans baking under the hot Cali summer sun for hours before getting in and then finding out there was not much to do. On its first day  it was supposed to be run across two days  authorities shut it down because the whole thing was a damn fire hazard. Then thing got canceled, and let’s just say folks were mad.Tana’s promised refunds, tweeting she’ll write the checks herself if she has to and also asking those who traveled far to email her to discuss compensation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/29/3641977/3641977_9063B88F25414B43918FEDFAAC04A357_180629_3641977_LAWMAN_CAM__Ep__5___GET_CHAPO_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A3C/B40/A3CB4095D2ABABD1D58B99D6FE3278E2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,News,Satire,tanacon,vidcon,tana mongeau,vidcon,youtube,youtube con,vidcon 2018,tanacon canceled,tanahallway,anaheim,marriott suites,youtube fails,youtubers,youtube creators,youtube fans]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641783</guid>
      <title>Images show North Korea continuing work at nuclear facility</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  Commercial satellite photos from June 21 show construction continuing at North Korea's Yongbyon Nuclear Scientific Research Center.According to 38 North, images show modifications to the 5 MWe reactor's secondary cooling loop appear to be finished from the outside, however determining the reactor's operational status was difficult. The status of the Radiochemical Laboratory where the plutonium is separated from spent fuel rods remains uncertain, while the sites Thermal Plant coal bins show usage, suggesting operations there have continued.    Building of support facilities around the Experimental Light Water Reactor, ELWR, also look to be complete externally.Work at the site however, should not be seen as having any relationship with the country's pledge to denuclearize.    According to 38 North, North Korea is expected to proceed with nuclearization until they are given specific orders from Pyongyang.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/28/3641783/3641783_83CAFD75205246B7AB7100B53D232C59_180628_3641783_Images_show_North_Korea_continuing_work_at_nucle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/95E/AD3/95EAD333EB7B52A9B2A99503FC2880F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Korea, Yongbyon Nuclear Research Facility, North Korea nuclear infrastructure, North Korea nuclear improvements]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641744</guid>
      <title>Rescuers search flooded caves for missing Thai soccer team</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHIANG RAI, THAILAND  Heavy rains and flooding are hampering search and rescue efforts for a young soccer team and their coach, who went missing in northern Thailand.The Bangkok Post reports that a dozen boys aged 11 to 16 and their 25-year-old soccer coach have been missing since going into Chiang Rai's Tham Luang cave on Saturday, June 22.The long cave complex has several chambers which have flooded due to rain. Rescue divers found handprints in one area, but have yet to reach a section of dry ground where the boys are believed to be trapped.High-pressure pumps have been installed inside the cave to drain flooded passages, but persistent rainfall has kept water levels rising.Workers searching for alternative entryways found a vertical shaft that likely lead into the cave, and dropped food and water in case the team was nearby.Authorities are also planning to drill new passageways to speed up the hunt for missing soccer players. They remain hopeful that the team will survive since tourists trapped in the cave during past floods were rescued once the waters receded.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 10:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/28/3641744/3641744_3289C06FE3924CB48E9EF91637BF91C5_180628_3641744_Rescuers_search_flooded_caves_for_missing_Thai_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/53E/FDD/53EFDD30652E9D6D666E8F5D41A92BFF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Thai cave, missing boys, soccer, football, missing soccer team, missing football team, soccer players, Tham Luang cave, Thailand cave, cave divers, Chiang Rai]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641664</guid>
      <title>Mars to appear bigger and brighter in next month's night sky</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARS   Mars will appear bigger and brighter from Earth in the next few weeks, reports Newsweek.Next month, Mars will be closest it has been to Earth in the past 15 years.The planet will be 35.8 million miles from Earth.It reportedly takes twice the amount of time for Mars, around 687 days, to orbit the sun than it does for Earth. NASA reports that Mars will be in "opposition" at the same time. This means Mars and the Sun will appear on opposite sides of Earth.Mars will be visible to the naked eye, looking like a bright, orange star.Mars will reportedly appear "five times brighter than usual" and spectators will be able to view the planet in the evening sky, which will appear dimmer and dimmer as Earth moves away from Mars.Astronomer Dean Regas, told Newsweek that most of the world, except Alaska, northern Canada, Greenland and Iceland would be able to view the phenomenon next month after sunset.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 08:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/28/3641664/3641664_0965BAFF57584049A2A6DDB50044C33A_180628_3641664_Mars_to_appear_bigger_and_brighter_in_next_month_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C23/486/C23486B597A34CDA2A922A5D93616B7C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Mars, Earth,Sun,  Mars and Earth in opposition, Mars appears brighter and larger, viewing Mars from Earth, Astronomy, Space, Mars comes close to Earth, Circular orbits, Space exploration]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3641546</guid>
      <title>Lady goes full Trump in rant on Latino guy and his mom</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  A woman has gone viral for experiencing a bad case of verbal mud butt after she berated a Latino guy and his moms. She even dropped in some oh so colorful Trump catch phrases like "illegals" and "rapists" while losing on the man. According to CNN, 27-year-old Esteban Guzman is a systems administrator and a part-time landscaper. He and his mother were doing yard work when they were confronted by the angry woman. In the now viral video, Guzman asks "Why do you hate us?""Because you're Mexicans," the lady shoots back. "We're honest people right here," Guzman replies."Yeah, rapists," the woman says. "Even the president of the United States says you're a rapist." Yeah, but he also says he's only 239 pounds. She also thought it necessary to call them "animals" as well.The exchange has already racked up more that 7.38 million views on Twitter. Nice one lady.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 06:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/28/3641546/3641546_C8D89209D61F4AD3A6CE2CCB73D22904_180628_3641546_Lady_goes_full_Trump_in_rant_on_Latino_guy_and_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E63/F95/E63F95C34BD22EF875A17419EFB845B1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Entertainment, Woman cites Trump in rant, #MeToo, MeToo, Woman goes on rant, Woman rants on landscaper]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642779</guid>
      <title>Japan space probe reaches asteroid 3 BILLION KM away</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RYUGU ASTEROID  A Japanese space probe has reached its destination after travelling through space for three years.The Hayabusa 2 spacecraft blasted off in December 2014, Reuters reports. This week it arrived at its destination, Asteroid Ryugu, some 3 billion kilometers from Earth.Reuters reports Hayabusa 2 will orbit the asteroid for a few months in order to map its surface before it attempts a landing. The probe will use explosives and a cannon to craft a hole the surface, then collect from samples from the area.After the Hayabusa 2 has finished its work on the asteroid, the probe will begin a year-and-a-half journey back to Earth. It's expected to return in 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 13:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/29/3642779/3642779_C28A3E7C5980485CBE1D37D2440D4C77_180629_3642779_Japan_space_probe_reaches_asteroid_3_BILLION_KM__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD3/568/FD3568B1B31FE016F24F9F6F45C35A07.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, jaxa, space probe, hayabusa-2, hayabusa, space mission, science, ryugu asteroid, asteroids, space, science, NASA, Japanese science, JAXA spacecraft, NASA spacecraft, the big bang, origins of the universe, Asteroid ryugu mission, landing on an asteroid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642569</guid>
      <title>Five dead as man with grudge shoots up Maryland newsroom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANNAPOLIS, MARYLAND  Five people are dead and many others injured after a man with a grudge targeted a newspaper office in Maryland.The Baltimore Sun reports that a suspect wielding a shotgun and smoke grenades shot through the glass doors of the Capital Gazette office around 2:40 p.m. on Thursday.According to one witness, he opened fire on several people, killing two women and three men, and injuring at least three others.Employees reportedly hid under their desks during the deadly incident and pleaded for help on social media.Police arrived within a minute of the shooting, surrounding the gunman and taking him into custody. Civilians were escorted out of the building soon after.The shooter was later identified as 38-year-old Jarrod Ramos, a local with a long-standing grudge against the Capital Gazette. He previously sued the paper for defamation, but lost after failing to prove that what the paper published about him was false.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 10:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/29/3642569/3642569_F2456C55A41245C6A51A9B38DA636EE0_180629_3642569_Five_dead_as_man_with_grudge_shoots_up_Maryland__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/132/74D/13274D927D6E1FAFFF2FE59832C7D0E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, shooting, gunman, capital gazette, capital gazette shooting, newsroom shooting, newspaper office, vendetta, grudge, defamation suit, jarrod ramos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642548</guid>
      <title>Animals becoming nocturnal to avoid humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA  Like the dinosaurs millions of years ago, humans are now the planet's super predator, and it's driving all other wildlife to take the night shift.In a new study published in the journal Science, researchers from the University of California, Berkeley analyzed previous studies that captured the 24-hour movements of over 62 medium to large-bodied mammal species across six continents.They found that human disruption made animals 1.36 times more nocturnal on average, meaning those that typically split activities evenly between day and night became 68% more active at night.Human disturbance in this case wasn't just limited to destructive behavior. Even activities like hiking, farming, or wildlife-viewing evoked the same behavioral pattern.The consequences are potentially negative. Animals that lack the traits to thrive nocturnally become vulnerable to non-human predators, affecting their chances at survival and reproduction.Scientists have already noticed some of these changes. Coyotes in California's Santa Cruz Mountains have begun hunting at night to avoid hikers, forgoing their usual daytime prey of squirrels and birds for nocturnal rats and rabbits.Though more research needs to be conducted on the topic, it's important for humans to be more mindful of how we're impacting animal habitats, and aim for coexistence.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 10:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/29/3642548/3642548_D994890699A6405199F0D2E7CE4749E8_180629_3642548_Animals_becoming_nocturnal_to_avoid_humans_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/823/40C/82340C3992C7106E124F576BF6603839.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, nocturnal animals, fear of humans, animals going nocturnal, nocturnal wildlife, nocturnal, diurnal, animals avoiding humans, human disturbance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3642436</guid>
      <title>Chinese oppression intensifies in Xinjiang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA  China's continued crackdown against the country's Uyghur ethnic minority shows no signs of abating.Uyghurs are a Turkic Muslim minority primarily located in the Xinjiang Province in western China. Since the arrival of a new regional party secretary from Tibet in 2016, they have been facing increasingly constraining measures, reports the New York Times.Authorities can arbitrarily send people to detention camps considered suspicious, without charge or trial. Displaying religious signs, having relatives abroad, or even speaking Chinese poorly have proved to be enough to set off alarm bells.No official figures exist, but a recent report by the Jamestown foundation estimates that more than 100,000 people are currently being held indefinitely. This goes alongside a widely-reported mass surveillance program.Chinese authorities claim that the crackdown is only directed against Islamic terrorism and separatism, reported state-run newspaper China Daily. However, repeated human rights violations have been reported by various NGOs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 08:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/06/29/3642436/3642436_957DFB588A284810B1FDF42F1E806115_180629_3642436_Chinese_oppression_intensifies_in_Xinjiang_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D26/B56/D26B5619A4217A5767E02370DC922D5E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, china surveillance, china surveillance state, xinjiang, uighurs, uyghurs, china uighurs, china police database, detention camp, reeducation camp, repression, police state, Chinese communist party, communist party, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
