<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 11:31:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>4004252</guid>
      <title>Stool Tests May Help Spot COVID-19 Transmission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHUHAI, CHINA  Health authorities might be able to detect COVID-19's spread by testing the sewers of a community for the coronavirus's RNA.Citing a new study in Gastroenterology, British Columbia Centre of Disease Control told the CBC that wastewater testing could be an early warning system for community transmission.According to a research team from China's Guangdong Province, traces of SARS-CoV-2's RNA have been found in the stool samples of hospitalized patients. The study involved 73 patients of both genders whose ages ranged from 10 months to 78 years old. Stool samples of 39 patients, or 53 percent, tested positive for the coronavirus RNA."Additionally, some patients started testing negative for the virus in respiratory samples, even as their stool samples continued to show positive results. Endoscopy indicated that the 17 patients, or 23 percent of the total, were still infected and that they may have been able to infect others via fecal-oral transmission.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 09:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/01/4004252/4004252_87932E8142D84DFAA6FB8AEC51DE82C3_200601_4004252_Stool_Tests_May_Help_Spot_COVID_19_Transmission_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[COVID-19, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, stool test, stool tests, viral RNA, oral-fecal transmission, wastewater testing, wastewater tests, sewage testing, sewage tests, Sun Yat-sen University, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004210</guid>
      <title>Mysterious Anomaly in Earth's Magnetic Field Is Spreading</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  A mysterious anomaly in the Earth's magnetic field that stretches from South America to Africa is spreading and scientists do not understand why.New data from the European Space Agency's SWARM constellation of satellites show that a weak spot in the Earth's magnetic field known as the South Atlantic Anomaly has been growing in size since 1970 and may possibly be developing a second cell centered above the coast of southwest Africa.The Earth's magnetic field, which is generated by the dynamo action of its molten metal core, protects the planet from the full impact of solar and cosmic radiation. According to the ESA, over the last two centuries, the global magnetic field has lost 9 percent of its strength on a global average.For now, the most significant effect of the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly is interference with satellites and spacecraft that pass over the region. However, the Earth's magnetic field destabilizes and reconstitutes itself over geological time, with sometimes even the north and south magnetic poles trading places.It is not clear what is causing the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly, but it could be related to the African Large Low Shear Velocity Province, one of two giant underground masses of rock that float like hidden continents where the Earth's mantle meets the outer core.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/01/4004210/4004210_D565CBDD97894AE79B86A9268F401068_200601_4004210_Mysterious_Anomaly_in_Earth_s_Magnetic_Field_Is__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[South Atlantic Anomaly, magnetic field, electromagnetic field, solar wind, radiation, European Space Agency, ESA, SWARM, satellite, African Large Low Shear Velocity Province, magnetic pole, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004159</guid>
      <title>Man Aims Bow and Arrow at 'Black Lives Matter' Protestors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY  A video of a white man aiming a bow and arrow at demonstrators has gone viral, as Black Lives Matter protests spread across the world demanding justice over the killing of George Floyd.The footage which has been viewed millions of times on Twitter shows a man, now identified as Brandon McCormick, getting out of his car yelling 'all lives matter' before producing a hunting bow in the middle of the protests in Salt Lake City, Utah.In the video, a woman is heard shouting 'look at this, call yourself an American?' as he readies the weapon and replies, 'Yes I'm an American, all lives matter!' McCormick then turns away from the camera and takes aim at protesters before the woman screams, 'Don't you dare!'In a different clip showing another angle, the protestors can then be seen taking cover behind cars to get out of his line of sight. Suddenly a group rushes McCormick, tackling him to the ground where they pummel and disarm him. According to social media users, his car was then flipped over, and according to McCormick during an interview, was then set on fire. A beaten McCormick, with a cut above his eye, told the reporter what happened, claiming protesters attacked him after he shouted from inside his car, saying, 'first I got beat up when I yelled, 'All Lives Matter,' then I pulled out weapons, then I got beat up some more.'McCormick claimed that two black men 'beat me through my open window' before he got out with the hunting bow.When the reporter urged him to see a doctor for his cut, McCormick said, 'I can't afford to, I'm on unemployment.'According to KSL.com, McCormick also had a large knife in his possession and was taken into police custody.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 06:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/01/4004159/4004159_E6FE9D0C2D3F48C1B4FAE6D8578B505C_200601_4004159_Man_Aims_Bow_and_Arrow_at__Black_Lives_Matter__P_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004084</guid>
      <title>Authorities to the Rescue as Woman's Car Won't Stop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUERNSEY, OHIO  State Highway Patrol released dashcam footage of a heart-racing moment a 20-year-old female driver called into the Washington County Sheriff's Office, claiming her vehicle wouldn't slow down or stop due to mechanical malfunction. The Facebook post from the 28th of May details the driver on Interstate 77 going at high speeds. The Washington County Sheriff's Office then connected the panicked woman to the Cambridge Post where a dispatcher attempted to keep her calm, giving suggestions on how to stop her racing vehicle.In the video, troopers then maneuver into position to warn traffic, and after being given instructions to slowly apply her hand brake, the vehicle slowed to a stop in the median. With thanks to the calming dispatcher and actions from the highway patrol, the situation ended with no injuries or damage.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 03:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/01/4004084/4004084_A7F56C7C412548309439F0114F0B84C4_200601_4004084_Authorities_to_the_Rescue_as_Woman_s_Car_Won_t_S_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004632</guid>
      <title>Thai Man Steals 126 Flip-Flops to Have Sex With Them</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NONTHABURI, THAILAND  A man has been caught with his pants down, stealing his neighbors' flip-flops in order to have sex with them. The man, identified as 24-year-old Theerapat Klaiya has a fetish for flip-flops and nabbed 126 pairs from his neighbors in Nonthaburi, central Thailand. Officers identified the pervert using footage from CCTV set up outside his latest alleged victim's home. Investigating officers searched Klaiya's home and discovered his vast collection of stolen footwear, that he claims he has been collecting for more than two years.He then allegedly told officers that he would wear the flip-flops around his home as it turned him on. He would then cuddle and kiss them, rub them on his naked body and then 'have sex with them.'Police officials claimed that most of the shoes were worn out and that his collection included dozens of different brands, sizes, and colors.The vast array of footwear was laid out in front of the Nonthaburi police station as part of a press conference on Monday the 25th last week. Police said the man admitted to three charges of nighttime theft and snatching, possessing a digital transceiver without permission, and violating the Wuhan virus curfew. Major Colonel Ekkaphop Prasitwattanachai told local media it was not the man's first offense of a similar act.He said, 'After we arrested the suspect, we also found out that he had already been arrested last year for stealing flip-flops in another district. He fully admitted stealing the sandals for lewd purposes, so he will be detained at the station until a court appearance for prosecutors to decide on the next part of the legal process for him.'TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 10:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/02/4004632/4004632_A5E2B66818B04E598A2F4F259C3CCAA6_200602_4004632_Thai_Man_Steals_126_Flip_Flops_to_Have_Sex_With__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004605</guid>
      <title>ESA's Solar Orbiter to Pass Through Tails of Comet ATLAS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  The European Space Agency's Solar Orbiter has been given the rare opportunity to conduct some "bonus science" in a serendipitous rendezvous with the tails of the comet ATLAS during the next few days, the space agency detailed in an article on its website.The Solar Orbiter was launched on February 10, 2020 and is en route to the inner solar system to study the Sun and inner heliosphere. The encounter with ATLAS had not been planned. In May, Geraint Jones of the UK's Mullard Space Science Laboratory discovered that the spacecraft would pass through the comet's tails as early as May 31, according to an article on UCL's website.The instruments used to study ATLAS were not scheduled to be fully functional until the probe's first solar observation on June 15. ESA scientists moved that timeline forward to begin collecting data when the probe passed through ATLAS's ion tail on May 31 and June 1. The Solar Orbiter will cross ATLAS's dust tail on June 6.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 09:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/02/4004605/4004605_20AE8D4D0F424015816F920B4D8653D3_200602_4004605_ESA_s_Solar_Orbiter_to_Pass_Through_Tails_of_Com_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[European Space Agency, ESA, Solar Orbiter, comet ATLAS, comet, ATLAS, ion tail, dust tail, gas tail, plasma tail, TomoNews, space, solar system, sun, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004450</guid>
      <title>E-cigarettes May Be Triggering Gum Inflammation in Users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLUMBUS, OHIO  A team of researchers has found unhealthy bacteria and inflammation in the gums of e-cigarette smokers that could lead to more severe gum diseases. Research published in the journal Science Advances found that the gums of healthy individuals who used e-cigarettes contained damaging bacteria and showed signs of gum disease.The team of specialists studied the gums of 123 individuals. 25 of them were smokers, another 25 were non-smokers, 20 used e-cigarettes, 25 were former smokers who used e-cigarettes and 28 were both cigarette and e-cigarette smokers.Results showed that e-cigarette use causes a change in the microbial landscape of the gums, making its healthy bacteria unrecognizable to our immune system. This then triggers an inflammatory response in the gums and coats healthy bacteria with a layer of slime.This phenomenon was observed even in those using non-nicotine e-cigarettes. This caused the team of researchers to believe that the liquid in electronic cigarettes could be triggering this phenomenon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/02/4004450/4004450_9D777DBB4992442589C4EBCC21F02C1B_200602_4004450_E_cigarettes_May_Be_Triggering_Gum_Inflammation__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, Next Animation, Next Media, feature, sidebar, video, explainer, image, illustration, graphic,  E-cigarettes, vaping, vape, vaping illness, gum disease, electronic cigarettes, oral microbiome, oral disease, gum disease, inflammatory response, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005042</guid>
      <title>SARS-CoV-2 Could be a Hybrid of Bat and Pangolin Viruses: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA  SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, could be a hybrid that descended from different clades of bat and pangolin viruses, according to new research in Science Advances.Writing in a news release, the team says the bat virus RaTG13 is the closest genetic relative to SARS-CoV-2, with a 96.3 percent RNA similarity. However, the bat virus does not have the spike protein parts used by SARS-CoV-2 for infecting humans.Yet another close relative, a clade of SARS-like pangolin virus from China, has receptor-binding domains that closely match the corresponding parts of the novel coronavirus.The bat and pangolin viruses likely recombined to form SARS-CoV-2. Recombining may occur when two similar viruses infect the same cell. When this happens, molecules that made up the distinct viruses are reshuffled into a new pathogen.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4005042/4005042_813D34934D8840C3BD69712AF01D1F61_200603_4005042_SARS_CoV_2_Could_be_a_Hybrid_of_Bat_and_Pangolin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005016</guid>
      <title>Scientists Found the World's Biggest Volcano</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANOA, HAWAII  Researchers have found the Earth's largest and hottest volcano northwest of Honolulu in the central northern Pacific.The shield volcano Puhahonu is mostly submerged, with only a third of its volume above the sea level as atolls named the Gardner Pinnacles. Puhahonu means "turtle surfacing for air" in Hawaiin. Writing in Earth and Planetary Science Letters, scientists say the research vessel Falkor charted the ocean with sonar and gravity mapping technology.According to the survey, Puhahonu is 90 km wide and 275 km long, or twice the size of Mauna Loa, formerly the world's largest known volcano.Scientists say the shield volcano's size was probably the result of abundant magma flowing from a very hot spot in the mantle. The temperature of the magma that created the Puhahonu is suggested by the forsterite content that is the highest among Hawaii's volcanoes. According to the study, Puhahonu is so massive that the Earth's crust and mantle buckled under its weight, which sank the bulk of the volcano under the sea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4005016/4005016_65C4F5729A394BD186F950CF527EE0CA_200603_4005016_Scientists_Found_the_World_s_Biggest_Volcano_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Puhahonu, Gardner Pinnacles, biggest volcano ever, biggest-ever volcano, hottest volcano, shield volcano, sonar, gravity mapping, Falkor,  Earth and Planetary Science Letters, University of Hawaii at Manoa, U.S., science, geology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004998</guid>
      <title>Armed Men Demand Dog in Bizare Home Invasion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PRINCE GEORGE, CANADA  Police are bemused over a home invasion incident that involved two suspects who weren't looking to grab pearls or wads of cash, but a dog. Citing authorities, a report from CBC News says a call came in on the evening of May 29 that two men brandishing what appeared to be guns entered a Prince George home and demanded the occupants hand over a dog.The occupants refused and the intruders quickly fled after officers arrived at the scene of the crime. Police say they arrested two suspects shortly after the incident, which they believe was calculated. Prince George RCMP said in a news release that 'The two individuals entered the residence and demanded the occupant hand over the dog. It's not clear what led up to the point of the home invasion or whether there's a relationship or squabble over it.'They also added that the suspects and one of the adult male victims were known to each other and that fortunately no one, including the dog, was physically injured; Police are not releasing the breed or any details about the sought-after pup.23-year-old Shayn Robert Bulmer and 23-year-old Dylon Sadillo McLemore were both charged with break and enter, possession of a weapon, and two counts of assault with a weapon. According to the report, officers found a rifle, a BB gun that was made to look like an assault rifle, and that body armor was left behind at a residence when the suspects fled from police out the back door. The RCMP said the suspects are being held in custody pending a court appearance on Tuesday, and that more charges may be considered.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4004998/4004998_1952DC155DA14BA7969B21869ED4182D_200603_4004998_Armed_Men_Demand_Dog_in_Bizzare_Home_Invasion_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004883</guid>
      <title>The Closest Exoplanet to Our Earth Has Been Confirmed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA  A team of specialists from the University of Geneva has confirmed the existence of an exoplanet orbiting in the habitable zone of a neighboring sun. Researchers have confirmed the presence of Proxima Centauri B, an exoplanet that orbits in the habitable zone of the star closest to our sun, Proxima Centauri, according to a report published in the journal Astronomy and Astrophysics.Researchers from the University of Geneva were able to confirm its existence by using a new generation spectrograph located in Chile called ESPRESSO.Their observations showed that Proxima B is 1.17 times the mass of Earth and orbits its sun in 11.2 days.Proxima B receives similar energy from its sun and could, therefore, harbor life. However, this exoplanet's sun is an active red dwarf and it hits the exoplanet with roughly 400 times the amount of X-rays that Earth receives.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 05:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4004883/4004883_DDD7A687098C4AB0BE6751BB38B7A059_200603_4004883_The_Closest_Exoplanet_to_Our_Earth_Has_Been_Conf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Proxima b, proxima centauri, space, earth-like planet proxima b, TomoNews, ESPRESSO, earth sized planet, exo planet,  new planet, life in outer space, what is proxima b, where is proxima b, life in proxima b]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005428</guid>
      <title>Man Smashes Car Window to Rescue Trapped Dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SWANSEA, WALES  A video has emerged of a man smashing his way into a car to rescue a dog at a supermarket car park on a scorching hot day. The clip was captured by 29-year-old Zoey Thronton, who was shopping at a Tesco in Swansea last Sunday; she claimed that the suffering dog was inside on its own for 'at least 30 minutes.'According to Wales Online, Zoey noticed a woman looking concerned and went over to see if everything was okay, saying, 'we went over to see if everything was alright and it turns out that the dog was inside, it was really hot.''The window was open a little bit but we were there for at least half an hour before any action was taken.''It's long enough for a dog to overheat in a car.'She even alerted the surrounding shops to send out a message over the tannoy system to try and locate the neglectful owners before their window was smashed, however, to no avail. Out of nowhere, a man jumps into action and smashes the window and jumps through the car to rescue the dog. Zoey stated that the dog was panting heavily and that the police, who received a call at 2.30 pm had arrived even before the owners got back. South Wales Police have, like so many, warned that dogs can die in hot cars.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 10:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/04/4005428/4005428_5C0F9B65BE9E4E5080DCAB63782623F7_200604_4005428_Man_Smashes_Car_Window_to_Rescue_Trapped_Dog_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005326</guid>
      <title>New Ebola Outbreak in the Democratic Republic of the Congo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KINSHASA, DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF THE CONGO  The Government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo has confirmed the deaths of five individuals who were infected with Ebola.Citing authorities in the Democratic Republic of Congo, the United Nations Children's Fund reports that a new Ebola outbreak has occurred in the country's city of Mbandaka. This is the eleventh outbreak in the country since the virus's discovery in 1976.Nine individuals are reported to have been infected. Five of them have died. The individuals died between the 18th and 30th of May but were confirmed to be Ebola-related yesterday.The virus's incubation period lasts from 2 to 21 days. Symptoms of the Ebola virus include fever, headache, muscle pain and fatigue. These symptoms are followed up by vomiting and diarrhea.Ebola is passed on by human-to-human transmission. Individuals can be infected if they come in contact with sweat, mucous, saliva, blood, or other body fluids of infected people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 06:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/04/4005326/4005326_1AFD8F53A17A44CC85178B11FBE03E95_200604_4005326_New_Ebola_Outbreak_in_the_Democratic_Republic_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[ebola virus, virus, viral outbreak, Congo, West Africa, ebola outbreak, congo ebola outbreak, ebola outbreak in congo,ebola outbreak news, ebola outbreak congo, health, world, news, world news, conflict, humanitarian agencies, Congo, infectious diseases, disease, illness, healthcare, united nations, world health organization, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005778</guid>
      <title>Scientists Designs Squid-Like Transparent Human Cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRVINE, CALIFORNIA  Scientists have engineered color-shifting abilities into human cells. Researchers say their project is inspired by female opalescent inshore squids that evade predators by changing their colors from translucent to opaque white.According to the study in Nature Communications, squids and octopuses can cloak because their skin contains leucophore cells, which includes protein molecules called reflectins. This substance scatters light and creates an iridescent camouflage.In a news release, the scientists say they took human embryonic kidney cells and introduced genes that express reflectin. These cells are then cultured and examined under a microscope.The study's co-author was cited as saying the cells grew ball-shaped nanostructures throughout the cell bodies, and the spheres contain reflectin molecules. This means the reflectins behaved optically as if they were in squids. Thumbnail credit: PEXELS / MARTIN]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 07:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/05/4005778/4005778_72D753EE1E4C46BC8970E736D7E294A3_200605_4005778_Scientists_Designs_Squid_Like_Transparent_Human__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[squid-inspired, squid-like transparency, translucent squid, translucent squids, offshore squid, offshore squids, optical camouflage, light scattering, biotechnology, genetic engineering, reflectin, reflectins, nanostructure, human cells, human cells, University of California Irvine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005728</guid>
      <title>A Rare Dino Related to T-Rexes Has Been Discovered in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VICTORIA, AUSTRALIA  Five years after the discovery of a pterosaur fossil, a PhD student in Australia noticed that it had been mislabeled and that it actually belonged to a rare dinosaur called Elaphrosaurus. Paleontologists at Australia's Swinburne University of Technology discovered they had mistakenly identified a fossil as the bone of an ancient flying reptile called pterosaur, but it actually belonged to a rare dinosaur called elaphrosaur. This is the first elaphrosaur found in Australia.Citing Stephen Poropat, the lead author of the study, The Guardian reports that only three other elaphrosaurs species have been found in Tanzania, China and Argentina.The elaphrosaur was part of the theropod family, which includes predators like the Tyrannosaurus Rex and velociraptors. It was roughly as tall as a small Emu and measures 2 meters from its head to the end of its tail."According to the research published in the journal Gondwana Research, the elaphrosaur the team discovered lived during the cretaceous period. At this time, Australia's land was located in the Arctic Circle.Researchers believe that the elaphrosaurs may have lived in a habitat containing a diverse variety of plants and trees such as conifers, gingkos, ferns, horsetails, conifers, and flowering plants.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 05:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/05/4005728/4005728_3FC383ED67484297934B58E108C0C351_200605_4005728_A_Rare_Dino_Related_to_T_Rexes_Has_Been_Discover_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Dinosaurs, extinction, asteroid, asteroid, deadliest possible angle, impact angle, Chicxulub crater, elaphrosaur, Swinburne University of Technology, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006545</guid>
      <title>Mum Dies After Drinking Two Liters of Coke Per Day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INVERCARGILL, NEW ZEALAND  A mum of three died after drinking nearly two liters of Coke, plus energy drinks, per day. 34-year-old Amy Louise Thorpe from Invercargill, New Zealand was also 15 weeks pregnant when she was found unresponsive and face down on her bed on December 4 in 2018. She suffered an epileptic seizure and died.According to findings released by coroner David Robinson, her excessive divulgence on caffeinated fizzy drinks may have been the reason why. The inquest heard that Thorpe would guzzle down two liters of Coke and between 500ml to one liter of energy drinks per day. Thorpe, who had a history of epilepsy and other conditions, found that her pregnancy increased her seizure frequency to about once a week.According to the New Zealand Herald, Thorpe was seen by neurologist Graeme Hammond-Tooke in November 2018, who reported the epilepsy diagnosis was uncertain but treated her on the basis of that diagnosis. He encouraged her to try another antiepileptic medication, however, she was reluctant to change her drugs or undergo further tests. And just weeks later, she was found unconscious and face down on her bed with her torso leaning over the bedside cabinet. Paramedics desperately tried to revive her but sadly they were unable to save her life.Her partner, who was unnamed in the report, described her as being 'addicted' to caffeinated drinks.When the coroner sought advice from Thorpes' Neurologist about the significance of caffeine in this case, the associated professor reported that studies suggested drinking caffeine increased seizure susceptibility while in some cases, chronic use of caffeine may protect against seizures.Dr. Hammond Tooke said, 'In the case of Ms. Thorpe, I think it is possible that excessive caffeine contributed to poor seizure control.'In 2010, there was another incident of a woman dying from a coke overdose from the very same city in New Zealand. The woman, Natasha Harris drank up to eight liters of Coke a day for several years before her death.At the time, Coca-Cola said that it could not be proven that drinking large quantities of the drink contributed to her death.A company spokesperson said that they were disappointed that the coroner had chosen to focus on the combination of excessive consumption of Coca-Cola and other health and lifestyle factors as the probable cause of her death.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 23:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006545/4006545_D6777C6AEF5A4C3981863E74F9EC8616_200608_4006545_Mum_Dies_After_Drinking_Two_Liters_of_Coke_Per_D_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006776</guid>
      <title>Explainer: What Young Great White Sharks Eat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  Scientists from Australia say the most detailed study to date showed that great white sharks hunted more seabed-dwelling prey than they expected. This paper is published in Frontiers in Marine Science.Researchers from the University of Sydney studied the stomach content of 50 juvenile great white sharks caught by the New South Wales Shark Mesh Program, according to a news release from the university.Scientists found mid-water fish like salmon made up 32 percent of the sharks' diet, bottom-dwelling fish such as stargazers made 17 percent, reef fish like Eastern Blue gropers 5 percent, and batoid fish like rays made 15 percent. Sharks also eat cephalopods, and they usually begin feeding on marine mammals and other sharks after growing larger in size.The study tracked the seasonal migration of Australia's great white sharks and found that they ranged from the coastal seas of southern New Queensland to northern Tasmania. Sharks range further as they mature.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 12:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006776/4006776_DF9A18A50A024CA79ED177674A7DBCD7_200608_4006776_Explainer__What_Young_Great_White_Sharks_Eat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Main keyword or keyword phrase you are targeting, a few variations of your main keyword, two to three tags that describe video's overall category, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006670</guid>
      <title>Dancing Chinese 'Aunties' Brawl Over Public Square</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YA'AN, SICHUAN, CHINA  Two groups of Chinese dancing 'aunties' came to blows over a prime spot on a public square. Reported by The Paper on June 2, the two groups had no previous bad blood and simply came to blows over a spot to practice their dance moves; police are now looking into the incident.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 09:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006670/4006670_F9B60660E8FF46C6ABDB4B11CDC0B5D8_200608_4006670_Dancing_Chinese__Aunties__Brawl_Over_Public_Squa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006628</guid>
      <title>How Maize Turned Into a Staple Ancient Mesoamerican Crop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALBUQUERQUE, NEW MEXICO  Archeologists may have found out when cave-dwelling prehistoric Mesoamericans began eating maize as a staple, according to a new study in Science Advances.Researchers examined the carbon isotope content of 52 skeletons from various rock shelters in Belize. The bones belonged to a representative sample of men, women and children, and evidence showed they were consuming more and more maize.Writing in a news release, researchers say pre-maize hunter-gatherers from around 9,000 years ago ate wild animals and plants. Then, about 4,700 years ago, the population began to consume maize, which made up 30 percent of their diet.In the following millenia, Mesoamericans adopted sedentary farming and maize consumption increased to 70 percent of the food they ate.The authors speculated that human selection and spontaneous genetic changes to the plants then led to maize crops to grow bigger cobs, bigger seeds and more seed rows.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006628/4006628_8F0A0BE39E114A8189822350A8D8734A_200608_4006628_How_Maize_Turned_Into_a_Staple_Ancient_Mesoameri_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[ancient mesoamerica, maize, corn, corn plants, mesoamerica, rock shelter, rock shelters, carbon isotopes, carbon isotope, skeletons, hunter-gatherer, agriculture, plant domestication, history, archeology, U.S., University of New Mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006594</guid>
      <title>How Rubber Bullets Can Injure You, Explainer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Rubber bullets fall under the category of kinetic impact projectiles that are used for crowd control purposes by law-enforcement. This is how badly they can injure you. According to a 2016 report by Physicians for Human Rights and the International Network of Civil Liberties Organizations, rubber bullets can be spherical or cylindrical and can be made of hard rubber, plastic or PVC. They can also be fired as single shots or in groups of multiple projectiles within a cartridge.Not all crowd control projectiles are made of rubber though.  San Antonio journalist, Mark Dunphy, shared a photo of his injuries on Twitter after being shot by a wooden projectile. According to a report published in BMJ Open in 2017, rubber bullets can cause serious injuries and even death.The study found that out of 1,984 individuals who sustained injuries from kinetic impact projectiles, 53 died and 300 were permanently disabled from the injury. 71 percent of the survivors had severe injuries.If an individual receives a shot from a rubber bullet in the neck it could lead to permanent damage or a deadly injury to their airways. A shot sustained in the eye could lead to losing it and a point-blank shot could lead to death.According to the report by Physicians for Human Rights and the International Network of Civil Liberties Organizations, rubber bullet impacts affect bones, muscles, and limbs most severely.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 03:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006594/4006594_022EE785B3EA4CA195C91E97C9E5064A_200608_4006594_How_Rubber_Bullets_Can_Injure_You__Explainer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[George floyd, ahmaud arbery, Black lives matter protests, black lives matter, blm, black lives matter walk, Rubber bullets, riots, protest, crowd control, crowd control setting, how lethal are rubber bullets, crowd control methods, crowd control weapons, What are rubber bullets, How dangerous are rubber bullets,  TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006999</guid>
      <title>YOU IDIOT: Chinese Man Shoves Chopstick up his Bum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIANGYANG, HUBEI, CHINA  In an attempt to poke his hemorrhoids, an old man from China stuck a chopstick up his bum.On arriving at his local hospital, the 68-year-old underwent an X-ray scan which revealed a strange concealment, there was a metal chopstick all the way up in his guts. The man explained away this potential watershed moment by stating that he was poking around at his hemorrhoids and well, the rest is history. According to the Doctor, he told reporters that it was 'very rare' for such an anus incident to occur. Fortunately for the man the surgeons managed to wriggle that stick out without too much drama.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 05:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/09/4006999/4006999_769216F1FDB54D0882215E8B5816E6E3_200609_4006999_YOU_IDIOT__Chinese_Man_Shoves_Chopstick_up_his_B_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006956</guid>
      <title>Human mini-liver transplanted into rats are fully-functional</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PITTSBURGH  Researchers created a functioning mini-human liver and successfully transplanted it into rats. According to a report published in Cell Reports, experts from the University of Pittsburgh successfully developed and transplanted functioning human mini-livers into rats.Scientists created the mini livers by using human skin cells and then reverting them into a stem cell state. These cells are called induced pluripotent stem cells and other types of cells can derive from them.They then used chemicals and hormones to induce differentiation. This pushed the induced pluripotent stem cells into becoming liver cells. The newly created liver cells were then seeded on mini-liver bioreactors.The lab-grown livers were then transplanted into five immunosuppressed mice or mice whose immune system would be less likely to reject the organ. Four days after the transplant, the mice were dissected in order to examine how well the  implanted organ functioned.After dissecting the rats, researchers found all five rats had blood circulation issues around the graft of the mini-liver. However, the rats had human liver proteins in their blood serum indicating that the livers were working properly.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 04:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/09/4006956/4006956_78DAF2AE83CD48C58863FFBA0E2CB538_200609_4006956_Human_mini_liver_transplanted_into_rats_are_full_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Bioengineered Human Liver, rat liver,  human mini liver, University of Pittsburgh, organ transplant, liver transplant, Successful Transplant, lab-grown livers, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006940</guid>
      <title>Train Forced to Stop Because of Arrogant Chinese Woman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZIYANG, SICHUAN, CHINA  A woman in Sichuan province brought a train to a halt with nothing more than her own carelessness. Footage from Pear Video shows a woman of about 40-years-old on the 2nd of June waltz across a railroad in the city of Ziyang whilst nattering on the phone, her negligence for her surroundings forced the train to actually stop. The lax woman, despite the cries of train workers continues to walk on the tracks until finally responding to yells from people waiting at the crossing. She casually steps off the tracks and, you guessed it, continues talking on the phone. According to Pear Video, this section of the track is primarily used for transporting goods and, fortunately for the woman, usually runs at a slower speed. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 03:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/09/4006940/4006940_29363A6D80244215B4ED290A8CEB0B0C_200609_4006940_Train_Forced_to_Stop_Because_of_Arrogant_Chinese_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007417</guid>
      <title>Virus Outbreak in China May Have Started Far Earlier Than Reported</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  Satellite imagery of vehicle traffic around hospitals in Wuhan suggests the coronavirus may have struck the city months before the outbreak was acknowledged, according to Harvard University researchers.The manuscript of the study has yet to be peer reviewed.According to the paper, the team reviewed satellite traffic images at the parking lots of six hospitals in the autumn of 2019. The researchers found a surge in the number of parked cars after comparing the data to the same period in the previous year.At the Wuhan Tianyou Hospital, which is one of the city's largest, the team counted 285 cars and trucks. This traffic volume is viewed as a proxy for respiratory patient intake and the count marked a 67 percent increase over 2018.Additionally, the team analyzed internet search terms in China and found a significant uptick in searches for the words "cough" and "diarrhoea."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 09:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007417/4007417_DEE97567655249B391FD68266B333525_200610_4007417_Virus_Outbreak_in_China_May_Have_Started_Far_Ear_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[chinese covered up coronavirus, china covered up corona deaths, china lied people died, china lied about coronavirus, COVID-19, coronavirus, corona virus, sars-cov-2, pattern analysis, vehicle traffic, parking lots, hospital traffic, internet search term volume, internet search terms, Wuhan, China, Harvard University, pandemic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007304</guid>
      <title>Chinese Guy Shoots Himself in the Chest With Crossbow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANNING, GUANGXI, CHINA  A Chinese man can consider himself extremely lucky after he accidentally shot himself in the chest with a crossbow, narrowly missing his heart. Citing a post on Chinese Twitter knock-off, Weibo, which has now received over half a million views, the so-far-unnamed man was filmed on the 6th of June with a bolt sticking out of his chest and actually poking out of the other side. The man can be seen held up, almost in display as he likely reconsiders his life. The source claims that he was practicing archery at home when he accidentally shot himself.Incredibly, doctors said that he missed his heart by a mere one centimeter and that, obviously, he is incredibly lucky to be alive. Fortunately for the man, the arrow was successfully removed during a much needed emergency operation. The man is now recovering from his piercing wound and hopefully recovering from when he landed on his head at birth.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 04:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007304/4007304_2721F1DC0D2540EB83B5484C668B8889_200610_4007304_Chinese_Guy_Shoots_Himself_in_the_Chest_With_Cro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007299</guid>
      <title>Man Rams Mistress's Car Off Second Floor Parking Lot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI  A man has been convicted after ramming his mistress's car off a second floor parking garage.As seen in the CCTV, the man, who was driving his wife's car slid into reverse and crashed into the parked car.The man, surnamed Zhou then rammed into the car a second time, smashing his girlfriend's car straight through a wall; the car then fell from the second fall floor. When Zhou was arrested by the police, he tested positive for being over the limit. He then tried to convince police that he, in fact, fell unconscious at the wheel and had no intention of hitting his 'bit on the side's' car. According to local news, thankfully this week Zhou was convicted of crimes including intentionally destroying property and dangerous driving.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 04:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007299/4007299_1940D68054DD4FE99C4DA3AA36C2F22F_200610_4007299_Man_Rams_Mistress_s_Car_Off_Second_Floor_Parking_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007292</guid>
      <title>WHO finally recommends wearing masks in public places</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA  The World Health Organization on June 5 changed its guidance on wearing masks to curb the transmission of the COVID-19 disease, recommending governments encourage everyone to wear masks in public places.The WHO said evidence from studies in recent weeks showed masks could serve as "a barrier for potentially infectious droplets."The organization had previously said there was not enough evidence to say that healthy people should wear masks.The WHO now recommends wearing masks in public settings such as stores, at work, social or mass gatherings, and in closed settings such as schools or places of worship.The global body also recommends wearing masks in cramped conditions such as slums and refugee camps, and on public transport.To prevent critical resources from being diverted from healthcare workers, the WHO recommends that members of the general public wear fabric or "non-medical" masks.These masks should have at least three layers  an absorbent inner layer, a filter, and an outer layer that does not easily absorb water.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 04:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007292/4007292_5CA7FF5850C441789D6688FAD59DAD62_200610_4007292_WHO_finally_recommends_wearing_masks_in_public_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Educational, animation, 3D, graphics, COVID-19, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus, corona virus, virus, WHO, World Health Organization, coronavirus mask, mask, COVID-19 disease, medical mask, non-medical mask, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007264</guid>
      <title>Ex-astronaut Kathy Sullivan dives to deepest known point on Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISLE OF MAN, UNITED KINGDOM  Undersea explorer Victor Vescovo and Kathy Sullivan, the first American woman to walk in space, dived into the Challenger Deep last Sunday, according to a report in the New York Times.The Challenger Deep is the deepest known spot on Earth. It is roughly 10,902 to 10,929 meters deep.Sullivan and Vescovo captured images of the deep sea while aboard the Limiting Factor, a deep-sea research submersible that can withstand 2,200 tonnes of pressure. It is designed to travel into the deep oceanic trenches of the ocean called the hadal zone.Once the pair ascended back into their ship, they called a group of astronauts in the International Space Station, which at the time was located around 409 kilometers above Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 03:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007264/4007264_CC8C659AACCD4C49A3A798D46F92E12B_200610_4007264_Ex_astronaut_Kathy_Sullivan_dives_to_deepest_kno_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[mariana trench, the challenger deep, Kathryn Dwyer Sullivan, Kathryn Dwyer, Kathryn Sullivan, Kathryn D. Sullivan, how deep is the mariana trench, deepest part of earth, deepest part of the ocean, first american woman in space, first woman in space, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007811</guid>
      <title>Amazon Halts Police Use of Its Facial Recognition Technology</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  Amazon announced that it will ban police use of the company's facial recognition tool Rekognition for a year, in a blogpost dated Wednesday.Earlier this year, an Amazon executive told PBS that not even Amazon knows the exact number of police departments that utilize Rekognition.According to a 2018 study by MIT Media Lab, facial recognition tools were more prone to errors when identifying people of color, and products from major tech corporations misgendered dark-skinned women 35 percent of the time.A 2019 study by the same institution further states that Amazon's Rekognition mislabelled women of color as men 31 percent of the time, while Microsoft's technology made the error only 1.5 percent of the time.Citing a statement from Clearview AI, The Verge reports that Amazon, Google and IBM have exited the law enforcement facial recognition market, which left the field to Clearview. In the statement, Clearview asserts that its product "actually works."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 10:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/11/4007811/4007811_5EBCFD0707434C62B5449E5E5BF864CE_200611_4007811_Amazon_Halts_Police_Use_of_Its_Facial_Recognitio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[facial recognition technology, facial recognition tool, Amazon, Rekognition, police departments, police department, law enforcement, racial bias, racism, biometrics, technology, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007755</guid>
      <title>Chinese Homeowner Finds Builders Stuffed Walls With Litter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEIZHOU, GUANGDONG, CHINA  A homeowner has discovered that his builders used trash to fill his walls. Whilst renovating, the owner found that part of the interior of the wall was filled with trash, including milk cartons and plastic cups.In another clip from the video, which was posted on the 3rd of June, the disgruntled owner demonstrates the ease at which the wall can be scraped away at.According to Pear Video, the homeowner has since filed a complaint about the shoddy workmanship. The property management office has pushed responsibility onto the original builders and the local housing ministry is now investigating the matter.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 09:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/11/4007755/4007755_69630CA4747649B08D99803B5E0C4980_200611_4007755_Chinese_Homeowner_Finds_Builders_Stuffed_Walls_W_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007719</guid>
      <title>Taiwan Repels 'Multiple' Chinese Fighters Over Taiwanese Airspace</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Taiwan's air force scrambled planes to warn off "multiple" Chinese fighter jets that had briefly entered Taiwan's air defence identification zone on June 9, the country's Ministry of National Defense said in a statement.The Su-30 fighters, some of China's most advanced jets, were issued verbal warnings to leave and Taiwanese air force jets "took active responses to dispel" the intruders, the ministry said."The military has full surveillance and control of all activities in the sea and air that surround Taiwan, and the public can rest assured of our capability to uphold security for our national territory," the ministry said.The defense ministry also confirmed that a U.S. C-40A transport plane had just hours before passed over Taiwan with permission near Taipei before heading south along the country's coast.The incidents occurred a day after the commander of the U.S. 7th Fleet confirmed that the guided-missile destroyer USS Russell had passed through the Taiwan Strait the previous week, according to a report in the Stars and Stripes. This was the U.S. Navy's seventh such transit this year and second in two weeks.The Chinese incursion also came hours after Taiwan's defense ministry announced the country's annual Han Kuang exercises, which had been postponed due to the coronavirus, will be conducted in July and September, Taiwan's Central News Agency reports.The annual exercises test the country's capabilities to ward off attack from China's People's Liberation Army.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 08:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/11/4007719/4007719_E2084FC49E8C41328F5B627EE0812C77_200611_4007719_Taiwan_Repels__Multiple__Chinese_Fighters_Over_T_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taiwan china relations, taiwan china war, taiwan china dispute, taiwan china border, liaoning aircraft carrier, south china sea dispute, Chinese military exercise, U.S. Navy, destroyer, Taiwan Strait, Taiwan, China, U.S., defense, F-16V, TomoNews, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007648</guid>
      <title>Meanwhile in Russia: Mom Pregnant With Step-Son's Baby</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KRASNODAR KRAI, RUSSIA  35-year-old Russian influencer, Marina Balmasheva from the western region of Krasnodar Krai, was married to husband 45-year-old Alexey, for 13 years before they got divorced. After their marriage ended, she started a relationship with Alexey's son, 20-year-old Vladimir.  Why did they get divorced? Her ex told a Russian talk show that he discovered the relationship when he heard the pair having sex.Saying, 'I could not fall asleep one night when I heard them having sex. Then I understood that Marina was cheating on me with my son.'And just last month, to make matters worse, she recently posted a throwback picture essentially bringing further attention to their previous relationship, making it all the more weird. Now Marina has revealed that she is expecting a baby with Vladimir.In an Instagram video, Marina handed her hunk the positive pregnancy test and embraced him. The couple also announced their plans to marry since finding out about the pregnancy.The influencer with more than 400,000 followers shared the news on Instagram where she wrote, 'I'm tired of hiding. Everything is possible in this world. We are four weeks and yes, that is why we decided to get married.'Of course, she opened herself up to criticism with one person rightly pointing out, 'What shocks me most is that this boy grew up before her very eyes.'So, is she worried about her new man potentially running off with a younger model? No, says Marina, 'I understand that in some time he may meet another younger woman and leave me but I think – no. He will grow into a brave real man.'TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 04:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/11/4007648/4007648_54F891F9E6DD44B9A30971243B461C54_200611_4007648_Meanwhile_in_Russia__Mom_Pregnant_With_Step_Son__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008318</guid>
      <title>Anti-Protest Weapons, Explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS    American police officers have been using a variety of crowd-control weapons against black lives matter demonstrators. These weapons can cause serious injuries and, in some instances, even death.Chemical irritants used as crowd control weapons such as pepper spray and tear gas contain a chemical commonly known as CS gas which can cause a burning sensation and inflammation in the eyes, mouth, throat and lungs, Reuters reports.Flashbangs, also known as stun grenades, are considered disorientation devices. The sound and bright light flashbangs emit when they explode stun those standing around their explosion. However, Reuters reports that they can severely burn bystanders if fired at close range.The flash and sound emitted by flashbangs can cause temporary loss of hearing and sight as well as loss of balance.Sting-ball grenades contain pellets that deploy once the grenade explodes. Some also contain chemical compounds and others also emit bright lights and sounds upon explosion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 14:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008318/4008318_C8FCDA9241D241FA8F5FDB89998C3447_200612_4008318_Anti_Protest_Weapons__Explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Rubber bullets, riots, protest, crowd control, crowd control setting, rubber bullets, plastic bullets, crowd control, riot, less lethal weapons, protests, kinetic impact projectiles, KIP, black lives matter, black lives matter protests, blm, George floyd, ahmaud arbery, anti protest weapons, pepper spray, sting-ball grenades, flashbangs, blm, black lives matter, ahmaud arbery, george floyd, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008305</guid>
      <title>Explainer: What is Teargas?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  Tear gas is a chemical weapon used for crowd control that causes irritation to the eyes, mouth, throat, lungs and skin, thus incapacitating individuals.The most common chemicals found in a tear gas canister are 2-chlorobenzalmalononitrile, commonly known as CS gas, and chloroacetophenone, a component that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention describes as having a "sharp irritating odor."Individuals exposed to tear gas may experience wheezing, shortness of breath and vomiting along with a burning sensation in their eyes, nose and skin.If exposed to the anti-riot agent for a prolonged time, individuals can develop serious eye illnesses such as scarring, cataracts and glaucoma. It may also lead to respiratory issues such as asthma.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008305/4008305_B800B2F2301241F1B7DFA8E1F33595E0_200612_4008305_Explainer__What_is_Teargas__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[What is inside tear gas, What is tear gas, how does tear gas hurt you, How does tear gas work, Can tear gas cause permanent harm, is tear gas a chemical weapon, can tear gas kill you, can tear gas hurt you, how bad does tear gas hurt you, chemicals in tear gas, chemicals found in tear gas, why does tear gas hurt, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008189</guid>
      <title>Revealed: Pentagon Held War Game to Quash Gen Z Rebellion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Pentagon conducted a war game in 2018 that pitted armed forces against a youth uprising dubbed "Zbellion," according to documents obtained by the Intercept via the Freedom of Information Act.The troubling revelation came days after Secretary of Defense Mark Esper urged states to "dominate the battlespace" in dealing with Black Lives Matter protests.Esper later withdrew the comment and signed orders to remove paratroopers from Washington, DC.The war game envisioned members of Generation Z  radicalized by the Great Recession and student debt  would start a nationwide uprising in 2025.The rebels would see themselves as "agents for social change" with the goal of helping to "move the world forward."According to the scenario, an insurgent group called Zbellion would start a protest movement in Seattle. From there, civil unrest would spread to New York City; Washington, DC; Los Angeles; Los Vegas; and Austin.The military expected tech-savvy insurgents to launch cyber attacks against financial institutions to redistribute wealth, to fund their colleagues, and to "spread a call for anarchy."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 09:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008189/4008189_1469DDBFCAEF4B94B1F161A983CFCC2C_200612_4008189_Revealed__Pentagon_Held_War_Game_to_Quash_Gen_Z__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Zbellion, generation z rebellion, activists, insurrection, revolt, war games, war game, military exercise, military exercises, black lives matter, BLM, protests, protest, politics, U.S.]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008097</guid>
      <title>Floodwaters Take Down Three-Story Building in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGXI, CHINA  After some torrential flooding in parts of southern China earlier in the week, a three-story building crashed into a river in Guangxi.Footage of the crash was posted to Miaopai on the 10th of June which shows the moment the building's foundations crumble apart, sending the building sliding down into the floodwaters.Signs of the collapse were actually discovered in advance so the building was evacuated ahead of time with no casualties reported.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 07:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008097/4008097_C4997456074A409B9D6C0D52356FA3C9_200612_4008097_Floodwaters_Take_Down_Three_Story_Building_in_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008049</guid>
      <title>New Ancient Roman City Found Without Excavating</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, UNITED KINGDOM  Researchers from the University of Cambridge and Ghent University in Belgium have discovered the remains of Falerii Novi, an ancient Roman city just 50 kilometers away from Rome that has been buried for roughly 13 centuries. Their research was published in the journal Antiquity.The team of archaeologists discovered Falerii Novi by attaching a ground-penetrating radar or GPR to an all-terrain vehicle and then using it to map the buried city. A GPR sends radio pulses into the ground and then analyzes the waves that bounce off objects underground.The resulting 3D images put together by the team showed that Falerii Novi had a theatre, a market, a bath complex and temples as well as shops, monuments and atrium houses.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008049/4008049_562BE7703EC34F478A1955E90C58FD3B_200612_4008049_New_Ancient_Roman_City_Found_Without_Excavating_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Ground penetrating radar, GPR, Ancient roman city found, ancient roman city, roman city, archaeology, Falerii Novi, ancient roman city without excavating, no excavation, roman empire, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008007</guid>
      <title>Dancing Chinese 'Aunties' Stomp on Glass-Bottom Bridge!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANGZHOU, CHINA  A glass-bottom bridge became a dance floor for some hyperactive dancing 'aunties', causing the likely already fragile bridge to shake worryingly. The swaying of the bridge caused alarm amongst visitors, prompting a security guard to get involved. In the clip, a petrified individual can be heard shouting, 'Stop dancing! The bridge is going to break!' The video which was posted on the 10th of June has received 1.64 million views with netizens, rightly condemning those troublesome dancing aunties. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 04:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008007/4008007_C70072AEDDE5400EB5C44347FD50DB9B_200612_4008007_Dancing_Chinese__Aunties__Stomp_on_Glass_Bottom__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009103</guid>
      <title>China Braces for Second Wave of COVID-19 Outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China has put Beijing on alert as a rash of 59 domestic COVID-19 cases was reported in the city as of Monday, according to Beijing Municipal Health Commission.Reuters reports that the city has put the neighborhood of Huaxiang on high alert and raised the epidemiological risk level for 10 other neighborhoods from low to medium.The health commission seems to be focusing its efforts on the Xinfadi wholesale food market. Contact tracing has revealed that all cases were linked to the important food market situated in Beijing's Huaxiang neighborhood.An unnamed chain restaurant that sells traditional Beijing noodles was closed down after two employees tested positive for the coronavirus.Beijing has put all companies with employees who have visited the market on quarantine.Citing the state-run Health Times, officials told Reuters that genetic sequencing suggests the virus may have come from Europe to China.They were cited as saying the virus may have spread via contaminated meat, seafood or feces from the infected.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 10:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/15/4009103/4009103_EE7156FCA4C544BCBF36CA0C087327DF_200615_4009103_China_Braces_for_Second_Wave_of_COVID_19_Outbrea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[COVID-19, COVID, coronavirus, SARS-CoV-2, second wave, Xinfadi, Xin Fa Di, wholesale food market, food market, Beijing, China, health, science]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009005</guid>
      <title>Chinese Woman Made $423,000 From Flight Cancellations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NANJING, CHINA  A 45-year-old woman surnamed Li has been arrested by police for making paper off the misfortune of Chinese commercial flights taking off late. The serial scammer booked hundreds of flights between 2015 and 2019, flights she had zero intention of actual boarding; instead, her plan of action was to buy flight delay insurance and turn delays into a serious income. So, how did she know which flight would take off late? Well, I've got to hand it to her, Li would analyze local weather conditions and online reviews to assess which flights would be susceptible to delays or cancellations.Using this methodology, according to Chinese outlet The Paper, she booked over 900 flights using both her name and the names of friends and relatives to make a huge $423,000. However, she got way ahead of herself and her illegal success gained the attention of the authorities.Li was arrested on the 12th of June by police in Nanjing who announced that she had been arrested on fraud charges. According to the report, her scam has had an after-effect on some Chinese travel service providers who have fixed the loopholes that permitted Li to commit such offenses. Amendments were made such as the flight actually needing to be used for the compensation to be paid.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 07:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/15/4009005/4009005_AD740F98A07640979929B125F88F0A3C_200615_4009005_Chinese_Woman_Made__423_000_From_Flight_Cancella_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008960</guid>
      <title>Chinese Company 'Team Building': Motivating or Abuse?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LUOYANG, HENAN, CHINA  In the pursuit of milking every ounce of effort from their staff, some Chinese companies within the borders of the communist regime, punish their employees, usually for not reaching their targets; these punishments in the past have seen staff spanked on stage and even forced to drink cups of urine. The latest example, however, comes from the Henan city of Luoyang on the 10th of June, where a video captures the moment a real estate agency forces its workers to do push-ups in the street while having water poured on their backs because according to the report via Boiling Point Video, they failed to meet sales targets.After the footage made its rounds online, Chinese netizens expressed their outrage, however, the agency involved in the matter claimed that it was an old video and that such practices were no longer condoned.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 04:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/15/4008960/4008960_2D563B1B59C5487187F3FE5D70566BE4_200615_4008960_Chinese_Company__Team_Building___Motivating_or_A_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009499</guid>
      <title>Ancient Crocodiles May Have Walked on Two Feet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JINJU, SOUTH KOREA  Experts have found evidence which indicates that ancient crocodiles could have been bipedal.Experts from South Korea's Chinju National University of Education discovered many fossilized animal tracks in 2019 that they now believe could belong to an ancient crocodile that walked on two feet. Their research was published in the journal Scientific Reports.The team found the fossilized footprints at a site located west of Sacheon City in South Korea's South Gyeongsang Province. The team has named the animal Batrachopus grandis.The footprints measure up to 24 centimeters in length and the heel print, digits and impressions of the pads look very similar to those of crocodile track marks, the BBC reports, citing Professor Martin Lockley from the University of Colorado at Denver, a co-author of the study.The Batrachopus grandis legs were about the same height as a human adults' legs. The fact that there are no tracks of the ancient crocodiles' tails dragging behind them and the closeness of the footprints suggests this animal could have been bipedal.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 09:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/16/4009499/4009499_01FC3867EA1043BA8AD04B4A006D7517_200616_4009499_Ancient_Crocodiles_May_Have_Walked_on_Two_Feet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Batrachopus grandis, ancient crocodile, Chinju National University of Education, fossils, fossilized tracks, fossilized footprints, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009355</guid>
      <title>Man Goes to Hospital With Itchy Nose, Doctor Pulls Out Leech!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGXI, CHINA  A man from rural Guangxi, China recently visited his nearby hospital complaining of some serious discomfort way up in his nose. According to the report from Pear Video on the 14th of June, the unnamed man explained to the doctor that he frequently needed to itch his nose and that the sensation was coupled with bleeding and the feeling that something was crawling around in his nose. After a prompt examination, the doctor discovered that the man from the rural part of town was right, there was a live leech poking around in his nose.So, how did it get up there?It turns out that the man had drunk water from a spring in the forest. The doctor warned him not to do it again.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 04:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/16/4009355/4009355_E7A6D847A21440AB9E6192D90ABC3ED5_200616_4009355_Man_Goes_to_Hospital_With_Itchy_Nose__Doctor_Pul_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009307</guid>
      <title>Scientists Have Found Anomalous Structures Around Earth's Core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLLEGE PARK, MARYLAND  Geophysicists from the University of Maryland analyzed seismic waves around the world and found large unusual structures near the Earth's core. The study was published on June 12 in the journal Science.The team of researchers analyzed 7,000 seismograms from earthquakes of 6.5 magnitude or greater that occurred from 1990 to 2018 using Sequencer, a machine learning algorithm.They specifically searched for echoes of seismic waves known as shear waves, or S waves, beneath the Pacific Ocean Basin.Their results uncovered an anomalous structure under the volcanic Marquesas Islands in the South Pacific. The results also showed that a previously known structure beneath the Hawaiian Islands is much larger than had been thought.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 02:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/16/4009307/4009307_0C167240861641E4AD0CAAD1AC9CFF13_200616_4009307_Scientists_Have_Found_Anomalous_Structures_Aroun_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Earth's core, seismometers, earthquakes, sequencer, structures underground, geophysics, university of maryland, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009923</guid>
      <title>North Korea Blows Up Inter-Korea Joint Liaison Office</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  North Korea blew up the joint liaison office in the border city of Kaesong used for bettering ties with South Korea after days of rising tensions on June 16.South Korea's Ministry of Unification has confirmed the story with a statement registering its "deep regret" and protest over the North's action.According to the BBC, the joint liaison office was established in 2018 to improve communications, though industrial cooperation in Kaesong was already halted by 2016. The Guardian reports South Korea evacuated the liaison staff in January due to the coronavirus pandemic.North Korea issued a statement saying, "We have exploded the eye-sore north-south joint liaison office," adding that "there are [sic] nothing to be implemented and no future for the north-south relations."North Korea leader Kim Jung-un's sister Kim Yo-jong has been making threats to demolish the liaison office.The BBC reports that during Kim Jung-un's absence in April, several observers speculated that Kim Yo-jong could become his successor.North Korea's cited reason for destroying the site was that defectors have ballooned propaganda leaflets over from the South.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 09:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/17/4009923/4009923_B6A906F89886499DB289F5D6BB984EFA_200617_4009923_North_Korea_Blows_Up_Inter_Korea_Joint_Liaison_O_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[inter-korea liaison office, north-south liaison office, joint north-south liaison office, joint liaison office, Kaesong, Kim Jong-un, Kim Yo-jong, North Korea, Democratic People's Republic of Korea, Republic of Korea, North Korea, South Korea, defense, security, politics, news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009855</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus Could Infect the Brain: Scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE  A new study from Johns Hopkins University suggests the coronavirus may infect the brain and replicate in brain cells.The Financial Times reports the journal Altex is in the process of reviewing this paper.Scientists used tiny balls of cultured brain tissue called mini-brains to simulate the virus's effect on human brain tissue.The mini-brains called Brainsphere are utilized for pharmaceutical testing and virus research.Microscopy of the mini-brains shows SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, can infect neurons and multiply tenfold in three days.Since mini-brains do not have the blood-brain barrier found in real brains, it is not known if the virus is able to penetrate into the brain on its own.However, severe inflammation  which is observed in COVID patients  can break down the barrier.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 08:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/17/4009855/4009855_97412E9908D84A729835F9033B9D5AF9_200617_4009855_Coronavirus_Could_Infect_the_Brain__Scientists_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[COVID-19, COVID, coronavirus, brain, brain cells, infect human brain, infect human brains, infect brain, neurons, blood-brain barrier, mini-brains, mini brains, mini brains, mini brain, brainsphere, brainspheres, Johns Hopkins University, U.S., health, science, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009780</guid>
      <title>Highly Magnetized Star Detected as Source of Fast Radio Bursts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA  The first fast radio burst to be discovered in the Milky Way has been traced back to a magnetar known as SGR 1935+2154 located 32,616 light-years away from Earth, astronomers researching the phenomena told Nature magazine.The burst was detected by satellites including NASA's Neil Gehrels Swift Observatory, and radio telescopes operated by the Canadian Hydrogen Intensity Mapping Experiment, or CHIME, and by the Survey for Transient Astronomical Radio Emission 2, or STARE2, in the U.S.Fast radio bursts are brief but cataclysmic high-energy blasts that flare for just milliseconds but release as much energy as our Sun generates in 80 years, according to previous findings published in Nature.A magnetar is described in the Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics as a kind of highly magnetized neutron star, the compressed core of a star that exploded in a supernova and collapsed in on itself.Citing University of Toronto astronomer and CHIME member Paul Scholz, Nature magazine explains that because they spin so quickly, magnetars build up huge reservoirs of energy that could produce powerful cosmic blasts.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 05:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/17/4009780/4009780_B8DEE2DA60A147C3B5D6264E14CAE9BB_200617_4009780_Highly_Magnetized_Star_Detected_as_Source_of_Fas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[fast radio burst, astronomy, space, magnetar, neutron star, magnetic field, star, supernova, black hole, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009746</guid>
      <title>Chinese Woman Smashes Plane Window 30,000 ft in the Air!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HENAN, CHINA  A woman has been arrested after smashing a plane window in a drunken rage when the plan was 30,000 ft in the air.According to the report from WeVideo on the 12th of June, 29-year-old Li had necked two 250ml bottles of baijiu before boarding her flight from Xining to Yangcheng on the 25th of May. Police said that Li has been drinking because she had just been dumped by her boyfriend. Onboard the flight she went berserk, lost control of her emotions, and started thumping one of the windows on the plane; as she lashed out the cabin crew tried to calm the woman. A photo was shared by police that shows that Li was actually able to crack the window.The plane was then forced to make an emergency landing roughly half-way through its journey at an airport in Henan province where officers were waiting to cuff Li. Just how drunk was she? Per the report, her blood alcohol level was at 100 ml. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/17/4009746/4009746_9AE15C8D36F84582A5E3F0ACFCBB24F0_200617_4009746_Chinese_Woman_Smashes_Plan_Window_30_000_ft_in_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010418</guid>
      <title>Over 600 New Covid-19 Cases Detected in Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERLIN  More than 600 people at a slaughterhouse located in Rheda-Wiedenbruck, Germany, have tested positive for coronavirus, according to Deutsche Welle. The slaughterhouse is run by the Tonnies Group, the leading meat processing company in Germany.Local authorities have called for the plant to shut down and for the suspension of school and preschool activities in the area until June 29. Roughly 7,000 people in the region have been asked to quarantine to prevent the spread of the virus.The conditions inside slaughterhouse worker dormitories may have exacerbated the spread of the virus. The Guardian quotes a migrant worker as saying that up to five people would live in the same room and that a dorm they lived in had mice and cockroaches.A large percentage of employees at meat processing facilities in Germany are not German. In fact, Deutsche Welle reports that according to trade unions, up to 80 percent of those employed in these factories are migrant workers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 11:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010418/4010418_1A7E51224EC0482A871743C2E6E01026_200618_4010418_Over_600_New_Covid_19_Cases_Detected_in_Germany_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[germany, coronavirus in germany, coronavirus, covid-19, coronavirus germany, SARS-CoV-2, COVID-19, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, Wuhan virus, Wuhan pneumonia, pneumonia, COVID-19 virus, COVID-19 pandemic, slaughterhouse, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010393</guid>
      <title>North Korea Shoos Away Envoys, Vows Sending Troops to DMZ</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG  North Korea said on June 17 that it will deploy troops to the tourist resort of Mount Kumgang and the city of Kaesong on the border.According to North Korea's state-run KCNA, South Korean President Moon Jae-in made overtures to send a special envoy to talk with Pyongyang.KCNA says North Korean leader Kim Jong-un's sister Kim Yo Jong has rejected the "tactless and sinister proposal."In a separate statement, the North Korean People's Army states that it will reinstate police posts that had been formerly withdrawn from the border, and troops will reinforce likely landing areas for propaganda balloons from defectors in the South.Previously, North Korea has cited the anti-regime pamphlets as a pretext for blowing up the liaison office.According to the KCNA, North Korea will resume sending its own propaganda to South Korea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 10:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010393/4010393_98A55F86DF1F4A59844787805D2B952D_200618_4010393_North_Korea_Shoos_Away_Envoys__Vows_Sending_Troo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[North Korea, South Korea, troops, DMZ, demilitarized zone, diplomatic crisis, joint liaison office, inter-Korean joint liaison office, north-south joint liaison office, Kaesong, Mount Kumgang,  Kim Jong-un, Kim Yo-Jong, Moon Jae-in, politics, news, defense]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010248</guid>
      <title>'Rough Sex Gone Wrong' Defense to be Outlawed in the U.K.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  In a move that will make the sexually aggressive think twice, the U.K is set to ban the so-called, 'rough sex gone wrong' defense. Never heard of it? Well, according to the BBC, as it stands, if someone kills another person during sexual activity they could face the lesser charge to murder, manslaughter. To murder someone, there needs to be the intent to kill or to cause them grievous bodily harm.However, campaigners of 'We Can't Consent To This' have been pushing for the defense of 'rough sex gone wrong' to be outlawed and that they want an expectation that murder charges are brought against those suspected of killing a person during sexual activities.How common is it? Well, the campaign group collated 60 examples of women who were killed during so-called 'sex games gone wrong' in the U.K., since 1972.Interestingly, the group claims that 45% of these 'rough sex gone wrong' cases actually ended in a 'lesser charge of manslaughter, a lighter sentence or,' get this… 'the death not being investigated as a crime at all.'In a move to outlaw the excuse used by lawyers, a justice minister has told MPs that it was 'unconscionable' that the defense can be used in court to justify or excuse the death of a woman 'simply because she consented.'Speaking to MPs at the Commons' Public Bill Committee, MP Jess Phillips said, 'The law should be clear to all - you cannot consent to serious injury or death, but the case law is not up to the task.'She said when a woman is dead 'she can't speak for herself' but any man charged with killing a woman or a current or former partner could 'simply say she wanted it.'The Domestic Abuse Bill for England and Wales is due to become law later this year.The 'We Can't Consent to This' campaign group said what had happened in Parliament 'was genuinely a big step forward', and that, 'We should know within weeks what their proposals are and if they've gone far enough.'Chiming in, British PM Boris Johnson has said, 'We are committed to ensuring that the law is made clear and that defense is inexcusable.'TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 06:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010248/4010248_D1735D928BBF41E7A02962C4CD60A232_200618_4010248__Rough_Sex_Gone_Wrong__Defense_to_be_Outlawed_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010186</guid>
      <title>Devastating Mudslide Destroys Village in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DANBA, SICHUAN, CHINA  On the morning of June 17, a truly devastating mudslide destroyed almost every building in one village. The clip, which was posted to Miaopai was filmed by a resident of rural Danba county from the safety of the high ground, the gargantuan rush of water and mud devastate the landscape, utterly destroying what was once a village. The local man in the video can be heard saying that he can only see 4-5 buildings that have survived. Incredibly, only two people are missing from what could have been catastrophic. Per the report, the mudslide saw more than 5,500 households and 20,000 people evacuated; 14 of which were rescued after the disaster hit. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 03:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010186/4010186_908559E4308040D5A29B921E997362E0_200618_4010186_Devastating_Mudslide_Destroys_Village_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010171</guid>
      <title>Chinese Woman Caught Spitting on Elevator Buttons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SIPING, JILIN, CHINA  A woman has been caught on CCTV spitting a big green onto the buttons in an elevator.The incident was posted on Weibo and took place on the 13th of June in a residential building in the city of Siping. In the clip, we see the woman step into the elevator, take off her hat and mask, and then, in a counter-epidemic-prevention move, spit over the buttons. As she goes to leave the elevator, she puts her mask back on.The thick spit was noticed by residents of the building and was quickly brought to the attention of security staff who watched the security tape to find out who the rank culprit was.The worst part about this is that it turned out the woman didn't even live in the building, she was just a visitor. The woman was detained by police for just a mere seven days, however, netizens made their voice heard and are calling for her to receive a harsher punishment.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 02:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010171/4010171_D366AB13B9F748C6BB0DFA4E9BDCC248_200618_4010171_Chinese_Woman_Caught_Spitting_on_Elevator_Button_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010153</guid>
      <title>China-India Himalayan Border Clash Turns Deadly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI  Indian and Chinese border defense troops had a deadly encounter last Monday that left at least 20 Indian soldiers, including a colonel, dead, according to the Times of India.The New York Times reports a dozen Indian soldiers remain missing. They are thought to have been captured by Chinese forces.The clash occurred in the Galwan Valley region of eastern Ladakh. Details of the encounter are unclear. However, the Guardian reports that the altercation seems to have happened when Indian border troops unexpectedly met Chinese troops while patrolling.China and India have had decades-long disputes over the Line of Actual Control which separates the two countries. The two countries fought a war over the region in 1962 and have since continued to have frequent conflicts in the area.And what does China have to say about this deadly incident? Well, according to China's Global Times, it was the Indian troops who provoked the attack by crossing the Line of Actual Control.The jingoistic state-run outlet also claims that the clash was "intentionally staged" as an effort to take over Chinese territory and deflect attention from India's management of the COVID-19 epidemic.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010153/4010153_4312AD552E654C039F1965BC02D6CB31_200618_4010153_China_India_Himalayan_Border_Clash_Turns_Deadly_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[China, india, china and india, china india border, china india border conflict, himalayan border, sino-indian war, india china border, india china border, himalayan border conflict      TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010911</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus Has Contaminated Beijing's Major Food Market</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China has published the preliminary report on the Xinfadi market, a major food distributor that is linked to Beijing's latest surge in coronavirus cases, according to Reuters.Citing the initial findings, Reuters reports the market's seafood and meat stalls were heavily contaminated by the virus. The Chinese report speculates that low temperatures and high humidity helped the virus to thrive at the market.Citing the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention, Reuters reports that most Xinfadi employees who became sick worked in the seafood section, followed by the beef and mutton section.Patients linked to the seafood section were the first to show symptoms.Inspectors found the virus on chopping boards used for imported salmon. Reuters reports that Chinese authorities have warned the public against eating uncooked salmon and halted imports of the fish from European suppliers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 12:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/19/4010911/4010911_BEC005AB01DC465A9ECD2116CBBC69C1_200619_4010911_Coronavirus_Has_Contaminated_Beijing_s_Major_Foo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[COVID-19, COVID, SARS-CoV-2, coronavirus, Xinfadi, Xin Fa Di, food market, Xinfadi market supermarket, second wave coronavirus outbreak, second wave, Beijing, China, health]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010749</guid>
      <title>China Violates Taiwan's Airspace for the Fourth Time in Nine Days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Taiwan's air force on Wednesday warned off Chinese warplanes that approached the country, the defense ministry said, reporting the fourth such intrusion in just nine days.The Chinese J-10, a fighter jet, and Y-8, a turboprop surveillance aircraft, entered Taiwan's air defence identification zone to the southwest of the country on Wednesday.Taiwanese fighter planes issued a verbal warning to the Chinese aircraft to leave and the Chinese planes "immediately left" the air defence identification zone, the ministry said.The latest incursion comes after a J-10 fighter entered Taiwan's air defence identification zone from the southwest on Tuesday.On Friday, a Chinese Y-8 was issued a verbal warning by Taiwan's air force to leave its air space in the same area.The Y-8 flight came only a few hours after Taiwan announced it had conducted missile tests at two locations off its eastern coast.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 07:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/19/4010749/4010749_2FA13FB1462F46BEB1A566C248A8EE1F_200619_4010749_China_Violates_Taiwan_s_Airspace_for_the_Fourth__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Taiwan, China, U.S., defense, F-16, J-10, J-11, Y-8, fighter jet, warplane, surveillance plane, air identification zone, Taiwan Strait, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010734</guid>
      <title>WARNING: Chinese 'Street Patrol' Beat Dog to Death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YONGZHOU, HUNAN, CHINA  A video posted to Chinese social media on June 17, shows yet again, a dog being beaten to death on the street by Chengguan officers. These Chengguan, are essentially street security in place of police tasked with enforcing various routine regulations and they're known for their heavy-handed approach to usually minor misdemeanors.In this video, that we cannot show, the dog, according to the report was the pet of a woman who lives in a residential community in the Hunan city of Yongzhou, the woman had the papers to back up her ownership claim, however, unfortunately for this pup, these so-called 'urban management officers' caught the dog running about without a leash so, they whacked it to death with metal poles and chucked its body in the back of a truck.According to the report, there is a sign in the neighborhood that actually warns if a dog is not tied up it will be killed, at the very least, however, you'd expect them to do it humanely, not execute the animal in the street by being bludgeoned to death. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 07:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/19/4010734/4010734_2FBDB74F8AD34DE584BC8B9BF1DF2967_200619_4010734_WARNING__Chinese__Street_Patrol__Beat_Dog_to_Dea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010673</guid>
      <title>The Moment 'Bob the Builder' Gives a Lift in his Bulldozer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIANYANG, HUBEI, CHINA  A courteous bulldozer operator was filmed coming to the rescue of those in dire need of getting to work.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 05:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/19/4010673/4010673_2027B958326447749DBC18D8C933CA3B_200619_4010673_The_Moment__Bob_the_Builder__Gives_a_Lift_in_his_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011229</guid>
      <title>Tourists could be sent to space using a giant balloon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, FLORIDA  A new company called Space Perspective wants to send tourists and research payloads up into the stratosphere in a pressurized capsule elevated by a large balloon, according to Space.com.The capsule is called the Spaceship Neptune and it can hold up to 9 people, including the pilot. The capsule has large windows from which passengers will be able to observe Earth's curvature. It will also contain a bathroom and a bar.It will take the Spaceship Neptune roughly two hours to reach its maximum altitude of 30,000 meters or about 100,000 feet after taking off from the old Shuttle Landing Facility at NASA's Kennedy Space Center on Florida's Space Coast. The capsule will be suspended by a large hydrogen-filled balloon.Passengers will spend two hours suspended in the stratosphere. Their descent back into Earth will take another two hours. The passengers would then be picked up by a recovery boat waiting for them at sea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 14:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/20/4011229/4011229_58ED76DB9D3845ADB544CB4A3C4A9259_200620_4011229_Tourists_could_be_sent_to_space_using_a_giant_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Space perspective, space tourism, space travel, Spaceship Neptune, Jane Poynter, Taber MacCallum, Commercial Spaceflight, hydrogen balloon, space exploration, space flight, flight to space, TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011066</guid>
      <title>Fossilised Egg Could be Linked to Ancient Marine Reptile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEYMOUR ISLAND, ANTARCTICA  Nine years ago, scientists discovered a 68-million-year-old fossilised egg on Seymour Island in Antarctica. New research published in the journal Nature suggests the egg may have belonged to an ancient marine reptile called a mosasaur.The fossilised egg has a soft shell and measures 29 centimeters in length and 20 centimeters in width. It is the second-largest egg recorded to date. That is roughly five times the size of a medium-sized chicken egg.Mosasaurs were marine reptiles that lived during the dinosaur era. Evidence suggests that mosasaurus gave birth to live young. However, the egg could have hatched right after being laid. This mode of reproduction is called ovoviviparity.Mosasaurs belong to an order of reptiles called squamates or scaled reptiles whose ancestors split from the ancestors of dinosaurs, birds and crocodiles roughly 240 million years ago. Lizards and snakes also belong to this group.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/20/4011066/4011066_5C06B8A008CF47E3BE72650E0D5BDD0B_200620_4011066_Fossilised_Egg_Could_be_Linked_to_Ancient_Marine_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Seymour Island, fossilised egg, marine reptile, extinct sea lizard, sea lizard, mosasaur,   TomoNews satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011775</guid>
      <title>Why you should shut the toilet lid to prevent the spread of COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANGZHOU, CHINA  Researchers from China's Yangzhou University have used computer simulations to show that water flushed in an uncovered toilet can eject infected aerosol droplets up to three feet, or one meter, in the air, according to a study published on June 16 in the journal Physics of Fluids. Up to 60 percent of the particles reach above the toilet seat and these droplets can remain airborne for up to a minute, the researchers found.The virus could then infect others who inhale the aerosols or come into contact with infected surfaces, such as by touching door handles or toilet seats where the droplets have landed.In the journal the researchers noted that more attention needs to be paid to toilets as potential sources of infection and even toilet design, writing, "According to the characteristics of fecal-oral transmission, there will be a large amount of viruses within a toilet when a confirmed case uses it. Thus, toilets should be regarded as one of the infection sources."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 09:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/22/4011775/4011775_B8B0A883C6B647F6A7E5A970D5E2632B_200622_4011775_Why_you_should_shut_the_toilet_lid_to_prevent_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[SARS-CoV-2, COVID-19, coronavirus, novel coronavirus, oral-fecal transmission, toilet, transmission, Yangzhou University, China, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011734</guid>
      <title>CERN Approves Plan for 
Gigantic New Particle Collider</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA  The CERN Council in Geneva, Switzerland on June 19 approved the construction of a new 100-kilometer circular supercollider called the Future Circular Collider.This new collider is 73 kilometers larger than the Large Hadron Collider. The construction is expected to begin in 2038 and cost at least €21 billion.According to Nature, the new collider will be developed in two stages. In the first stage, CERN will create an electron-positron collider with the goal of creating and studying Higgs boson particles.In the second stage, the collider will be turned into a proton-proton smasher with capabilities of reaching collision energies of 100 teraelectronvolts. Currently, the Large Hadron Collider can reach 16 teraelectronvolts. This collider would be used to look for and study new particles.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 08:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/22/4011734/4011734_30229520614C46909EAD1C38D8364EAA_200622_4011734_CERN_Approves_Plan_for__Gigantic_New_Particle_Co_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  cern, switzerland, geneva, large hadron collider, higgs boson, particle physics, particle colliders, particle accelerators, future circular collider, particle collider, CERN wants to build the biggest particle collider ever, CERN wants to build, biggest particle collider, CERN plans to build particle collider, CERN particle collider, CERN builds particle collider, CERN conceptual proposal, CERN future circular collider, CERN wants to build new collider]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011673</guid>
      <title>George Floyd Guilty Cop Filmed Shopping for Oreos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PLYMOUTH, MINNESOTA  An angry shopper confronted an officer involved in the killing of George Floyd as he shopped at a grocery store.The video which was posted to Twitter on the 21st of June captures fired Minneapolis police officer, J. Alexander Kueng being confronted by an angry female shopper at a Cub Foods in Plymouth after he was released on bail from Hennepin County jail on a $750,000 bail.26-year-old Kueng was arrested and charged with aiding and abetting murder and aiding and abetting manslaughter for not intervening when officer Derek Chauvin kneeled on Floyd's neck, leading to his death. The disgruntled shopper filming asks how he afforded his $750,000, but he does not respond.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 05:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/22/4011673/4011673_F05A291701F246838074AC8DEEC5B8DE_200622_4011673_George_Floyd_Guilty_Cop_Filmed_Shopping_for_Oreo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011633</guid>
      <title>4-year-old Boy Falls From 29th Floor and Survives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHANGZHOU, JIANGSU, CHINA  After being irresponsibly left home alone, a four-year-old boy is extremely lucky to be alive after falling from the 29th floor of a residential high-rise in China.  Yang Yang from Changzhou city Jiangsu province was left in the care of his grandmother on the 8th of June by his migrant worker parents. According to the report posted to Miaopai on the 19th, Yang Yang's grandmother, at some point during the day, decided to irresponsibly 'run errands' for 15 minutes leaving the boy home alone inside the 29th-floor apartment watching television.Whilst grandmother diddled about, Yang Yang climbed onto the kitchen cabinet and fell out of a carelessly left open window. He plummeted some 90 meters down. Incredibly, the boy's fall was broken as he hit trees below before landing in a flower bed.Finally, after running those crucial errands, his grandmother returned, finding her grandson lying in the dirt; he was gravely injured but miraculously alive.Yang Yang was in critical condition for more than a week, suffering from respiratory failure, broken ribs, and a concussion, however, fortunately, he is now awake and it seems out of life-threatening danger. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 03:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/22/4011633/4011633_1BFD9749C7EB4B449CAEBD8BFEC4495C_200622_4011633_4_year_old_Boy_Falls_From_29th_Floor_and_Survive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012046</guid>
      <title>Astronomers Discover Youngest Known Kagnetar</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN BASILIO, ITALY  Astronomers at NASA and the ESA have discovered a neutron star that is the youngest known magnetar ever recorded.Swift J1818.0−1607 was born in a supernova that would have been visible from Earth 240 years ago.A magnetar is a kind of highly magnetized neutron star, the most powerful magnetic objects in the universe. Only 30 magnetars in the Milky Way have been found.The star is located 16,000 light-years away from Earth in the constellation Sagittarius and  is 16,240 years old.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 04:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/23/4012046/4012046_5FBADA43477C4F57A910EECC6AF10653_200623_4012046_Astronomers_Discover_Youngest_Known_Kagnetar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[fast radio burst, astronomy, space, magnetar, neutron star, magnetic field, star, supernova, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012443</guid>
      <title>New Study Suggests Pluto Started Out With a Liquid Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA CRUZ, CALIFORNIA  New research published in the journal Nature Geoscience suggests Pluto started out with a liquid ocean that has been slowly freezing over time.The findings are based on an analysis of pictures of Pluto's surface taken by NASA's New Horizons mission. These show extensive ridges and troughs consistent with the planet expanding as its ocean froze.Pluto is thought to possess a liquid ocean beneath a thin icy surface and a mantle of watery ice, according to the paper, which was published on June 22.The study suggests the heat energy that allowed for a liquid ocean came from rocks colliding with and raining down on Pluto as the planet formed. Heat may also have been generated by radioactive elements in the rocks.The new research suggests Pluto may be more capable of supporting alien life than we had previously thought.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 07:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/24/4012443/4012443_E2938AA40A8D402B927B977D53E8B19D_200624_4012443_New_Study_Suggests_Pluto_Started_Out_With_a_Liqu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Pluto, Kuiper Belt, liquid ocean, ice, astronomy, NASA, New Horizons, TomoNews]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012804</guid>
      <title>Buried Alive: Chinese Authorities Deal With Wildlife Surplus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIANING, HUBEI, CHINA  Some rural authorities in China have been tasked with the 'removal' of animals now banned under new Chinese wildlife trade regulations. How they go about this, is horrifying. However, with the Wuhanvirus bringing the world almost to its knees and with pressure from the international community, Chinese authorities pressed pause on the trade of wild animals; bamboo rats, porcupines, and snakes didn't make the list of livestock.The video you just saw is how local authorities are dealing with these now banned animals. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 06:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/25/4012804/4012804_68E0B197638447918F88D12D1C143FCF_200625_4012804_Buried_Alive__Chinese_Authorities_Deal_With_Wild_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012767</guid>
      <title>Chinese Floods Turn Bridge Into Dystopian 'Waterfall'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TONGREN, GUIZHOU, CHINA  Watch the moment floodwaters cascaded off the side of a bridge, creating a spectacular 'waterfall'.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 03:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/25/4012767/4012767_3B74A308C4E74397850A535A735D6A43_200625_4012767_Chinese_Floods_Turn_Bridge_Into_Dystopian__Water_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012736</guid>
      <title>Chinese Man Loses an Eel Inside His Bum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, GUANGDONG, CHINA  A Chinese man from Dongguan, Guangdong province was suffering from long time constipation and decided that he'd try his hand at something different, so he forced a live eel into his bum to try and relieve his suffering.According to the report via Miaopai on the 21st of June, the man who is in his fifties had heard somewhere that putting an eel into your anus could help with bowel movements; so what did he do? Research first? Get a second opinion? No. He went to the market, bought an eel, and started stuffing. Expectedly, the 'medicine' had some severe consequences, the 40cm long eel was stuck and causing havoc.Incredibly, this guy hung about for five days with a live eel inside his body before he decided it was time to go to the hospital, however, by that point the eel had done some serious damage. His colon was ruptured and he had severe contamination to his digestive tract and septic shock. Thankfully, fast-acting doctors performed surgery and extracted the eel. The doctors said that if the man had waited any longer he would have died. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 01:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/25/4012736/4012736_5380885378524E799A9168008ED9263B_200625_4012736_Chinese_Man_Loses_an_Eel_Inside_His_Bum_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012733</guid>
      <title>Chinese Woman Flops Through Bus Window After Being Rejected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARBIN, HEILONGJIANG, CHINA  Watch the moment a woman is refused entry onto a bus because she wouldn't show her health QR code, so she climbed through the window and flopped face-first onto the bus seat. TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2020 01:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/25/4012733/4012733_805F6767595A474C8C0AB00D5E92E894_200625_4012733_Chinese_Woman_Flops_Through_Bus_Window_After_Bei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4014038</guid>
      <title>'Adult Experience Centers' Offer Room With Shareable Sex Dolls</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  In an undercover report by Chinese outlet, The Paper so-called 'adult experience centers' are offering the service of sex with sharable sex dolls.TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_StoriesYou Idiot! - People doing stupid thingshttp://bit.ly/You-IdiotRecent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNewshttp://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNewsUltimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every dayhttp://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...Thanks for watching TomoNews!Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUSFollow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsusSubscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNewsWatch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.comCheck out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCjCheck out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1fGet top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 09:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/29/4014038/4014038_5C7B908A8DB242BE8C90595CC8C29234_200629_4014038__Adult_Experience_Centers__Offer_Room_With_Share_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, satire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4014021</guid>
      <title>Did a Volcano in Alaska Bring Down the Roman Republic?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RENO, NEVADA  According to new research, a powerful volcanic eruption in modern-day Alaska around 44 B.C. may have contributed to the Roman Republic's downfall on the other side of the globe.This study was published in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.The eruption left a 10 km wide crater in Mount Okmok that survives to this day, the research team led by Joe McConnell of Desert Research Institute said in a news release.The event likely caused destabilizing environmental changes that paved the way for the imperial system after Julius Caesar was killed.According to the team, the estimated time of the volcano's eruption, which would have led to climate-altering levels of fallout, coincided with a period of extreme cold, crop failures and famines in the written records.Scientists used various materials to date the eruption including tree ring-based climate records from Scandinavia and volcanic remains called tephra from the Arctic ice.The climate records and tephra both supported the hypothesis of an eruption in Alaska.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 08:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/29/4014021/4014021_368EDE00E7184C21ADA5E6802B424905_200629_4014021_Did_a_Volcano_in_Alaska_Bring_Down_the_Roman_Rep_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Fall of the roman republic, rise of the roman empire, ancient rome, ptolemaic egypt, ptolemaic kingdom, ancient egypt, volcano eruption, volcano in Alaska, mount okmok, umnak island, tephra, arctic circle, arctic ice, ice cores, ice core, climate change, extreme cold, crop failure, famine, history, archeology, hydrology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
