<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 19:31:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3788970</guid>
      <title>China unveils ambitious Greater Bay Area plan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China's State Council has revealed details of a plan to promote economic cooperation among several major cities in the Pearl River Delta.The Greater Bay Area plan will integrate and transform Hong Kong, Macau, and nine other cities in China's Guangdong province into 'a global center of technology, innovation, and economic vibrancy.According to HSBC research, the region is currently home to 70 million people, and produces 37% of the country's exports and 12% of its GDP. With closer integration of the cities, China hopes this output will increase.The South China Morning Post reports that the plan is for cities to serve as key hubs for different sectors. Hong Kong will be the international finance, transport, and trade center, while Macau will serve as a hub for tourism and platform for trade with Portuguese-speaking countries.Other core cities include Guangzhou as the provincial capital and administrative hub, Shenzhen as the center for technology and innovation, and Dongguan as a high-tech manufacturing hub.Infrastructure is being developed to increase connectivity between cities. This includes the Hong Kong-Zhuhai-Macau bridge, which is the world's longest sea crossing bridge, and the high speed rail link from Hong Kong to the Mainland.According to the BBC, the Greater Bay Area is being set up to rival Silicon Valley, and major metropolitan areas like Tokyo, San Francisco, and New York. But while the Greater Bay Area's GDP already surpasses that of San Francisco, it lags behind New York and Tokyo.The region could face challenges in economic integration, since Hong Kong and Macau have their own monetary, legal, and political systems separate from the Mainland. Talent distribution across the 11 cities may also be an issue, since most will be drawn to the bigger cities like Hong Kong and Guangzhou.The Hong Kong Free Press reports that the plan has been met with skepticism by the island's pro-democracy lawmakers, who allege that the development of Mainland cities will come at the expense of Hong Kong.A Bloomberg opinion piece notes that 'Hong Kong seems to be the likely loser', adding that the plan is vague on how integration will affect Hong Kong and Macau's special status.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 11:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/02/28/3788970/3788970_772A6CC463A448ADB21474EE73242E1E_190228_3788970_China_unveils_ambitious_Greater_Bay_Area_plan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AD6/9BD/AD69BD15EB62B21242A479814E788FD8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Greater Bay Area, China Greater Bay, China economic hub, Greater Bay, South China, economic hub, China silicon valley, China, Hong Kong, Macau, Guangdong, Guangzhou, Shenzhen, Pearl River Delta]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788875</guid>
      <title>India, Pakistan claim to down each other's jets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI/ISLAMABAD  India and Pakistan have both said they shot down each other's fighter jets on Wednesday. Reuters reports both countries have ordered airstrikes over the last two days, the first time in history the two nations have done so, while ground forces have exchanged fire in more than a dozen locations. According to Reuters, tensions rose on Tuesday when India launched an airstrike in Pakistan territory on what it said was a militant training base. Reuters reports that a senior Indian government source said 300 militants were killed in the strike, while Pakistan says no one died. According to CNN, Pakistan says its air force shot down two Indian fighter jets in the disputed border region of Kashmir.India confirmed the loss of one plane and said it shot down a Pakistani jet as it responded to the incident. The Pakistan government's official Twitter account posted a video of the man it claimed was an Indian pilot who had been shot down. According to CNN, India and Pakistan both control parts of Kashmir, but each claims the region in full. Countries from around the world have called on both nuclear-armed nations to show restraint.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/02/28/3788875/3788875_B04938F137A940369F2F54D18E9DB7E1_190228_3788875_India__Pakistan_claim_to_down_each_other_s_jets_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B95/73B/B9573BE243DC35FC82A21CD9E74AE1F8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, India, Pakistan, Kashmir, India Pakistan airstrikes, India Pakistan tensions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788869</guid>
      <title>Chunky rat rescued from manhole in Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BENSHEIM, GERMANY  A not so slim rat will live to eat another day after getting rescued by a whole bunch load of rescue workers from getting stuck in a manhole cover.According to the BBC, animal rescuer Michael Sehr told local media, "she had a lot of winter flab and was stuck fast at her hip  there was no going forward or back."Sehr is from the local professional animal rescue in Rhein Neckar[b] and was first on the scene, but Fatatouille was too much for him to handle, so he called in the big guns. According to the local fire department, a whole mess of volunteer firefighters responded to the Sunday afternoon call. The manhole cover was lifted up and propped up on wedges while Sehr went in and got Slim Shady free. The team then did a quick photo shoot with Fats before releasing her back into the sewer. The animal group posted the shots and the whole rescue video up on their Facebook page.  As for the rat, she said she's going to cut out carbs and maybe look into Atkins or Paleo, possibly some juice cleanses. But for sureno gluten.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/02/28/3788869/3788869_57853FBCE61D4EFCBC0A5F1309293D9B_190228_3788869_Chunky_rat_rescued_from_manhole_in_Germany_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/264/875/2648752CE43204985E4429A63005617C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fat rat, rat, rat stuck in manhole, rat stuck in sewer, fat rat stuck]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788861</guid>
      <title>First CRISPR clinical trial 
approved outside of China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA / SWITZERLAND  The FDA has given approval to two pharmaceutical companies to begin a human gene-editing trial.A joint clinical trial led by CRISPR Therapeutics and Vertex will use gene editing to target sickle cell disease and beta-thalassemia. This will be the first confirmed CRISPR gene editing clinical trial to take place outside of China.According to a CRISPR Therapeutics news release, the gene-editing therapy, called CTX001, will be used to modify a patient's stem cells to increase hemoglobin levels in red blood cells.The first trial of gene-editing will be tested on two patients, with each being administered a single dose of CTX001. The patients will be monitored to see when the edited cells start producing mature blood cells, according to the news release.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/02/28/3788861/3788861_6A14A80CC3234846AF4D4E0D36751DB1_190228_3788861_First_CRISPR_clinical_trial__approved_outside_of_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7F1/58C/7F158CF69ADCEE562DA410EB22B302F0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, crispr babies, crispr china, crispr gene editing, 
CRISPR, CRISPR technology, gene-editing, DNA, editing DNA, CRISPR-cas9, altering human DNA, crispr human, CRISPR therapy, CRISPR gene editing clinical trial, gene editing, human DNA, CTX001, CRISPR therapeutics, vertex pharmaceuticals, sickle cell disease]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788860</guid>
      <title>Illegal gold mine in Indonesia collapses trapping 43</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SULAWESI, INDONESIA  At least 43 people are trapped inside an illegal gold mine in Sulawesi, Indonesia, according to local authorities.According to the Indonesian National Disaster Mitigation Agency, a landslide has trapped roughly 43 people inside an illegal gold mine in the Bolaang Mongondow region of North Sulawesi, Indonesia.Local authorities say the landslide happened on Tuesday at  9:00 p.m. local time causing the mine's supportive beams and planks to collapse.According to national disaster agency spokesman Sutopo Purwo Nugroho to Reuters, rescuers have found at least 3 dead bodies and rescued 14 miners.Conditions near the mine remain dangerous forcing local authorities and rescue teams to use simple tools such as spades and ropes to search for survivors.Small scale gold-mining is illegal but local authorities fail to report them and often overlook the practice. Accidents are a common occurrence in these mines due to the lack of regulation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/02/28/3788860/3788860_2804A1410114451F83E5A687555055D2_190228_3788860_Illegal_gold_mine_in_Indonesia_collapses_trappin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0A0/4D0/0A04D073F1F133410AD65EF4C7C5F8EA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Indonesia mine collapse, mine collapse, gold mine collapse, Indonesia gold, mine collapse, mine disaster, landslide Indonesia, landslide, landslide sulawesi, indonesia disaster]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788851</guid>
      <title>NYC's Central Park Tower to be world's tallest residential building</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  NYC real estate development firm Extell is giving the Big Apple a newly designed tower on West 57th Street, also known as Billionaire's Row.The Guardian reports that a 472 meter high skyscraper called Central Park Tower is being built right next to New York City's Central Park. The tower is designed by architecture firm Adrian Smith + Gordon Gill.The building features luxury apartments with glass windows where residents of the tower can get a "million dollar view" of NYC's Central Park, according to Archinect.An exclusive club called the Central Park Club will also be located within the skyscraper, according to a news release by the architectural firm.The club will include amenities such as an 18 meter swimming pool, a resident's billiard's lounge and a sauna and steam room.If everything goes according to plan, Central Park Tower will be the tallest residential building the world once it opens.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 09:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/02/28/3788851/3788851_6AB7AED6A94642E090ABCCDDC8E3EDDF_190228_3788851_NYC_s_Central_Park_Tower_to_be_world_s_tallest_r_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/702/F0A/702F0A9613F8AD407C7CE0525D0830AA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, architecture, central park tower, skyscrapers, US skyscrapers, architecture new york, central park tower construction, central park tower apartments, central park tower 2019, nyc architecture, central park tower nyc, skyscrapers new york, skyscrapers nyc, tallest residential building in the world]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3788735</guid>
      <title>NASA's newest telescope could find as many as 1,400 exoplanets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  NASA's Wide Field Infrared Survey Telescope, or WFIRST, is a future flagship mission planned to make new observations about our universe, according to a new study published in The Astrophysical Journal.The two main objectives of the spacecraft is to study dark energy and to locate exoplanets by using gravitational microlensing."The new telescope will have the ability to map out different galaxies 100 times faster than the Hubble Space Telescope, according to a news release by The Ohio State University.WFIRST will also continuously look at 100 million stars at the center of the Milky Way galaxy and analyze the light to determine if there are any exoplanets out there.According to the university's news release, the telescope could discover as many as 1,400 new planets outside our solar system.Ohio State University quotes Matthew Penny, lead author of the study, as saying, the telescope's infrared light allows the device to "see through dust that lies in the plane of the Milky Way in between us and the galactic center..''The WFIRST mission is currently in its planning stages and is planned to launch in the middle of 2020, following NASA's James Webb Space Telescope.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 06:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/02/28/3788735/3788735_CE37A0CE147A4208A779283148A8EC52_190228_3788735_NASA_s_newest_telescope_could_find_as_many_as_1__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5E7/E01/5E7E013D9F1086546CC7683CFDDEA57C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa, telescope, exoplanets, nasa telescope, WFIRST, wide field infrared survey telescope, cosmos, unknown planets, dark energy, exoplanet nasa, gravitational microlensing, microlensing exoplanets, microlensing event, milky way, astrophysics, dark energy nasa, WFIRST telescope, WFIRST telescope nasa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789621</guid>
      <title>Chinese teen turns mom's $119 into $2,500 in just 8 days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DEZHOU, CHINA  A teen in Dezhou in China's Shandong Province proved to be a savvy young entrepreneur after he turned a two-grand profit from a mini game arcade in just 8 short days.According to China Press, the 14-year-old got the idea after seeing similar stalls at the plaza during winter break, and thought it might be a good way to earn some dough.The kid borrowed 800 RMB, or about $119, from his mom, and used it to buy 400 glasses and about 300 ping pong balls.The game's pretty simple: each glass has money ranging from 5 to 100 yuan or about 75 cents to 14 bucks.To play, people fork over $10 for 10 ping pong balls. If they manage to land the ball in a glass, they get to keep whatever moolah is inside.Needless to say, the place was a hit. The teen earned 17,000 RMB, or $2,500, in 8 days, with enough extra to pay off two assistants. He could have earned more, too, except it was time to go back to school.And don't think he forgot his momma either. Son of the year says he's getting her a new phone.Best kid ever.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 14:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/01/3789621/3789621_7FA99704D36A43EA87F49A200486688C_190301_3789621_Chinese_teen_turns_mom_s__119_into__2_500_in_jus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/456/803/456803A9EAA7875E816C63668F04F819.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hustle, teen hustle, chinese teen makes money, teen business, money making, arcade, mini arcade, ping pong arcade, game stall, school break, how to hustle, how to make money]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789617</guid>
      <title>Failed Russian Venus probe could crash back to Earth this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  A failed 1970s Russian Venus probe which has been trapped in Earth orbit could crash back into the planet this year. According to Space.com, the Cosmos 482 Venus probe was launched on March 31, 1972, but due to a rocket malfunction, failed to escape Earth's orbit. A large portion of the failed spacecraft still remains in orbit today as space junk, but according to experts could fall back to Earth this year.According to Don Mitchell, who studies Soviet space history talking to Space.com, when the Cosmos 482 mission failed, a heavy frame of tanks and equipment were jettisoned from the probe and burned up in Earth's atmosphere. However, the Cosmos 482 Venus entry capsule is still adrift, orbiting the Earth every 112 minutes. The lander mass is 1,091 pounds (495 kilograms) and is equipped with significant thermal protection. According to satellite watcher Thomas Dorman talking to Space.com, the failed probe could fall back to Earth this year or mid next year. According to Space.com, previous estimates had the probe falling between 2023 and 2025.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 13:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/01/3789617/3789617_5D904209CD5B44C7B585467B1187277B_190301_3789617_Failed_Russian_Venus_probe_could_crash_back_to_E_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F93/251/F932511E4579C7F45BF9745D589BED2B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Russia Kosmos 482, Kosmos 482 probe, Venus Kosmos 482 probe, failed Russian Kosmos 482 probe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789600</guid>
      <title>How the Democratic party will stage its primary debates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Democratic National Committee has announced that it will limit the number of presidential debate participants to 20 candidates. The debates will be held in June and July on two separate consecutive nights depending on the number of candidates who qualify. The Associated Press reports that candidates will qualify for the debate if they earn at least 1 percent support in three separate national or early primary state polls conducted from January 1 to two weeks before the debate.They can also qualify if they receive campaign donations from 65,000 people across 20 different states, with a minimum of 200 unique donors per state. Candidates will be assigned randomly to the two stages regardless of their polling percentages.Efforts for a fairer and less poll-driven selection process for the nominees comes after voters in the 2016 elections felt the DNC was biased against the then outsider Senator Bernie Sanders. Hillary Clinton won the primary but went on to lose to Republican candidate Donald Trump.These claims stemmed mainly from allegations by former DNC chair Donna Brazile. In her book Hacks: The Inside Story of the Break-ins and Breakdowns that Put Donald Trump in the White House, Brazile accuses Clinton of rigging the primary elections in her favor by signing a joint fundraising agreement with the DNC and the Hillary Victory Fund.The exact dates and locations for the debates are yet to be confirmed. The DNC announced that NBC, MSNBC, and Telemundo will broadcast the June debates on back-to-back nights, and CNN will broadcast the July debate on back-to-back nights. There will be a total of 12 debates.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 13:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/01/3789600/3789600_AC3A493C24234949913ACDC5B299A833_190301_3789600_How_the_Democratic_party_will_stage_its_primary__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EAE/B2E/EAEB2E059E4B6FE5AA6BC85E3E182ACC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, How the Democratic party will stage its primary debates, Democratic party will primary debates, democratic party, primary debates, DNC, Democratic National Committee, Bernie Sanders, democratic debate, democratic primary]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789592</guid>
      <title>How the Democratic party will stage its primary debates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Democratic National Committee has announced that it will limit the number of presidential debate participants to 20 candidates. The debates will be held in June and July on two separate consecutive nights depending on the number of candidates who qualify. The Associated Press reports that candidates will qualify for the debate if they earn at least 1 percent support in three separate national or early primary state polls conducted from January 1 to two weeks before the debate.They can also qualify if they receive campaign donations from 65,000 people across 20 different states, with a minimum of 200 unique donors per state. Candidates will be assigned randomly to the two stages regardless of their polling percentages.Efforts for a fairer and less poll-driven selection process for the nominees comes after voters in the 2016 elections felt the DNC was biased against the then outsider Senator Bernie Sanders. Hillary Clinton won the primary but went on to lose to Republican candidate Donald Trump.These claims stemmed mainly from allegations by former DNC chair Donna Brazile. In her book Hacks: The Inside Story of the Break-ins and Breakdowns that Put Donald Trump in the White House, Brazile accuses Clinton of rigging the primary elections in her favor by signing a joint fundraising agreement with the DNC and the Hillary Victory Fund.The exact dates and locations for the debates are yet to be confirmed. The DNC announced that NBC, MSNBC, and Telemundo will broadcast the June debates on back-to-back nights, and CNN will broadcast the July debate on back-to-back nights. There will be a total of 12 debates.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 13:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/01/3789592/3789592_91C893AF4AD64410A8E70B8776E6CC49_190301_3789592_How_the_Democratic_party_will_stage_its_primary__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F2/F28/8F2F28D6E2FAD00EDB0BDF3E2F1DC4F6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, How the Democratic party will stage its primary debates, Democratic party will primary debates, democratic party, primary debates, DNC, Democratic National Committee, Bernie Sanders , democratic debate, democratic primary]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789586</guid>
      <title>Iceland allows more than 2,000 whales to be killed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REYKJAVIK, ICELAND   Iceland's government has announced it will be allowing whaling companies to kill more than 2,000 whales within the next five years, reports the Associated Press.According to the Animal Welfare Institute Iceland has had a bumpy relationship with the International Whaling Commission after it imposed a moratorium on commercial whaling back in 1986.Iceland withdrew from the IWC but came back in 2002 and continued to hunt whales under a special permit that allowed them to kill protected species under the guise that it was being done for scientific purposes.Now, the Icelandic government is allowing whale hunters to kill over 2,000 whales per year over the next five years.The Associated Press reports that the Icelandic government has announced that whaling will be permitted for at least another five years.Iceland's Fisheries and Agriculture Minister Kristjan Thor Juliusson announced that whalers would be allowed to harpoon 209 fin whales and 217 minke whales every year until 2023.The World Wildlife Fund lists fin whales as an endangered species.Iceland has four harpoon-equipped vessels. According to the Directorate of Fisheries, in 2018, they hunted 5 minke whales and 145 fin whales.According to the University of Iceland, whaling is profitable for the country, bringing in roughly $11.8 million per year between 2009 and 2017.However, the AP reports that politicians are increasingly opposing whaling practices as they believe it damages the country's image and affects tourism which is a growing industry in the country. Last December, Japan announced it would be withdrawing from the IWC in order to resume commercial whaling for the first time in 30 years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/01/3789586/3789586_8B95C85C3D554F569F25624D8074B2D6_190301_3789586_Iceland_allows_more_than_2_000_whales_to_be_kill_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B8C/CB6/B8CCB61B62CC3AFCC4A3B91E5D69586E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Iceland whaling, iceland to kill whales, hunting endangered fin whales, hunting endangered fin whales in Iceland, Iceland hunting endangered whales, endangered whales, killing whales, whale hunting, Iceland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789503</guid>
      <title>Man coughing blood for 2 months finds massive throat leech</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YIBIN, CHINA  A 60-year-old Chinese man in Yibin had an itchy throat and bloody cough for about two months, turns out it was only a leech. According to Red Star News, the man named Li had been trying to find a cure but kept getting misdiagnosed. He finally figured out why things have been sucking for him so much after he saw a specialist at a hospital in Xingwen County. Dr. Zhang Dadong performed an endoscopy on Li and found a big old 10 cm long leech chilling in his windpipe. The doctor called in some help and a team of them helped sedate and finally pull out the leech using some forceps. Looks like Li, who is from countryside town of Daba, ingested the eggs when he drank some untreated water. The larva then hatched in his throat and had a buffet blood feast for about two months, growing to quite an impressive size. The doctor advised people from the area to boil their water first before drinking it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 10:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/01/3789503/3789503_77AECC994AE8465491DEF15150E233C5_190301_3789503_Man_coughing_blood_for_2_months_finds_massive_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/70E/3A7/70E3A7A28C2BE39774513E188E6186D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, coughing, itchy throat, 2 month cough, China, Chinese man coughing, Chinese man itchy throat, leech]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3789193</guid>
      <title>Tennessee man dips his nasties in customer's salsa over 89-cent tip</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARYVILLE, TENNESSEE  Petty revenge over a bad tip has landed a dude in Tennessee in some seriously hot water.The Daily Times reports that on January 12, a woman ordered Mexican food through the Dinner Delivered service and tipped 89 cents.According to the Blount County complaint affidavit, driver Chaneese Booker picked up the food with pal Matt Web in tow, complaining about the low tip for a 30-minute drive.As payback, Web decided to dip his nasty jalapeno poppers into the customer's salsa, with Booker filming the entire thing and laughing in the background.The pair found messing with the woman's food so hilarious that they bragged about their shenanigans and sent the video of the deed to a group chat, where it was seen by April Pennington.Pennington reported the disgusting duo to Dinner Delivered, and eventually put the video up on Facebook to expose them.Booker ended up getting fired by the delivery service, while Web was arrested and is facing felony charges for "adulteration of food, liquids, or pharmaceuticals."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 02:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/01/3789193/3789193_B70DD27EC7DF46759989CCCFFA42AE5B_190301_3789193_Tennessee_man_dips_his_nasties_in_customer_s_sal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CDB/38E/CDB38E029EBEEAE7550CC5EA6A61D053.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, salsa dip, salsa, double dipping, jalapeno poppers, chili, huevos, food delivery, dinner delivered, bad tip, bad tipping, 89 cent tip, maryville tennessee]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790810</guid>
      <title>FedEx unveils new autonomous delivery robot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEMPHIS, TENNESSEE  FedEx could soon be carrying packages to your home via a delivery robot.FedEx plans to use robots to automate its delivery system, the Washington Post reports.The company is teaming up with DEKA Development & Research Corp to create the delivery robot, which is to be tested this summer. The robot, called FedEx SameDay Bot, is powered by batteries that are attached to its wheels. Cameras and software to avoid obstacles will also be incorporated into the robot. The self-driving vehicle will be able to travel up to speeds of 10 miles per hour as it drives on sidewalks and roadways.According to Reuters, the robots will be used to handle home deliveries for companies such as Walmart and Pizza Hut.The robot will complement the company's SameDay City service, according to a FedEx press release.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 10:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/04/3790810/3790810_D6B6189A744F4A4A94B8D54075FAA310_190304_3790810_FedEx_unveils_new_autonomous_delivery_robot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA9/5CF/BA95CF0CB70D337DF280F8D4843F4F56.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fedex, fedex robot, fedex delivery robot, walmart, pizza hut, home deliveries, automation, self driving robot, delivery robot, automatic delivery robots, automated delivery vehicle, autonomous delivery system, autonomous vehicles, autonomous vehicle technology, robot delivery service, automated goods delivery, robot technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790778</guid>
      <title>SpaceX Dragon capsule successfully docks with ISS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA  An unmanned SpaceX Dragon capsule has successfully docked with the International Space Station as part of its demonstration mission, according to the BBC.  According to Reuters, the 16-foot-tall (4.9 meter) Crew Dragon capsule was launched atop a Falcon 9 rocket from Florida's Kennedy space Center at 2:49 a.m. on Saturday and deployed into orbit 11 minutes later. According to the BBC, the Dragon test vehicle autonomously attached itself to the international docking adapter. The BBC reports the Crew Dragon approached the ISS using lasers and software to guide itself in, while astronauts aboard the space station monitored the docking.  According to BBC, the capsule's "soft capture" contact with the space station occurred at 10:51 GMT, with a full and secure docking confirmed around 10 minutes later. According to Reuters, the capsule was carrying 400 pounds of supplies and test equipment, and a test dummy named "Ripley."Ripley is equipped with sensors around the head, neck and spine to monitor how a flight would feel for a human. The Crew Dragon is scheduled to stay at the ISS for five days, while the three crew members of the space station perform tests on the capsule to see how it is holding up in space. On Friday morning, after being checked out and loaded with cargo, the capsule will undock from the ISS and then plunge back toward Earth. Parachutes will deploy during the capsule's decent, where it should plunge into the Atlantic Ocean near Florida for retrieval.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 09:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/04/3790778/3790778_8AE1771F53814FE89AE583DD96E09755_190304_3790778_SpaceX_Dragon_capsule_successfully_docks_with_IS_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/573/31E/57331E600E672797C4D4E10E04889B73.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, SpaceX, SpaceX Dragon capsule, SpaceX ISS, SpaceX docks ISS, SpaceX Crew Dragon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790709</guid>
      <title>Canada monitoring negative behavior of 'at risk' people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ONTARIO, CANADA  Canadian authorities are using databases to track 'at risk' individuals, according to a Motherboard investigation.Canadian authorities are using a shared database called 'The Risk-driven Tracking Database' or RTD to track so-called 'at risk' individuals. The RTD is part of a larger Canadian pre-crime policing network called 'The Hub' that partners law enforcement, school staff, social workers, healthcare workers, and local governments.Police and civilian agencies can access this database to gather information of individuals believed to be at risk which includes people living in dangerous neighborhoods and those that could become criminals or victims, allowing them to intervene in case of emergencies.Individuals are registered into the RTD if local authorities report abnormal behavior to The Hub. This data can then be used to request intervention from other law enforcement agencies or institutions.Authorities can input an individual's sex, location and age group including other 'risk factors' such as mental health, criminal involvement, negative behavior and physical health status.Currently, there are only two RTDs, one in Ontario and the other in Saskatchewan. However, according to the Correctional Service of Canada, there are roughly 100 active Hubs in the country as of 2016.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 07:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/04/3790709/3790709_7FF19EC4642B48C289070819916C2047_190304_3790709_Canada_monitoring_negative_behavior_of__at_risk__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EF0/F1F/EF0F1FB95478C093DC96471C420FF156.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Canada monitoring negative behavior of at risk people, Canada monitoring negative behavior, canada monitoring, canada surveillance, china surveillance, social credit system, canada social credit system, china social credit system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790658</guid>
      <title>Mysterious Planet Nine could be discovered in a decade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA  New research suggests we might be able to spot the mysterious Planet Nine sooner than we thought. In 2016 scientists from California Institue of Technology published research in the Astronomical Journal that found new evidence of the existence of Planet Nine. The scientists used mathematical models and computer simulations to map out the hypothetical planet's orbit after finding abnormal alignments of six objects in the Kuiper Belt suggesting that a larger object's gravity was pulling them.The Kuiper Belt is a ring of icy objects located beyond the orbit of Neptune. Within it are several thousand celestial bodies, several of which have their own moons.Planet Nine remains unseen. However, a paper published last month by the same Caltech team in the journal Physics Reports suggests that it could be detected within a decade.Results also showed that its mass is probably five to 10 times the mass of Earth.They estimate Planet Nine to be about 400 astronomical units away from the sun, which is the equivalent of 60 billion kilometers or 37 billion miles. These new estimates suggest that the planet is closer and potentially brighter than previously thought, making it easier to detect in the coming years.In a second paper published in the Astronomical Journal, the same group of researchers calculated the percentage of potential bias of their observations. Results showed the probability was just one in 500.In a Caltech press release, Konstantin Batygin, one of the lead researchers of both papers said, quote, 'The prospect of one day seeing real images of Planet Nine is absolutely electrifying. Although finding Planet Nine astronomically is a great challenge, I'm very optimistic that we will image it within the next decade.']]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 06:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/04/3790658/3790658_ADF633BEA61D4E63B2C612261E03C029_190304_3790658_Mysterious_Planet_Nine_could_be_discovered_in_a__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/76B/257/76B257A92A708CD7C4761C9A8D379BAE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mysterious planet, planet nine, planet nine discovery, planet nine found, evidence of planet nine, planet nine evidence, planet nine orbit, planet nine discovered]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3790575</guid>
      <title>Nanoparticle injections let mice see infrared light, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANHUI, CHINA / WORCESTER, MASSACHUSETTS  Researchers from China and the U.S. used nanoparticles to enhance the vision of mice, allowing them to see in infrared, according to a new study published in the journal Cell.A team of researchers from the University of Science and Technology of China and the University of Massachusetts Medical School injected nanoparticles into the eyes of mice that gave them the ability to see infrared light without compromising their normal vision.Humans and mice are not able to see infrared light naturally. Both species can only see to light in the visible spectrum.According to the study, the pupils of the mice that received the nanoparticles injection were constricted. This meant their eyes were able to detect infrared light even during the day. Mice that only received a buffer solution did not have constricted pupils.Jin Bao, one of the researchers from the University of Science and Technology of China, explained in the study that nanoparticles were able to anchor to the photoreceptor cells in the eyes, also known as the rods and the cones, and convert the infrared light to make it appear as a green color.The nanoparticles do this by capturing the longer infrared wavelengths and sending out shorter wavelengths in the visible spectrum. This is then absorbed by a rod or a cone, which then sends sends a signal to the brain, tricking the brain into believing that visible light has hit the retina.This technology could be used in security and military operations in the future, according to the study.Senior author Tian Xue said in the study this technology is exciting because it could "eventually enable human beings to see beyond our natural capability."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 03:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/04/3790575/3790575_8029139232DC4CFCA955923DE4935FF1_190304_3790575_Nanoparticle_injections_let_mice_see_infrared_li_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F38/163/F38163696267DA7F268853419328B216.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, usa, nanotechnology, mice, infrared light, seeing infrared light, nanotechnology 2019, nanotechnology mice , injecting nanoparticles into mice, nanoparticles, making mice see infrared light, supervision, enhancing vision, infrared light nanoparticles, infrared light mice]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791486</guid>
      <title>US deploys THAAD missile system in Israel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JERUSALEM  The U.S. deployed its most advanced air and missile defense system in Israel for the first time, according to U.S. and Israeli military officials on Monday, Reuters reports. The Terminal High Altitude Area Defense system, or THAAD, deployment was intended to test the U.S. military's ability to rapidly deploy such weapons around the world, according to a spokeswoman for U.S. European Command. According to Reuters, Lockheed Martin builds and integrates the THAAD system, which is designed to shoot down short- medium- and intermediate-range ballistic missiles. Raytheon builds its advanced radar. According to Army Technology, the THAAD system is designed to protect against incoming ballistic missiles at ranges of 200 kms and altitudes of up to 150 kms. According to Army Technology, the THAAD battery typically operates nine launch vehicles each carrying eight missiles, with two tactical operations centers and a ground-based radar. THAAD intercepts incoming ballistic missiles in their final phase of flight, according to Reuters. Radar first detects incoming threats, identifies the target and engages. An interceptor missile is fired from the launcher, and then uses kinetic energy to destroy the incoming missile.  According to Reuters, the deployment comes amid rising tensions between Israel and Iran over Israel's bombing campaign in Syria and comments in which Iran's foreign minister said he could not rule out the possibility of military conflict between the two countries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 13:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/05/3791486/3791486_8184089C2D9340399BC40342FFD235D6_190305_3791486_US_deploys_THAAD_missile_system_in_Israel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/011/AF8/011AF8D73CCDB44CC779297EA6847173.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, THAAD, THAAD system, US deploys THAAD, Israel THAAD system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791335</guid>
      <title>Indiana man accidentally blasts himself in his junk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARION, INDIANA  A 46-year-old Indiana man accidentally popped one off into his little soldier early last Thursday, according to police.According to the Sacramento Bee, police say Mark Anthony Jones from Marion, was walking on an Indiana parkway with his 9 milly tucked in his waistband without a holsteralways a solid move, and it just looks way cooler. Is Marion, Indiana really a hotbed for criminal activity on a Thursday morning? Probably not, but it's better to be safe than sorry. Or in this case...just sorry. According to the po po, the one-man Delta force was walking when he felt his burner start to slip, so he reached down to adjust it. Then the strangest thing happened, Rambo accidentally squeezed one off right through the old sausage and teabags.  Terminator then got himself to the emergency room post-haste. Police were then called to the emergency room at Marion General Hospital at 6:44 a.m. to interview the American Self-Sniper. Unfortunately, Black Hawk Down didn't have an Indiana permit for the piece, so his case is now going to be referred to prosecutors for possible charges.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/05/3791335/3791335_FCEB458F85DB454395B9AA98373ACA0C_190305_3791335_Indiana_man_accidentally_blasts_himself_in_his_j_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7BD/A66/7BDA6676E79DFF13CB064700823C934A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man accidentally, Mark Anthony Jones Marion, Mark Anthony Jones Marion accident, Mark Anthony Jones Indiana accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791256</guid>
      <title>'Keto Crotch': The smelly side effect of the popular diet?</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  The Keto diet is currently in the news for the wrong reasons. The ketogenic diet is a high-fat, low carb plan where healthy fats make up 80 percent of a person's daily calories, and protein 20 percent.This involves eating roughly 50 grams of carbohydrates a day, equivalent to a bagel or a cup of white rice. In comparison, the U.S. Department of Agriculture recommends 225 to 325 grams of carbs a day.When carbs are taken out of the diet, the body burns up glucose reserves and then breaks down stored fat into fatty acids.The New York Post cites social media users on Reddit threads and Twitters boards as saying the diet is making women smelling a bit strange "down there."Women are complaining about "keto crotch," a strong odor coming from their private parts once they've taken on the keto diet."Liza De Fazio, a registered dietitian nutritionist, told Insider that the keto diet could change the pH levels of the body, which may result in a different odor than usual.However, California-based obstetrician and gynecologist Jen Gunter refuted the dietician by tweeting: "Food does not change vaginal odor ... if your sweat or breath smells of ketones then everywhere else will too."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 07:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/05/3791256/3791256_89FF3DFBFEB244889ABF6CF9CE1B785F_190305_3791256__Keto_Crotch___The_smelly_side_effect_of_the_pop_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9B0/235/9B0235C1C1F03BECC1B027B2C1AE5911.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, keto diet, side effects of keto, keto diet before after, keto diet side effects, keto diet side effects long term, keto diet side effects body odor, body odor, keto diet smelly side effects, popular diets, popular diet keto,  stinky side effects of keto, ketogenic diet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791090</guid>
      <title>Deep sleep important for brain to clear out toxic proteins: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCHESTER, NEW YORK  The depth of one's sleep can affect the brain's ability to adequately remove waste and toxic proteins, according to a new study published in the journal Science Advances.An increase of toxic proteins such as beta amyloid and tau in the brain are often linked with Alzheimer's disease, according to a University of Rochester Medical Center news release.The researchers injected six mice with six different anesthetic regimens to replicate different stages of sleep.This was to identify if a certain phase of sleep could be associated with the glymphatic system, which the brain uses to clear waste.The scientists determined the best glymphatic system activity takes place in the stage that was most similar to a human's deep, non REM, short-wave sleep, efficiently stimulating the cleaning process of the brain.Mice that were given anesthetics which did not lead to slower brain activity had a decline in glymphatic activity, according to the study.The study reinforces the link between poor sleep and Alzheimer's disease, and the importance of deep sleep for the brain's cleaning system to work effectively.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 02:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/05/3791090/3791090_7524C79E9BCA4F608B27E7E096514F71_190305_3791090_Deep_sleep_important_for_brain_to_clear_out_toxi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AD/9A9/1AD9A91F366F53E506F5C5278F6C9B27.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, sleep, clearing toxic proteins, beta amyloid, toxic proteins, tau, deep sleep, sleeping, brain waves, deep sleep important for brain to clear toxic proteins, alzheimer's, alzheimer's protein, REM, sleeping and alzheimer's disease, glymphatic system, brain, glymphatic system sleep]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3792331</guid>
      <title>Self-driving cars may be more likely to hit black people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA  If you happen to be of a darker persuasion, you might want to keep your head on a swivel next time you see an autonomous vehicle, because according to a new study, it might not see you. According to a new study from the Georgia Institute of Technology, the darker your skin, the more likely you might be to getting hit by a self-driving car, because automated vehicles may be better at detecting whiter pedestrians. According to Vox, researchers wanted to see how well self-driving cars detected people with different skin colors. They analyzed a large dataset of images that had pedestrians and divided them up into light-skinned and dark-skinned groups using the Fitzpatrick scale, a system for separating human skin tones from light to dark. The researchers found that the dark-skinned group was less accurately detected by five percentage points than the light-skinned group.  They found the difference to still be significant when they controlled for variables like time of day or the occasionally blocked view of pedestrians. The study is called "Predictive Inequity in Object Detection," and has yet to be peer reviewed. Another area researchers might want to analyze is whether detection can be affected when white people are in blackface. Better yet, can black people can increase their chances of survival by putting on whiteface?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 13:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3792331/3792331_2374F62B28384838B2978FFEBA3C45C9_190306_3792331_Self_driving_cars_may_be_more_likely_to_hit_blac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A10/D68/A10D685B8FC614E6F0FFE26C3E39426B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, self-driving cars, autonomous vehicles, autonomous cars, self-driving cars pedestrians, Georgia Institute of Technology, self-driving vehicles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3792326</guid>
      <title>Man charges obese passenger $150 for encroaching on his seat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  A man hilariouslyor horrificallycharged a large and in charge passenger sitting next to him on a flight $150 for encroaching on his seat. The anonymous man wrote about his experience on a Reddit AITA forum and has since taken off. The guy was apparently flying on a five-hour cross country flight and specifically chose a row with no middle seat and picked the aisle seat. He then goes on to say, "a very obese man boards and I can tell instantly he is going to have a tough time fitting in any of the seats." Karma immediately kicks in, with the large passenger cruising over to the window seat next to the guy. "He sits down and is easily seeping into about  of my seat," he goes on. "I sit down and am pressed up against him, making me uncomfortable."So after about 60 seconds of that, the guy lets the bigger gentleman know that this isn't going to fly. The larger man tried to take up less space, but let's say he hit a bit of turbulence.After talking to a flight attendant, she says big guy could buy a second seat, but that idea crashed because the flight was full. Other ideas that didn't take off were booking another flight and sitting next to someone else that wouldn't mind. So that's when the guy said he would "put up with" the situation for $150 bones. The big fella instantly agreed and handed over the benjamins, saying he "appreciated" it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 13:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3792326/3792326_24CB46B7F99C4437A2BE2F10385A0BCA_190306_3792326_Man_charges_obese_passenger__150_for_encroaching_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B13/E40/B13E40E9EEA0782FD314AA59946AE61A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, airplane, airplane seats, airplane passenger, large passenger, encroaching, small airplane seats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3792214</guid>
      <title>Teen spikes step dad's drinks with cattle tranquilizer to be funny</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LIMA, WISCONSIN  A Wisconsin teen was busted for spiking his step dad's drinks with cattle tranquilizer, and apparently did it for funsies.According to the criminal complaint, Tyler Rabenhorst-Malone is facing felony charges for placing foreign objects in edibles and second degree recklessly endangering safety.It all began in January 2018, when the 17-year-old's stepfather went to the doctor for some pretty odd symptoms- he was stumbling, slurring his speech, breathing heavily, and had a droopy face.Doctors chalked it up to one too many energy drinks, stress, and not enough snooze. But when it happened again, step figured something else was up.In April, Mom reported that a box of oxytocin mixed with rompun went missing from the barn.Step dad soon got suspicious that it was his step son was, and found two used syringes shoved in a corner of the barn that he thought the boy was using to mess with his drinks.After he gave samples to the po-po, the state lab found both the drinks and syringes tested positive for Xylazine, which is used to sedate large animals.When confronted, the teen told officers he never wanted to hurt his dad, and just did it to be funny.Not funny now that you're about to go to jail though, is it?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3792214/3792214_7B64739DE06B4F2A9B5B7BD82B8AF522_190306_3792214_Teen_spikes_step_dad_s_drinks_with_cattle_tranqu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AA5/AC6/AA5AC6F95F18524F3C8A099D533FA4D1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cattle tranquilizer, cow tranquilizer, spiked drinks, wisconsin teen, animal tranquilizer, droopy face, slurred speech, animal sedative, sedative, tranquilizer, xylazine, oxytocin, rompun]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3792087</guid>
      <title>Kylie Jenner named youngest self-made billionaire ever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA  The youngest of the Kardashian-Jenner family has officially been named the world's youngest self-made billionaire by Forbes.Kylie Jenner was just a child when her sisters started filming popular reality show Keeping up with the Kardashians back in 2007.Since then, she has constantly courted controversy for things like getting lip injections at a young age and for allegedly undergoing plastic surgery.All this worked in her favor and exponentially increased her social media following. Kylie even acknowledged this in an interview with Forbes saying, "It's the power of social media, I had such a strong reach before I was able to start anything."The 21-year-old acquired the bulk of her fortune through Kylie Cosmetics, a makeup company she launched in 2015 when she was just a teenager, according to Forbes.Kylie launched the company with the infamous Kylie Lip Kits, directly through social media to her tens of millions of fans.The company has since gone on to be worth at least US$900 million, with Kylie owning 100 percent of the company.However, many have argued that the 21-year-old can't be "self-made" because her family are well-known reality TV stars, and gave her the platform to succeed and build her cosmetics company.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 10:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3792087/3792087_B26E253E7B7E4C65ACE75B1FF1B67C6D_190306_3792087_Kylie_Jenner_named_youngest_self_made_billionair_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DF6/B09/DF6B096F57FC191C0F23FC40EF8F680D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, self-made billionaire, kylie jenner, youngest self made billionaire, kylie jenner billionaire, self made billionaire kylie jenner, youngest self made billionaire forbes, youngest billionaire, kylie jenner rich, how kylie jenner became rich, how rich is kylie jenner 2019, kylie cosmetics, the kardashians, the richest kardashian, kylie cosmetics net worth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791948</guid>
      <title>London patient is second to be cleared of HIV</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  A case study published in the journal Nature details the successful treatment of a patient in London, who is now in long-term HIV remission.CNN reports that a man known as the London patient has become the second person in the world to be cleared of HIV after the Berlin patient more than a decade ago.According to the New York Times, the two men achieved the milestones after undergoing bone marrow stem cell transplants intended to treat their cancer.In both instances, patients received stem cells from donors with a rare genetic mutation of the protein CCR5, making them HIV-resistant.HIV typically uses the CCR5 on the surface of immune cells to enter those cells, but is unable to latch on to the mutated version of the protein.According to the New York Times, the transplanted immune cells replaced the London patient's vulnerable cells, and destroyed the cancer without any harmful side effects.He remained on antiretroviral drugs until stopping in September 2017. The Guardian reports that blood tests have shown no signs of the virus for the past 18 months.Anton Pozniak, president of the International Aids Society, says the findings reaffirm the belief that AIDS is curable.He told the Guardian that the hope is there will eventually be a safe, cost-effective, and easy way to achieve results with gene technology or antibody techniques.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 08:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3791948/3791948_08667377A0E7432E9357F3E04AD0B921_190306_3791948_London_patient_is_second_to_be_cleared_of_HIV_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C12/67E/C1267E9310EE8A5A72BDD09F83623674.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, HIV, AIDS, HIV cure, London patient, Berlin patient, cancer, Hodgkin's lymphoma, cancer cure, stem cell transplant, bone marrow transplant, stem cells]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791937</guid>
      <title>'Broken heart' syndrome linked to the brain, new study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZURICH  A new study published in the European Heart Journal says that the brain might be linked to broken heart syndrome.Also known as takotsubo syndrome, a broken heart is often caused by shock usually after a stressful or emotional event.The syndrome has similar symptoms to a heart attack such as breathlessness and chest pain, according to the study.The study goes on to suggest that an increase of stress hormones could be linked to the broken heart syndrome.The researchers looked at brain scans of 15 patients with broken heart and found decreased connectivity between the limbic system, which processes emotions, and the autonomic nervous system which controls breathing and heartbeat.Jelena Ghadri, a researcher involved with the study, was quoted by the BBC as saying "Emotions are processed in the brain so it is conceivable that the disease originates in the brain with top-down influences on the heart."According to the BBC, it could take weeks, days or even months for the heart muscle to recover from the syndrome.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 08:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3791937/3791937_3D0229236B95497FA6590CBC570C8248_190306_3791937__Broken_heart__syndrome_linked_to_the_brain__new_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A77/D07/A77D07689D5A6E30CC77D35EA5EDD974.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, brain, study, broken heart syndrome, broken heart, broken heart science, broken heart linked with brain, broken heart syndrome symptoms, stress, heart broken, heartbreak,  takotsubo syndrome, brain heart connection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791868</guid>
      <title>Self-powered sensors track firefighters during blazes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HAMILTON, CANADA  Researchers have created a motion-powered, fireproof sensor that can track movements of people who work in high-risk environments like firefighters, steelworkers and miners, according to a McMaster University press release.  McMasters researchers, working with partners at other colleges, have created a low-cost sensor that is about the size of a button-cell battery. According to the release, the sensors can be incorporated into the sole of a boot or under the arm of a jacket, wherever motion creates a pattern of constant contact and release to generate the energy the sensor needs to function. By harvesting electricity from movement, the sensor uses triboelectric, or friction-generated, charging for power.The sensors can track the movement and location of a person in a burning building, a mineshaft or other hazardous locations, alerting those outside if movement stops. The key material in the sensor, a new carbon aerogel nanocomposite, is fireproof and never needs charging from a power source. The sensors have been successfully tested at temperatures up to 300 degrees Celsius without any loss of function. The development teamfrom McMaster, UCLA and University of Chemistry and Technology Praguedescribes the new device in a paper published in the journal Nano Energy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3791868/3791868_A4CD47F82E024C7D89FF08FB301D2991_190306_3791868_Self_powered_sensors_track_firefighters_during_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/023/0D8/0230D88D0C3091629D9067B28BA31995.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, self-powered sensor, triboelectric charging, firefighters, steelworkers, miners, high risk environments]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791844</guid>
      <title>No link found between measles vaccine and autism, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK / STANFORD, CALIFORNIA   A study in the Annals of Internal Medicine has confirmed that getting a Measles, Mumps and Rubella vaccination won't cause a child to develop autism.Researchers involved in the study examined more than a half a million Danish children born between 1999 and 2010 to see if there was a link between getting vaccinated and receiving an autism diagnosis.The study found that the vaccine isn't linked to an increased risk of autism. The researchers explained that a vaccination wasn't likely to cause autism, adding that it also is not responsible for autism cases that appear after vaccination takes place.The news comes in wake of several measles outbreaks in the U.S. Many parents there refuse to have their children vaccinated against the disease because they believe vaccinations cause autism.There are six measles outbreaks across the U.S., according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.Symptoms include high fever, red eyes, and a rash that begins on the face.The CDC says the virus is contagious as it stays in the airspace when an infected person has coughed or sneezed. 90 percent of those not immune to the virus will likely become infected.The CDC also recommends getting the measles, mumps, and rubella vaccine to prevent any new outbreaks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3791844/3791844_24A6E0B3A7F34D71B51B4FB03D93C163_190306_3791844_No_link_found_between_measles_vaccine_and_autism_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5E2/5CE/5E25CE73B564C006C74DF0364DD89F2B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, measles, measles vaccine, autism, measles vaccine doesn't cause autism, MMR vaccine, MMR vaccine explained, no link found between measles vaccine and autism, measles vaccination, measles outbreak, measles outbreak 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3791831</guid>
      <title>China's plans to explore Mars and build a power plant in space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING   China plans to build the first solar power plant in space and embark on a mission to Mars.China intends to build a solar power station that would orbit earth at a distance of 36,000 kilometers, according to reports from China's Science and Technology Daily.Components of the solar power plant would be sent to space where they would then be assembled, according to CNN.Pang Zhihao, a researcher from the China Academy of Space Technology, told the newspaper the solar station would be able to draw energy from the sun without any interference from Earth's atmosphere.A receiving station will be built in the northern Chinese city of Xian. The electricity could hypothetically be beamed to Earth via microwaves or lasers, although more research needs to be done on the effects these would have on humans and animals.In addition to the orbital power plant, China also has plans to send a rover to Mars.The country has opened its first Mars simulation base in China's Qinghai Province. The area resembles the Martian surface with its dry and arid climate, according to Global Times.China's Mars mission is being called the Mars Global Remote Sensing Orbiter and Small Rover, or HX-1.The lander will touch down on the northern hemisphere of Mars, according to the State Council of the People's Republic of China's website.The lander will contain a rover with six wheels and four solar panels and will be able to explore Mars by itself.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2019 06:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/06/3791831/3791831_894599BEF06F4F988F2A342268898DC6_190306_3791831_China_s_plans_to_explore_Mars_and_build_a_power__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C04/CC2/C04CC2CFC0BB26CD038BCAB180FC72B1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, mars, mars mission, china mars mission, mars lander mission, china space mission, china space, space power plant, solar energy, china solar power station, solar power station in space, space solar power station, solar power plant in space, solar energy, china in space, chinese space mission]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3792797</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show North Korea rebuilding nuclear missile site</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  Beyond Parallel and 38 North, websites that monitor North Korea, have noticed activity at the country's Tongchang-ri[g][h][i] satellite launch facility.Also known as the Sohae[j][k] launch facility, Beyond Parallel released images of the site being partly constructed. The photos are said to show partially built structures, including a vertical engine test stand and rail-mounted rocket transfer.The vertical engine test stand was partly dismantled in August 2018, according to Beyond Parallel. The outlet referred to the ongoing activity at the missile base as "deliberate and purposeful."However, 38 North founder Joel Wit, said on Twitter that movement at the missile testing site provides "no evidence" that North Korea is preparing to launch another ICBM.The news follows the recent Trump-Kim summit in Vietnam where both sides didn't come to an accord on denuclearization, CNN reports. CNN quotes Trump as saying he would be "very disappointed" if Kim Jong Un has restarted North Korea's missile program.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 10:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/07/3792797/3792797_2FB65A320143425FB7779B55FA76C5DD_190307_3792797_Satellite_images_show_North_Korea_rebuilding_nuc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A75/CF1/A75CF1272C875C8F4F21B94B8457D060.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Korea, missile testing site, missile, missile launch, launch vehicle, nuclear missile, nuclear missile testing site, north korean missile site, Tongchang-ri satellite launch facility, Tongchang-ri, north korean missile launch pad, missile base, north korea missile base, north korea missile, denuclearization]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793586</guid>
      <title>Genetically tweaked microbe can make plastic from plants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADISON, WISCONSIN  A genetically engineered microbe is the key to producing biodegradable plastics from a common plant waste material.According to research from the University of Wisconsin-Madison, N. aromaticivorans is a type of soil bacteria that can digest lignin from plant cells and turn them into smaller hydrocarbons.Lignin is a polymer found in the cell walls of woody plants, which although abundant, is difficult to break down. It has such little value that paper mills that have been stripping lignin from wood for centuries merely dispose of it in boilers.During digestion, the bacteria turns lignin into 2-pyrone-4, 6-dicarboxylic acid, or PDC. By removing three genes from the microbe, University of Wisconsin-Madison scientists were able to make PDC the end point for the digestion process.UWM researcher Miguel Perez says bioengineers in Japan used PDC to make a variety of materials for consumer products, and found it performs the same or better than petroleum-based additives in PET polymers, like plastic bottles or synthetic fibers.As a plastic alternative, PDC would naturally break down in the environment, but wouldn't leach compounds as it degrades.Researchers have so far managed to turn 59 percent of lignin's compounds into PDC, but suggest greater efficiency might be achieved with further gene-tweaking.The study is published in the journal Green Chemistry.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793586/3793586_261E337DDE5248E297B329B471E8F6C6_190308_3793586_Genetically_tweaked_microbe_can_make_plastic_fro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F67/D83/F67D8363B7281B0C370983BA9FD55C13.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic from plants, plant plastic, plastic alternative, biodegradable plastic, plastic, lignin, soil bacteria, genetically engineered microbe, genetically engineered bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793582</guid>
      <title>Residents of Paris street want gates to keep Instagrammers out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  Life on a photogenic Parisian street has turned nightmarish for its residents, who now have to deal with all the crazy things people do "for the 'gram."According to radio station France Info, Rue Cremieux in Paris' 12th arrondissement is a small cobblestone street lined with pastel-colored houses that's become a huge hit on Instagram.So while there are no cars on the picturesque street, there are hordes of tourists who come day in and day out, all to strike a pose...or fifty.Over 30,000 photos on Instagram are hashtagged Rue Cremieux, making it one of the most popular photo spots in Europe.For people who actually live there though, it sucks. Residents told the radio station that while weekdays are relatively quiet, weekends bring rappers, screaming bachelorette parties, and other rowdy visitors.One local documented the shenanigans on the Instagram account Club Cremieux, which shows flash mobs, photo shoots, and random yoga poses on people's doorways.Fed up residents are now demanding that the city install gates at each end of the street to keep out annoying 'grammers at night and on weekends.The city of Paris has until the end of summer to figure out a working solution. Otherwise, everyone might just take to the streets.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793582/3793582_9C37F55CD51F40D2A10FD3A1B223B503_190308_3793582_Residents_of_Paris_street_want_gates_to_keep_Ins_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/983/2E3/9832E36CAFF7B8AF684F3737224F9740.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, rue cremieux, club cremieux, paris pastel street, instagram, instagrammable street, photogenic street, for the gram, instagrammable, instagrammers, insta tourism]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793563</guid>
      <title>China leaked chat log reveals massive scope of CCP spying</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  A leak of around 364 million online records in a Chinese database has exposed the massive scope of state surveillance in China, according to the Financial Times. According to security researcher Victor Gevers at Dutch non-profit GDI Foundation, who found the database, the files show GPS locations, file transfers, identity card numbers, and chat logs. According to Gevers, the database was freely accessible online to anyone with the IP address, and user profiles were stored together with photographs, addresses and locations. He also added that the main database was providing information to 17 other servers depending on which area the data came from. According to the Financial Times, a large number of the records had the names and addresses of internet cafes on them. According to AFP, Chinese law requires internet cafes to record the identities and "relevant" online activity of users, and provide them to the public security bureau on request. This has lead to the growth of internet cafe monitoring software. The records in the databases have labels referring to Chinese social-media apps like WeChat and QQ, in addition to WeChat payment records and QQ account numbers. According to the AFP, Gevers also found another publicly accessible database that contained personal information such as ethnicity and GPS tracking data of 2.6 million people in Xinjiang. Access to this database, however, has since been closed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 12:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793563/3793563_EB0E108CB01D4D43B91DC0622D1A2F13_190308_3793563_China_leaked_chat_log_reveals_massive_scope_of_C_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A4D/D48/A4DD48CA9C44F0C589346F5F97A0133B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china surveillance, china chat log leak, china online surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793397</guid>
      <title>China drops English propaganda rap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING   China seeks to appeal to the masses by releasing English rap song promoting the CCP's annual meeting, reports The Guardian.It's no secret, China is very much eager to show off and with the Chinese communist party's annual meeting right around the corner, they're taking their propaganda to a whole new level.They decided they'd propagate their message to the entire world this year via a bizarre rap song titled, 'Two Sessions': To the World from China'. The track was released by Xinhua News, China's official state-run press agency, and was delivered by a Chinese rapper called Su HanThe video is a weird combination of stock footage-like videos mixed with shots of Su Han rapping what seems to be lyrics directly translated from Chinese using Google. He talks about how the 'joy of success is like a weekend car ride around the pool' and how he will school us in 'Chinese manners'.  The rap song tackles some real-life issues though, like poverty. In Su Han's words, 'Poverty's such a travesty, a clumsy tragedy.' True that Su Han, true that.However, not all his lyrics are that eloquent. At one point he urges us to 'Eject all the rapaciousness like shaking off nephrolithiasis.' For those who don't have their medical lingo on check, nephrolithiasis is the medical term for kidney stones. So yeah he's telling us to shake off our rapaciousness (?) like we would shake off our kidney stones.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 09:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793397/3793397_8476280A964D489195578323C09209D9_190308_3793397_China_drops_English_propaganda_rap_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E98/FEE/E98FEE36551D322FC5A7113A0359907C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china two sessions, china liangui, china su han, china rap, china english rap, china propaganda rap, chinese bizarre rap, china rap video, china rap video propaganda, china propaganda]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793385</guid>
      <title>Farmer accuses vegan activists of killing piglets while protesting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LINCOLNSHIRE, ENGLAND  Animals' rights activists from Meat The Victims decided to raise awareness about veganism by storming a farm in the UK.As many as 200 protesters decided to stage a protest at Sandiland Farm to protest the brutal conditions for pigs at the farm, Lincolnshire Live reports.Images on social media show the protesters hugging and cuddling the pigs.However, Silvia Hook, one of the owners' of the farm, says the mob of protesters frightened the pigs and caused the death of two piglets.The protestors deny her claim and released a video showing pigs that were already dead when they got to the farm.The vegan protesters said they are advocating for a vegan lifestyle so that the animals can be free.Hook told Lincolnshire Live the protesters have "already done a lot of damage," and called them "ridiculous" for calling themselves animals right activists.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 09:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793385/3793385_CDD1D9941F2C4F8AAF66A50D9DFEDE00_190308_3793385_Farmer_accuses_vegan_activists_of_killing_piglet_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/51E/1A0/51E1A0F4F57855F6BD8F2290489513F7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, lincolnshire, vegan,veganism, vegans storm into farm to hug piglets,  vegans UK, militant vegans uk, vegans storm  into pig farm, Meet the victims protest, Meat the Victims protest UK, Meat the Victims protest UK farm , animal rights, activists, vegan activists, vegan stampede UK, Sandilands Farm]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793331</guid>
      <title>Women accused of killing Kim Jong-nam await trial</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR, MALAYSIA  One of the women suspected of murdering Kim Jong Un's elder half-brother, Kim Jong-Nam is set to testify in court next week, reports the AFP.In February 2017, Kim Jong-Nam was traveling from Kuala Lumpur to Macau when he was reportedly poisoned by two women, now identified as Doan Thi Huong from Vietnam and Siti Aisyah from Indonesia. Citing unnamed police sources, state news agency Bernama reported that one woman sprayed chemicals on Kim Jong-Nam's face and immediately after, the second woman held a cloth over his face for 10 seconds. Reuters reported that traces of the deadly nerve agent VX was found on the women's clothing. VX blocks signals between the nervous system and the body's muscles. This causes muscular paralysis which results in death via asphyxiation.Malaysian officials also identified four other men at the airport who are suspected of being North Korean agents that directed the attack.The Washington Post reports that U.S. officials believe Huong and Aisyah were following direct orders from Pyongyang while Huong claims that she thought she was participating in a prank television show. Huang is believed to have been recruited by North Korean officials while working at a bar in Hanoi. North Korea has denied any type of involvement, however, the four agents who were identified by Malaysian officials fled the country soon after the attack took place.Kim Jong Nam and Kim Jong Un are both sons of former North Korean leader Kim Jong Il, however, they were born to different mothers. Some speculate that Un felt threatened by his elder brother and orchestrated his assassination.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 08:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793331/3793331_11AF951DE5A2428996E856349D16F9B6_190308_3793331_Women_accused_of_killing_Kim_Jong_nam_await_tria_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/036/021/036021FAE77FA48660B797AEF4866CFA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, DPRK Women accused of slaying Kim Jong Nam await trial,  Kim Jong Nam, Women accused of slaying Kim Jong Nam, Kim Jong Un, DPRK, North Korea, Kim Jong Nam assasination, kim jong nam poisoned, kim jong nam death, who killed kim jong nam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793317</guid>
      <title>Taiwanese aboriginal BBQ vendor goes viral</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHIAYI, TAIWAN   Beautiful Taiwanese aboriginal woman goes viral after customers share a video of her online, reports ET Today.Taiwan's National Alishan Scenic Area is famous for its mesmerizing mountain views but visitors now are more interested in photographing other kinds of scenery.A barbeque stall near the popular national park is attracting lines of hungry customers and they're not just after the meat on the grill.The real attraction seems to be the beautiful woman behind the grill seen in this video hurriedly tending to her customers while wearing a tight black shirt with a plunging neckline. According to Taiwan's ET Today, the Barbeque Queen's real name is Ruo Yan. She's a member of the Cou indigenous group in Southern Taiwan and her enchanting looks have made her a viral sensation. The Grill Goddess started making rounds online after a customer at the barbeque stand shot a video of her hard at work.It didn't take long for creepers online to track-down Rou Yan and learn more about her past. Turns out she has previously worked as a model and in the performing arts, but now in her free time helps her parents out at their barbeque stand. Good looks, good vending skills, and good daughter? We can see why she's got fans.But Rou Yan isn't the first  and probably won't be the last  of Taiwan's long list of attractive vendors that have gone viral.Let's see so far we've had the 'Hot Bean Curd Seller' with his washboard abs, then we had the delicate market butcher dubbed 'Pork Princess' and also a doll-like Mickey D's cashier that the public named 'McDonald's Goddess'. C'mon Taiwan, we need to step our nickname game up.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 08:09:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793317/3793317_191CE55E406042FD8D300310BF270CBB_190308_3793317_Taiwanese_aboriginal_BBQ_vendor_goes_viral_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B66/173/B66173908EC88249209B5CC8E5F1A425.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Taiwanese aboriginal BBQ vendor goes viral, Taiwanese aboriginal BBQ vendor, Taiwanese aboriginal BBQ, Taiwanese aboriginal, Taiwanese, taiwanese viral, taiwanese viral food, taiwanese barbeque goddess, barbeque goddess, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793262</guid>
      <title>Japanese AI cameras can spot shoplifters before they steal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  A Japanese startup has developed AI camera software that can detect if someone is likely to shoplift, according to Bloomberg.Vaak has developed artificial intelligence software that looks for potential pilferers by analyzing security camera footage for fidgeting, restlessness and other potentially suspicious body language. According to Bloomberg, the AI uses algorithms to look through security-camera video and notifies staff about possible shoplifters via a smartphone app. According to Next Shark, Vaak Eye looks at more than 100 characteristics, including a person's face, clothes, movement, stride, direction and even purpose. Demonstration videos show the software identifying a person's sex, age, location, belongings and actions while calculating a suspiciousness rate estimate. The software also keeps track of every store item a person picks up and for how long each things is held. According to IT Media, as of Dec. 12, Vaak Eye has detected at least seven shoplifters in test stores. The images of the suspects were subsequently given to po po. Vaak Eye is currently keeping an eye out in 16 stores around Tokyo. So if you're going to be in Tokyo, you better start watching your back.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 06:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793262/3793262_48F61C6D3D9E405484F1CFCF25FA08A4_190308_3793262_Japanese_AI_cameras_can_spot_shoplifters_before__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/78C/746/78C7460FC67980B3F7EBB40033791C24.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, AI, Artificial Intelligence, AI cameras, Japan AI cameras, Vaak AI camera, shoplifting, shoplifters]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793256</guid>
      <title>This is why 'ji32k7au4a83' is a super common password</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  If you're a person that's on the hunt for an ultra secure password, try this oneji32k7au4a83. Last week, hardware/software engineer Robert Ou asked over Twitter why ji32k7au4a83 was such a commonly spotted password on HIBP. According to Gizmodo, Have I Been Pwned is an aggregator started by security expert Troy Hunt to help people find out if their email or personal data has shown up in any big data breaches. The site can check if your password has shown up in any big data breaches, and in this case, ji32k7au4a83 been identified in 141 breaches by HIBP. But why? Blame the Taiwanese. According to Ou's Twitter responses, the password is coming from the Bopomofo system for typing Mandarin. So in Taiwan, when you want to write the Mandarin phrase "", you type in ji32k7au4a83, which in English literally translates to "my password." Guess it's time to update '123456'.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 06:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/08/3793256/3793256_A5F965A532C14C4A8B14716CD34284E2_190308_3793256_This_is_why__ji32k7au4a83__is_a_super_common_pas_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/27D/10A/27D10A1766ED6D6AA3814856FF5E31D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, password, password security, Taiwan Bopomofo system, Taiwan Zhuyin Fuhao, Taiwanese typing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3793762</guid>
      <title>Homeless man, NJ woman admit to GoFundMe scam</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA  A homeless man and a New Jersey woman admitted to concocting a fake story on GoFundMe that raised over $400,000 in donations, according to the Philadelphia Inquirer. Military vet Johnny Bobbitt, 36, pleaded guilty in court to conspiracy to commit money laundering. Bobbitt faces six to 30 months in prison for this charge.Katelyn McClure, 28, admitted to one count of conspiracy to commit wire fraud. She's looking at up to 33 months in a federal pen. According to the Inquirer, what's even better is Bobbitt, McClure and her former boyfriend Mark D'Amico are still staring at conspiracy and theft-by-deception charges in a pending case brought by Burlington County prosecutors.The three amigos are accused of suckering 14,000 donors around the world who gave money to help Bobbitt get off the streets. Dumb, dumber and dumbest told donors Bobbitt came to McClure's rescue when she ran out of gas on an exit on Philly's I-95 one chilly night in fall of 2017.The story touched hearts as it instantly went viral, with the trio even going on national television to help sell the lie.   Too bad it all started to go haywire after Bobbitt sued the couple for not getting his fair share of the loot. Prosecutors say D'Amico and McClure blew the money on a BMW, a trip to Sin City, and trips to casinos and Disney parks. Disney parks!? Classy. D'Amico was not in court with Bobbitt and McClure, and federal prosecutors have not commented on their plans. Whatever they are, can't be good for D'Amico.Lesson of the dayif it sounds too good to be true...]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 01:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/09/3793762/3793762_42FC77BF93AE45038DD7160358FC602C_190309_3793762_Homeless_man__NJ_woman_admit_to_GoFundMe_scam_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FA5/6C0/FA56C0A8D32D9176D54756E566721875.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, GoFundMe, GoFundMe scam, homeless man GoFundMe scam, Johnny Bobbitt, Katelyn McClure, scam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794910</guid>
      <title>Man proves hipsters look alike by mistaking hipster photo as himself</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  An angry bro threatened to sue a magazine after claiming his photo was used in an article, only to later learn that it wasn't actually him.According to CBC, MIT Technology Review published an article in February on the "hipster effect", a phenomenon in which anticonformists all end up looking the same. With the article came a Getty stock photo of a stereotypical bearded hipster decked out in flannel and a beanie, which pissed off a reader claiming the photo was of him.On Twitter, editor-in-chief Gideon Lichfield wrote that the man accused them of slandering him by implying he was a hipster, and threatened to sue.He even had some unkind words about the study, which was simply a mathematical model explaining how folks who turn away from mainstream fashion will see their individual style choices sync up eventually.All in all, nothing scandalous, unflattering, or even remotely controversial.The publication contacted Getty Images to check that everything was A-ok, which in turn prompted Getty's legal team to dig into the matter.Turns out the model in the photo didn't have the same name as the angry emailer. And when Lichfield's team wrote back to the dude saying as much, he conceded, but didn't offer up an apology.So ironically, by misidentifying himself as the hipster in the photo, the man ended up proving the study's premise true. Guess that's 1 point for science and a glaring 0 for the beard.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/11/3794910/3794910_2D996481F2F145098176BCD52AD40DBF_190311_3794910_Man_proves_hipsters_look_alike_by_mistaking_hips_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BEB/004/BEB0040E3EF669B4E28CB97B7D05B727.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hipster effect, MIT tech review, angry man, hipster study, mistaken identity, wrong photo, wrong hipster, all hipsters look alike, hipsters look alike]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794887</guid>
      <title>Ethiopian Airlines flight crashes, killing all 157 on board</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BISHOFTU, ETHIOPIA  An Ethiopian Airlines plane headed for Nairobi crashed minutes after take-off on Sunday, killing all 157 people on board. According to Reuters, Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 left Bole Airport in Addis Ababa at 8:38 a.m. local time, before losing contact with the control tower at 8:44 a.m. According to data published by FlightRadar24, the plane took off in good weather and clear visibility and struggles to ascend at a stable speed. According to data published by FlightRadar24 on Twitter, during the first three minutes of flight, the vertical speed was unstable after take-off. According to chief executive of the airline Tewolde GebreMariam, the pilot had sent out a distress call and was cleared to return to the airport. After losing contact with air traffic controllers, the plane crashed into the ground near Bishoftu, a town southeast of the capital. Passengers from 33 countries were aboard the flight, said GebreMariam. According to Reuters, the aircraft, a 737 MAX 8, is the same Boeing model as the Lion Air flight that crashed in the Java Sea after take-off from Jakarta on Oct. 29, killing all 189 people on board.Boeing has said it is sending a technical team to help with the Ethiopian-led crash investigation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 12:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/11/3794887/3794887_51948B7888224DAAB833371B4B63AB57_190311_3794887_Ethiopian_Airlines_flight_crashes__killing_all_1_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C26/8AE/C268AE289F7258F4772F16ED06B88F81.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Ethiopian Airlines, Ethiopian Airlines crash, Boeing 737 MAX 8, Boeing 737 crash, Boeing 737 MAX 8 crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794799</guid>
      <title>China building water absorbent 'sponge cities'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA  China is fixing faulty drainage systems, urban flooding and water scarcity by building 'sponge cities', reports The Guardian.  Cities in China are facing many obstacles including rapid population growth, urbanization and climate change. That being said, water has been one of its main problems, particularly faulty drainage systems, urban flooding and water scarcity.China's solution to this? Building water absorbent cities. Let us explain.In 2013, China announced that its major cities would undergo water infrastructure development that would enable them to absorb and process water. The on-going project is called the Sponge City program and began in the Central City of Wuhan in Hubei province.All cities participating in the program have to guarantee that 20 percent of their urban areas have sponge features by 2020. These sponge features must be able to retain 70 percent of the city's stormwater, reports The Guardian.These sponge features include rain gardens, green space, artificial wetlands, swales and new drainage systems. In the city of Wuhan, 20 percent of the city's urban land would cover roughly 170 square kilometers out of its total urban area of 860 square kilometers.The program currently includes 30 cities. The new target requires them to ensure that 80 percent of their urban land will be capable of absorbing and re-using rain and stormwater.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 09:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/11/3794799/3794799_F2C1EAB5E3CC4BFDB3A952CF3170364E_190311_3794799_China_building_water_absorbent__sponge_cities__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D5D/007/D5D0072595B76EB48C727DDFE373491F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china flood management, china urban planning, china sponge cities, china sponge city, wuhan china, china building sponge cities, environmental engineering, green cities, green city, eco city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794795</guid>
      <title>NASA preparing for first all-female space walk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAIKONUR, KAZAKHSTAN  On March 29 NASA will conduct the first all-female spacewalk in history, reports Interesting Engineering. What a perfect way to end Women's History Month!Christina Koch and Anne McClain will be part of Expedition 59, which will also be supported on the ground by a team of women, with Mary Lawrence and Kristen Facciol serving as lead flight director and lead spacewalk flight controller.Women make up less than 11 percent of over 500 people who have been to space. Before this spacewalk, expedition teams had always been all-male or mixed.NASA calls spacewalks EVA's which stands for extravehicular activity. Spacewalks are conducted mainly for maintenance, conducting experiments or testing new equipment.McClain and Koch were both selected by NASA in 2013 and each was one of 6,100 applicants. Their class was the first in NASA history that had an equal number of male and female candidates.McClain is a major in the U.S. Army and a pilot and Koch is an electrical engineer who has worked on expeditions in the South Pole and the Arctic. Can you imagine what their resumes look like?The expedition will be a first for both women. McClain is already aboard the ISS as part of Expedition 58 but this will be her first spacewalk. For Koch, it will be her first spaceflight.And for all women on Earth, this is a giant leap for womankind.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 09:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/11/3794795/3794795_121F9100DF8C49788C91D6051DA47230_190311_3794795_NASA_preparing_for_first_all_female_space_walk_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BD5/6BB/BD56BBA246DEC2C887D6F17F2F2710D9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa all female space walk, nasa space walk, nasa all female team, nasa all female astronauts, nasa female astronauts, nasa all women team, nasa women, nasa historic spacewalk, nasa womens history, nasa women in nasa]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794776</guid>
      <title>New AI tech can 'read' your expressions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS  New tech developed by a US-based AI company can scan your face and read your emotions.Affectiva has developed emotional detection technology that can be used to translate human facial expressions. This technology uses two main techniques: computer vision and supervised learning, The Guardian reports.Computer vision is used to clearly identify facial expressions while supervised learning is used to train the algorithm to recognize expressions it has already seen.The company has already gathered data from 7.5 million faces in 87 countries, according to Affectiva's website.The company uses EMFACS or Emotion Facial Action Coding System to recognize facial expressions such as a scowling face for anger or a smiling face for happiness.The Guardian quotes Meredith Whittaker, from the research institute AI Now, as saying that recruiting companies and schools are already using this technique to assess facial expressions of candidates or students.She added that the technology could harm an individual if the analysis isn't completely accurate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 09:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/11/3794776/3794776_102F1F45BA9645ED9115C928A30F242D_190311_3794776_New_AI_tech_can__read__your_expressions_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A31/B32/A31B3240FB4EAFE44FE02EAA7B51C55E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, AI, technology, surveillance, facial emotions, surveillance technology, Affectiva, affectiva ai, affectiva emotion recognition, affectiva emotion ai, artificial intelligence, Ai emotions, artificial emotional intelligence, artificial emotional intelligence affectiva]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794691</guid>
      <title>Chinese guy throws coins in plane engine for good luck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANQING, CHINA  A Lucky Air flight had some bad luck after a guy chucked a few coins at the engine before the flight for good luck. According to a Lucky Air Weibo post, Flight 8L9960 from Anqing to Kunming on Feb. 17 had to be scrapped after ground crew found two coins on the ground near the left engine. After the crew made an announcement, a 28-year-old male passenger named Lu ratted on himself and said he had tossed the coinage at the plane to keep the flight safe. The flight was immediately canceled with all 162 passengers minus Lu having to wait until the following day to be rebooked for flights to Kunming.  Lu was detained by the airport authorities. Lucky Air says the fortunate incident cost them twenty grand and have said they plan to take legal action against Lu. Funny thing is, this isn't even the first time this has happened. According to the Weibo article, this is at least number four, which everyone knows in Chinese is super lucky.The Lucky Air post then actually went on to explain the importance of engines and why they are allergic to coinsyikes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 06:23:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/11/3794691/3794691_A6871141B7D74C9B943FAC5DFA9FEF26_190311_3794691_Chinese_guy_throws_coins_in_plane_engine_for_goo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E49/21D/E4921DC9E9F910AE11B978198AD868F8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Lucky Air, Lucky Air China, Lucky Air China flight canceled, Chinese passenger, Lucky Air Weibo]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3794649</guid>
      <title>Berlin pursues 'sponge city' plan to deal with climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERLIN  As heatwaves and urban flooding become increasingly common across northern Europe, Berlin's local government is pursuing a "sponge city" approach to address the effects of climate change.According to a report by Deutsche Welle, municipal officials are taking steps to transform Berlin into an urban sponge to allow nature itself to help cool temperatures and reduce runoff from storms.Moss and grass are being planted on rooftops to absorb rainwater. Buildings are being painted in light colors to reflect heat instead of absorbing it.Carlo Becker, the architect of Berlin's Sponge City strategy, explained to Bloomberg that the idea is to use rain water to cool the city naturally by imitating the natural water cycle.The city also plans to add more green spaces and urban wetlands to efficiently absorb rain water.Heike Stock, the official in charge of managing the program, told Deutsche Welle the idea of the urban sponge is to "avoid sealing up too much of the ground surface with concrete or tarmac" and to allow water to be absorbed into the ground through permeable surfaces.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 04:43:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/11/3794649/3794649_2B099E29948E4539AB32CD1D5BC8E55E_190311_3794649_Berlin_pursues__sponge_city__plan_to_deal_with_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ABC/873/ABC8739EC3592B6E9495E6B47B8C90E0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, germany, berlin, sponge city, architecture, german architecture, sponge city berlin, sponge city germany, sponge city concept, sponge city project, germany architecture, futuristic architecture, futuristic architecture design, climate change, transforming berlin, urban sponge, urban planning, urban development]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795463</guid>
      <title>All you need to know about the Boeing 737 Max 8</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED STATES  The United States has told airlines the Boeing 737 Max 8 is safe to fly as investigators found two black box recorders from Sunday's downed Ethiopian Airlines jet, according to Reuters. According to Reuters, China and Indonesia have both grounded their 737 Max 8 fleets on Monday, citing safety concerns. Investigators in Ethiopia found two black box recorders early on Monday that will help authorities figure out what brought the plane down in a crash that killed 157 people. The accident comes months after the same model jet crashed in Indonesia killing 189 people. The 737 Max 8 is a single-aisle plane that has a quieter cabin, more legroom for passengers and was designed to be more fuel efficient. The plane measures 39.52 meters long, with a wingspan of 35.9 meters. It is equipped with LEAP-1B engines and has a range of 6,550 kilometers.  According to the New York Times, the 200-seat Boeing 737 Max 8 has been a popular plane after being introduced in 2017, with more than 4,000 planes ordered in the first six months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 11:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/12/3795463/3795463_97326A61CA43456FBEFD4545038C44DF_190312_3795463_All_you_need_to_know_about_the_Boeing_737_Max_8_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/38B/4A5/38B4A520E60AC44A84A21E0D43A3D392.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing, Boeing 737 Ethiopian Airlines, 737 Max 8]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795438</guid>
      <title>Paraglider nails landing only to get nailed by attacking kangaroo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANBERRA, AUSTRALIA  A paraglider in Australiaaffectionately known as the Florida Down Underwas given a proper welcome by a couple of kangaroos. In a hilarious clip posted to Twitter by SBS News, the high flyer is seen touching down after a two hour journey. According to ITV News, Paraglider Dundee came down, sticking a nice landing in a national park, when he immediately gets greeted by two kangaroos. The paraglider offers a friendly, "What's up skip?" However, it's clear one of the kangaroos is in no mood for cheeky puns, so the joey pops him twice. The marsupials then decided to get their hop on and bounce after messing with the paraglider. What's even better, there was no phone reception in the Namadgi National Park, so dude had to pack up his paraglider and hoof it for several miles before he was able to call someone to come get him.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 11:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/12/3795438/3795438_FDB1F32C06E94A7691DD0174C41BD52F_190312_3795438_Paraglider_nails_landing_only_to_get_nailed_by_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2F0/E44/2F0E44DCD84484531ACC6F482FFF4F32.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, paraglider, paraglider hit by kangaroo, paraglider attacked by kangaroo, Australia, Australia kangaroos, kangaroo attacks paraglider]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795264</guid>
      <title>Northern Red Sea coral expected to survive despite global warming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EILAT, ISRAEL  Coral reefs near the Israeli city of Eilat are thriving despite years of extensive farm fishing and climate change.Scientists in Israel have found that coral reefs in the northern Red Sea are unusually  resistant to rising sea temperatures and acidification, according to a study published in the Journal of Experimental Biology last month.Coral in the Red Sea had been damaged by cages that were used for fish farming from 1995 to 2008. The cages have since been removed and the coral has flourished, even as coral reefs are in decline nearly everywhere else around the world.Researchers at the Inter-University Institute for Marine Sciences in Eilat theorize that the coral's resistance came about due to natural selection 18,000 years ago, when corals that were able to survive in warmer water migrated from the Indian Ocean through the Bab al-Mandab strait, where water temperatures were higher.The Associated Press quotes Jacqueline De La Cour, from the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration's Coral Reef Watch, as saying this gives us hope that species would be able to adapt to survive.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 07:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/12/3795264/3795264_B6B2BA763E9841FEA3810B7B6C8FD63F_190312_3795264_Northern_Red_Sea_coral_expected_to_survive_despi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7DF/D79/7DFD79E8FA354EBBC535349E29F7AC63.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, israel, coral reef, red sea coral reef, abandoned oil pipeline, israel coral reef, israel coral, eilat israel coral reef, eilat, coral reef conservation, global warming, climate change, coral reef surviving rising temperatures, rising sea temperatures, acidification]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795231</guid>
      <title>Facebook removes (then restores) Senator's anti-big tech ads</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook had removed ads placed by Warren's presidential campaign which called for tech companies, such as Facebook, to be broken up before the ads were restored, Politico reports.Warren and her team released an article on Medium last week, which says that tech giants have too much power these days and have "bulldozed competition."It also says that companies such as Amazon, Google and Facebook must be broken up to promote fair competition in the marketplace.Warren also pointed out that these companies have made money out of selling private information and have hurt small businesses and "stifled innovation" in the process.To promote this campaign policy, Warren released the ads onto Facebook and elsewhere.Facebook initially took down the ads saying that it "goes against Facebook's advertising policies."Politico quotes a spokesperson from Facebook saying that the company has since restored the ads "in the interest of allowing robust debate."Warren posted a tweet saying: "Curious why I think FB has too much power? Let's start with their ability to shut down a debate over whether FB has too much power."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 06:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/12/3795231/3795231_C0AD2A6C2DEC4C1DB53DCD03CDE1E65D_190312_3795231_Facebook_removes__then_restores__Senator_s_anti__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7D6/2EF/7D62EFBEC5EF759B25EFBA5D87518347.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, facebook, whatsapp, instagram, elizabeth warren, elizabeth warren ads on facebook, facebook controversies, facebook scandals, facebook deletes ads, elizabeth warren facebook, facebook scandals 2019, elizabeth warren ads facebook, facebook political ads, advertisements, political advertisements, facebook takes down Elizabeth warren ads on facebook, elizabeth warren presidential campaign, facebook advertising policies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795122</guid>
      <title>Chinese man's eyeball pops out after fall, doesn't realize till later</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JINAN, CHINA  A man from eastern China probably didn't see this coming when he knocked a few back while at home and slipped, SEE-riously injuring his eye. According to a Pear Video report, the spectacle occurred last Monday night when a 26-year-old guy from the Lixia district in Jinan took a tumble inside his house and knocked himself outamong other things. It's all fun and games until someone loses an eyeshould probably be some kind of Chinese proverb in this case.  His family found him the next day passed out in a pool of blood, so they rushed him to the clinic. Unfortunately, they didn't notice he was sporting a new Nick Fury look. He was later transferred to the Shandong Qianfoshan Hospital, where doctors realized something didn't look right with the man. Family members rushed home and called the hospital once they put eyes on the missing eyeball, according to Dr. Ma Baofeng from the ophthalmology department talking to local reporters. According to the doctor, the eye had been on its own for at least six hours before the patient showed up at the hospital, making it impossible to pop back in. It's still unclear what caused the eye-popping incident, but you can probably blame it on the alcohol.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 03:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/12/3795122/3795122_CF8D47106C6D4C86A3FB6E0800D87422_190312_3795122_Chinese_man_s_eyeball_pops_out_after_fall__doesn_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5D5/991/5D59913F7CED7B6394AD09E9A7A78C78.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, Chinese man, Chinese man slips, Chinese man falls, Chinese man eye]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795111</guid>
      <title>Mercury in Retrograde explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  When Mercury is in retrograde, it appears as if the planet is moving backwards when viewed from Earth's sky.This is because Mercury completes an orbit faster than Earth does, according to reports from NASA.According to Vox, as Mercury passes Earth, Earth's line of sight will shift so that Mercury will appear to retrograde for around three weeks when viewed from our planet.This is because both Mercury and Earth are orbiting the solar system at different speeds at the same time, creating an illusion that the planet is moving backwards.Mercury is currently retrograding from March 5 to March 28 and will retrograde two more times later this year, according to Newsweek.Dr. Mark Hammergren, an astronomer at Adler Planetarium, told Mental Floss that there is zero evidence that a planet retrograding is something we should worry about.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 03:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/12/3795111/3795111_A1581CF1D3A042049686E5A2B6883E29_190312_3795111_Mercury_in_Retrograde_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F8/5EB/8F85EB406D21968350C3AC9F9C194CBC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mercury, retrograde, mercury retrograde, mercury in retrograde, astronomy, mercury retrograde 2019, mercury retrograde explained, mercury retrograde explained without astrology, mercury retrograde astronomy, what is mercury retrograde, astrology,retrograde motion, planet retrograding, solar system, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795092</guid>
      <title>Woman attacked by jaguar after crossing barrier to take selfie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LITCHFIELD PARK, ARIZONA  A woman in Arizona learned the hard way that zoo barriers are there for a reason, after a close encounter with jaguar claws.CNN reports that the lady, who's in her 30s, was at the jaguar enclosure at Arizona's Wildlife World Zoo, Aquarium, and Park on Saturday, when she crossed the barrier for a photo op.She was attempting to take a selfie when the female black jaguar whose cage she was cozying up to pounced and swiped at her with its claws.According to ABC15, Adam Wilkerson and his family heard her screaming and saw the jaguar claws-deep in her arm. Wilkerson's mom shoved a water through the cage to distract the cat, and he pulled the woman back as soon as the claws were off.Paramedics were called to treat a nasty gash on the lady's left arm. She was taken to the hospital to get stitches, but was released the same day.Needless to say, there was little to no sympathy for the selfie-taker on social media, and most were more concerned that the jaguar would be put down for the attack.The zoo was firmly on their cat's side, and announced on Twitter that she'd keep all nine of her lives, since really, it was the human's fault.Though to the human's credit, she did apologize to zoo officials for all the negative publicity from her ill-advised photo op.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 02:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/12/3795092/3795092_9A3FD5235FD54465A7C9182ACEAD69B8_190312_3795092_Woman_attacked_by_jaguar_after_crossing_barrier__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/557/163/557163F2D83C5879FE103B3B2BD16420.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, jaguar claws woman, jaguar claws, black jaguar, wildlife world zoo, woman survives jaguar attack, jaguar attacks woman taking selfie, selfie fail, deadly selfies, stupid selfies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796135</guid>
      <title>North Korea's fake elections leave Dear Fat Leader off the ballot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA  North Korea just held its rubber stamp parliamentary elections and shockerthe authoritarian leadership won in a landslide.According to the BBC, one interesting thing about the fake elections was that Kim Jong-un did not appear on the ballot. If confirmed, this is the first time a North Korean dictator has not run for its pretend parliament. The regime uses the elections to legitimize its iron grip over the country, much in the same way the China uses fake elections to elect their rubber stamp National People's Congress.In North Korea's ballot, each voting slip has only one state-approved candidate on it. Well that makes deciding who to vote for easier. State media announced the names of the 687 deputies selected to the Supreme People's Assembly on Tuesday. According to the BBC, voting was mandatory for all North Koreans above the age of 17. The play parliament is chosen every five years and the turnout is always around 100 percent. But it's clear from this year's turnout that no rigging took place as the turnout was only 99.99 percent. According to NK's official news agency KCNA, that's because some were "abroad or working in oceans" so were unable to participate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 13:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3796135/3796135_5978C873F9AB401F91FD446E1B84B16C_190313_3796135_North_Korea_s_fake_elections_leave_Dear_Fat_Lead_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C99/BAA/C99BAA6D1243C81268E8AE6D476A87F5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Korea, North Korea elections, North Korea parliamentary elections, Kim Jong Un, Supreme People's Assembly]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796102</guid>
      <title>Celebrities and coaches charged in college scam</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS  Celebrities, CEOs and college coaches from elite universities are charged for participating in a college admissions bribery scam, reports the Associated Press.Fifty people, including Oscar nominee Felicity Huffman and Lori Loughlin from Full House as well as CEOs and college coaches, were involved in a bribery scam in which dirty rich parents paid their kids' way into top ranking schools.Among these universities are Yale, Stanford, the University of Southern California, Wake Forest and Georgetown. The cases span from 2011 to 2019.During a press conference, FBI Special Agent Joseph Bonavolonta said the parents spent anywhere between $200,000 and $6.5 million for their children's admission.According to a cooperating witness, Loughlin allegedly paid $500,000 so both of her daughters could be enlisted as recruits for the USC rowing team. The thinking behind this was that it could help facilitate their admission. Neither had experience in the sport.According to court documents, Loughlin's husband even provided a cooperating witness implicated in the scam with staged photos of their daughters on a rowing machine for the application.Their younger daughter, Olivia Giannulli, who is a 'lifestyle' Youtuber with nearly 2 million subscribers was under fire just last year for posting a video in which she said, "I do want the experience of like game days, partying  I don't really care about school, as you guys all know."Olivia has faced a lot of backlash after the allegations of bribery became public. On an Amazon sponsored-video where she gives a tour of her USC dormitory, a YouTube user commented, "Dorm room bought by Amazon, college admissions bought by mommy."Court documents show that Laughlin and her husband were told to say that their payment was a donation that would go to underserved kids. Both their daughters were accepted to USC.Huffman, on the other hand, paid a $15,000 bribe to alter her older daughter's SAT scores. The bribe was also disguised as a donation.No students were charged according to Andrew Lelling, the US attorney for Massachusetts. In a press conference, Lelling said, "For every student admitted through fraud, an honest, genuinely talented student was rejected."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 12:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3796102/3796102_DF694D04079041089F4173F6EF291E70_190313_3796102_Celebrities_and_coaches_charged_in_college_scam_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8BE/9C6/8BE9C6943895065CDDEC49DD723FF0FA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, america's largest college scam, college scams, admissions scam, college admissions scam, college prep, Lori laughlin, Felicity Huffman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795958</guid>
      <title>Doomed Ethiopian Airlines plane smoked, rattled before crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ADDIS ABABA, ETHIOPIA  Witnesses have come out to describe what they saw moments before the crash of Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302.The CEO of Ethiopian Airlines told CNN that pilots of Flight 302 reported 'flight control problems' to air traffic control. This suggests the plane wasn't responding to inputs, and pilots were losing control of the aircraft.Witnesses interviewed by Reuters said they had seen smoke billowing out behind the plane, and heard a loud rattling noise, like straining and shaking metal.The farmer whose field the plane crashed in said it made a sharp turn above a field of panicked cows, while another eyewitness claimed it was trailing clothes and papers as well as smoke.The aircraft was trying to climb and lift its nose, according to two other witnesses, but failed and crashed nose-first into the ground before then exploding.According to Reuters, the debris field was roughly the size of two soccer fields.Reuters reports that investigators have recovered the flight data recorder and cockpit voice recorder, which will be sent overseas for scrutiny. It's unclear at the moment where or when the data will be analyzed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 08:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3795958/3795958_897EA7FFCA934254B574E19E7AF97F37_190313_3795958_Doomed_Ethiopian_Airlines_plane_smoked__rattled__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AED/FE7/AEDFE7D51E6A310FE7592F332266AFC6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plane crash, ethiopia crash, ethiopian airlines crash, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing Max, Boeing, Ethiopian Airlines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795909</guid>
      <title>A second Boeing 737 Max goes down in less than a year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAKARTA, INDONESIA  Boeing is under scrutiny as two of its aircrafts have crashed in less than a year.In October of 2018, Lion Air flight JT610 flew from Jakarta and crashed in the waters off of Java."The aircraft was also a Boeing 737 Max 8 which ended up killing all 189 passengers and crew members aboard, according to the Washington Post.An investigative report release in November of last year says a malfunctioning sensor was one of the reasons the flight crashed.The aircraft's sensor sent faulty data to the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which caused an alert that the plane was in danger when it was not.This led the system to automatically position the plane's nose downward in order to prevent a stall.Since the reading was erroneous, the pilot had to struggle to correct the plane's position.The pilot was unsuccessful in his attempts to save the plane, which crashed into the sea 11 minutes after take off.According to the Washington Post, investigators are looking to see if there are similarities between the Lion Air crash and the recent plane crash in Ethiopia as both flights crashed shortly after take-off and at low altitudes.China, Indonesia and Singapore have now banned all 737 Max 8 aircrafts from their airspaces in the wake of the two plane crashes, The New York Times reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 08:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3795909/3795909_4943780F73D048778DE52C5100DBA9FB_190313_3795909_A_second_Boeing_737_Max_goes_down_in_less_than_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/08F/DA8/08FDA8D748B2281DF7621650ECEAE86F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Indonesia plane crash, plane crash indonesia, indonesia plane crash survivors, lion air, indonesia plane crash 2018, java plane crash, jakarta, boeing, lion air flight 610, boeing 737 Max, lion air indonesia, lion air crash, lion air crash 2018, lion air crash latest news, lion air crash animation, plane crash, boeing 737 Max 8 crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795884</guid>
      <title>US orders Boeing to improve 737 MAX 8 after two crashes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.   Now US regulators are demanding Boeing make modifications to improve the aircraft, reports Al Jazeera.   The US Federal Aviation Administration is demanding Boeing make improvements toanti-stalling software and the aircrafts' maneuvering system. The FAA has given Boeing until the end of April to finalize the improvements.In an open letter to civil aviation authorities, the FAA stated that Boeing is also updating training requirements and flight crew manuals to go with the new updates to the maneuvering system. These updates include changes to the airplane flight manual, flight crew operations manual and airplane maintenance manual.According to CNN, some airlines are temporarily suspending 737 MAX 8s from flying following last Sunday's crash. These include airlines from China, Singapore, Indonesia, Mexican airline Aeromexico, Argentine airline Aerolneas Argentinas, Cayman Airways and Comair Airways. American Airlines, Southwest Airlines among other airways have announced they will not suspend the aircraft. According to the FAA, there are currently 387 737 MAX 8 and 9 jets flying worldwide, 74 of which are registered in the U.S.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 07:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3795884/3795884_47A0BFB923A84AB39EE9E48C282FC430_190313_3795884_US_orders_Boeing_to_improve_737_MAX_8_after_two__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1B4/318/1B43181D6C08F39F6AFC2AB8E02D24E6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,Ethiopian Airlines,Ethiopian Airlines crash,Boeing 737 MAX 8,Boeing 737 crash,Boeing 737 MAX 8 crash,Indonesia plane crash,plane crash indonesia,indonesia plane crash survivors,lion air,indonesia plane crash 2018,java plane crash,jakarta,boeing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795839</guid>
      <title>NYC to open tallest observation deck in the Western Hemisphere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  New York City is set to open the tallest observation deck in the Western Hemisphere at 335 meters, reports CNN. The newest addition to New York's skyline costs a whopping $28 billion and will include more than 100 retail shops, cultural venues among other amenities. New York's newest skyscraper, named Edge, will be the tallest outdoor observation deck in the Western Hemisphere and the fifth-tallest in the world.Edge will stand at over 1,100 feet tall, around 335 meters. Its biggest attraction is a 7,500-square-foot or 697-square-meter observation deck that protrudes from the building. The edges of the deck are lined by 6-foot-tall glass walls, providing visitors with a full view of New York City's skyline.Once opened, Edge's observation deck will stand taller than the Empire State Building and the Top of the Rock at the Rockefeller Center, which measure 1,050 feet or 320 meters above street level and 850 feet or 260 meters above street level respectively.The building is set to open in the first quarter if 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 06:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3795839/3795839_95602162B40144EAB3E25878DB0ACC76_190313_3795839_NYC_to_open_tallest_observation_deck_in_the_West_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7BA/FD9/7BAFD903AB645DFE821954A27B87CD30.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tallest observation deck in the Western Hemisphere, tallest observation deck, tallest building, tallest skyscraper, new york city buildings, tallest outdoor observation deck, tall buildings, new york city, new york observation deck]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795821</guid>
      <title>Mystery database lists breed ready status of 1.8M Chinese women</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Weird things have come out of China, but probably none as disturbing as this list straight out of The Handmaid's Tale.According to the Guardian, Dutch internet expert Victor Gevers was searching for open databases in China when he stumbled on an insecure data cache with info on over 1.8 million Chinese women.Screenshots Gevers posted of the database to Twitter shows fields labelled in English. It details names, addresses, phone numbers, and marital status, but also lists oddly specific and troubling information, such as location and whether or not they're 'breed ready.' Gevers said on Twitter that the women's ages range from 15 to 94, with the average being 32. The youngest breed ready lady is 18, the oldest 39. Eighty-nine percent are single, 10 percent divorced, and 1 percent widowed. More than 80 percent of them also live in Beijing.There's also fields in the dataset labelled "Political" and "hasvideo," followed by links to Facebook  which is still banned in China.According to Gevers' Twitter account, the database has been unavailable as of Monday afternoon.There's no telling what kind of organization the database was made for, but folks on Twitter are speculating that it could be a government registry, or a dating app.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 06:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3795821/3795821_56B5115B2730429DAAE91B6E84AD5B58_190313_3795821_Mystery_database_lists_breed_ready_status_of_1_8_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0EE/756/0EE756199F225024F08338D589CF17EC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, breedready, breed ready, chinese database, china birth rate, china database, data breach, chinese women, open database, database]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795807</guid>
      <title>NASA spots hopping water on the surface of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOON  Data from NASA's lunar orbiter has shed light on water movement on the moon's surface.According to NASA, scientists previously thought moon was arid, with water existing mainly as ice pockets in craters near the poles. But in recent years, they have identified surface water in sparse molecule populations bound to regolith, or lunar soil.Observations gathered by an instrument on NASA's Lunar Reconnaissance Orbiter indicate that water moves around the dayside of the moon.Water molecules remain bound to the regolith until surface temperatures peak during lunar noon. They then thermally desorb and either bounce to a nearby location that is cold enough, or stick to the moon's weak atmosphere until temperatures drop and they can return to the surface.Scientists have hypothesized that hydrogen ions in the solar wind may be generating most of the moon's water. But as the supply doesn't decrease even when the moon is shielded from solar winds, it suggests water builds up over time instead of raining directly down.A paper detailing the findings has been published in the journal Geophysical Research LettersPlanetary Science Institute senior scientist and lead author Amanda Hendrix says lunar water can be used to make fuel or for radiation shielding or thermal management. This could make future missions more affordable as these materials don't need to be launched from Earth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 05:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3795807/3795807_C6AF674A4C1C4294A6C54FC3A9E90B4A_190313_3795807_NASA_spots_hopping_water_on_the_surface_of_the_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/665/8F8/6658F8DDDD2591CFE101B8E902126937.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, NASA, moon, hopping water, water on moon, moving water, lunar water, lunar orbiter, lunar reconnaissance orbiter, LRO]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3795763</guid>
      <title>Man survives being swallowed by whale</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORT ELIZABETH, SOUTH AFRICA  A South African diver almost became the modern-day Jonas after being swallowed by a 15-meter-whale, reports Sky News.Dive tour operator Rainer Schimpf was filming a sardine run off the coast of South Africa's Port Elizabeth Harbor. His goal was to shoot some sharks hunting fish. Little did he know he'd be the one turning into chow.Schimpf told Sky News that as he was concentrated on looking for the sharks when the water around him suddenly turned black. Out of the blueliterallyhe felt a weird pressure on his hips. That's when he realized he was inside the mouth of a Bryde's whale.Bryde's whales are huge, they can weigh up to 20 tons and just one flick of this beast's flipper could easily crack some ribs. Knowing this, Schimpf decided to just wait  the big fella out and see if it would eventually let him go.Lucky for Schimpf, he didn't taste like krill. He resurfaced after the whale spat him out feeling a bit dazed and confused. His first reaction? Asking the team photographer if he got the shot."It's important to note that whales are not blood-thirsty human-eating machines. In fact, the whale Schimpf encountered was probably as confused as he was when it munched down on him.Whales are normally quite peaceful, eating shrimp, crabs, anchovies, mackerel, sardines, and other small fish and crustaceans. Okaymaybe these little guys don't think whales are so peaceful, but you get the idea.That being said, it might have been Schimp's quick reflexes that saved him. Schimpf told Sky News, 'there was not really time for fear at that moment, just pure instinct.']]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 03:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/13/3795763/3795763_CF8FCFCE00D44C31AAA15E4094D73BF4_190313_3795763_Man_survives_being_swallowed_by_whale_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C31/6D1/C316D110049011E125A6F1E286F13B24.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, diver swallowed by whale, man swallowed by whale, Diver Is Nearly Swallowed By A Whale, whale swallows man, whale eats man, whale swallows man, man almost eaten by whale]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796914</guid>
      <title>U.S. grounds Boeing 737 Max aircraft after new evidence</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. and Canada have joined a growing list of countries that have banned the controversial Boeing 737 Max 8 aircraft, following two fatal crashes that took the lives of 346 people.CBS reports that Canada's transport authority banned all Boeing 737 Max 8 and 9 planes from its airspace on Tuesday. A day later, the U.S. announced it would also be grounding the aircrafts.President Trump told reporters at the White House that planes currently in the air will go their destinations, and then be grounded until further notice.According to CNBC, the Federal Aviation Administration cited new satellite evidence showing that the flight track of Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 was similar to the Lion Air flight that crashed in October.According to CBS, investigators of the Lion Air crash believe pilots battled the aircraft's automated anti-stall system, which repeatedly pushed the plane's nose down, possibly due to wrong information from sensors.Whether or not the same is true for the Ethiopian Airlines crash has yet to be determined.CNBC reports that investigators have recovered Flight 302's black boxes, and will be sending them to France for analysis this week. Over 40 countries and regions, including the EU, China, India, Australia, Mexico, and Brazil, had already grounded the 737 Max 8 and 9 due to safety concerns days before the U.S. decision.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 17:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/15/3796914/3796914_BC50479A71894734838269B242A940FD_190315_3796914_U_S__grounds_Boeing_737_Max_aircraft_after_new_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Boeing 737 Max, 737 Max 8, 737 Max 9, Ethiopian Airlines crash, Lion Air crash, Boeing 737 Max ban, plane crash, MCAS, anti-stall system]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796911</guid>
      <title>Dad beats son for perving around female dorm</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW TAIPEI CITY, TAIWAN  A son got the umbrella beating of a lifetime from dear old dad after he was caught creeping around the ladies' dorm.According to UDN, 24-year-old IT engineer Chen snuck into the female dorm at Taiwan's Tamkang University Friday night disguised as a woman.Photos from the New Taipei City Police Department show Chen wearing a long skirt and coat, wig, glasses, and a surgical mask. He also had a scarf around his neck to hide his Adam's apple.He wasn't a very convincing crossdresser, though, because students flagged his odd appearance and constant trips to the fourth floor bathroom. A couple of ladies also caught him trying to snap shots of them in the shower, and cornered him in a stall. They also alerted an instructor, who in turn called the cops.Officers picked the perv up and found he was carrying a pinhole camera with a memory card full of nasty voyeur shots. Naturally, they did what any self-respecting Asian cop would do, and called his folks.His old man was so pissed at his pervy ways that he chased him inside the police station and beat the crap outta him with an umbrella.Chen has been transferred to the Shilin District Prosecutor's Office, where he's facing charges of Offenses Against Privacy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 16:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/15/3796911/3796911_48232EAF36B3442A8F3D212C5C4A80A3_190315_3796911_Dad_beats_son_for_perving_around_female_dorm_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/418/E87/418E8799A2681801C54E2BBE91DCF2BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man dressed as woman, female dorm, pinhole camera, crossdressing man, man dressed as woman, bathroom perv, dad beats son with umbrella]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796771</guid>
      <title>China's Muslim concentration camps continue abuses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA  The U.S. State Department slammed human rights violations in China's Muslim concentration camps throughout Xinjiang as the worst "since the 1930s."According to Reuters, U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo brought up abuses by Iran, South Sudan, Nicaragua and China in the department's annual "Country Reports on Human Rights Practices," but told the press China was "in a league of its own when it comes to human rights violations."At the same briefing, Michael Kozak, head of the State Department's human rights and democracy bureau, commented on the abuses of Uighurs in Xinjiang saying, "rounding up, in some estimations  in the millions of people, putting them into camps, and torturing them, abusing them and trying to basically erase their culture and their religion and so on from their DNA. It's just remarkably awful."That's a pretty accurate description of Chinese society as a wholeremarkably awful.  China initially lied about the concentration camps, even though the entire world knew they were lying. Beijing then tried their typical sideshow antics of saying they had boarding schools rather than concentration camps. To be clear, even blind people can see they're concentration camps. The State Department report says Chinese goons have arbitrarily locked 800,000 to probably more than two million Uighurs, ethnic Kazakhs and other Muslims in camps with the sole purpose of erasing religious and ethnic identities.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/14/3796771/3796771_A5BD29FB4F724F6F85BC0D677EB9AD60_190314_3796771_China_s_Muslim_concentration_camps_continue_abus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5A0/95E/5A095E6855848F627A47B1183FE3E35A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China concentration camps, China human rights abuses, China Xinjiang right abuses, China Xinjiang detention centers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796762</guid>
      <title>Saudi plane hangs a uey after mom forgets baby at airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FORGETFUL SKIES  A flight on the way to Malaysia had to hang a uey back to Saudi Arabia after a mom realized she Home Aloned her kid at the airport.According to Gulf News, Flight SV832 was on its merry way to Kuala Lumpur when the pilot put in a request to head back to the airport in Jeddah when the rockstar mom told cabin crew she forgot her child. Apparently, the mother, in the process of getting from the boarding area at the terminal of the King Abdulaziz International Airport to the aircraft forgot one little thingher baby. In a video posted to YouTube, the pilot is heard asking an air traffic controller, "May God be with us. Can we come back?"   The guy in tower is then heard asking other colleagues what the proper protocol is for baby chilling at terminal with no mama. "The flight is requesting to come back," he tells someone else. "A passenger forgot her baby in the waiting area, the poor thing." Seriouslyand to think, it's only just beginning for this kid.  After a brief pause, the plane is given permission to return to the gate with the air traffic controller adding, "this is totally a new one for us." Upon returning to the gate, it's unclear if the mother remembered what they had turned around for.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 12:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/14/3796762/3796762_AADCF44BBF994333829D822FAC7DC519_190314_3796762_Saudi_plane_hangs_a_uey_after_mom_forgets_baby_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FC8/15A/FC815A94D642F75E8AF283E1323C0AF7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Saudi plane turns around, plane turns around, mom forgets, mom forgets airport]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796640</guid>
      <title>Flight delayed after Chinese passengers throw coins for luck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JINAN, CHINA  Chinese women were escorted off a flight for throwing good luck coins at the plane's engine before the trip, delaying the flight for two hours, reports Beijing News. There are several things you can do ensure your travel plans go smoothly. Print out copies of your passport, label your luggage, pack extra toiletries and oh...Don't throw coins into the plane's engine.Apparently, this isn't common knowledge. According to Beijing News, two women on board a Lucky Air flight from Jinan to Chengdu delayed the flight for two whole hours after being spotted tossing coins at the plane's engine like it was some sort of wishing well.Sure enough, nothing bad happened on their flight...because they were kicked off of it. After making sure the coinage hadn't wrecked the engines, airport authorities escorted the ladies off the plane.Lucky Air hasn't confirmed whether or not it will take legal action against the women. If they do, these ladies are going to have to drop some coin and lawyer up.China has had the good fortune to have this preflight ritual happen at least five times, three of which have happened on Lucky Air flights. Guess they are pretty lucky to keep getting such awesome passengers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 10:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/14/3796640/3796640_870FA4681B424DAE9C71DFE63CD438C2_190314_3796640_Flight_delayed_after_Chinese_passengers_throw_co_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D64/04A/D6404AAFB977998D8A759A92DAE8F244.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Lucky Air, Lucky Air China, Lucky Air China flight canceled, Chinese passenger, Lucky Air Weibo, woman throws coin in airplane engine, woman in airplane, lucky coin, woman throws coin in engine, coin engine]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796592</guid>
      <title>Facebook's big tech data deals are under criminal investigation: NYT</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook is now under criminal investigation by federal prosecutors for data-sharing deals it struck with other tech giants such as Amazon, Apple, Microsoft and Sony, according to the New York Times. Two anonymous sources told the New York Times that at least two high-profile electronic companies have been subpoenaed to provide records to a grand jury in New York. The files are said to concern the companies' partnerships with Facebook.Facebook had previously let companies view users' friends and contact information among other data, according to the New York Times. This information was sometimes given without consent. The social network says it has phased out most of these partnerships over the last two years.Facebook is also under investigation by the Federal Trade Commission for the Cambridge Analytica scandal where third-party apps were allowed access to access user data.According to the New York Times, Facebook could be hit with a multi-billion dollar fine for violating user privacy.The social network released a statement saying that they are quote "cooperating with investigators and take those probes seriously." They added that they have "provided testimonies," "answered questions" and will "continue to do so."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 09:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/14/3796592/3796592_256819BA43C94F52AECF3B87DE957A6E_190314_3796592_Facebook_s_big_tech_data_deals_are_under_crimina_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/78E/249/78E249F22BF49831A7F24D65FE91EBF3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, facebook, facebook scandals, facebook data, facebook data-sharing, facebook under criminal investigation, facebook privacy, facebook investigation, facebook user privacy, facebook data-sharing deals, tech companies, social media, facebook data deals, facebook sharing user information with other companies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796553</guid>
      <title>Japan's space agency and Toyota are making a moon car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN  Japan's space agency and Toyota are teaming up to build a lunar exploration vehicle as part of the country's plan to get astronauts on the moon by 2029, The Japan Times reports.Toyota and the Japan Aerospace Exploration Agency are to construct a pressurized self-driving moon rover that will use the car manufacturer's fuel cell vehicle technology.According to Forbes, a fuel cell vehicle or FCV uses a fuel cell of compressed hydrogen and oxygen. These molecules react with each other to create electricity for the vehicle.Toyota said in a press release, that these fuel cells only emit water and can generate a lot of energy.The rover will be six meters wide and 3.8 meters tall. This is around the size of two microbuses, according to a JAXA news release.With 13 cubic meters of space, the vehicle is expected to have a 2 to 4 passenger carry capacity.According to Toyota, the rover will be able to travel more than 10,000 km on the moon's surface. The country is planning a series of manned missions to the moon between 2029 and 2034, The Japan Times reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 08:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/14/3796553/3796553_23740A136C6D410888807A101602E599_190314_3796553_Japan_s_space_agency_and_Toyota_are_making_a_moo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ECF/AA9/ECFAA98FA9A084B38B6157A6A2490A96.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, japan, toyota, space, moon rover, japanese space agency, JAXA, JAXA and toyota, toyota space vehicle, space exploration, space, toyota concept vehicle, lunar exploration, space vehicle, toyota moon rover, japan toyota moon rover, JAXA toyota]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796315</guid>
      <title>Slovenian woman saws off  hand to get insurance payout</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LJUBLJANA, SLOVENIA   A woman in Slovenia is being accused of deliberately losing her hand in order to claim hundreds of thousands of euros in insurance money.According to the BBC, relatives took the 21-year-old to a hospital in January following what they claim was an accident with a circular saw while sawing branches.But the cops weren't buying it, instead accusing the lady and her family of insurance fraud.Police told ABC News that the woman had taken out five different insurance policies in the months leading up to her "accident" and would've gotten 400,000 or about $430,000 for her injury, with monthly payments of $3,388 for ten years.They believe the woman, with one of her accomplices, cut off her left hand just above the wrist and deliberately didn't bring it to the hospital to ensure a permanent disability. But they were foiled when doctors called the po-po to retrieve the hand, and then sewed it back on.The woman and a 29-year-old relative have both been detained, and could face up to 8 years in prison if convicted of insurance fraud.But hey, at least she's got her hand back.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 02:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/14/3796315/3796315_B2D89DB6D34A4568A7AA5691DE7E904C_190314_3796315_Slovenian_woman_saws_off__hand_to_get_insurance__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/540/F9A/540F9AC59900AFCF25B3C1162E221FE9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, insurance fraud, insurance fraud scheme, fake accident, staged accident, insurance scheme, severed hand, saw off hand, cut off hand, slovenia insurance fraud]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797371</guid>
      <title>Florida woman shoots boyfriend for snoring too loudly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COCOA, FLORIDA  A lady in Florida went crazy on her new boyfriend after a booze-fueled argument about his loud snoring.According to the arrest affidavit, Lorie Morin and Brett Allgood had been dating for all of three weeks when their night troubles came to a pretty violent head.Allgood was anything but a silent sleeper, and his super loud snoring disturbed Morin so much one night that she elbowed him in the ribs to wake him up. He spent the rest of the night on the couch.In an attempt to make it up to his girlfriend, he showed up the next day with flowers, chocolates, a bottle of her favorite rum, and snoring strips.Booze was maybe not the best idea though, because several rum cokes later, Morin suddenly started ramming into Allgood about his snoring.While he tried to leave to avoid a fight, crazy drunk lady picks up her shotgun and blasts him in the side. When the cops showed up, she fed them a fake sob story about the gun accidentally going off while they were packing stuff.Luckily, Allgood survived his shooting and later set the story straight. The cops arrested Morin after getting her to fess up to everything.According to court documents, the 47-year-old is being charged with attempted murder and aggravated battery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 12:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/15/3797371/3797371_7438D99B784B427BB166412D47578BFF_190315_3797371_Florida_woman_shoots_boyfriend_for_snoring_too_l_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A33/5F4/A335F4386D805A22D6853C6C4BF1A6E2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, snoring, loud snoring, accidental shooting, snore, loud snore, snoring too loudly, violent girlfriend]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797350</guid>
      <title>Taiwan implements one of the world's toughest bans on plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  The island nation of Taiwan is all set to implement a complete ban on plastic by 2030.According to Taiwan's Environmental Protection Administration, the government will limit the use of plastic by implementing a plastic ban in phases, and is encouraging the public to use reusable straws and bags to help combat plastic pollution.Starting later this year, stores are to be prohibited from providing in-store customers with single-use straws.In 2020, stores will face fines if they provide customers with disposable utensils. Stores will also be restricted from providing plastic straws for take-outs.Customers could choose to purchase plastic straws or bags if they are willing to pay extra to the store till 2025.By the year 2030, Taiwan's plastic ban will be fully implemented, with stores completely banned from providing any plastic bags, disposable utensils, plastic cups, bottles and straws.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 11:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/15/3797350/3797350_83D062D33F37479AB2B59E609220B9A3_190315_3797350_Taiwan_implements_one_of_the_world_s_toughest_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/504/7E1/5047E1DE6ED4216740E1040EDE4DCF6E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic, plastic pollution, taiwan, plastic ban, taiwan plastic ban, ban plastic movement, ban plastic straws movement, taiwan bans plastic straws, plastic pollution solution, restricting plastic, combat plastic pollution, plastic ban,  plastic ban taiwan, taiwanese plastic ban]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3796987</guid>
      <title>Recent 737 Max 8 crashes unrelated says aviation expert</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED STATES  Despite some similarities between the two recent Boeing 737 Max 8 crashes, aviation expert Peter Lemme talking to Scientific American believes they are unrelated.Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 crashed on Sunday shortly after takeoff killing all 157 people on board. The Boeing 737 Max 8 aircraft was the same type involved in the Indonesia Lion Air Flight 610 crash five months earlier. Both flights appeared to have difficulties sustaining a normal climb, and fell shortly after takeoff.A possible cause of the Indonesia crash was a malfunction in the automated anti-stalling feature called the Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, or MCAS. According to Scientific American, because Boeing outfitted the Max with bigger engines, their placement relative to the plane's center of gravity causes a tendency for the nose to tip upward. The MCAS is designed to automatically push the nose back down when this happens, preventing the aircraft from stalling, or losing lift.  In the case of Lion Air, experts suspect a faulty sensor may have triggered MCAS to engage when the plane was flying normally, causing the nose to repeatedly dip. Using data from FlightRadar24, Lemme studied how Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302 flew in the six minutes before disappearing from radar. With Flight 302, the plane got to 1,000 feet, which at that point lost about 400 feet of altitude. The plane then flew level for about 30 seconds, about 500 to 600 feet above the ground, which according to Lemme is not normal.  The airspeed continued to increase to over 300 knots at under 1,000 feet above ground. After that 30-second period, the plane began to climb normally until they disappeared from radar. Now that the black boxes have been recovered from Flight 302, investigators will see what information they reveal about the cause of the crash.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 03:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/15/3796987/3796987_A45664D2A9C342D19F72C1304A5800D6_190315_3796987_Recent_737_Max_8_crashes_unrelated_says_aviation_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DE6/9B3/DE69B3A3D85E6018B1E4749604C85E14.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Boeing 737 Max 8, Ethiopian Airlines Flight 302, Lion Air Flight 610]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797694</guid>
      <title>An Asteroid NASA wants to sample is spinning very fast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Asteroid Bennu has been found to revolve quicker over time, according to research published in Geophysical Research Letters.NASA's OSIRIS-REx began approaching the asteroid last year. The spacecraft travelled 2.2 million kilometers from Earth and stationed itself 19 kilometers from Bennu.The discovery was made via ground-based telescopes and the Hubble Space Telescope. Scientists looked at data from 1999, 2005 and 2013 and observed that the asteroid was increasing its rotational speed over time. According to the study, the OSIRIS-REx spacecraft will independently determine Bennu's speed of rotation by flying closer to the asteroid."The scientists believe that sunlight may be causing Bennu to spin faster as it hits the asteroid from various angles. This is known as the YORP effect.Asteroid Bennu is currently traveling across space at 101,000 kilometers per hour and is able to complete a rotation every 4.3 hours.According to the study, Bennu's speed of rotation has increased by around 1 second per century. The asteroid is estimated to be around 4.5 billion years old.OSIRIS-REx was sent to collect data and sample the asteroid using the Osiris Visible and Infrared Spectrometer and Osiris Thermal Emission Spectrometer.The spacecraft will use its Touch-and-Go Sample Acquisition Mechanism to extract rocks and dirt from the surface of asteroid Bennu in July of 2020.It is expected to travel back to Earth and drop off a capsule containing asteroid samples in September 2023.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 07:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/16/3797694/3797694_9943E38A810C44458848AE051F42F420_190316_3797694_An_Asteroid_NASA_wants_to_sample_is_spinning_ver_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BDB/A21/BDBA2188F81696BC21370EE22873A781.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa, asteroid sampling, asteroid, nasa asteroid sampling mission, NASA OSIRIS-REx, asteroid Bennu, NASA asteroid Bennu, OSIRIS REx mission, nasa asteroid bennu, asteroid bennu nasa, nasa space exploration, asteroid bennu sample, YORP effect, OSIRIS-REx spacecraft, osiris-rex spacecraft arrives at asteroid bennu, OSIRIS-REx spacecraft asteroid bennu, asteroid bennu spins faster and faster]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797658</guid>
      <title>Scientists reverse time
using quantum computer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW   A team of researchers from the Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology used a quantum system program to reverse the state of a quantum computer a fraction of a second into the past.According to the paper published in the journal Scientific Reports, they performed the experiments on two quantum bits, also known as qubits. Qubits are represented by a one, a zero or both at the same time.During the first stage of the experiment, the two qubits were unaltered. In the second stage, called 'degradation,' scientists used a computer program to alter the order of the previous stage, causing the qubits to become a random assortment of ones and zeros.This process is then followed by the time reversal stage. At this time the program reverses the chaotic effect on the qubits. Finally, during the 'regeneration' stage, the qubit reverts to the same original state before it had been disrupted by the computer program.The program was able to successfully restore 85 percent of the cases where two qubits where involved.Through this program, the researchers were able to create a state that evolved against the second law of thermodynamics, which states that the state of entropy or disruption of the universe increases over time. Meaning that changes of a state in a closed system can remain static but cannot be reversed.The researchers used the example of cue balls on a pool table. Imagine them formed in a pyramid shape at the center and then being hit, causing them to disperse.Now imagine the process in reverse. The balls retrace the path they took when they were hit and return to the original triangular formation. This is similar to what the researchers accomplished with quantum bits.Although this doesn't mean we will be traveling through time on a DeLorean anytime soon, it will help us achieve a deeper understanding of quantum physics and time.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 06:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/16/3797658/3797658_8E146DE3E9CF4A919BC3AFE4B5C4440B_190316_3797658_Scientists_reverse_time_using_quantum_computer_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7EB/AA8/7EBAA8119D80963EBE30EE8F8FC1F78C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, time travel, reverse time, scientists reverse time, scientists go back in time, physicists reverse time]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3797656</guid>
      <title>China 'indirectly benefiting' from Google, says US general</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  One of the highest-ranking U.S. military officials said this week that Google's collaboration with China is indirectly benefiting the Chinese military, reports Reuters. U.S. Marine General Joseph Dunford spoke on the matter during a Senate Armed Services Committee hearing this week.During the meeting he said, quote: "We watch with great concern when industry partners work in China knowing that there is that indirect benefit." End quote. In contrast, Google has been withdrawing from partnerships with the U.S. Military. In 2018, the tech giant said it would no longer be competing for a $10 billion cloud computing contract with the U.S. Department of Defense. Google stated that the reason behind this was that the company's principles did not align with the DoD project.In June 2018, Google announced it would not be renewing a contract that allowed the U.S. military to analyze aerial drone imagery after it had expired.A spokesperson from Google told CNN that although they have backed out from projects with the Pentagon they are still working closely with the military in other ventures.The spokesperson also added, quote, 'We deeply respect the US military and we are working with them to solve problems in areas like cybersecurity, logistics, transportation, and planning'. End quote.'Google's collaboration with China has made the world a bit uneasy. Last March, Google's plans to create a censored search engine called Dragonfly tailored specifically for China ended after it caused internal conflicts among the company's privacy team, according to reports by The Intercept.Prior to the internal issue, human rights groups including Chinese and Uighurs protested against the Dragonfly project outside Google's offices around the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 06:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/16/3797656/3797656_70F9FA0CF06A4BE4A288AAEBB96A8C78_190316_3797656_China__indirectly_benefiting__from_Google__says__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0D7/C51/0D7C516D00BE05D11190BFACEE6C8BF9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China indirectly benefiting from Google, says US general, China, Google, US, Chinese military, China and Google, Google collaboration with China, Joseph Dunford, US Department of Defense, google dragonfly, dragonfly, dragonfly china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798777</guid>
      <title>How the Christchurch mosque shootings unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHRISTCHURCH, NEW ZEALAND  Fifty people are dead, and many more injured after a gunman opened fire in two mosques in Christchurch, New Zealand.According to the BBC, Brenton Tarrant live-streamed the attack via a head-mounted camera. At 1:40 p.m., he walked into the mosque through the front entrance and began shooting at people inside, killing 42. Afterwards, he got into his car and drove to another mosque in Linwood, where he killed eight.Stuff.co.nz reports that police officers later forced Tarrant's car from the road, dragging him out of the vehicle and taking him into custody.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 14:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798777/3798777_92096FA847424474A9EC545B4B76895A_190318_3798777_How_the_Christchurch_mosque_shootings_unfolded_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/241/2C7/2412C724F883FC452F01788BBC450C81.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Christchurch shooting, Christchurch attack, Christchurch timeline, Al Noor mosque, Linwood mosque, Christchurch tragedy, mosque attack]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798718</guid>
      <title>Australian guy blocks arrow with his smartphone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NIMBIN, AUSTRALIA  It's not everyday your phone is an actual lifesaver, but in the case of this guy Down Underthat's exactly what it was.According to the BBC, police say a 43-year-old man in the town of Nimbin, about 110 miles south of Brisbane, had a bit of a dust up with another man on Wednesday. According to the po po, it all went down when the attacker, carrying a bow and arrow, got into it with the man outside his house. The guy then took out his phone to photograph Rambo First Blood Part II.This caused the suspect to try out his best Hawkeye impression and let one loose. Amazingly, the arrow only pierced the guy's phone, knocking it back into his face. Luckily, he only suffered a small cut.   Robin Hood, 39, was later busted at the scene by authorities. According to the cops, the two guys knew each other. Robin Hood Men in Tights was charged with assault and property damage offences, and is scheduled to appear in court next month.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798718/3798718_2B305890F0F44CA49309A5BD82025F56_190318_3798718_Australian_guy_blocks_arrow_with_his_smartphone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A99/FCB/A99FCB91226E2479FE4B2F49861B5756.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bow and arrow, smartphone stops arrow, mobile phone stops arrow, Australia, Down Under, phone stops arrow]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798637</guid>
      <title>You may be able to use your face to pay for a China subway ride</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA  A subway station in Shenzhen is testing facial recognition software to allow riders to pay the fare with their face, according to the South China Morning Post. At the Futian station, rather than using a ticket or scanning a QR code on a smartphone, commuters can scan their faces on a tablet-sized screen at the entrance gate. Their fare is then automatically deducted from their linked accounts. And all you have to do is register your biometric facial data beforehand with the subway operator, who will definitely be sharing that with the CCP, if they don't have it already. The plus side to this system, you don't have to worry about forgetting your subway card again. The downside...it makes it that much easier for Emperor Xi and his goons to keep constant tabs on everyone. The algorithms for the facial recognition tech were designed in a lab run by Shenzhen Metro and Huawei. Shenzhen Metro did not give a timeline as to when this big brother tech will roll out at all stations. China has already been using facial recognition to pay for things. At KFC stores across China since 2017, people can buy fried chicken by scanning their face. Wow...that's pretty earth-shattering considering how hard it is to buy fried chicken is this world. But seriously, it's only your biometric data. And don't worry, China would never do anything sketchy with that data like spy or keep tabs on people.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 10:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798637/3798637_1D2CF7F9506D41DE9945EFC5C49C2BFF_190318_3798637_You_may_be_able_to_use_your_face_to_pay_for_a_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DAD/D2F/DADD2FBD621B3C5A120CFAC4561E2D83.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, China facial recognition, China facial recognition pay, Shenzhen subway facial recognition pay, facial recognition]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798600</guid>
      <title>Man develops brain infection after cleaning ear with cotton swab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COVENTRY, UNITED KINGDOM  A man in the UK developed a skull infection years after getting part of a cotton swab lodged in his ear.According to a case study published in BMJ Case Reports, a 31-year-old from Coventry was rushed to the hospital after collapsing and suffering seizures.Doctors diagnosed him with necrotising otitis externa, which is a bacterial infection that started in the ear and spread to the bone, targeting the lining of the skull. The man had reported pain and discharge from his left ear ten days before he was hospitalized, along with nasty headaches, nausea, and vomiting. More worryingly, he'd been starting to forget people's names, and later admitted he had been experiencing intermittent ear pain and hearing loss for the past five years.A CT scan revealed two inflamed patches full of pus in the base of his skull, right beside his left ear canal.Doctors went in to treat the infection, but instead found the tip of a cotton bud surrounded by wax. They removed the Q-tip tip and put him on hospital rest and a two-month course of antibiotics, according to the Coventry Telegraph. The man is now infection-free, and will probably never use a cotton swab ever again.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798600/3798600_5DE0147298994FE4A394AFA7A9471D3F_190318_3798600_Man_develops_brain_infection_after_cleaning_ear__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FB9/CD2/FB9CD244ACEA17883597C8F862A51778.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, brain infection, cotton buds, cotton bud infection, ear infection, skull infection, q-tip, q tip, cotton swab, cleaning ears]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798599</guid>
      <title>Russian submarine capable of carrying six nuclear devices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Russia's state media has announced that its navy will begin to test a war submarine capable of carrying six thermonuclear warheads.According to The Barents Observer, Russia's new war submarine called 'Belgorod' will be the world's longest submarine ever built, measuring 184 meters.Russian state media, TASS, reports that the Belgorod will be able to carry six underwater drones called 'Poseidon'.Each of these drones is capable of carrying nuclear warheads weighing up to 2 megatons. Their operational depth is 1,000 meters, making them difficult to intercept.Foreign Minister of Norway Ine Eriksen Soreide told The Barents Observer that it was 'worrying that countries are developing new nuclear capabilities.'According to Russian state media, the Belgorod will be deployed by summer 2019.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 09:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798599/3798599_7FE192C477E5469C8C0F7C6B44A9217D_190318_3798599_Russian_submarine_capable_of_carrying_six_nuclea_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/287/D86/287D86B414E04F073D26E98495D4B6BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, russian submarines, nuclear devices, russia, russia submarines, russia belgarod, russia poseidon, russia torpedo, russia navy, putin, vladimir putin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798554</guid>
      <title>NYC Mayor Bill de Blasio's $10 billion plan to save Manhattan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANHATTAN, NEW YORK  New York's mayor has plans to expand Manhattan's coastline to safeguard the island from the effects of climate change.Mayor Bill de Blasio wants to artificially extend the southern tip of Manhattan to protect it from rising sea levels and storm surges, the New York Times reports.According to a Lower Manhattan Climate Resilience Study, 37 percent of Lower Manhattan will be at risk from a storm surge by 2050.In an op-ed published in New York Magazine, de Blasio said the coastline of Lower Manhattan will be extended as much as 500 feet into the East River.Landfill will be used to extend the coastline. This would create a rising berm that would be above future sea levels, according to the New York Times.He added that grassy berms in parks and removable barriers will also be used to protect the island from storm surges.According to de Blasio's op-ed in New York Magazine, the coastal extension project will cost around US$10 billion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 08:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798554/3798554_A139A3A58309491CB784D76C3374AAA7_190318_3798554_NYC_Mayor_Bill_de_Blasio_s__10_billion_plan_to_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/82F/01C/82F01CDDBB6FEC8BCDFB78EFC4F8478E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, manhattan, rising sea levels, climate change, climate change new york city, combating climate change, manhattan climate change, Bill de Blasio, Bill de blasio manhattan, saving manhattan from rising sea levels, lower manhattan, increasing manhattan coastline, rising sea levels manhattan, increasing the size of manhattan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798497</guid>
      <title>Green tea reduces risk of obesity in mice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLUMBUS, OHIO  Research from Ohio State University has found that green tea lowered the risk of obesity in mice.The scientists tested their hypothesis on a group of male mice. Half of the mice were fed a high-fat diet while the rest were fed healthy meals.They further separated the two groups into two sub-groups.Half of the mice that were fed a high-fat diet had a green tea extract mixed into their foods while the other half did not. The extract was also placed in the meals of 50 percent of the mice that were fed a normal diet.Researchers observed that mice on a high-fat diet mixed with green tea had gained around 20 percent less weight than those whose diet didn't consist of any green tea.The green tea fed mice were also found to have lower insulin resistance and healthier microbes in their body, according to the study.Lead author of the study Professor Richard Bruno, speaking on the Ohio State University website, said, "This study provides evidence that green tea encourages the growth of good gut bacteria, and that leads to a series of benefits that significantly lower the risk of obesity."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 06:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798497/3798497_60B3E658C42048F58EABC4BA2DA9B8EC_190318_3798497_Green_tea_reduces_risk_of_obesity_in_mice_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F8/290/8F8290F6CA6418091E9C60709727582A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, health, mice, obesity, green tea, green tea mice, green to found to prevent obesity in mice, green tea benefits, green tea weight loss, green tea study, green tea body weight, preventing obesity, green tea health benefits, green tea extract, green tea study]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798387</guid>
      <title>China college class requires students get WeChat friends</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHENGZHOU, CHINA  A Chinese professor apparently gave his students one of the dumbest college assignments of all timeadd as many possible friends on WeChat. According to the BBC, students unlucky enough to be taking the the Internet and New Media course at Henan University of Economics and Law were given the pointless assignment on March 10.  It's weird taking a class in China on the internet, when all they have is a insanely censored and policed intranet. Anyways, according to the students, they need to add at least 1,000 new WeChat buddies to pass the assignment, which accounts for 30 percent of their final grade. Think of WeChat as basically a WhatsApp knockoff. To get full marks on the assignment, students are required to add 1,667 friends. Some students reached out to Pear Video to complain about the assignment. In response, a teacher from the college tried to write a letter to explain the idea was to prepare students for real life. "This assignment comes from a core module in the course. What we're saying is that afterwards, when these students look for work, they will have the basic skills necessary for this type of social media operation."So basically, it's teaching them nothing. Apparently, the Pear Video story has been seen more than seven million times on Weibo, China's Twitter knockoff, and has attracted more than 10,000 comments. No wonder Chinese people send their kids to study in the U.S.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 02:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/18/3798387/3798387_7B5E8AF0B6D24EA090A2ACAD32C1BA0C_190318_3798387_China_college_class_requires_students_get_WeChat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BEE/2D2/BEE2D2AE65D79473DF7BCFFA08837F0B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, China WeChat, College WeChat assignment, China college WeChat assignment, Chinese college students]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799327</guid>
      <title>Boeing 737 Max 8 pilots trained on iPads instead of flight simulators</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  As investigations continue into the causes of recent Boeing 737 Max 8 crashes, pilot training has now become a focus, according to the New York Times. Specifically, if pilots were sufficiently prepared for the new software on the aircraft. When the plane was introduced, Boeing thought that pilots who had flown earlier models didn't need additional simulator training and U.S. regulators agreed. According to the New York Times, normally for new plane models, pilots train for hours in huge flight simulators. This didn't happen with the Max line of planes. Instead, many pilots with 737 experience learned about the plane by looking at an iPad for two hours. Part of the reason was that as Boeing rushed to finish the plane, flight simulators made for the Max weren't ready. Greg Bowen, the training and standards chair at the Southwest pilots association, was told by senior leadership at the airline the engineering data necessary to design simulator software was still being finalized right up until the plane was nearly completed. According to Bowen, "they were building the airplane and still designing it. The data to build a simulator didn't become available until about when the plane was ready to fly."What's more troubling is that the training that was provided by Boeing did not cover any of the new software that would be used in the 737.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 12:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/19/3799327/3799327_AFEF804806274014A8FC5A39BDE95426_190319_3799327_Boeing_737_Max_8_pilots_trained_on_iPads_instead_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/869/DF5/869DF56C086F390D5049AFAA908C46CE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing 737 iPad training, Boeing pilots ipad training, pilots iPad training]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799274</guid>
      <title>Gunman arrested after killing 3 in Utrecht tram shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UTRECHT, NETHERLANDS  A Turkish man has been arrested following a shooting on a tram in Utrecht.The BBC reports that the shooting took place at around 10:45 a.m. on board a tram in Utrecht's 24 Oktoberplein junction.According to the New York Times, witness accounts indicate that someone had activated the emergency brakes, as passengers screamed and clamored to escape.Reuters reports that at least three people were killed and nine others injured. According to the New York Times, some were wounded by shattering glass.After the gunman stepped off the tram, the Telegraph reports that he escaped in a stolen red Renault Clio. Police conducted house-to-house raids and arrested the suspect after an eight-hour manhunt.Authorities initially said the shooting was a terrorist incident, but later claimed they were not ruling out a personal motive.According to Turkey's Anadolu news agency, relatives of 37-year-old suspect Gokmen Tanis said the shooting was due to a family dispute. They alleged that only one person  possibly his former wife  was the intended target.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 11:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/19/3799274/3799274_9BF1799C307F4C7099D669102079DA95_190319_3799274_Gunman_arrested_after_killing_3_in_Utrecht_tram__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BBF/F1F/BBFF1F97F4F51BF7BD2018A383BB25DE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, utrecht shooting, utrecht tram shooting, utrecht tram, dutch tram shooting, gokeman tanis, utrecht]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799146</guid>
      <title>Sextuplets pregnancy: Woman births 6 kids in 9 minutes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON, TEXAS  A woman in Texas gave birth to six babies within 10 minutes last week, according to Fox News.Thelma Chiaka gave birth to sextuplets. She birthed two sets of twin boys and one set of twin girls between 4:50 a.m. and 4:59 a.m. on Friday March 15, 2019 at the Woman's Hospital of Texas in Houston, according to Fox News.Fox News cites a press release by the hospital, as saying that the babies' weight was around 1 pound 12 ounces to 2 pounds 14 ounces.The odds of having sextuplets is 1 in 4.7 billion, according to the Woman's Hospital of Texas. The hospital said the woman named her daughters Zina and Zuriel. The names of the four boys haven't been revealed yet, according to Fox.The new born babies and the mom are in stable condition and are to receive treatment at the hospital's advanced neonatal intensive care unit.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 08:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/19/3799146/3799146_324CB5C116DB4CD49891663EA7E56E7D_190319_3799146_Sextuplets_pregnancy__Woman_births_6_kids_in_9_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8BC/E6C/8BCE6C9001F1903BD744C1B444ACD8B3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, woman, texas, The woman's hospital of Texas, woman gives birth to six babies, birthing stories, women giving birth in houston, sextuplets in texas, six babies born, six babies in texas, six babies in nine babies, six babies born in houston, woman gives birth to six babies in nine minutes, texas babies, sextuplets babies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799141</guid>
      <title>Moisturizer could reduce risk of age-related disease, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Scientists have found that using a skin moisturizer might reduce the risk of developing diseases such as Alzheimer's and diabetes.A small pilot study by the University of California, San Francisco found that inflammation of the skin may play a role in chronic illnesses.Around age 50, our skin begins to lose moisture and the skin's permeability barrier starts to break down. The barrier acts as a shield to retain water in our bodies and keep pathogens out.In younger skin, inflammatory cytokines are released to help repair cracks in the barrier.As the skin ages and the barrier weakens, more cytokines are released by the immune system.Cytokines eventually enter the bloodstream, and according to the study can cause inflammation that affects the rest of the body.The study had 33 participants between the ages of 58 and 95. They were asked to apply moisturizer twice a day for a month.The moisturizer contained cholesterol, free fatty acids and ceramides  all of which are essential for skin health.The scientists observed that the cytokine levels of the participants were found to be nearly equivalent with people in their thirties at the end of one month.In a news release the University of California, San Francisco said the researchers now plan to conduct a large scale study to test if moisturizing creams can actually delay or prevent age-related diseases caused by inflammation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 08:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/19/3799141/3799141_42D212830D9B4B78BA054675885A792D_190319_3799141_Moisturizer_could_reduce_risk_of_age_related_dis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5BE/F0C/5BEF0C81A8733A12435B24E13B7393C8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, moisturizer, skin moisturizer, heart disease, diabetes, alzheimer's disease, skin, age-related chronic disease, Cytokines, skin moisturizer, inflammation, inflammaging, dermatological symptoms, cytokine in skin, cytokine response in skin, moisturizer good for skin, applying moisturizer]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799093</guid>
      <title>A new solar system is forming nearby</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATACAMA DESERT, CHILE  A team of researchers have detected planets forming around a young star similar to the sun according to a press release from ALMA.  According to the paper published in Astrophysical Journal Letters, DM Tau is located in the Taurus constellation 470 light-years away from Earth. It is between three and five million years old and weighs roughly half the mass of the sun.The researchers spotted the system forming using the Atacama Large Millimeter/submillimeter Array known as ALMA.ALMA is a radio telescope that captures radio waves from the universe. It is located in the Atacama Desert in northern Chile.Using the ALMA, scientists were able to view two rings of dust forming around the star. The inner ring is 4 astronomical units, known as AU,  from the star and the second ring is 20 AU away. Scientists believe this is where the planets are forming.The team hopes to gain a better understanding of the origin of planets like Earth by studying the formation of this neighboring solar system.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 06:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/19/3799093/3799093_0B5ABE365DD84D5190C3C7F727FE781D_190319_3799093_A_new_solar_system_is_forming_nearby_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15A/50F/15A50FED831B49A4ADFE1874743F2D4B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, new solar system, solar system, DM tau, scientists discover new solar system, scientists find new solar system, taurus constellation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799090</guid>
      <title>Eating too many eggs increases heart disease risk, study says</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Not egg-specially good news if you happen to be a fan of eggs. According to a new study, eating too many delicious eggs can increase risks of heart disease and permanent sleep. According to Northwestern Now, the large-scale Northwestern Medicine study examined pooled data on 29,615 U.S. racially and ethnically diverse adults from six prospective cohort studies for up to 31 years of follow up. The study was published last Friday in the medical journal JAMA. According to co-author of the study Norrina Allen, "the take-home message is really about cholesterol, which happens to be high in eggs and specifically yolks.""As part of a healthy diet, people need to consume lower amounts of cholesterol. People who consume less cholesterol have a lower risk of heart disease."One large egg can have up to 186 milligrams of dietary cholesterol in the yolk. Eating less than 300 milligrams of cholesterol per day used to be the U.S. dietary guideline recommendation, until it was dropped in 2015. The study found eating 300 mg of dietary cholesterol per day was associated with 17 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease and 18 percent higher risk of all-cause deaths. The cholesterol was the driving factor independent of saturated fat consumption and other dietary fat. They also found eating three to four eggs a week was associated with 6 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease and 8 percent higher risk of any cause of death. So does this mean giving up eggs and red meat? Of course notmoderation is the key. And maybe cut out the daily three-egg breakfast omelette.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 06:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/19/3799090/3799090_2FD1D5498B0048A3A8C157447E328436_190319_3799090_Eating_too_many_eggs_increases_heart_disease_ris_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C61/390/C613908EEF26EE868474D9339B1D4C26.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, eggs, eggs health, eggs cholesterol, egg consumption study, heart disease, eggs bad for you]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3798988</guid>
      <title>'Clear similarities' between Ethiopian and Lion Air crashes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ADDIS ABABA   There are "clear similarities" between Indonesia's Lion Air and Ethiopian Air crashes, according to the Ethiopian government.AFP reports that Ethiopia's transport minister, Dagmawit Moges, told a press conference on Sunday that flight data recorders from Ethiopian Airlines flight 302 have been recovered in good condition. So far the data extracted shows similarities between the Ethiopian Airlines crash and the Lion Air crash that occurred in October 2018.According to the AFP,  both aircrafts experienced irregular climbs and descents as well as fluctuations in altitude before crashing minutes after take off. Experts also identified issues with the plane's automated Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, which stops the plane from stalling.According to the New York Times, new evidence suggests that the stabilizers on the Ethiopian Airlines flight were tilted upwards and forcing down the nose of the plane.Flight recordings and cockpit voice recordings from the Ethiopian Airlines flight have been sent to France's air safety agency for further analysis. They are working in collaboration with American and Ethiopian investigators.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 03:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/19/3798988/3798988_02467F8155CC4035B5797A4B8ABE05FE_190319_3798988__Clear_similarities__between_Ethiopian_and_Lion__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C90/61E/C9061E689AD9473C5FC3BF9986D3F4F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, similarities between ethiopian and indonesian flights, similarities between ethiopian airlines and lion air, indonesia plane crash, plane crash indonesia, indonesia plane crash survivors, lion air, indonesia plane crash 2018, java plane crash, jakarta, boeing, lion air crash latest news, plane crash, boeing 737 Max,boeing 737 Max,  boeing 737 Max 8 crash, Ethiopian Airlines, Ethiopian Airlines crash]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799880</guid>
      <title>Artificial meat: Scientists make bacon on blades of grass</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BATH, ENGLAND  A team of researchers from the University of Bath have developed bacon fibers using pig stem cells and blades of grass, reports the BBC.First, they take a tissue sample from a pig and extract stem cells from the tissue. Stem cells have the capacity of turning into different kinds of cells including muscle, fat or ligaments. After the cells are isolated they are placed in a container for cultivation. They are then placed on blades of grass where they continue to grow into meat fibers.Millions of muscle, fat and ligament cells are required to make a single fiber of bacon. This makes it difficult for cultured meat to be produced at a large scale and sold commercially.Lab-grown meat is expensive. Back in 2013 a group of scientists in the Netherlands made the first lab-meat burger, and it cost over US$280,000 due to the time and effort that was needed to cultivate the cells.Scientists are hoping this new method can be an alternative for the future of lab meat production.According to the BBC, lab-grown meat won't be commercially available for at least five more years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 10:54:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/20/3799880/3799880_2652053B172B482BAFEB83F7BFCFE5E9_190320_3799880_Artificial_meat__Scientists_make_bacon_on_blades_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/086/50B/08650B598A3D59A8D715BC06FE6596E9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, artificial meat, lab grown meat, tube meat, vegan meat, lab grown meath how is it made, fake meat, clean meat, cruelty free meat, slaughter free meat, meat from lab, grown meat, meat, cultured cells, artificial meat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799781</guid>
      <title>New technique generates hydrogen fuel from seawater</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA  Stanford researchers have developed a water-splitting system that can produce clean hydrogen fuel using saltwater.According to a Stanford University press release, hydrogen fuel can be generated via electrolysis, which splits water into hydrogen and oxygen using electricity. The process typically uses fresh or purified water, as saltwater has been known to corrode.A new system developed by a team of Stanford scientists uses solar cells to power two electrodes in water, causing hydrogen gas comes out of the cathode, and oxygen to come out of the anode.To prevent corrosion from the chloride in saltwater, negatively charged nickel layers were coated on to the anode to create a barrier.Nickel foam conducts electricity, and nickel-iron hydroxide sparks electrolysis. Nickel sulfide, repels chloride and prevents it from getting to the core metal.The multi-layer device can run for more than a thousand hours, compared to just 12 without the negatively charged coating. It can also conduct 10 times more electricity and help generate hydrogen from seawater at a faster rate.According to the team, the technology have other applications beyond generating energy, such as generating breathable oxygen underwater for divers or submarines.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 09:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/20/3799781/3799781_4722FC2CBC2E499F970FC36C7A66C796_190320_3799781_New_technique_generates_hydrogen_fuel_from_seawa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/16B/01C/16B01C4BDA4AFD901D72EF1F6835E08F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  hydrogen fuel, clean fuel, fuel from seawater, clean hydrogen, green energy, electrolysis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799736</guid>
      <title>Huge meteor explodes in Earth's atmosphere</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAMCHATKA PENINSULA, RUSSIA  A fireball entered Earth's atmosphere and exploded with the energy of 173 kilotons of TNT, according to data collected by NASA.The US Air Force reported a massive explosion just 25.6km above the Earth's atmosphere off the coast of Russia over the Bering Strait. The BBC reports the explosion took place last year on December 18.According to NASA, the meteor entered Earth's atmosphere at 32 kilometers per second with an impact energy of roughly 173 kilotons. This is ten times the energy released by the Hiroshima atomic bomb.Using NASA data, meteor specialist Peter Brown at Western University in Canada calculated that the meteor was 10 meters wide and weighed 1,400 tons. According to The Guardian, the explosion was recorded by a network of infrasound sensors which are used to detect covert nuclear bomb tests.This meteor explosion was the third largest fireball to enter Earth's atmosphere in modern times, following the 2013 Chelyabinsk explosion and the Tunguska fireball in 1908. All of these explosions have occurred in Russia.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/20/3799736/3799736_B6E081B94A1B41EBA2051EE8656A6F07_190320_3799736_Huge_meteor_explodes_in_Earth_s_atmosphere_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,huge meteor,huge meteor explodes,meteor explodes near Earth,meteor explodes,meteor explosion,big meteor explosion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3799565</guid>
      <title>Design issues with the Boeing 737 Max 8</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED STATES  The crashes of Lion Air Flight 610 on October 29, 2018, and Ethiopian Airlines Flight 409 on March 10 have brought attention to the design and software of the Boeing 737 Max 8. According to Asia Times, the 737 Max series is equipped with new CFM Leap-1B engines, which forced re-engineering of part of the airplane. Fitting the new engines meant moving them forward and lengthening the front landing gear to keep the engines from scraping the ground. This changed the plane's center of gravity and also altered the airflow on the wings.  The new, heavier and larger engines resulted in Max planes having a strong tendency to pitch nose up, which is why the MCAS, or Maneuvering Characteristics Augmentation System, was introduced. According to Asia Times, MCAS was a suboptimal fix to the pitch problem created by relocating the newer engines. It is designed to push the nose down and prevent the plane from going into a stall. MCAS was intended to deal only with a specific flight risk.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2019 03:54:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/20/3799565/3799565_7C85C3BFE5F6425987A05C22D610DBD4_190320_3799565_Design_issues_with_the_Boeing_737_Max_8_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/134/8B6/1348B6AA7E80F4082CA10ED4CCF8C244.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Boeing 737 Max 8, Boeing 737 Max 8 engines, 737 Max 8 MCAS, 737 Max 8 LEAP 1B engines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800618</guid>
      <title>Bodycam video shows why Miami Dade po po was suspended</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  Miami-Dade police suspended an officer for his actions during the arrest of a woman who claimed a man pointed a shotgun at her. The cop had threatened to involuntarily commit the woman to a hospital, told her he didn't like her tone of voice, and threatened to arrest her if she didn't calm down. According to the Miami Herald, bodycam footage released by the police shows Dyma Loving never threatened the officer. She spoke clearly and only became slightly agitated after Officer Alejandro Giraldo's threats.On March 5, Loving and Adrianna Green, 22, called the police after a man named Frank Tumm, who lives next door to Green, pointed a shotgun at them. The two told police they were walking past Tumm's house when they got into a verbal altercation. Tumm had retrieved a shotgun and pointed it at them. Police later arrested Tumm, after originally letting him go.But the real story is how Officer Alejandro Giraldo completely lost it during the arrest. In the video, Giraldo repeatedly yells at Loving to calm down and to chill out, when clearly he's the only one who is freaking out. And like you'd expect, Giraldo eventually throws Loving in cuffs and arrests her. Loving was charged with disorderly conduct and resisting arrest without violence. Giraldo was suspended last week by Miami-Dade Police Director Juan Perez after cellphone video of the crazy arrest taken by a friend of Loving made the rounds on social media.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 13:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/21/3800618/3800618_653EA7CBC7C94EFD847368FCB40E2DA1_190321_3800618_Bodycam_video_shows_why_Miami_Dade_po_po_was_sus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/96E/ED7/96EED7D25116BDAA540AD808E3441F92.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bodycam, bodycam video, bodycam footage, Miami Dade police, Miami Dade officer suspended, police officer suspended]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800615</guid>
      <title>Changes in ocean conveyor belt foretold major climate shifts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  In the Atlantic Ocean, a giant 'conveyor belt' carries warm waters from the tropics into the North Atlantic, where they cool and sink and then return south to the deep ocean.Ocean water circulation affects global climate, regulating weather patterns in the Arctic, Europe and around the world. More and more research suggests this conveyor belt system is slowing down, causing some scientists to fear it could cause temperatures to plummet in Europe and warming waters off the east coast of the U.S.According to a Columbia University press release, a new study published in Nature Communications has provided insight into how quickly changes in Atlantic Ocean circulation could affect major climate changes.  The study was carried out by researchers at Columbia's Lamont-Doherty Earth Observatory, working with the Norwegian Research Center. It was the first to precisely calculate the time lags between past changes to the ocean conveyor belt and major climate changes.The study looked at the Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation, or AMOC, and specifically focused on a section where water sinks from the surface to the bottom of the North Atlantic. Researchers took sediment core samples drilled from the bottom of the Norwegian Sea, a lake sediment core from southern Scandinavia, and ice cores from Greenland. Comparing data from the three cores revealed that the AMOC started weakening about 400 years before a major cold snap 13,000 years ago. It began strengthening again about 400 years before an abrupt warming 11,000 years ago.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 13:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/21/3800615/3800615_F6240AD81196448B9D28D2357821409C_190321_3800615_Changes_in_ocean_conveyor_belt_foretold_major_cl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7A0/744/7A07440F01912FCE8B3F646302ADA81C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ocean conveyor belt, Atlantic ocean conveyor belt, AMOC, Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation, climate shift, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800412</guid>
      <title>Beijing plans island city on Woody Island in the Paracels</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH CHINA SEA  The Chinese government has announced plans to build up a strategic island in the Paracels, despite strong opposition from the U.S.The South China Morning Post reports that China is planning to build an 'island city' on Woody Island and neighboring islets Tree and Drummond. According to the Communist Party secretary of Sansha, the aim is to turn the island and two islets into a national key strategic service and logistics base.According to the Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative, Woody Island is China's main military base in the Paracels, and is equipped with an airstrip, aircraft hangars, ports, and missiles.Woody Island is also home to a settlement of about 1,000 people, and serves as the administrative capital of the three island chains it claims in the South China Sea.The U.S. has long criticized China's expansion and militarization of the disputed region, and challenges territorial claims with freedom of navigation operations, despite protests from Beijing.According to the South China Morning Post, two American B-52H Stratofortress bombers capable of carrying nuclear weapons flew over the South China Sea on March 14 for the second time in 10 days.U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo also spoke out last week criticizing China's 'illegal island-building in international waterways.' He also accused Beijing of using coercive means to block energy development in the South China Sea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 09:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/21/3800412/3800412_8A4E50E1DFB6475DBDB018716FDC9076_190321_3800412_Beijing_plans_island_city_on_Woody_Island_in_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/323/E96/323E96E99FEF18BAEF7294B2149E3679.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, south china sea, china, woody island, sansha, paracels, island city, tree islet, drummond islet, south china sea expansion]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800166</guid>
      <title>Flat Earthers plan Antarctic expedition to edge of the Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NOT THE EDGE OF THE WORLD  Some people will go to the ends of the Earth just to prove something. For flat earthers, it's all too literal. According to Forbes, the latest plan to win the disk vs ball debate involves an Antarctic expedition to reach the edge of the world. The "real exact science," Flat Earth International Conference founder Robbie Davidson told Forbes, is that if you squish down a globe, Antarctica would be an ice shore that goes all the way around the Earth.It would have been nice to just have the crazies all sail right off the face of the planet. But apparently we're also in a dome, so that's not gonna happen.The flat earthers claim the Antarctic ice wall stretches 60,000 miles on a pancake vs just 14,500 on a ball, and think that by sailing around its coast, they can get the distance to flat out prove their point.According to Forbes, this all stems from a belief that the UN Antarctic Treaty of 1961 doesn't allow private explorations of Antarctica. Nevermind that a dude just did a solo trek across the continent, complete with GPS proof. But since the G in GPS stands for globe, the flat earthers are having none of it.In any case, we're all looking forward to that Antarctic expedition. Let's hope they get that spectacular failure on video.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 02:49:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/21/3800166/3800166_37B3020CD73A4797810203DA852ECC2C_190321_3800166_Flat_Earthers_plan_Antarctic_expedition_to_edge__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/880/155/880155042962DA07070092DEE9F3BF90.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, flat earth, flat earthers, antarctica expedition, antarctic expedition, dome earth, edge of the earth, edge of the world, colin o'brady]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3801214</guid>
      <title>Snake catcher removes 45 rattlesnakes from under house</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALBANY, TEXAS  A north-central Texas homeowner was watching some television last week, when the cable started acting up, according to KWQC.According to a Facebook post by Big Country Snake Removal, the man snaked his way under the house and ran into "a few" rattlesnakes, so he made a tactical retreat and called in the pros. According to KWQC, when guys from Big Country Snake Removal had a look for themselves, they MAY have counted more than a FEW. They posted an almost 18-minute long video of the hours long removal job to Facebook, which has already racked up more than a million views. According to the post, the snake catchers arrived around lunchtime and immediately upon crawling under, could see they were dealing with a whole mess of rattlers45 to be exact.  The video shows Big Country owner Nathan Hawkins and a partner take the snakes out one by one from the small crawl space under the house. The house was clean with a well-kept yard, but the post wisely added, "rattlesnakes don't care how nice your house is or what kind of car you drive- they simply care about survival."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 12:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/22/3801214/3801214_A18DE3390AB347D6B4FD131411926BDA_190322_3801214_Snake_catcher_removes_45_rattlesnakes_from_under_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0BB/C11/0BBC1132E1367EF5DA07362E4958CB98.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, rattlesnakes, rattlesnakes under house, rattlesnake removal, Big Country Snake Removal, snake under house]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3801144</guid>
      <title>China to build 'experimental ship' that could be nuclear icebreaker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China is looking to build a massive nuclear-powered vessel described as an 'experimental platform', which some speculate could be a nuclear icebreaker.According to the South China Morning Post, the China General Nuclear Power Group is looking to build a nuclear powered ship measuring 498 feet long and 98 feet wide, with a displacement of 33,069 tons.The vessel could be fitted with two 25 megawatt compact pressurized water reactors to propel it to a maximum speed of 11.5 knots.China has not specified what the ship will be used for, referring to it only as an 'experimental ship platform.'The vessel's size has been described by Hong Kong-based military commentator Song Zhongping as similar to that of Russian nuclear icebreakers.Russia is the only country that operates nuclear-powered icebreakers, which is used to plow through thick ice-covered waters to maintain and develop the Northern Sea route.China already has a conventionally powered polar icebreaker, which was launched last year to boost its polar research and expedition capacity.But having a nuclear icebreaker is important for expanding its presence in the Arctic Ocean.Song told the South China Morning Post that if experiments using icebreakers go well, the technology could be used to develop next-generation aircraft carriers.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 10:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/22/3801144/3801144_832FD8335AC44F3BBBF98857C8D829F7_190322_3801144_China_to_build__experimental_ship__that_could_be_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/653/9E8/6539E8A81CE61BDDE938B4D1869D547C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nuclear icebreaker, icebreaker, nuclear ship, nuclear vessel, china nuclear icebreaker, russia nuclear icebreaker, experimental ship, china icebreaker, russia icebreaker, russia leader icebreaker, northern sea route, russia arktika icebreaker]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3801073</guid>
      <title>A restaurant makes 3D sushi with diners' bodily fluids</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  A Japanese restaurant is making customized 3D-printed sushi for each of its diners by studying samples of their bodily fluids, reports KXAN.The Tokyo restaurant, called Sushi Singularity, will ask its customers to send in samples of their saliva, urine, and stools and use them to create 3D-printed sushi tailored to meet their dietary needs.After clients make a reservation at the restaurant they will receive a health test kit containing vials to collect samples of their feces, urine, and saliva. Once completed, the kit is then sent back to the restaurant for analysis.Using the data gathered through the samples, the restaurant then creates customized sushi recipes in order to meet the client's dietary needs. Using the recipe, a 3D-printing machine makes the sushi and injects the raw vitamins, proteins, and minerals the client needs.Sushi Singularity is one of many ventures by a Japanese culinary innovation company called Open Meals.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 09:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/22/3801073/3801073_DE3E3F1E45BA4468BE50DC39DC230D8B_190322_3801073_A_restaurant_makes_3D_sushi_with_diners__bodily__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2DF/A1C/2DFA1C5D6D21144AB5C41AB732DF32B0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,3d printed food, 3d printer, 3d printed sushi, 3d print sushi, japan, 3d printed foods, japanese food, sushi teleportation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3801068</guid>
      <title>China clones its best police dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Chinese authorities have successfully cloned one of their top police dogs, reports Chinese state media, global Times. China's top police doggo, a Kunming wolfdog called Huahuangma, is so good at sniffing out drugs and perps that in 2016 the Chinese Ministry of Public Security classified her as a first-class meritorious dog. They decided they needed more dogs exactly like her. So they cloned her.According to Chinese state media, Global Times, researchers from the Sinogene Biotechnology Company and the Yunnan Agricultural University have cloned the wonder dog in an attempt to test whether or not it would be viable to mass-produce police dogs.The cloned doggie, called Kunxun, was a success. Chinese authorities claim her DNA is 99.9 percent similar to Huahuangma's. Kunxun is now three months old and will begin training in crowd control, drug detection and evidence retrieval. She will graduate at 10 months old. If successful, Kunxun would have trained to become a police dog in record time. According to the Global Times, it usually takes five years for a pooch to become a police dog and costs roughly $60,000. They did not state the cost of cloning.China is not the first to mass produce professional dog investigators. That trophy goes to South Korea. According to ABC news, in 2009 South Korea deployed drug-sniffing dogs that had been cloned from a Labrador retriever proficient in drug sniffing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 09:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/22/3801068/3801068_3B1D238ED144483F8CCC758FB8A468F4_190322_3801068_China_clones_its_best_police_dog_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BBA/382/BBA38238AFF01B54BA7EA0534C082C85.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china clones dogs, police dog, china clones police dog, dog clones, cloning, animal cloning, cloning animals, china clones]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800889</guid>
      <title>Exxon Valdez Spill: It's been 30 years since one of the US biggest oil spills</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PRINCE WILLIAM SOUND, ALASKA   The Exxon Valdez oil spill in Alaska was one of the biggest U.S. oil spills ever to occur, according to the Atlantic. Today we revisit how it happened.According to The Atlantic, on March 24, 1989, the Exxon Valdez oil tanker was entering Alaska's Prince William Sound. It had departed from the Trans Alaska Pipeline terminal on March 23 at 9:12 pm and was carrying 53.1 million gallons of oil.At 12:04 am the tanker slammed into Bligh Reef, tearing open its hull and spilling 11 million gallons of oil into the water and the surrounding environment. That's the equivalent of 17 Olympic-sized swimming pools.According to Scientific American, nearly 2,000 kilometers of the shoreline were contaminated. Wildlife in the area was also severely damaged. Thousands of otters, harbor seals, seabirds and fish were killed.According to the Environmental Protection Agency, three methods were used to clean up the spill: burning the oil on the water's surface, mechanical cleanup via oil skimmers and chemical dispersants.High-pressure hot water was also used to clean the surrounding beaches until it was determined that it was cooking microorganisms present in the shores which in turn damaged the soil.According to a case study by the International Tanker Owners Pollution Federation Limited, Exxon Mobil had to pay $4.3 billion as a consequence of the spill in addition to the $2 billion it spent the first year on clean-up efforts.The Exxon Valdez oil spill is the second largest spill in history second to the Deepwater Horizon oil spill in the Gulf of Mexico, where an explosion at a BP oil rig killed eleven workers and spilled 53,000 barrels of oil per day for three months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 05:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/22/3800889/3800889_87ADF2B5FF2B48F4A289191663538B00_190322_3800889_Exxon_Valdez_Spill__It_s_been_30_years_since_one_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/503/843/503843D392D8C62EB7659265D8F1A539.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, exxon valdez oil spill, oil spill, exxon valdez, exxon oil spill, exxon oil spill video, exxon oil spill clean up, oil spill cleanup]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3800879</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong plans massive $79 billion artificial island project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Hong Kong has announced plans to spend $79 billion to construct one of the world's largest artificial island projects.The Guardian reports that Hong Kong is planning to build 1,000 hectares of artificial islands off the coast of Lantau Island.The project, called 'Lantau Vision Tomorrow,' is more than twice the size of Dubai's Palm Jumeirah, which was also created by land reclamation.According to the South China Morning Post, the first phase will provide up to 260,000 residential units, 70 percent of which will be reserved for public housing.A new transport network is also being built, which will include road and rail links to connect the future man-made islands to Hong Kong Island, Lantau, and Tuen Mun.The plan has received criticism from environmental groups, who say the building work will be damaging to local species such as the endangered pink dolphin.The Guardian reports that Greenpeace and the World Wildlife Fund have argued that authorities should instead develop former industrial areas called brownfield sites, arguing that it is cheaper and less harmful to the environment.Reclamation work on 'Lantau Vision Tomorrow' is scheduled to begin in 2025, with the first residents expected to move in by 2032.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2019 05:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/22/3800879/3800879_408F70AB79494BD7B713FCC279D44F05_190322_3800879_Hong_Kong_plans_massive__79_billion_artificial_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5DF/DEC/5DFDEC0A884A2B007386DEAE9C05F558.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hong kong, lantau island, lantau vision tomorrow, hong kong reclamation, land reclamation, lantau island reclamation, hong kong housing, hong kong housing crisis, reclaimed land]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3802235</guid>
      <title>Crashed 737 Max jets lacked safety features Boeing sold as extras</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  The doomed 737 Max jets in Indonesia and Ethiopia were not equipped with two notable safety features because Boeing charged an additional cost to install them.According to the New York Times, the MCAS software on the Boeing 737 Max takes readings from one of two angle of attack sensors on the plane that aligns itself with oncoming airflow.If MCAS detects that the plane is pointed up at a dangerous angle, it automatically swivels the horizontal stabilizer and pushes the nose down to prevent stalling.Two optional safety features could have kept the MCAS in check: the angle of attack indicator displays readings from both sensors, and the disagree light activates when the sensors' data do not match.Both features were sold by Boeing as optional extras and were not included on the crashed Lion Air and Ethiopian Airlines planes.According to the New York Times, the safety features could have helped pilots detect any erroneous readings. This would have also allowed a manual override of the system.The Times, citing a Boeing bulletin, says this can be done by temporarily counteracting the MCAS movement, cutting off electrical power to the stabilizers, and then cranking a wheel to manually pull them back to the correct position.Experts told the newspaper that the two features are vital for flight safety. But because neither is mandated by the FAA, Boeing was able to sell them as upgrades.The company has since announced that it will make the disagree light standard on all new 737 aircrafts, but the angle of attack indicator will remain an optional extra that airlines can buy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 04:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/25/3802235/3802235_57451A92D5644748A5CD45F21243E42C_190325_3802235_Crashed_737_Max_jets_lacked_safety_features_Boei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/412/4FC/4124FC99FB5978FC25D33D9369669999.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, boeing 737 max, boeing safety features, boeing crash, ethiopia airlines, lion air, boeing 737 crash, angle of attack indicator, disagree light, safety upgrades, optional extra]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3802211</guid>
      <title>Man throws shoe with gun at roach, shoots himself in the foot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DETROIT  A D-town gentleman accidentally busted a cap into his own foot early Tuesday morning while attempting to take out a cockroach, according to WDIV-TV. According to WDIV-TV, police said the 50-year-old man, who uses a wheelchair, was at his house on the block of 18700 Albion Street when he spotted the roach. So in an effort to kill the bug, he decided to throw his shoe at la cucaracha. Only problem is, Big Sean forgot he was strapped and had his revolver tucked in his shoe.  The piece fell out of the shoe and a round was discharged right into the guy's foot. According to the Detroit Free Press, police told them they could not confirm if the accidental non-fatal shooting was because of a bug, but said One-Shot-One-Kill was in stable condition after being taken to the hospital.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 03:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/25/3802211/3802211_05CE54AEFB094AC98B21DE7DDAFEEA03_190325_3802211_Man_throws_shoe_with_gun_at_roach__shoots_himsel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/44F/9FD/44F9FDB28DCF994C809F16C6021F847C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cockroach, man accidentally, detroit man accidentally, man wheelchair cockroach, cockroach shoe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803123</guid>
      <title>Kaohsiung Mayor Han kowtows to Beijing official in Hong Kong</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Kaohsiung Mayor Han Kuo-yu is off prancing around in Hong Kong, Macau and other Chinese cities, but wasted zero time kowtowing to China and selling out Taiwan. According to the Taipei Times, on Friday afternoon, Han met with Wang Zhimin, director of the Liaison Office of the Central People's Government in the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region. Han's office conveniently left the meeting off his published seven-day itinerary they released before the trip. But let's be clear this meeting was planned WELL in advance, as these things with Beijing always are. And when Beijing calls, good subordinates come running.   During his campaign, Han bragged he would strive for "100 percent economy, zero percent politics." This would appear to tip the political scale away from zero. It's very telling however that Han would make a special trip, head polished, tail tucked between his legs to the liaison office. What it shows everyone is the "one country, two systems" is nothing but a sad joke.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 13:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/26/3803123/3803123_489D4B33FBCA49D8ACC8C678F721B82F_190326_3803123_Kaohsiung_Mayor_Han_kowtows_to_Beijing_official__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4D1/8CA/4D18CA30CBB70FF4568AF4064049E011.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, KMT Han Kuo-yu, Han Kuo-yu, Han Kuo-Yu meets Beijing official, Han Kuo-Yu meets CCP official, DPP vs KMT]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803117</guid>
      <title>Man tries to sneak tortoise pastries though airport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERLIN  A man tried to sneak three tortoises into Germany by trying to pass them off as a bunch of pastrieslet's just say it was a turtle disaster.   According to the Potsdam main customs office, officials stopped the 69-year-old man on March 2, who had just arrived from Cairo, Egypt at Schnefeld Airport in Berlin.According to the Local, it appears the man wanted to leave the security area without declaring anything, but when customs officers shell-ected to look at his bag, they found something peculiar. Customs officials discovered what looked like a box of pastries, or that's what the box said at least. When officers asked the man what they were, he said it was chocolate. However, the authorities were shell shocked when they found three Moroccan tortoises inside instead. Since the animals are protected by the Convention on International Trade In Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora, they were confiscated. The customs office said further investigations will be carried out by the Federal Agency for Nature Conservation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 13:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/26/3803117/3803117_DF2ADCBA2A76463097EACA3BC0B54456_190326_3803117_Man_tries_to_sneak_tortoise_pastries_though_airp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/32C/D46/32CD4610B4FA422782378C0F8E07B435.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tortoise, tortoieses, man sneaks tortoises, man tries to sneak tortoises, tortoise pasteries, tortoise cakes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803110</guid>
      <title>China begins construction of floating nuclear power plants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING    China is planning to build 20 floating nuclear power plants in the South China Sea, reports Asia Times. Chinese authorities have officially announced plans to start building the first floating nuclear power plant in the South China Sea. These are designed to power surrounding artificial islands being built in the region.Floating nuclear power plants are offshore platforms containing small nuclear reactors built to power hard to reach islands or islets.Floating power stations are believed to be less prone to natural disasters because emergency situations such as a melting core can be cooled by pumping in seawater.  Roughly 20 floating nuclear stations could be built to power troops and residents in the  Spratly and Paracel islands. These regions are disputed between China, Taiwan, Malaysia, the Philippines, and Vietnam.Asia Times reports that the first floating nuclear reactor will be functional and sea-worthy by 2021. A prototype is currently being tested off the coast of China's Shandong province.According to Chinese state news agency, Xinhua Net, the first floating nuclear power platform would cost roughly US$2.1 billion.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 13:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/26/3803110/3803110_B4D71062849B4A73B4EFFAD2FBEEFCC4_190326_3803110_China_begins_construction_of_floating_nuclear_po_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1CF/7C7/1CF7C728D3C754CE636D24D6DFC4C243.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China begins construction of floating power plant, china building floating power plant, china builds power plant, floating nuclear power plant, floating power station, floating power plant, nuclear power, south china sea, spratlys, paracels, china]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803053</guid>
      <title>Greenland's fastest-melting glacier is growing again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ILULISSAT, GREENLAND  A study has found that Greenland's fastest-thinning glacier is growing again, but scientists say that it may just be temporary.According to NASA JPL, the Jakobshavn glacier in Greenland has been thinning and retreating over the last 20 years.But research published in Nature Geoscience has found that since 2016, the glacier's melting has slowed.NASA reports that it also grew taller by 100 feet between 2016 and 2017.Researchers suspected that this was due to a climate pattern known as the North Atlantic Oscillation, which cools then warm the North Atlantic Ocean every five to 20 years. In 2016, the water temperature in Disko Bay cooled, reaching temperatures that were lower than in the late 1980s.The team used an ocean model to trace the cool water to a current that carries water around Greenland's southern tip, and northward along its west coast.The Associated Press reports that according to study co-author and NASA climate scientist Josh Willis, the findings indicate that glacier retreats and advances are much more sensitive to ocean temperatures than previously thought.  Temperatures are still rising slowly from global warming, and with over 90 percent of heat trapped by greenhouse gases going to the oceans, melting will be worse in the long run.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 11:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/26/3803053/3803053_80C01DD82AA64258B1D96C79912391DB_190326_3803053_Greenland_s_fastest_melting_glacier_is_growing_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CBC/150/CBC150186AD8FF7078C253548FF1C63D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Greenland glacier, Jakobshavn glacier, Greenland ice sheets, Greenland ice melt, Jakobshavn, Sermeq Kujalleq, melting glaciers, North Atlantic Oscillation, climate change, global warming, Greenland]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803044</guid>
      <title>NASA to send mini helicopter on Mars 2020 mission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARS  NASA's Mars 2020 mission will include a mini helicopter that is set to be the first heavier-than-air vehicle to fly within the Red Planet's thin atmosphere.According to NASA, an autonomous rotorcraft called the Mars Helicopter will fly with the Mars Rover in 2020. The small helicopter will be carrying a camera to capture photos of the Martian surface for transmission back to Earth.The atmospheric pressure on the surface the rover is targeted to land on is equivalent to 100,000 feet above the surface of the Earth  over twice as high as any helicopter has reached.To generate enough lift, the Mars Helicopter's main body will be the size of a softball and weigh just four pounds.It will fly up to 15 feet off the surface using two sets of four-feet-long rotor blades spinning at 2,400 rotations per minute  ten times faster than any Earth helicopter.The Mars Helicopter will attempt up to five flights, each time flying a little farther and lasting up to 90 seconds.A solar array will recharge the lithium-ion batteries that will be used to rotate the blades and keep the vehicle warm through the frigid Martian night.Scientists at NASA's Jet Propulsion Laboratory say that if the rotorcraft works as planned, future missions to Mars could deploy more helicopters to extend the reach of the landers they arrive on.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 11:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/26/3803044/3803044_738994F9F6FA4B8E85412CC8FD07AE25_190326_3803044_NASA_to_send_mini_helicopter_on_Mars_2020_missio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/938/DE5/938DE5A986330B1A25FE6CC047215D45.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Mars helicopter, Mars 2020, Mars rover, Mars mission, NASA helicopter, NASA, helicopter on Mars, Mars]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3802874</guid>
      <title>Nokia says phones sent user data to China by mistake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HELSINKI  Finland's Data Protection Ombudsman is investigating HMD Global over claims that its Nokia 7 Plus phones sent user data to China.NRK reports that based on a tip from a phone owner, Nokia 7 Plus phones sent out unencrypted data, which includes location, sim card, and the phone's serial number.The data packages were sent to a server in China owned by China Telecom.According to Nokia, phones purchased in regions like the EU, U.S., and India send data for phone warranty and diagnostics to HMD Global servers in Singapore. Data from phones bought in China are sent to servers in China in order to comply with the country's Cyber Security Law.According to a statement from HMD Global, the Chinese device activation client was mistakenly installed on a single batch of Nokia 7 Plus phones that were meant for countries outside China.Reuters reports that the Finnish investigation would look into whether any data rules that involved personal information were breached and if there has been a legal justification for it.The company says no personally identifiable data was processed or shared to a third party, and claim the error was fixed in February by switching the client to the correct country variant.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 07:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/26/3802874/3802874_D557F78D61CB4457B83380238528C7DC_190326_3802874_Nokia_says_phones_sent_user_data_to_China_by_mis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CD8/E6A/CD8E6AB456A824976E350B47A420052F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nokia, nokia 7 plus, nokia data breach, nokia data leak, data sent to China, nokia phones, China server, HMD global, China Telecom]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3802739</guid>
      <title>Record-breaking Danjiang bridge set to rise in Taiwan by 2024</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  Construction has begun on Danjiang Bridge, the world's longest, single-mast, asymmetric cable-stayed bridge.According to Zaha Hadid Architects, Taiwan's 920-meter long Danjiang bridge will span the mouth of the Tamsui river that flows through Taipei.The bridge will be supported by a slender 200-meter tall concrete mast, which is positioned so that it does not obstruct the waterway, or the scenic views. The single-mast design also minimizes disruption to the riverbed and local habitat.Archinect reports that the new crossing will reduce congestion on local roads as it links two major highways on opposite sides of the river. It is also set to improve connectivity with the Port of Taipei, and Taoyuan International Airport.Dedicated road, cycle, and pedestrian lanes will be built on the bridge. Also included are plans to  accommodate the future expansion of the Danhai Light Rail network.The Danjiang bridge construction project has a budget of $405.2 million. It will be constructed in 68 months and expected to open by 2024.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 02:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/26/3802739/3802739_B9DF60AB6BF94CF4A0E1D5306060B014_190326_3802739_Record_breaking_Danjiang_bridge_set_to_rise_in_T_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CDB/B2F/CDBB2FD498C3E787394943B5EE864B0D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bridge, cool bridges, danjiang bridge, taiwan bridge, single mast bridge, asymmetric cable stayed bridge, tamsui river, zaha hadid architects, record breaking bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803768</guid>
      <title>Southwest 737 Max 8 makes emergency landing in Orlando</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORLANDO  A Southwest Airlines Boeing 737 Max 8 plane was forced to make an emergency landing on Tuesday afternoon at Orlando International Airport. According to the Orlando Sentinel, there were no passengers on board. Two pilots were flying the plane to California for storage, when they experienced a performance issue with one of the engines 10 minutes after takeoff. The aircraft turned around and landed safely. The incident occurred around 3 p.m.The plane was being ferried to Victorville, California for storage. According to Dan Landson, a spokesman for Southwest, "the Boeing 737 Max 8 will be moved to our Orlando maintenance facility for a review." According to a March 13 FAA order that grounded all Boeing 737 Max aircraft, airlines are allowed to fly the planes without passengers to locations for storage and maintenance. The emergency landing comes as federal regulators continue to investigate two deadly crashes involving 737 Max 8 aircraft in Ethiopia and Indonesia. According to the Orlando Sentinel, Southwest has 34 Max planes. On Saturday, the airline began flying them to Victorville to free up space at airports where they have been temporarily parked.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 13:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/27/3803768/3803768_203032DE3AC44915B957346E0235B5B0_190327_3803768_Southwest_737_Max_8_makes_emergency_landing_in_O_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/34C/ED5/34CED5B38A2D860ACF708B5C27A01626.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Boeing 737 Max 8, Southwest 737 Max 8, Southwest Max emergency landing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803698</guid>
      <title>Drunk driver flies 5 stories off highway in Taipei</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW TAIPEI CITY, TAIWAN  A man in Taipei got behind the wheel while under the influence, and ended up flying his car right off an expressway  to disastrous consequences. According to Apple Daily, the accident happened just before 7 a.m. on March 24. The driver, surnamed Chen, was on his way home after driving his girlfriend to work.While on the elevated No. 65 highway in New Taipei City, Chen lost control of his white SUV. The vehicle swerved and hit a street light pole before launching over the guardrail.It fell over five stories off the edge before crashing onto the embankment of a concrete skating rink in the park below.The 36-year-old was still breathing when rescuers pulled him out of the mangled wreckage. He was rushed to the hospital, but ultimately died.Blood drawn from the hospital later revealed that Chen had been driving while totally sloshed, with his blood alcohol at 1.2 milligrams per liter. The legal limit in Taiwan is 0.15.His girlfriend told the cops she didn't notice anything odd or smell any alcohol while he was driving her, but did admit that the two of them had a little drink the night before.According to Apple Daily, some have questioned whether the guardrail on the expressway had been too low, but police say even a higher guardrail doesn't stand a chance against a car ramming at it full speed.What people should really take away from this is don't drive drunk.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 11:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/27/3803698/3803698_85BB0F4810014012B0CD8FF762512D4A_190327_3803698_Drunk_driver_flies_5_stories_off_highway_in_Taip_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0AA/9B9/0AA9B98EC9A658FFEB21FE0DD26B82C2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, car accident, drunk driver, driver flies off bridge, car flies off bridge, bridge accident, taipei car accident, car flies off highway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803619</guid>
      <title>Prosecutors drop all charges against Empire's Jussie Smollet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Prosecutors have dropped all charges against Empire actor, Jussie Smollett, who was accused of hiring two acquaintances to stage a racial attack against him, reports CNN. According to a statement issued by the Cook County State Attorney's Office, the 16 felony disorderly conduct charges against Smolley were dropped in exchange for Smollett carrying out 16 hours of community service and a $10,000 bond forfeiture to the City of Chicago.Joseph Magats, the lead prosecutor in this case, told CNN that Smollett was not a danger to the community, however, he did clarify that he did not believe Smollett was innocent.Chicago authorities are up in arms over the decision. Chicago mayor, Rahm Emanuel told CNN that the actor was using a hate crime to advance his own career, adding, "This is without a doubt a whitewash of justice and sends a clear message that if you're in a position of influence and power, you'll get treated one way. Other people will be treated another way."Chicago police superintendent, Eddie Johnson, also expressed his disappointment during a press conference on Tuesday saying, quote, "Do I think justice was served? No. What do I think justice is? I think this city is still owed an apology." Some politicians expressed concern over what kind of precedent this staged attack was setting. Current Senator and 2020 presidential candidate Kamala Harris took to Twitter to share a message of sadness and frustration following the announcement.  In it, she says that false police reports, "not only diverts resources away from serious investigations but makes it more difficult for other victims of crime to come forward."Not everyone is unhappy about the outcome. Many celebrities close to Smollett celebrated the decision in social media. Empire star, Taraji P. Henson, told USA today she was "happy that the truth has finally been set free."The official Twitter for the writers of Empire, simply tweeted a photo of a CNN TV report on Smollett with the caption, "see y'all Wednesday. #empire #empirefox"Smollett continues to declare his innocence, right before leaving court on Tuesday he told reporters, "I have been truthful and consistent on every ingle level since Day One."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 09:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/27/3803619/3803619_AE2D54DD7B804B039DCEFC0B62631D09_190327_3803619_Prosecutors_drop_all_charges_against_Empire_s_Ju_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F5/463/8F5463E62B5E00FAFAC975293455D8ED.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, jussie smollett charges dropped, jussie smollet charges, charges dropped, Jussie Smollett, staged attack, racist attack, planned attack, fake crime, hate crime, Empire, taraji p henson, chicago police]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803463</guid>
      <title>Huawei CFO carrying iPhone, iPad, and MacBook Air when arrested</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER   Looks like someone is a bit of an Apple aficionado, unfortunately that someone is Huawei Chief Financial Officer Meng Wanzhou, who was busted last December in Vancouver on charges ranging from fraud to money laundering.   According to a court filing reported by Bloomberg, when Canadian po po arrested the Huawei executive at the behest of the U.S. on Dec. 1 during a stopover at Vancouver International Airport, they found her rocking an iPhone 7 Plus, an iPad Pro and a MacBook Air.Okay, she was carrying one sole Huawei product, the Mate 20 RS Porsche Edition.    According to Bloomberg, Meng's lawyers have filed an application seeking a copy of the data stored on the Apple products, oh yeah, and one Huawei device. They also requested the devices be sealed. In an email from Canada's justice department to Bloomberg, the crown prosecution consented and the devices will be transferred "to the British Columbia Supreme Court Registry pending an assessment of solicitor-client privilege."This isn't the first time Huawei employees have used iPhones. It demoted and cut the pay of two workers after the company's official New Year's greeting was sent out "via Twitter for iPhone."But Meng most likely will be okay, Huawei was founded by her billionaire father Ren Zhengfei. And on the bright side, it's easier to get Apple products into U.S. prisonsas long as you've got a good prison wallet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 06:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/27/3803463/3803463_30CEEF017C76416580782D008BF08107_190327_3803463_Huawei_CFO_carrying_iPhone__iPad__and_MacBook_Ai_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ECA/E98/ECAE98B1EA9F987CB6860D5FBA94F746.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Huawei, Huawei CFO Apple products, Huawei, Meng Wanzhou, Meng Wanzhou Apple, Meng Wanzhou Apple fan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803459</guid>
      <title>Pentagon conducts successful salvo missile defense test</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOMPOC, CALIFORNIA  The U.S. military said it successfully tested a missile defense system to knock down an Intercontinental Ballistic Missile class target on Monday, according to Reuters.  The test was meant to simulate how well the U.S. could respond in the event of a missile threat from a country like North Korea or Iran. The U.S. Missile Defense Agency said two ground-based interceptor missiles were launched in the test. The first interceptor hit and destroyed the re-entry vehicle, and the other "looked at the resulting debris and remaining objects, and, not finding any other re-entry vehicles, selected the next 'most lethal object' it could identify, and struck that," it said. The dummy target was launched from the Reagan Test Site in the Marshall Islands in the Pacific, more than 4,000 miles (6,400 km) from Vandenberg Air Force Base in California, where the two interceptors were launched, the agency said. According to the Associated Press, the Pentagon is putting additional billions of dollars into expanding its arsenal of missile interceptors, which are based largely at Fort Greely in Alaska.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 06:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/27/3803459/3803459_A145567C762F4567858FECDC522BEA18_190327_3803459_Pentagon_conducts_successful_salvo_missile_defen_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE8/4FC/BE84FC902892251E9259152E7DA64EAC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US missile defense system, US military missile defense system, US salvo missile defense, US interceptor missile]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3803435</guid>
      <title>New Taiwan building will have rooftop farm and market</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAINAN, TAIWAN  A Dutch architecture company has begun construction of an open-air market that will feature a roof-top farm in the south of Taiwan, according to design magazine Dezeen. Dutch firm, MVRDV, has started building the Tainan Xinhua Fruit and Vegetable Market in Taiwan's southern city of Tainan. This is being made in collaboration with the county's City Government Agriculture Bureau. The building's main purpose is to become a food supply hub for the city as well as a tourist attraction. The market will cover a total of 80,000 square meters or roughly 862,000 square feet. It will be built as an open space with a crop-terrace-like rooftop. Each level of the terrace will be used to grow different kinds of produce.A closed building will be built on one side of the market, intersecting with the terrace roof. In it will be the market's administrative offices, a restaurant, and an exhibition center.One corner of the east side of the terrace folds down and reaches ground-level. This allows visitors to walk up to the roof which has public seating and recreational areas.The building is scheduled to be complete in late 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 05:17:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/27/3803435/3803435_045F218C6A4046588D1603A33B4FA6E6_190327_3803435_New_Taiwan_building_will_have_rooftop_farm_and_m_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/29C/43A/29C43A01E67742F98DCEF1AFDFF661EB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, rooftop farm, open market, green building construction, green building design, building, green building, Taiwan, tainan taiwan, rooftop farm, open market]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804480</guid>
      <title>Google 'Dragonfly' project continues in secrecy: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  Google is carrying out secret reviews of Dragonfly, a censored search engine designed for China, according to a report by The Intercept.Google's infamous Dragonfly project, a search engine designed specifically for the Chinese government, was met with intense backlash from human rights activists and Google's own privacy team who believed the project lacked transparency.In December 2018, Google announced that it had terminated all efforts to continue the project. However, a recent investigation suggests Dragonfly is far from being terminated.  A report by The Intercept states that Google is now carrying out a secret internal review of the project.Usually, Google projects are assessed by both peers and managers, however, a source told The Intercept that a closed committee of Google execs will be examining the project directly.Other sources told The Intercept that the reviews were likely being kept secret due to the controversy Dragonfly faced when information about the project was leaked back in August 2018. At the time, only 0.35 percent of Google employees knew about the project.After the project was exposed, Google CEO Sundar Pichai told Google employees that from then on they would, quote, "definitely be transparent about Dragonfly as we get closer to actually having a plan of record. We definitely do plan to engage more and talk more."However, the project is still being kept secret from large portions of staff. An anonymous employee told The Intercept that Google was, quote, "holding any Dragonfly-specific documents out of employees' review tools, so that promotion is decided only by a committee that is read in on Dragonfly." In fact, Google employees had already suspected the project was still being developed. An Intercept report from March states that employees were carrying out independent investigations within the company.They found that code for Dragonfly had more than 400 new changes done in January and February this year, indicating that the project was still being developed. According to The Intercept, Google has not responded to requests for comments.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 21:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/29/3804480/3804480_E057780A54974D52B60A225923D4A209_190329_3804480_Google__Dragonfly__project_continues_in_secrecy__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/818/4D7/8184D78ED3264F0FBA813690FBE6CF79.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  Google, Google Project Dragonfly, Google Dragonfly, Google China censored search, Google China search, Google China Communist Party]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804361</guid>
      <title>Rescued migrants hijack merchant ship near Libya</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LIBYA  Migrants have hijacked a merchant ship which rescued them off the coast of Libya and it is now heading toward Malta, Italian Deputy Prime Minister Matteo Salvini and Maltese authorities said on Wednesday. According the FleetMon, the Palau-flagged tanker Elhiblu 1 was traveling from Turkey to Tripoli on Tuesday when it was diverted to a distressed migrant boat off the Libyan coast. According to DW News, the tanker rescued the migrants and resumed sailing toward Tripoli.  According to Salvini, when the ship was six nautical miles from port, it changed course toward Malta. According to Maltese authorities, the vessel is believed to be carrying 108 migrants made up of 77 men and 31 women. Maltese authorities confirmed the ship had been hijacked and said Maltese authorities were monitoring its progress and would not allow the vessel to dock in Malta.  Malta Today reports that a spokesperson for the Maltese armed forces said attempts to contact the ship's captain had been unsuccessful.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/28/3804361/3804361_8038EA466E114E5FB7BB350910EABB43_190328_3804361_Rescued_migrants_hijack_merchant_ship_near_Libya_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7CD/77E/7CD77E6BCDB130980E4C3C88FE03D84B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, migrants, migrants hijack ship, migrants hijack merchant ship, Libya, Malta]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804108</guid>
      <title>U.S. slams Russia after military planes deployed to Venezuela</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARACAS, VENEZUELA  The U.S. has accused Russia of meddling and aggravating political tensions in oil-rich but cash-strapped Venezuela.The Guardian reports that two Russian military planes, an Ilyushin Il-62 and an Antonov-124 cargo plane landed at Maiquetia airport near Caracas on Saturday. The two aircrafts were seen guarded by a contingent of Venezuelan national guardsmen.According to the BBC, Venezuelan journalist Javier Mayorca wrote on Twitter that 100 Russian troops disembarked with 35 tonnes of equipment.Russian military experts in the Guardian say the cargo plane may have been carrying spare parts. Venezuela was once one of the largest importers of Russian arms, and has warplanes, missiles, and other weapons in its arsenal that require maintenance.According to the Guardian, Russia is one of Venezuela's main allies, and has provided diplomatic, economic, and military support to the embattled regime of Nicolas Maduro.In December, Russia signaled its support for the oil-rich country by sending two TU-160 bombers to take part in a joint military exercise.The U.S. has repeatedly called for Maduro to resign, instead recognizing Venezuelan opposition leader Juan Guaido as the country's interim president.According to Reuters, the State Department condemned the Russian military deployment to Caracas, calling it a "reckless escalation of the situation."Secretary of State Mike Pompeo also told his Russian counterpart in a phone call to stop its "unconstructive behavior," warning that the U.S. and its allies "will not stand idly by as Russia exacerbates tensions in Venezuela."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 06:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/28/3804108/3804108_1110BE06F7054E489491BD8A48BCA1B2_190328_3804108_U_S__slams_Russia_after_military_planes_deployed_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EEA/801/EEA801322DB370D52305AD6EC73916BE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Venezuela, Russia vs US, russian military in venezuela, Nicolas Maduro, Russian planes land in Venezuela, Juan Guaido, Venezuela president]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804051</guid>
      <title>The worst ever US nuclear disaster explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIDDLETOWN, PENNSYLVANIA  Forty years ago, a calm early morning in Middletown, Pennsylvania turned chaotic when a nuclear plant began leaking toxic fumes into the atmosphere. According to the US Nuclear Regulatory Commission, roughly 140,000 people were evacuated.Today we know this as Three Mile Island Accident and here is how it all went down. On March 28, 1979, The Three Mile Island Unit 2 reactor, near Middletown, Pennsylvania partially melted down, releasing radioactive fumes into the atmosphere.According to the US Nuclear Regulatory Commission, the plant experienced its first malfunction at 4 a.m. that same day on one of the two reactors on site.A mechanical break down was causing the reactor's cooling system to fail, which in turn caused pressure in its primary system to rise. In order to fight the increasing pressure, a valve located on top of the reactor's pressurizer opened.The valve was supposed to close once the pressure levels were stabilized, however, it jammed and stayed open. Staff did not know the valve had failed to close because instruments in the control room did not indicate otherwise. It wasn't until alarms began to ring that the staff realized the reactor was releasing coolants due to the open valve.The US Nuclear Regulatory Commission reports that roughly 2 million people were exposed to a small amount of radiation, which they claim cannot cause health issues.The reactor is now permanently shut down and 99 percent of its fuel has been removed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 05:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/28/3804051/3804051_94C4B92E5E68432BAD929A00572EEBE4_190328_3804051_The_worst_ever_US_nuclear_disaster_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C7D/F13/C7DF13F9D167CDE900EF751BB5D289A0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nuclear disaster, us nuclear disaster, worst nuclear disaster, worst nuclear disasters, worst nuclear disasters, explained, nuclear accident, nuclear disaster, three mile island accident, three mile island animation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804024</guid>
      <title>Pentagon green lights $1b for Trump's border wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. Department of Defense shifted $1 billion to begin new wall construction along the U.S.-Mexico border, according to Reuters. According to the BBC, the funds are the first under the national emergency declared by President Trump to bypass Congress in order to fund his promised border wall. According to Reuters, the Pentagon chief said on Monday the money would go toward planning and building a 57-mile section of "pedestrian fencing," improved roads and lighting along the border. According to CNN, the Department of Defense authorized the Army Corp of Engineers to begin planning and construction for the project on Monday night. According to Reuters, acting Secretary of Defense Patrick Shanahan said in a memo to Secretary of Homeland Security Kirsthen Nielsen that the Department of Defense had the authority to support counter-narcotics near international boundaries. Shanahan authorized the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers to begin planning and executing the project that involves building 57-miles of 18-foot-high fencing, constructing and improving roads, and installing lighting within the Yuma and El Paso sections of border.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 04:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/28/3804024/3804024_8E30F6710946455AB75E4D284607DE88_190328_3804024_Pentagon_green_lights__1b_for_Trump_s_border_wal_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/671/C49/671C4937F5E8DA006448DDCEB612E21E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Pentagon border wall, Pentagon border fencing, border wall construction, Trump, Trump wall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804887</guid>
      <title>Head transplant doctors claim spinal cord progress</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARBIN, CHINA  Surgeons from Italy and China claimed that two studies published Wednesday add evidence to their ability to treat irreversible spinal-cord injuries that will someday lead to the world's first human head transplant, according to USA Today. Sergio Canavero and Ren Xiaoping said new work they published in the journal Surgical Neurology International showed that monkeys and dogs were able to walk again after having their spinal cords "fully transected" during surgery and then put back together. The experimental procedures were conducted at Harbin Medical University in China and were supported by video evidence. The procedure involves applying a polyethylene glycol substance, or PEG, "to mend" severed or injured spinal cords.  Further research is needed on PEG in order to establish if it is ultimately able to help patients with spinal cord injuries and paralysis. Canavero and Ren have said previously that they want to use the technique with PEG as a basis for human head transplants. According to USA Today, most medical experts say attempting the procedure in humans would be a long shot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/29/3804887/3804887_9519160DAEF145278CDD2DE26E057283_190329_3804887_Head_transplant_doctors_claim_spinal_cord_progre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/436/6DF/4366DFC8AE4DC1058EE43D402A9D8CC7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, head transplant, spinal cord repair, spinal cord injury repair, severed spinal cord injury repair, Sergio Canavero]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804874</guid>
      <title>China's 'King Kong Barbie' likes to workout in a corset</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  A 21-year-old student is turning some heads with her jacked physique over China's intranet recently.   According to the Daily Mail, Cheng Lu may only be 5 foot 1, but she can apparently squat 265 pounds, which is more than twice her body weight. Cheng, who has been dubbed 'King Kong Barbie', live streams her workout sessions twice a day on Chinese video platforms Kuaishou and Douyin. She already has around 300,000 followers on both sites that tune in to watch her lift weights in the gymmany times while rocking a corset for some strange reason. She told the Daily Mail she got into lifting after a classmate took her to a bodybuilding competition, and she's been hooked ever since. Cheng is currently studying at Shenyang Sports College and is majoring in bodybuilding.She also said, "traditionally, Chinese people think women should look weak to be beautiful, but who says we can't do things men can do, just like Mulan in the ancient times." The little Chinese Hulk said her goal is to attend more professional bodybuilding competitions in the future. Maybe leave the corset at home too.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 10:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/29/3804874/3804874_2C7F664E189E44E0A7D5C12789339F55_190329_3804874_China_s__King_Kong_Barbie__likes_to_workout_in_a_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C77/254/C77254C2886EFA643380A264AB66C2D3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, King Kong Barbie, China King Kong Barbie, workout videos, exercise videos, kuaishou, douyin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804657</guid>
      <title>China has turned censorship into a business</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANDONG, CHINA  A Chinese online newspaper is profiting from online censorship services, reports Reuters. People.cn, China's online version of one of its biggest newspapers, is offering censorship as a product. According to Reuters, the website is helping companies monitor their content including websites, applications, music, and advertisements.The company uses a combination of human analysts and artificial intelligence to monitor content. Its AI platform uses machine learning to memorize new words that have been censored as well as government censorship rules. If there is data that the machine cannot categorize, it gets passed on to human analysts.Currently, they are providing services to Chinese news aggregator Jinri Toutiao, helping them detect and delete material that is not approved by the government. They also have a partnership with Liangziyun, a tech company that manages roughly 1,000 social media accounts.As of January, the company's net income has increased by 140 percent, that is equal to a net-profit of nearly $32 million.An independent researcher, named An, told Reuters that the censorship business will continue to grow, stating, 'with the development of 5G, the space and scale for the online content censorship market will only grow bigger and bigger.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 06:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/29/3804657/3804657_EE188D00EC4E483FAC6A2E77601E2431_190329_3804657_China_has_turned_censorship_into_a_business_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/754/D28/754D28F628CD2410E1CD5C953A0835B9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china censorship, china censorship laws, china censorship internet, chinese censorship, china media censorship, chinese censorship laws, chinese internet censorship, internet censorship,i nternet censorship in china, internet censorship, chinese firewall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804636</guid>
      <title>First direct look at super-Jupiter exoplanet reveals stormy skies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  Astronomers have made the first direct observation of an exoplanet using a technique known as optical interferometry.According to a press release from the European Southern Observatory or ESO, the exoplanet HR8799e was discovered in 2010, 129 light years from Earth in the Pegasus constellation.It is one of three planets orbiting around the star HR8799. CNN reports that the exoplanet lies closest to its host star, and takes 40 to 50 years to make a full orbit.Using the GRAVITY instrument on ESO's Very Large Telescope Interferometer, ESO scientists found that HR8799e is a 'super-Jupiter.' It is much more massive than any planet in our solar system, but also younger.Due to leftover energy from its formation and a powerful greenhouse effect, the temperature on HR8799e is an inhospitable 1,000 degrees Celsius or about 1,616 Fahrenheit.According to ESO, analysis showed that the exoplanet's atmosphere has more carbon monoxide than methane.Clouds of iron and silicate dust were also found, which when combined with the excess carbon monoxide, suggests a huge, violent storm in HR8799e's atmosphere.CNN reports that researchers are planning long-term follow up observations of HR8799e, and can study it more to learn more about the formation of planets and planetary systems.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 06:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/29/3804636/3804636_3B4425A276734521813EFAC0FED3D238_190329_3804636_First_direct_look_at_super_Jupiter_exoplanet_rev_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5E3/08B/5E308BED4E3FE36EC7450B8D4C2A92F8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, super Jupiter, exoplanet, new planet, HR8799e, Pegasus constellation, VLTI, European Southern Observatory, ESO]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804516</guid>
      <title>Scientists develop birth control earrings to prevent pregnancy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA  Scientists from the Georgia Institute of Technology have developed a novel form of birth control that's literally as simple as putting on an earring.A report published in the Journal of Controlled Release describes a technique that administers contraceptive hormones transdermally, via patches that can be mounted on earrings, necklaces, rings, or wristwatches.Contraceptive patches are already available, but the team believe incorporating them into jewelry could allow for a more attractive and discreet method of drug delivery.According to a press release from the Georgia Institute of Technology, researchers tested an earring patch that consisted of three layers.One layer is impermeable and contains an adhesive to hold it onto a piece of jewelry. The middle layer contains the contraceptive hormone in solid form, while the outer layer is a skin adhesive that allows the hormone to be transferred.Once it is in the skin, the contraceptive drug moves into the bloodstream and can then circulate through the body.The earring patches were tested on pigs' ears and the skin of hairless rats by being applied for sixteen hours and removed for 8.While drug levels dropped when the earrings were off, the patches were found to produce the necessary amounts of the hormone in the blood.The technology has yet to be tested on humans, but if ultimately used in the future, the patches would have be changed periodically, most likely on a weekly basis.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 02:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/29/3804516/3804516_B4858105B56E4DD081041ACBC3FCAE09_190329_3804516_Scientists_develop_birth_control_earrings_to_pre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3F2/DF3/3F2DF3291185CAF58C592D7037062E00.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, contraceptive earrings, contraceptive jewelry, pharmaceutical jewelry, birth control earrings, birth control jewelry, contraceptives, contraception, birth control]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3804492</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia using water from bone-dry California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLYTHE, CALIFORNIA  A Saudi Arabian food conglomerate is using Californian land and water for free through a century-old legal loop-hole, reports The Guardian.  Fondomonte Farms, a subsidiary from a Saudi Arabian food conglomerate called Almarai, owns 16 percent of the irrigated land in Blythe, California. They use this land to grow alfalfa which is then exported to Saudi Arabia as feed for the company's cows.Blythe is an arid region in California, however, its land is irrigated by the lower Colorado River. This river is also the main water supply for nearly 40 million people. Currently, the river is drying up due to climate change.According to The Guardian, Fondomonte Farms is using a loop-hole from a law dating back to the 1800s to benefit from the scarce water supply in the region for free. An 1877 water claim approved by the government allowed farmers and those living within the district to consume as much water as they needed for free due to the shortage of water in Blythe.The Palo Verde Irrigation District cannot sell the water in the area, they can only charge farmers $77 per acre-foot to cover the water district's overhead.  Apart from owning land in California, Almarai also owns 10,000 acres of land in Arizona that it bought back in 2014 as well as 30,000 acres in Argentina acquired in 2012.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 00:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/03/29/3804492/3804492_CB4B7AEDFD5341DB955B57DB62B6AFFA_190329_3804492_Saudi_Arabia_using_water_from_bone_dry_Californi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D84/8EC/D848EC19C5A0AF45027E14538A78789A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Saudi Arabia, California, drought, California drought, Saudi Arabia business, Saudi Arabia, Almarai, severe drought]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
