<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 19:31:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3665606</guid>
      <title>Apple's iCloud data to be stored in China's state-owned servers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA    Apple has announced state-owned China Telecom will now store iCloud user data in China.Apple had originally made a deal with Guizhou-Cloud Big Data, to move data from U.S. based servers to Chinese servers, reports TechCrunch.China Telecom then made a deal with Guizhou-Cloud Big Data to provide storage for iCloud in China.The encryption keys to iCloud data used to be stored in the U.S. but now will more than likely be stored in China.In a statement, Apple says it was forced to comply with new Chinese laws.Apple also told Reuters, even though they "advocated against iCloud being subject to these laws," they were ultimately unsuccessful.There are privacy concerns as this gives the Chinese government easier access to personal information, reports the BBC.However, Apple claims users in China can choose to opt out by choosing a country other than China for their iCloud account.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 12:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/31/3665606/3665606_9AB701770B7F4C54A42311614C1BD5E3_180731_3665606_Apple_s_iCloud_data_to_be_stored_in_China_s_stat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/255/C6F/255C6F1B02669CCEF1BD6C7ADF2827D8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  China, Apple, iCloud, China Telecom, privacy, user data, user storage, iCloud data, security concerns, encryption, privacy concerns, personal information, Chinese servers, US based servers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665397</guid>
      <title>Video of woman harassed and slapped by stranger goes viral</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  A video posted by a young French woman with the intention of putting a spotlight on sexual harassment has gone viral. In less than three days, it reached nearly 3 million views on Youtube. It was posted by Marie Laguerre, a 22-year-old architecture student living in Paris.On August, 24th, she was walking back home when a man in his thirties allegedly verbally harassed her. She said he wasn't the first person to do that that day. She was particularly upset and told him to 'shut up'. She thought the man didn't hear her, but the cafe's CCTV footage shows him grabbing an ashtray and throwing it at her.As if this wasn't enough, he doubles back and hits the poor girl in the face.Some bystanders tried to confront the aggressor, but he was quick to leave. Laguerre went back home, saying she was shocked by the violence. She realized her face was bruised and decided to go back to the scene of the incident a few minutes later. The cafe's owner gave her the security surveillance tape and took her to the nearest police station to file a complaint.The aggression caught on camera has revived a nationwide discussion about street harassment. France's gender equality minister reacted in an interview, saying she felt 'outraged'.The young woman explained that she put the footage online because this isn't just about her. According to her post, she says:  "I am sick of feeling unsafe walking in the street. Things need to change."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 09:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/31/3665397/3665397_FF4DB662D21743CB9E49ABFAAF20359B_180731_3665397_Video_of_woman_harassed_and_slapped_by_stranger__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D6F/190/D6F1904B3F0BD535737993FAD3995BD7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, MeToo, metoo, gender equality, Paris, France, street, cafe, Marie Laguerre, feminism, sexual harassment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665317</guid>
      <title>Massive sandstorm swallows Chinese city apocalypse style</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GOLMUD, CHINA  A massive sandstorm a couple of weeks agoswallowed Golmud city, in the Chinese province of Qinghai, severely reducing visibility. Golmud, in the Chinese province of Qinghai, is located high-up on the Tibetan plateau, 9,200 feet above sea level. Hence, the region often experiences extreme meteorological conditions. A week ago, while the rest of the country was facing record-hot temperatures and torrential rain showers, the area saw a significant amount of snowfall.But on June 25th, around 7:30 p.m., the people of Golmud suddenly had a much more terrifying vision. A massive cloud of sand suddenly appeared, coming fast toward the city. Netizens were quick to grab their phones and film the apocalyptic phenomenon. For an unknown reason, the Chinese government decided to take down most footage from social media.According to local reports, the gigantic cloud was almost 300 feet high. Within the cloud, visibility was extremely reduced, down to 300 feet in the outskirts of Golmud. Authorities issued warnings through loudspeakers, asking drivers not to go faster than 25 miles per hour. No casualties were reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 07:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/31/3665317/3665317_2FDA2AFC493F49BC93AE0D4342C4C77D_180731_3665317_Massive_sandstorm_swallows_Chinese_city_apocalyp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/906/4D9/9064D959505A5E848A6FB634F1E05034.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, Qinghai, Golmud, sandstorm, sand cloud, sand, desert, storm, apocalypse, end of the world, crazy weather, weather phenomenon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665306</guid>
      <title>'In my feelings' challenge is the new dumb challenge</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MERICA  Canadian rapper, singer, songwriter Drake has once again shaped the world of social media with his newest music. The dance, known as the "Do The Shiggy dance", created by comedian Shiggy, was inspired by Drake's latest song "In My Feelings" from his new album "Scorpion", and yes, another dumb, i mean, a viral challenge is born. The "In My Feelings challenge," aka the "Kiki challenge" involves people jumping out of a moving car and dancing alongside it to Drake's hit "In My Feelings," while the car continues moving.And of course, some smart aleck tried to do the challenge and … got hit by his own car, luckily he only got a few scratches.Some other people have been filmed crashing into poles, tripping on potholes or falling out of the cars.Celebrities, including Will Smith and Ciara, have joined in on the challenge by posting their own videos of the dance  at least they were smart enough not to jump out of a moving car. While the trend is still going on, America's National Transportation Safety Board is urging people to stop jumping out of cars for Drake, as it is probably best to listen to just his music while inside a moving vehicle.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 07:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/31/3665306/3665306_C89048D7E7264BB79C50C9910D3BC09F_180731_3665306__In_my_feelings__challenge_is_the_new_dumb_chall_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/82E/48E/82E48EA8B15CFD295B087F4D1422750A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, in my feelings, in my feelings challenge, in my feelings challenge fails, in my feelings dance, drake in my feelings, in my feelings challenge gone wrong, viral challenge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665120</guid>
      <title>Time capsule from 1968 to be opened in September</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMARILLO, TEXAS  A time capsule from the year 1968 will be opened in September this year, 50 years after it was placed inside the Helium Time monument in Texas.The Helium Time monument is a six story, stainless steel structure which was made to commemorate the 100th anniversary of the discovery of helium.The monument holds four time capsule columns that are slanted and hold books, artifacts, and documents to "tell the future generation about … life … in 1968," reports the Atlas Obscura.Helium is pumped into each column to "protect fragile documents" and other items from deteriorating.Each of the time capsules are scheduled to be opened at different time periods. The first one was opened after 25 years in 1993, and the rest will be opened after 50, 100, and 1000 years after their placements. The monument was reportedly created to remind future generations "the importance for efficiently utilizing natural resources."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 02:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/31/3665120/3665120_1C1FC16A466C44A2AF95541610FA705A_180731_3665120_Time_capsule_from_1968_to_be_opened_in_September_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/910/9F8/9109F813B63B7BE946AC6686EA659C76.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, Time capsule, monument, 1968, time-capsule columns, helium, helium-filled columns, natural resources, books, artifacts, documents]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665113</guid>
      <title>Old railway to be transformed into green corridor in central Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN    An old railway in central Taiwan will soon be designed into a public green space, reports Taiwan News.Part of the old railway will be transformed into a mile-long partially elevated greenway, where people can stroll around.The new green corridor will also include a bicycle lane.Mecanoo, the architecture firm designing the project, explained there will also be a tree-lined river along the newly transformed green corridor.Mecanoo said their goal is to "preserve the area's strong historic character" while giving new life to the old railway.The firm plans to integrate gardens, playgrounds, parks etc into the green corridor, reports Inhabitant.Local media reports the green corridor will be a space for leisure and recreational activities.Reports from local media say the project is expected to start later this year and be completed by 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 02:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/07/31/3665113/3665113_77538B4D183C485883D3FAA5BC385E43_180731_3665113_Old_railway_to_be_transformed_into_green_corrido_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/100/146/100146C0188A0E09DB8321E7E6F698F5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, Taiwan, railway, old railway, railroads, train tracks, Green space, public green space, public space design, going green, green design, green corridor, old railway to turn into green corridor, greenway]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666248</guid>
      <title>Facebook uncovers disinformation campaign to influence midterms</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook has uncovered a disinformation campaign that may have been aimed at influencing the upcoming U.S. midterm elections.According to a report from Facebook, 32 false pages and accounts on Facebook and Instagram between March 2017 and May 2018 have been removed after they violated a ban on coordinated inauthentic behavior.The operatives put out a total of 9,500 posts Facebook, luring 290,000 people, who reportedly followed at least one of the pages.From April 2017 to June this year, the accounts ran 150 ads worth $11,000, paid for in American and Canadian dollars. They also created 30 events which attracted the interest of 4,700 accounts.One bogus page that promoted a counterprotest even coordinated with administrators from legitimate pages to co-host the event. Those admins have since been notified.Facebook COO Sheryl Sandberg says investigation into the operation is still ongoing, reports the Washington Post.And while they haven't expressly identified the Russians as the culprits, tools and techniques used in this case were similar to those used by the Internet Research Agency, a Kremlin-linked group believed to have interfered with the 2016 presidential elections.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 10:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/01/3666248/3666248_A07B285591AC4EEDAF150095B5202D53_180801_3666248_Facebook_uncovers_disinformation_campaign_to_inf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9C8/EE4/9C8EE44BC3701CF369815A96A0C45781.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Facebook, fake accounts, Instagram, 2018 midterms, midterm elections, disinformation campaign, disinformation operation, Russian interference, internet research agency, politics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666196</guid>
      <title>Toddler hospitalised over bacterial infection from Florida beach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KEY BISCAYNE, FLORIDA  A Florida mom is warning the public after her 3-year-old daughter developed a bacterial infection at a south Florida beach.On July 21, Anais[f] Monteagudo celebrated her daughter Aaliyah's third birthday at Florida's Crandon beach in Key Biscayne[g]. Towards the end of the day though, Monteagudo noticed that her daughter's skin was red and swollen. Over the next few days, Aaliyah[h]'s infection developed into blisters that appeared on her lips, face, and arms. Monteagudo took her daughter to the hospital on July 24, where she saw others getting treated for similar symptoms, doctors said there's been a lot of similar cases coming from Key Biscayne[i] area.In her Facebook post, Monteagudo wrote about her her daughter's pain and how she will most likely develop scars all over hands and chin because of the infection.When Monteagudo got home, she learned that the Florida Department of Health in Miami-Dade County had put out an advisory on July 18 warning people against swimming due to high levels of fecal bacteria. NBC reports Monteagudo has since admitted that she should have checked the advisory to see if there were warnings before she took her daughter to the beach. She is now advising others to be more cautious before doing the same.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 09:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/01/3666196/3666196_BF671845F02C40939A5C51B0E97E29F2_180801_3666196_Toddler_hospitalised_over_bacterial_infection_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9A0/F65/9A0F6548D96A83A8EF8987E564118D68.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bacterial infection beach, bacterial infection florida beach, bacterial infection from beach water, signs of bacterial infection from beach, bacterial infection, bacterial infection on skin, bacterial infection symptoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666143</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Episode 8</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured by cops from around the globe.THIS WEEK: 1. Perth Amboy, New Jersey: Officer Savoia was dispatched to the railroad tracks for a welfare check. He ended up saving a man's life.2. Marshfield, Massachusetts: Police use bean bag rounds and K9 to subdue a threatening man.3. Scotland: A cow charges a Scottish cop who is trying to keep the road clear.4. Provo, Utah: An unnamed man helps catch a fleeing suspect.5. Atlanta: Officer rescues a 1-year-old baby locked inside a sweltering car.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 08:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/01/3666143/3666143_4929965DEB0247C38328B4DAC77B8B65_180801_3666143_LAWMAN_CAM__Episode_8_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A2D/140/A2D1408D1B1D9BA6B99B59B7F8677440.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, good cop, hero cops, cops doing amazing things, latest police videos, new police videos,  latest cop video, new cop footage, police footage, police body cam, police dash cam, police compilation 2018, cop videos, police chase 2018, latest police chase videos, crazy car chases, police pursuit,, us police videos, cop camera, lawman cam, tomonews lawman cam, police responding, police news, latest police video, latest police videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665880</guid>
      <title>Study shows being dehydrated can affect your cognitive ability</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  A study published in the Medicine & Science in Sports & Exercise shows that even becoming mildly dehydrated has the ability to affect one's ability to think clearly.Dehydration can impair the brain's ability to complete tasks such as proofreading, mental math, and even map recognition, reports Reuters.Mindy Millard-Stafford, co-author of the study, told NPR that it wouldn't take long to become mildly dehydrated in the summer, especially if you exercise outside.The study found that participants lost up to 1 to 6 percent of fluids equal to their body mass through exercise alone.Millard-Stafford commented to Reuters, saying human brain cells need water just like the cells in muscle.However, NPR reports, coffee or other caffeinated beverages also have a hydrating effect.Dr. Ronald Roth, a professor at the University of Pittsburgh School of Medicine, said if a person experiences fatigue, confusion, and muscle weakness among other symptoms, is a reminder to consume more fluids.Dr. Roth also said it is important to know when you are overdoing it and taking in too much water as that may lead to hyponatremia, which is an excess of water in the body compared to the ratio of sodium, Reuters reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 02:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/01/3665880/3665880_A81DF441D4944DF984C3753CE63C3633_180801_3665880_Study_shows_being_dehydrated_can_affect_your_cog_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CD8/44C/CD844C71623CFFDA2EC6345455332BCA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Study, mental performance, cognitive thinking, dehydration, mildly dehydrated, water intake, brainpower, fluids, water, dehydration symptoms, being dehydrated affects cognitive thinking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3665873</guid>
      <title>The different ways you could potentially lose your bitcoins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  With the rise of cryptocurrency, there is also the risk of losing your digital currency because of its decentralized model.Fraud is on the rise for cryptocurrency as anonymous accounts are usually used and there is no way of noticing suspicious transactions, reports Entrepreneur Asia Pacific.Password recovery can also be a problem because of the complex structure put in to supposedly prevent fraud, denying people access to their own account.Hacking is another issue for cryptocurrency. There are a large amount of crypto wallets out there which once hacked, won't ever be able to recover the digital money because of a weak security system.Virtual currency scams is another reason why some end up losing their cryptocurrency, with some on social media offering to send you a 100 Ether coins, or any other digital currency, if you send them just one, reports Bloomberg.As the number of cryptocurrencies available online keep on growing, sooner or later it may have to regulated because of the amounts of problems caused by deregulation of crypto.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 02:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/01/3665873/3665873_28D27A42A4EB4038A382BD3D1F43C0FD_180801_3665873_The_different_ways_you_could_potentially_lose_yo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/902/66D/90266D055CF316D650B745ADCB918FFA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cryptocurrency, hacking, virtual money, bitcoin, virtual scams, deregulation, crypto, hacking, password recover, fraud, digital currency, cryptocurrency explained, cryptocurrency investing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667273</guid>
      <title>Japanese company debuts
moving mosque for Muslims</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO    A Tokyo-based company is planning to launch a mobile mosque ahead of the 2020 Summer Olympics, reports Japan Today.The moving mosque takes the form of a large white and blue truck that expands into a place of worship.The back of the truck is able to flip open to reveal an entrance. The width of the truck would then double as the side of the truck slides out.A 48-square-meter room inside the truck should accommodate about 50 people at a time.Outdoor taps and a washing area would also be included in the mosque to allow worshippers to cleanse themselves before prayer.Yasuharu Inoue, the CEO of the project, said they want to share the idea of "omotenashi" or Japanese hospitality, with Muslim people.Inoue also said he hopes the mobile  mosque will help Muslim visitors feel at home as it would be able to travel to different Olympic venues if necessary.Inoue said he was inspired to create a mobile mosque after a trip to Qatar a few years ago.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 16:08:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3667273/3667273_0A7274DDC6954995BC178FDBC667F83F_180803_3667273_Japanese_company_debuts_moving_mosque_for_Muslim_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FBF/BD2/FBFBD2EABC10471B8EA0977CF79D22F4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Japan, Muslims, Mosque, Mobile Mosque, Japan Olympics 2020, Olympics 2020, prayer, religion, mosque prayer, mosque service, Japan tourism, mosque on wheels, olympics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667269</guid>
      <title>Queen's guard pushes annoying Chinese tourist out of the way</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WINDSOR / UNITED KINGDOM  A video showing a supposedly Chinese tourist shoved by a member of the Queen's guard has gone viral.The woman crossed the barrier preventing visitors from entering the prohibited area of the castle grounds to take a photo. The Queen's guard firmly pushed her before continuing his way.The short video was uploaded two weeks ago on Chinese social media Weibo, but it didn't mention the date of the incident. The original post  that has since been deleted  called the guard out for his "arrogance".BBC reporter Tim Hague reshared the footage, and tried to explain to Chinese netizens that the Queen's guard is an elite unit with very strict rules.The video also quickly gained popularity on Western media, reaching nearly 800,000 views on Youtube. Most netizens approved the guard's reaction, and blamed the tourist for not respecting the rules.Chinese travellers are regularly pointed out for their bad behavior when travelling abroad, which led the government to issue a 'Guide to Civilised Tourism and Travel' in 2013.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 16:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3667269/3667269_2ECA475A8CC94D158EA59284C203DB24_180803_3667269_Queen_s_guard_pushes_annoying_Chinese_tourist_ou_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9EF/9D1/9EF9D1CD46B0748658B478049E029839.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[Tomo News, News, tourists, Chinese tourists, China, UK, United Kingdom, Queen's Guard, Windsor, Windsor castle, tourist pushed away, guard shoves tourist, tourists behaving badly,  tourists taking pictures, viral]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666935</guid>
      <title>Rolls-Royce develops flying taxis that could be in the skies by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  Rolls-Royce is planning to launch a four-to-five seat flying taxi with a maximum speed of 250 miles per hour, reports the BBC.Rolls-Royce Motor Cars, which is owned by German car manufacturer BMW, is not related to this venture of creating flying taxis, according to the Chicago Tribune.The vehicle would be powered by six electric propulsors,using gas turbine energy.Rolls-Royce claims the flying taxi would also be able to take off and land vertically because of the wings ability to rotate 90 degrees.The company also claims that once the vehicle reaches its cruising height, its propellers would automatically "fold away and rely on several rear propellers for thrust."The EVTOL, or electric vertical take-off and landing vehicle, could be flying in the sky in the 2020s, reports Phys Org.According to a statement published by the company, the vehicle could be used for military purposes as well as cargo or personal use.The launch details were announced during the Farnborough International Airshow in Hampshire, located in the southern coast of England.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 08:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/02/3666935/3666935_B1B6EE8C4E764A1C9D5CCA02F60CA983_180802_3666935_Rolls_Royce_develops_flying_taxis_that_could_be__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F30/EA7/F30EA7230F3BB25A377205CAB2C017B6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, flying taxi, flying vehicles, skies, Rolls-Royce, gas turbines, vertical take off, vertical landing, Electric vertical take-off and landing vehicle, EVTOL, hybrid-electric vehicle, taking to the skies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666923</guid>
      <title>Breastfeeding moms who drink  may lower child's cognitive ability</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA    A recently published study found that children exposed to alcohol through breast milk may have reduced cognitive abilities.In the study, breastfeeding moms were asked about their alcohol consumption and their smoking habits with a questionnaire, reports CBS News.The study was then tested the children of these moms on their vocabulary, nonverbal reasoning, and cognitive processing every two years until the age of 11.Children of mothers who drank were shown to have lower test scores than those who didn't from age 6 to 7.However, the effects don't seem to be long-lasting as the same results weren't seen when the children turned 10 to 11.Dr. Elissa Rubin, medical director of Happy and Healthy Pediatrics, told CBS News that a mother should not breastfeed if she "feels any of the effects of alcohol in her system.."However, Dr. Rubin said an occasional glass of wine is fine as long as women drink water and eat a full meal afterwards.Smoking didn't appear to have an effect on children's cognitive ability, however researchers warn it still isn't a good idea to smoke.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 08:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-video/C24/41D/C2441DF72EF14EC292EEC70768E64AB1" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F4F/6FF/F4F6FFB12D7EDD3ED978D4BE8E5F6E66.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Study, researchers, infants, breast milk, alcohol, alcohol in breast milk, moms, breastfeeding, alcohol intake, study shows alcohol in breast milk may affect children's thinking]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666878</guid>
      <title>Shark stolen by thieves from aquarium in a baby stroller</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LEON VALLEY, TEXAS  Leon Valley police say three people took stole a horn shark from the San Antonio Aquarium Saturday afternoon.The shark has since been safely returned to the aquarium.According to the aquarium's Facebook page, the heist began with the trio stealing a female 16-inch-long horn shark named Helen from a open pool with their own net. The aquarium said the group later entered a filter room where they poured a bucket of bleach solution into the cold water exhibit filtration system. They then wrapped the shark in a wet blanket, put it in a bucket, and placed the bucket in a baby stroller. According to the surveillance footage provided by the aquarium, the trio was seen pushing the stroller away when an employee who walked past noticed something wasn't right.KSAT said the aquarium general manager rushed out to try to stop them, but one of the group refused, said his son was sick and drove away quickly, leaving his partners in crime behind.When police entered one of the suspects' residences, they were surprised to see that the culprit had an aquarium in his home. Luckily, the horn shark is still in good shape.Police arrested the suspect immediately, and the shark was returned to the San Antonio Aquarium.The arrested suspect was later identified as Anthony Shannon, 38, he was released from police custody after posting a $10,000 bail Tuesday afternoon.Police told KSAT that Shannon had some knowledge on how to handle marine life, and had a shark similar to the horn shark he stole. After the one he owned died he wanted to keep the stolen one as a pet to go with the other sea creatures in his fish tanks.KSAT said more arrests are expected in the case and police are working with the National Oceanic Atmospheric Administration to see if federal charges can be filed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 07:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/02/3666878/3666878_AC995F5A52BF46FD8AC57AE564839360_180802_3666878_Shark_stolen_by_thieves_from_aquarium_in_a_baby__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/143/7E0/1437E0943EBF93C7747E7AADC1DF5E35.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, stealing shark, shark stolen , shark stolen, shark stolen aquarium, shark stolen from texas aquarium, shark stolen from san antonio aquarium, san antonio aquarium shark]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666840</guid>
      <title>Demolition process goes wrong : building collapses on excavator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGRAO, CHINA  A building collapsed on an excavator operator after he misjudged the situation and parked in the wrong place.On July 29 in Shangrao City in the southeast of China, an unnamed excavator operator was instructed to take a small building down. He was pretty successful in demolishing the house, but he should've revised his basics about gravity.The operator completely misjudged the direction in which the building would collapse. The excavator ended up buried under a tide of rubble. Miraculously, no one was injured.The video went viral in China, reaching nearly 5 million views in less than two days. Netizens left comments advising the operator to start studying physics.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 07:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/02/3666840/3666840_F30A89D802EA4272B410B091898D55E2_180802_3666840_Demolition_process_goes_wrong___building_collaps_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/7C3/758/7C3758CD3EBA4C1BB5CC7E01FF694D83.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, caught on camera, dust cloud, demolition, demolishing, building collapse, excavator, operator, China, Jiangxi, Shangrao, miracle, safety issue]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3666661</guid>
      <title>Man contracts deadly infection from his dog's saliva</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MILWAUKEE, WISCONSIN   A man lost his arms and legs after his dog's saliva caused a blood infection in his body, reports The Washington Post.Greg Manteufel suffered from sepsis, or blood poisoning, from the bacteria called Capnocytophaga canimorsus after it entered his bloodstream from his dog's saliva.His wife was quick to rush him to the hospital after he went into septic shock, reports Milwaukee Patch.Apparently the sepsis caused Manteufel to develop multiple blood spots which looked like bruises on his chest, face and the rest of his body.The doctors then tried to stop the infection from spreading with antibiotics. However, that blocked blood flow and caused some tissue and muscles to die.According to The Washington Post, the doctors then amputated his legs from the knee down, as well as his hands.Dr. Silvia Munoz-Price, an infectious disease specialist, noted that Manteufel had contracted a rare infection and "more than 99 percent of people … will never have this issue ..."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 02:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/02/3666661/3666661_16D4C444027F46DBA15339C412BC67A3_180802_3666661_Man_contracts_deadly_infection_from_his_dog_s_sa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FC2/FCD/FC2FCD37A705274C95853B3215384647.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dog, saliva, infection, sepsis, septic shock, antibiotics, blood spots, blood infection, lost limbs, man's best friend]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3668080</guid>
      <title>Former waitress pays $1,000 back to restaurant she stole from</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TUCSON, ARIZONA  A former waitress is trying to make things right after stealing from a Mexican restaurant she worked at more than 20 years ago.Carlotta Flores, who owns El Charro restaurant in Tucson, Arizona received a letter last week from woman who had worked for Flores in the 1990s while attending the University of Arizona.In the letter, the woman who identified herself as a "thankful former employee" confessed that she was encouraged by fellow waiter to 'forget' to ring in a few drinks and pocket some cash.The former employee explained she grew up in the church environment and the theft was out of her character.And claimed she was a terrible waitress and was thankful that she was fired before the money she stole could add up to more than a few hundred dollars.Twenty years later, the woman said in the letter that she still carries great remorse and she's very sorry for the theft she committed. With the letter was an attached $1,000, which was a repayment added with 20 years of interest.In an interview with KVOA-TV, Flores said the letter deeply moved her and her employees. She added the letter had restored her faith in humanity, as her purse was recently stolen and the letter made her believe that there's still a lot of good people out there.Flores told reporters that the letter has made an impact on her, her business, and her family, adding that she hopes the woman will come forward so she can return the money.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3668080/3668080_E9C38AECCF5C42C38F1D087591EE7406_180803_3668080_Former_waitress_pays__1_000_back_to_restaurant_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C1C/2E2/C1C2E2DDF453DD507AECA14F73B4A423.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, good hearted people, honest waitress, honest people, make things right, stealing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3668071</guid>
      <title>CDC advises people not to wash, reuse condoms</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA, GEORGIA  It may be 2018, but Americans still need to be told to not reuse their rubbers.On the one hand, the Yanks at least know they ought to put on love gloves when they bang. But some folks who are either cheap, stupid, or misguidedly environmentally friendly have apparently taken to washing and reusing their Trojans, reports Fox 2 Now.Not only is it gross, but it also stops being useful protection against STDs, unwanted pregnancies, and other nasties.It's probably no coincidence that chlamydia, gonorrhea, and syphilis cases in the States have recently reached record highs. So much so that last week, the CDC had to tweet out what should've been pretty obvious advice, basically reminding people that their Durexes are single-use.There's ways to get prophylactics cheap or free, so please, for humanity's sake, put on a fresh one each time you're expecting action.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 14:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3668071/3668071_DBA60D42F35B414E83110945E9457AE2_180803_3668071_CDC_advises_people_not_to_wash__reuse_condoms_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/54A/45A/54A45AC3E83FDC8ADCBEF36CA65FFEAC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, condoms, rubber, CDC, condom safety, protection, reusing rubbers, do not reuse, reusable condoms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3668068</guid>
      <title>Mia Khalifa to get surgery after hockey puck busts implant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  Mia Khalifa needs to go under the knife after one of her implants got busted while watching this year's NHL run.The American-Lebanese adult star turned sports presenter told the Daily Star had been cheering on her team at the Stanley Cup playoffs when the incident occurred.A hockey puck was somehow sent flying towards the stands, shooting over the glass and catching the 25-year-old off guard.The 170 gram rubber puck smashed right into her left melon and ruptured her implant, though Khalifa says on an Instagram post it was worth it since she got to take the souvenir puck home. Way to look on the bright side.After the smash hit, Khalifa's left jug is now looking a bit deflated, so she's planning on surgery to get it fixed early next year.She claims it's not the most painful thing to have happened to her seeing her team lose once before was apparently way worse.Well, guess the Washington Capitals coming out as the 2018 champions at least makes her busted bust more bearable.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 14:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3668068/3668068_85DA38BEC0E440E39615A4E8B6C248F2_180803_3668068_Mia_Khalifa_to_get_surgery_after_hockey_puck_bus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/460/8CB/4608CB00D267C7A2120DF643EE7D7BBF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mia khalifa, celebrity, sports star, implants, ruptured implants, hockey, hockey accident, hockey injury, hockey puck, stray hockey puck, washington capitals, capital one arena]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667758</guid>
      <title>Study shows there's not enough CO2 in Mars to make it Earth-like</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARS    A new study from NASA shows that it may not be possible to make Mars habitable for humans using current technology.According to the research conducted by NASA, there isn't enough carbon dioxide on Mars required to create an Earth-like atmosphere.Mars does have carbon dioxide in its rocks and polar ice caps, reports Space.com.However, even if all the carbon dioxide was released, it wouldn't be enough to raise the atmospheric pressure to 1 bar which is necessary for the temperatures at the pole to be above the melting point of water.Apparently, Elon Musk does not agree with the scientists, and tweeted, "there's a massive amount of CO2 on Mars absorbed into soil that'd be released upon heating."The scientists said even if carbon dioxide from the soil were to be released, it would require the entire planet of Mars to be heated 100 meters below the surface which could take upto 10,000 years.They did agree that the released carbon dioxide could raise the atmospheric pressure, however it wouldn't be enough to warm up the atmosphere.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 09:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3667758/3667758_B76FE72B5975449D94A6E4A2B9AB520F_180803_3667758_Study_shows_there_s_not_enough_CO2_in_Mars_to_ma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ECA/AF5/ECAAF5F36822FF00C6C46CDBCA79AAB4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Mars, Space, NASA, terraforming Mars, carbon dioxide, habitable, making Mars habitable, atmosphere, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667720</guid>
      <title>Chinese man drowns expensive car in river to save on $3 car wash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENGDU, CHINA  A Chinese man parked his expensive car in a small river to avoid a car wash. The vehicle ended up being washed away.A Chinese man decided that he didn't want to $3 on getting his white Land Rover professionally washed, so he found a creative way to get a free car wash. He drove his car to a river nearby Chengdu, and parked it in the current.Unfortunately for him, his offbeat idea backfired pretty fast. The overlooking dam suddenly opened, releasing more water in the river and washing his car away. He was lucky enough to escape the vehicle before it was too late. Firemen intervened to rescue the individual.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 08:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3667720/3667720_559BEC899A944EFD85C9890319624552_180803_3667720_Chinese_man_drowns_expensive_car_in_river_to_sav_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B9D/6AD/B9D6AD3750FEBDF4BDE1C03D1ED0B7FE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, China, Sichuan, Chengdu, car wash, river, car drowned, genius idea, cheapskate, stingy guy, stingy man,  Land Rover, Range Rover, dumb idea, dam]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667707</guid>
      <title>China plans to capture an asteroid and bring it down to Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA   A group of Chinese scientists are planning to capture a small asteroid near Earth to study it for its resources. So far, the scientists have targeted an asteroid which is 6.4 meters in diameter and weighs several hundred tons, reports Xinhua.Li Ming Tao, a researcher involved with the project, said they aim to "turn asteroids with a potential threat to Earth into usable resources."The Chinese scientists plan to send a spacecraft with a huge bag which would wrap around a small asteroid and push it to Earth.The spacecraft would then unfold a heat shield which would "reduce the velocity of the asteroid" from 12.5 kilometers per second to 140 meters per second when it enters Earth's atmosphere.The scientists plan to study the asteroid and may choose to mine it for its resources.The asteroids may contain traces of history about the origins of the solar system and the origin of water and life on our planet, Xinhua reports.The team plans to launch the asteroid catcher by 2029 and bring back an asteroid by 2034.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 08:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3667707/3667707_8C0D020095804BC992721F239EE98280_180803_3667707_China_plans_to_capture_an_asteroid_and_bring_it__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DD2/94C/DD294C614FEAE83677E667AABA3DB11C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, scientists, asteroids, spacecraft, mining asteroids, capturing an asteroid, heat shield, space, bringing an asteroid to earth, minerals, spaceship, exploring space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667632</guid>
      <title>FDA warns against vaginal rejuvenation devices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SILVER SPRING, MARYLAND  The FDA has a message for anyone who's thinking of getting their nether regions done up: don't do it!Once upon a time, vag rejuvenation was something women had done to get cancerous cells or warts out of their downstairs plumbing, according to CNN.But somewhere down the line, someone decided it was a good idea to capitalize on societal pressure to obtain female bodily perfection. So instead of a legit medical procedure, it's now all about appearances. Plumper labia, improved elasticity, tighter skin? Check, check, and check.Apparently if you're looking to feel more confident and bring romance back into your relationship, all it takes is a visit to a cosmetic clinic and a laser to your hooha.As if that's not misleading enough, 'doctors' claim its painless and safe. The FDA begs to disagree though, saying it causes burns, scarring, and is in fact pretty damn painful.They've already sent out warning letters to companies inappropriately marketing the procedure for unapproved purposes, and are cautioning women to stay away.It's not just coochie rejuvenation, either. There's a ton of 'ancient' and 'natural' genital health remedies out there that aren't the least bit useful.So please, for the love of your lady garage, please leave it the hell alone.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 07:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3667632/3667632_62DDEEF5C3AF493D8C6C149CA95C27C2_180803_3667632_FDA_warns_against_vaginal_rejuvenation_devices_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8BE/B7E/8BEB7E1439F7AA7F9482B61B8BF4EBBE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, rejuvenation, FDA, unsafe devices, FDA warning, quack doctors, cosmetic procedure, cancer, cancerous tissue, warts, medical procedure]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3667405</guid>
      <title>Puppet-master fungus hijacks flies, kills them from inside out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA  Scientists have identified a fungal pathogen that hijacks hapless fruit flies and puppeteers them to their death.According to new research from UC Berkeley, when the fungus known as entomophthora muscae infects fruit flies, it infiltrates the nervous system early on.The host insect remains seemingly unaffected while the fungus feeds off its fat stores, but begins acting abnormally once the pathogen invades and destroys its organs.Eventually, the fly is forced to climb to an elevated spot, where the fungus grows out of its proboscis and sticks to the surface it's on, cementing it in place.The fly is then made to raise its wings to a 90-degree angle before dying, allowing new spores to be ejected from its exposed abdomen to infect new hosts.The existence of the fungus, whose scientific name means "destroyer of insects", has been known for over a hundred years. Similar pathogens exists that hijack ants and aphids, but scientists have yet to figure out how exactly how.The Berkeley researchers are especially curious about how the puppet-master fungus gets the fly to override survival instincts and climb to its death, and are now focusing their efforts to uncover the answer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/03/3667405/3667405_67EC579239AF4FCAA8E74323232A7927_180803_3667405_Puppet_master_fungus_hijacks_flies__kills_them_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CD3/6E6/CD36E642E0AA4A0C7EA41A26494E70BD.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, fly, zombie fly, fungus, puppeteer fungus, mind control fungus, spores, Entomophthora muscae, fruit flies, destroyer of insects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669719</guid>
      <title>Scientists successfully transplant bioengineered pig lungs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEXAS    A study published in Science Translational Medicine describes how scientists have successfully transplanted a bioengineered lung into a pig.Scientists created lung scaffolds by taking a lung from another pig and bathing it in a solution of sugar and protein.This leaves a skeleton of the lungs, stripping it of all the blood and living cells.The lung scaffolds are then treated with growth factor-filled hydrogels and nanoparticles which would prepare it to receive cells from the pig where the lung was going to be transplanted to.The cells were left in the lung scaffolds for 30 days where it prepared a brand new lung.The researchers noticed the pigs which received the bioengineered lung managed to grow blood vessel networks by two weeks.Researchers involved in the project said the same process could be used for human transplants five to ten years from now.This successful operation means organ donor shortages could become a thing of the past.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 11:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/06/3669719/3669719_D3FA8491FDF64E0F83AA24094FB13981_180806_3669719_Scientists_successfully_transplant_bioengineered_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7C8/04F/7C804F6D04BFBDD1067238784CD702A8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, science, medical breakthrough, bioengineering, lab-grown lungs, lung transplant, pigs, transplanting bioengineered lung into pigs, lung scaffold, lung in container, pig cells]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669712</guid>
      <title>Dozens killed as magnitude 6.9 quake rocks Indonesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOMBOK, INDONESIA  Rescue and evacuation operations are underway after several Indonesian islands were rocked by a deadly earthquake and strong aftershocks.Reuters reports that Indonesia's holiday island of Lombok was hit by a magnitude 6.9 earthquake around 6:46 p.m. on Sunday. According to the USGS, the quake had a depth of 31 kilometers and was felt in neighboring Bali.The powerful tremors triggered panic across the islands, as people fled homes and  buildings and ran onto the streets. At least 91 people have been confirmed dead, most of them killed by falling rubble in northern and western Lombok. Hundreds more are reportedly injured.The earthquake triggered an initial tsunami alert warning of waves up to half a meter, though this was later cancelled.It's the second to occur in Lombok in a week, after a 6.4 quake that shook the island on July 29 claimed 17 victims.More than 120 aftershocks, some ranging in magnitude from 4.3 to 5.4, were recorded following the massive quake. The death toll is also expected to rise as more news trickles in from the hardest-hit parts of the island.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 11:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/06/3669712/3669712_F368C8A320EF48B6B273A90B1F322682_180806_3669712_Dozens_killed_as_magnitude_6_9_quake_rocks_Indon_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/245/4F9/2454F94C0B520D5C3B78FB4BCC7D5694.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, earthquake, indonesia earthquake, deadly quake, deadly earthquake, lombok, bali, tsunami warning, quake, magnitude 7 earthquake, powerful quake, disaster, ring of fire, pacific ring of fire]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669680</guid>
      <title>Hand sanitizers becoming less effective against some bacteria</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA  New research has found that certain germs are becoming more and more resistant to hand sanitizers.CNN reports that alcohol-based disinfectants are widely used to eliminate germs, and have proven effective against reducing infections like those caused by the staphylococcus bacteria.But a recent study published in Science Translational Medicine noticed a rise enterococcal infections, suggesting that the bacteria that causes it may have developed a tolerance to alcohol.Alcohol is believed to kill bacteria by dissolving their cellular membrane, so it was thought that germs and viruses were unable to adapt to it.Researchers analyzed 139 types of bacteria from 1997 to 2015 and found that on average, those taken after 2009 tolerated alcohol more than pre- 2004 strains.Further testing showed that the alcohol-tolerant bacteria appeared in the guts of mice even after their cages were cleaned with sanitizing wipes.Currently, the enterococcus bacteria can only be killed with a 70% alcohol solution, according to NPR, though It's unclear if the bacteria will mutate to tolerate higher concentrations, or even build total resistance.The study authors say this doesn't mean people should give up hand sanitizers altogether, but there's a strong indication washing with soap and water is still the best way to eliminate germs."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 10:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/06/3669680/3669680_C2BF66CEB4B1405FA8A62D05EE3CC8B0_180806_3669680_Hand_sanitizers_becoming_less_effective_against__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/previews/688/C2F/688C2F9DD96D417B9797B31D96AD8EC4_2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hand sanitizer, bacteria, sanitizers, are hand sanitizers effective, alcohol, alcohol resistant bacteria, superbugs, germs, hand germs, hand washing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669589</guid>
      <title>China's bike-sharing utopia turns out to be a real nightmare</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China's dockless bike-sharing operators are reaching out to new markets, raising questions about the merits of this system.Big cities such as Los Angeles, Seattle, Washington D.C. and Boston have seen the arrival of new dockless bike-sharing services since last year,Most of the companies running these services originally started in China. While China used to be known as the "Bicycle Kingdom," most people have now traded their iconic Fenge bike for a modern SUV.What makes these bikes convenient is that they're cheap, and can pretty much be dropped anywhere. And that's precisely why they are so criticized.When you park your car in the street, or when you open a sidewalk cafe, you are using a public good for your own benefit. Hence, those activities are regulated, and you often need a permit to do so.On the contrary, when thousands of commuters drop their bicycles wherever is most convenient for them, they all accumulate in the same place, disrupting traffic, and affecting people's well-being.More than 1.5 million dockless bikes have been deployed in the mere city of Shanghai. And the competition is so fierce that Chinese operators have cut prices to almost zero.Bluegogo was once the third biggest operator in China, with 700.000 bikes across the country. Like many other companies, it went bankrupt in November 2017, leaving thousands and thousands of unusable bicycles in the streets to be handled by the authorities.More and more surreal 'graveyards' have appeared across the country to storage the countless broken and unusable bikes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 08:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/06/3669589/3669589_58CBFBAFEDB04D3688A8D69991CBD068_180806_3669589_China_s_bike_sharing_utopia_turns_out_to_be_a_re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/008/F6D/008F6D8657315F5822B5D495C69A9D21.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, bike, dockless bike, bike sharing, dockless bike sharing, bike operators, bicycle, bicycle operators, transportation, bubble]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3669505</guid>
      <title>Study finds plastics exposed to the sun emit greenhouse gases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HAWAII    A new study published in PLOS One shows that plastic releases greenhouses gases when exposed to the sun.The study found that some of the commonly-used plastics release methane and ethylene one they are exposed to sunlight.Dr. Sarah-Jeanne Royer, lead author of the study, said they originally set out to measure methane produced by organisms in seawater when she realized that most of the methane was being emitted from the plastic bottles in the sea, reports EcoWatch.Dr. Royer and her team tested plastics such as polycarbonate, polypropylene, polystyrene, and low-density polyethylene along with others found in food packaging, textiles, and other plastic goods. When plastic is exposed to light from the sun, it breaks down, which exposes more plastic area to the sun, resulting in greater gas emissions.One of the plastics, low-density polyethylene, was found to continue emitting gases even in the dark, after it had it had been exposed to the sun.The study found plastic bags, which is the most commonly used and discarded plastic in the world, emitted the largest amount of greenhouse gases.In a press release by the University of Hawaii, Dr. Royer and her team is now working to "constrain the overall greenhouse gas emissions from plastics."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 07:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/06/3669505/3669505_9D5ECFE1C00E45D2B26BDB04CC2FC32F_180806_3669505_Study_finds_plastics_exposed_to_the_sun_emit_gre_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D41/F7F/D41F7F7EF560CA342C8B17F582522C2C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Study, Hawaii, plastic, methane, greenhouse gases, Sun, global warming, climate change, greenhouse gas emissions, ethylene, study finds plastic emitting gases]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3670424</guid>
      <title>Venezuelan president survives drone assassination attempt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARACAS  Venezuela claims it has identified the mastermind and accomplices behind a failed attempt on President Nicolas Maduro's life.CNN reports that Maduro survived an alleged assassination attempt on Saturday after a drone exploded near where he was delivering a speech.Footage of the event show him looking up mid-speech as a loud bang is heard off-screen. Soldiers are then seen breaking formation and scattering. Though the president escaped unscathed, seven members of the national guard were reportedly injured by the blast.According to Venezuela's Interior Minister Nestor Reverol, assailants used two DJI M600 drones, each carrying a kilogram of C4 explosives. One drone was set to detonate above Maduro, the other in front of him.The Venezuelan military electronically knocked one of the drones off-course and caused it to detonate away from the target area. The second drone ended up crashing into an apartment building two blocks away from the event.Six people were detained and later charged in connection with the attack after authorities examined materials and electronic devices in their possession.The Madura administration accused the far right of trying to kill him, alleging that they conspired with Colombian President Juan Manuel Santos and Venezuelans in Miami.Critics say no evidence has been presented to back the government's claims. According to the Times of London, some have even speculated the attack may have been staged to let the president take action against his opponents.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 10:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/07/3670424/3670424_1EE001453796471BBECB2B19760BC020_180807_3670424_Venezuelan_president_survives_drone_assassinatio_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8A2/E85/8A2E85C861F2449B7D6EC61B8EF35B7F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, venezuela, president, nicolas maduro, maduro, assassination, assassination attempt, explosion, drone explosion, drone attack, far right, DJI M600 drone, drone signal jammer, venezuela politics]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3670342</guid>
      <title>Goats caught storming onto Boise neighborhood lawns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOISE, IDAHO   More 118 goats appeared out of nowhere in a Boise neighborhood early this month, reports KTVB.Neighborhood residents say the goats showed up around 7 in the morning, moving from lawn to lawn and chewing grass.Apparently, the goats occupied the roads and couldn't care less about the cars in the area.The goats attracted crowds of people who were snapping pictures and petting the animals.Joe Parris, KTVB reporter who broke the story, told The Washington Post though most people were excited to see the goats, "a few concerned homeowners [were] trying to shoo the goats off their property."It was only later that it was discovered that the goats were owned by a company called We Rent Goats, which sends its goats to clear weeds from fields, pastures etc.Around 8:30 a.m. local time, a We Rent Goats truck arrived and moved all the goats onto its truck.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 09:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/07/3670342/3670342_6B00001EA41A47A3BEDF683E74CF91D5_180807_3670342_Goats_caught_storming_onto_Boise_neighborhood_la_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/724/06F/72406FC7CB4AA6BA8495515E1E9F2717.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, goats, goats boise, neighborhood, goats on the loose, swarm of goats, animals, lawns, We Rent Goats, friendly goats, animal control, professional goats, goat crew, herd of goats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3670330</guid>
      <title>Russia enlists Steven Seagal to improve relations with the US</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW/WASHINGTON  Russia has enlisted 1990s action movie star Steven Seagal to help bolster ties with the U.S.Last week, the 66 year-old has been made a special representative to the country by Russia with task of to improving ties and humanitarian issues between the two nuclear powers. Seagal's role will also focus on  improving art and cultural exchanges.Writing on his official Twitter, Seagal   who holds Russian, Serbian and American citizenship     tweeted that he was "humbled and honoured" by the appointment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 09:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/07/3670330/3670330_94A85094BFED499DB0100725CD54957F_180807_3670330_Russia_enlists_Steven_Seagal_to_improve_relation_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C4D/656/C4D656263EDD202699870F92F9640D26.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, steven seagal, seagal russia, russia us relations, steven seagal russia, steven seagal putin, vladimir putin and steven seagal, diplomacy, 90s action movies, 90s action films, seagal martial artist]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3670047</guid>
      <title>Chinese drama: love rivals engage in furious car race on the highway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENGLAI, CHINA  A man named Mr. He engaged in a high-speed chase after another man named Mr. Wang, after the latter revealed He was living in a web of lies.After his girlfriend left him for He, Wang became very depressed. After some time, he heard that He, who claimed to be divorced, actually still had a wife and children. So, he called his ex-girlfriend to tell her, maybe hoping that would help them get back together.Unsurprisingly, this created tension between the two lovers, and when when He happened upon Wang one day the highway, it led to this surreal car chase.Wang quickly realized he was in serious trouble, managed to avoid a collision and turned back. But He also doubled back, nearly running over him. He was later arrested and charged for committing attempted homicide.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 03:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/07/3670047/3670047_DC8DD72A1DA9426D9DF3A97F4C4866C2_180807_3670047_Chinese_drama__love_rivals_engage_in_furious_car_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1CB/5BD/1CB5BDFAF46DAC42598A71914E9D46F7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, car chase, car pursuit, Fast and Furious, betrayed girlfriend, fooled girlfriend, divorce, couple, love drama, love affair, attempted homicide, nearly ran over, China, Shandong, Penglai, He, Wang]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671160</guid>
      <title>China blocks release of new Winnie the Pooh film</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Winnie the Pooh won't be getting his Chinese big screen debut now, or probably ever, thanks to his resemblance to China's top dog.The Hollywood Reporter first put out the news that Chinese censors denied the release of Disney's Christopher Robin film, which features the honey-crazed bear. They didn't say why, but everyone and their Chinese grandma knows it's because of Xi Jinping's hate-hate relationship with his pot-bellied doppelganger.Xi's nightmare started in 2013, when a photo of him and Obama walking together was compared with a pretty spot-on image of Pooh and Tigger doing the same exact thing. A year later, Xi Jin-pooh resurfaced on the internet, this time with Japanese prime minister Shinzo Abe as Eeyore. Needless to say, Xi Jinping is not a fan.So now if anyone on Chinese social media so much as breathes 'Pooh', you best bet the Great Firewall will block you, your whole family, and your cow.It's been pointed out that the film block may just be due to China's foreign film quota. So...Mission Impossible, Antman and the Wasp, and Skyscraper are all ok, but guess you're afraid of a cartoon bear.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 10:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/08/3671160/3671160_C7B480F2B2CA48DFAB9F285FE19BA5EE_180808_3671160_China_blocks_release_of_new_Winnie_the_Pooh_film_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/647/39B/64739BBF50213FA5F18B4419A1B91AF6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, winnie the pooh, pooh, xi jinping, china, censorship, china film quota, christopher robin, china film release]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671068</guid>
      <title>New study shows gut bacteria is a factor in weight loss</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCHESTER, MINNESOTA  A study published in Mayo Clinic Proceedings shows certain types of bacteria in our gut may influence weight loss and weight gain.Researchers from the Mayo Clinic in Rochester, Minnesota found that those who were successful in losing weight had an abundance of a bacteria called Phascolarctobacterium in their gut, while those who weren't had an abundance of bacteria named Dialister.  Gut bacteria is important as it breaks down food parts we can't normally digest. When this occurs, the bacteria creates "extra calories" for our body to digest, which results in a calorie boost.The study was conducted with 26 participants who were overweight and obese, and going through lifestyle changes.The participants were tracked for three months, during which they had to follow a low-calorie diet and were encouraged to walk 10,000 steps a day.The team of researchers collected fecal samples from the participants to find out which bacteria their body's digestive system contained.Purna Kashyap, a researcher involved in the study, explained to NPR that "people who lost at least 5 percent of their body weight had a different gut bacteria compared to those who did not lose 5 percent of their body weight."The bacteria Phascolarctobacterium had previously been associated with weight gain in a study involving obese rats.The Mayo researchers said their study suggests Phascolarctobacterium may increase the effects of lifestyle and dietary changes on weight loss. However, Kashyap added that there might be other types of bacteria that may influence dieting as well.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/08/3671068/3671068_087763A2E16A4DDC83FFDD60C9030CCF_180808_3671068_New_study_shows_gut_bacteria_is_a_factor_in_weig_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/905/926/9059267AC97697944AF20940C8E22186.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Study, US, bacteria, microbes, guts, gut bacteria, weight-loss, weight-gain, lifestyle, dieting, Phascolarctobacterium bacteria, Dialister bacteria, types of bacteria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671056</guid>
      <title>Plastic surgery on the rise as teens  want to resemble filtered selfies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS  More patients are getting cosmetic surgery to look like their "filtered" self online, reports CBS News.It is common nowadays to see people taking selfies of themselves, and then editing it before uploading it onto social media.There are a ton of apps such as photo retouching apps which let people do things such as smoothing out their skin to whitening their teeth, to changing their facial features.The researchers say young people's self-esteem is getting lower as a result, with people viewing filtered images of friends, families, and celebrities.This phenomenon  now dubbed as Snapchat dysmorphia  has people requesting cosmetic surgeons for fuller lips, bigger eyes, or thinner nose, in order to look like the online version of themselves.The authors of the study say social media is altering people's perception of beauty worldwide and is making people "lose touch with reality."They also added that clinicians should understand the impact of social media on people's self-esteem "to better treat and counsel their patients."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 09:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/08/3671056/3671056_F4FECB0F6935497B9313B34175E33C40_180808_3671056_Plastic_surgery_on_the_rise_as_teens__want_to_re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DCB/3A7/DCB3A761DF14622292A27EC0135CEB35.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, study, plastic surgery, selfies, photo filters, social media, self-esteem, teens, young adults, filtered images, online, social media addiction, selfie, photo editing apps]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671037</guid>
      <title>'Zero burial' campaign sparks massive controversy in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGXI, CHINA  Videos of coffins being seized and smashed in the Jiangxi province have sparked a big controversy in China.Chinese cities are developing fast, and this frenetic development has raised concerns regarding land management. One of the main issues is the lack of land space to bury dead people.Officials in Jiangxi province launched a "zero burial" campaign and forcefully confiscated people's coffins.The aim of the campaign is to make cremation the sole approved method for disposing of dead people's remains.The campaign goes against a longstanding burial tradition in rural China. The elderly often have tailor-made coffins stored at home in anticipation of their own death, a custom which they believe brings good fortune to the house. Videos were published on Chinese social media, showing rural residents lying in their coffins so they wouldn't be taken away.Such methods led to a massive outcry and sparked controversy. Even national media outlets described the campaign as quote 'cold-blooded and overbearing'.Local officials have since backtracked, saying that they would do their best to promote eco-friendly ways of conducting funerals without being quite so aggressive.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 08:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/08/3671037/3671037_FAFC71C097CA40048A63C9AC8585B92F_180808_3671037__Zero_burial__campaign_sparks_massive_controvers_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/462/914/462914FF727B285F7543CF55232D14A7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News, burial, funerals, China, Jiangxi, coffin, coffins, confiscated coffins, outcry, controversy, zero burial policy, zero burial campaign, Jiangxi coffins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671026</guid>
      <title>Musician kicked off AA flight after buying seat for cello</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  A DePaul University musician was humiliated and kicked off an American Airlines flight despite abiding by guidelines on travelling with her instrument.In a post on Facebook that has since been shared over 2,000 times, Jay Tang claims that when he got round trip plane tickets for his cellist wife Jingjing Hu last April, he also bought a seat for her $30,000 cello, even confirming with the AA rep that it would not be a problem.Hu had no trouble on the Chicago to Miami leg of her flight, but trouble started after she'd been verified and pre-boarded on the return flight home.A flight attendant informed her she had to get off because her cello was too big for the plane. Curiously, once she left, two people promptly came in and took her seats.By AA's own regulations, oversized instruments are allowed in the cabin with the an additional seat purchase, as long as it's not over 165 pounds.At the gate, Hu was told the next flight was also too small. She had airport police called on her for "not being understandable" and told she had to pay first or business class tickets to get home.She was eventually put on a larger aircraft that left the next day, but was anxious the whole time, and broke down in tears after finally reuniting with her husband in Chicago.American Airlines later sent a message to Tang explaining the fiasco as a miscommunication, but Tang isn't buying it.He and his wife want a sincere apology from AA, and are hoping other musicians can learn from their misfortune, reports NBC 5.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 08:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/08/3671026/3671026_49F646BD47DA471D85E61B980FD4973B_180808_3671026_Musician_kicked_off_AA_flight_after_buying_seat__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C29/8B3/C298B365764E64FF2378F28F3698A298.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, american airlines, aa, musician, cello, musical instruments on planes, musical instruments on flight, aa cabin rules, oversized baggage, baggage regulations]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671001</guid>
      <title>Canine influenza outbreak in Michigan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MICHIGAN  The number of canine influenza confirmed cases in Michigan has risen to 49 since mid-July, reports WNDU.According to AVMA, dogs can get canine influenza after being exposed to the H3N8 or H3N2 virus.It is a respiratory infection which can be caused by sniffing or licking dogs who have the virus or by sharing food and water with those dogs.Sick dogs who are coughing or sneezing may also pass on the virus to healthy dogs.Dogs may also be exposed to the virus by humans whose clothings or skin have been contaminated with the it.Michigan Department of Agriculture & Rural Development mentioned in a news release, symptoms may include fever, discharge from the eyes or nose, and coughing along with lethargic behavior."However, canine influenza can also be prevented with a vaccine.James Averill, Michigan's state veterinarian, told Michigan Live, "It's important that dog owners work with their veterinarians to protect their dogs."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 08:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/08/3671001/3671001_9C7C4265F314410981615E4B720B973C_180808_3671001_Canine_influenza_outbreak_in_Michigan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/22B/1EF/22B1EFEE816D6F111365DD6BF4ACA100.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, dog, canine influenza, dog flu, highly contagious, respiratory infection, virus, sick dogs, coughing, contamination, symptoms, disease, canines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671930</guid>
      <title>Scientists warn forest fires may work to reverse climate policies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA    As California battles the some of the largest wildfires in the state's history, scientists say just putting out the flames may not be enough.The amount of carbon being spewed out into the atmosphere may completely undo what climate policies have helped to prevent over the years, reports CAL Matters.The scientists involved in the study say when wildfires burn, only 15 percent of the carbon is released at the time.However, the remainder of the carbon continues to be released as the trees decay over the years and decades.According to the scientists, the carbon that continues to be released would contain more harmful compounds than the original forest fire.The study also warns that future fires that take place over previously burned land would make things even worse.In the wake of these natural disasters, we may be forced to find new solutions or face even greater disasters in the future, reports The Guardian.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 13:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/09/3671930/3671930_3F75A051F38E4FCF9DAB97418A13F000_180809_3671930_Scientists_warn_forest_fires_may_work_to_reverse_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/327/3D7/3273D7E6292F6F828A865F8B1129F4AC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, California, wildfires, California wildfires, wildfires in California, climate change, effects of climate change, climate policies, fires, forest fires, flames, atmosphere, carbon, burned land]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671919</guid>
      <title>Study says rising temperatures might turn Earth into a "hothouse"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD  Scientists are warning the public that a chain of domino events could take place if global temperatures continue to rise.A study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America says Earth is approaching "hothouse" conditions if global temperatures rise more than 2 degrees Celsius.Scientists also stated that once temperatures hit the tipping point, where Earth's natural systems will be triggered, this will further increase global warming.Right now, the earth's forests, land and other natural systems work to absorb around 4.5 billion tonnes of carbon, to prevent carbon from ending up in the atmosphere.However, if temperatures continue to warm the planet, these natural systems may end up releasing more carbon than they take in.In the report, the researchers warn rising temperatures could also lead to rising sea levels up to 60 meters from today's shorelines.Some places would become uninhabitable if the earth continues to get warmer and warmer.However, the researchers ended on an optimistic note, saying this catastrophe could be avoided if action is taken immediately to change how we are impacting Earth's natural systems.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 13:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/09/3671919/3671919_79622D50DB8C48C4A21715B8552D234E_180809_3671919_Study_says_rising_temperatures_might_turn_Earth__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6D8/116/6D811693CB6BE224695E442CC2193C00.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Earth, global warming, climate change, study, planet earth, rising temperatures, carbon dioxide, atmosphere, global temperatures, earth is warming]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671676</guid>
      <title>Unsurvivable heatwaves could hit the heart of China by 2070</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING, CHINA  A recent MIT study suggests that Northern China could become uninhabitable by the end of the century.The North China Plain is home to 400 million people and one of the most densely populated areas in the world. It is the core of the country and includes the capital: Beijing.But it's also an important agricultural area, where intensive irrigation leads to higher humidity in the air. This point is particularly important according to Elfatih Eltahir and Suchul Kang, the two researchers behind the study.To determine survivability in hot weather, they used an index called the wet-bulb temperature, which takes into account both humidity and temperature.They found that above a wet-bulb temperature of 35 degree Celsius (equivalent to 95 Fahrenheit), even a healthy person staying in the shade may not be able to survive.Using detailed model simulations of the area, they found that if global warming continues at the same pace, northern China will be the most critical hotspot in the world. If other areas  such as the Gulf or southern Iran  might be facing similarly dangerous heat waves in the future, they're far less densely populated than northern China. According to the researchers, these humid heat waves could 'push the area against the boundaries of habitability'.China is currently the first-ranked country in the world for greenhouse gases emission, just before the U.S.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 07:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/09/3671676/3671676_9874653352F74281B37A8BDE60207A45_180809_3671676_Unsurvivable_heatwaves_could_hit_the_heart_of_Ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9E7/6B6/9E76B614FCCE7007C84CF6A2DE135BE0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, News,climate change, global warming, research, study, MIT, climate, heatwave, heat wave, China, Northern China Plain, apocalypse, greenhouse effect, Beijing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671626</guid>
      <title>Google plans censored search engine for China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  A whistleblower has revealed that Google is planning to launch a censored version of its search engine in China.According to internal documents given to The Intercept, the project, codenamed dragonfly, will blacklist 'sensitive queries' such as freedom, religion, human rights,and anything else that's vaguely threatening to the Chinese government.Dragonfly's search engine will filter out websites already on China's hitlist, with the censorship also extending to images, spell check, and suggested searches.The mainland already has a tight lid on what its citizens can access, what with the Great Firewall blocking anything from the 1989 Tiananmen Massacre to Winnie the Pooh.Google had pulled out of China back in 2010, when it still had a conscience, but now its kowtowing to an oppressive regime for a slice of the lucrative Chinese market.The company has reportedly shown the new censorship toy to Chinese officials and is currently awaiting approval.It's already playing Big Brother in the free world by censoring YouTube content, so following China's strict censorship laws won't be a problem.Guess "don't be evil" doesn't apply to China, huh Google?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 06:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/09/3671626/3671626_76AB15F11F3646EBB8B753157031FEB5_180809_3671626_Google_plans_censored_search_engine_for_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1C4/78E/1C478E441CC1A6DC15D6AA382D0156DC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Google, China, Big Brother, great firewall, censorship, China censorship, censored search engine, google censorship, dragonfly, google dragonfly, project dragonfly]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3671482</guid>
      <title>China tests out its hypersonic aircraft and deems it a success</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China has tested out a new hypersonic aircraft  The Starry Sky-2    which could one day be used to carry nuclear missiles, reports The South China Morning Post.According to reports from Xinhua, the aircraft is a hypersonic experimental waverider vehicle.The hypersonic aircraft has a flatter, wedge-shaped fuselage and was launched by a multistage rocket into space in northwest China.The aircraft, which is still at the experimental stage, can ride on shock waves it generates.The China Academy of Aerospace Aerodynamics released a statement saying the Starry Sky-2 can travel at least five to six times the speed of sound."The academy also released pictures and videos of the test on WeChat, showing the aircraft twisting and turning. The aircraft then landed in a designated target zone.Zhou Chenming, a Beijing-based military analyst, told the South China Morning Post the aircraft may also have other military applications, adding there are still three to five years before the technology can be weaponized.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 02:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/09/3671482/3671482_5E49324717EE4CF5BA9CAE38A128C6F2_180809_3671482_China_tests_out_its_hypersonic_aircraft_and_deem_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A2D/D22/A2DD22C0F2A54173B8A74B829D9129A3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, aircraft, hypersonic aircraft, Aerospace technology, rocket, Starry Sky-2, flight test, aerospace industry, launch, space,  waverider, nuclear weapons, technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3672719</guid>
      <title>Two men in Toronto rescued from flooding elevator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TORONTO, CANADA    It had been flooding for the past few days in Toronto when two men trapped in an elevator almost drowned, reports Toronto Sun.Gabriel Otrin and Klever Freire were in the elevator when it suddenly stopped when it reached the basement. Water started rushing into the elevator and was quick to rise halfway up the chamber.The men first tried to open the elevator doors, when they couldn't, they climbed onto the handrails of the elevator to escape the waters.Gabriel tried to call the police with his cellphone, while Klever tried to pry open the maintenance hatch in the ceiling of the elevator.Luckily for them, two nearby police officers quickly responded to their call and soon reached the building.The officers headed downstairs and swam through the flooded basement to reach the trapped men, whom they freed by prying open the elevator doors with crowbars.  The men were taken to the hospital and treated for non-life threatening injuries, the BBC reports.They were also seen giving interviews to local media in Canada.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 13:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/10/3672719/3672719_36E2776CE2614DE2B02F47EB3B22ACC4_180810_3672719_Two_men_in_Toronto_rescued_from_flooding_elevato_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E83/B81/E83B817FCC94BEC8F0B0D36F0025F5BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Canada, flooding, floods, Toronto floods,  elevator, flooded elevator, water, water rushes into elevator, two men trapped in elevator are rescued, flooding in Canada]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3672459</guid>
      <title>Wearing boxers can boost men's sperm count</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON  Science may have finally answered the age-old boxers vs. briefs debate, at least as far as your swimmers are concerned.According to a new study led by the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health,  semen and blood samples were collected from 656 men seeking treatment at a fertility center with their partners. The men were also asked what the type of underwear they wore the last three months.Researchers found that while the subjects produced similar amounts of ejaculation fluid, boxer-wearers had 25% higher sperm concentration, 17% higher total sperm count, and better motility compared to those who wore jockeys or briefs.Brief wearers' blood had more follicle-stimulating hormones, which are released by the pituitary gland and associated with sperm production. This suggests the gland may have been boosting hormone production to compensate for lower sperm numbers.The Guardian reports that previous studies have found scrotal temperature to affect spermatogenesis, and that wearing loose-fitting underwear is better than tighter undergarments at keeping it cool.But while the new study shows a link between type of underwear and fertility, more research is needed to account for other factors and establish clear causality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 09:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/10/3672459/3672459_2E096BDD6FDE4568B342A5C7430B6A8D_180810_3672459_Wearing_boxers_can_boost_men_s_sperm_count_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4FC/C86/4FCC869B8DC176DF606F85C6FEB56118.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, sperm, sperm count, boxers vs briefs, boxer shorts, boxers or briefs, sperm concentration, sperm motility, swimmers, male reproduction, male fertility]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3672348</guid>
      <title>LAWMAN CAM: Episode 9</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Here's the latest police footage captured from cops around the globe.THIS WEEK: 1. London police engage in a crazy chase after four jetski riders on the Thames.2. Intoxicated driver who was being pulled over in Queensland, Australia proves you shouldn't drink and drive.3. Atlanta Police Department saves a passenger trapped in a burning car.4. Australian cop rescues a koala standing in the middle of the road.5. Reckless driver tries to escape with a stolen car in Prague, Czech Republic.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 07:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/10/3672348/3672348_7122595100C54CBFB35F750D5CEE7913_180810_3672348_LAWMAN_CAM__Episode_9_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/657/C43/657C436B55704896FDCBBD4AE361E984.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, good cop, hero cops, cops doing amazing things, latest police videos, new police videos,  latest cop video, new cop footage, police footage, police body cam, police dash cam, police compilation 2018, cop videos, police chase 2018, latest police chase videos, crazy car chases, police pursuit,, us police videos, cop camera, lawman cam, tomonews lawman cam, police responding, police news, latest police video, latest police videos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3672164</guid>
      <title>Temporary tattoo leaves UK kids with horrific burns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AGADIR, MOROCCO  A mom from the UK is warning parents to think twice before letting their kids get temporarily inked on holiday.Her warning comes after her sons were left with horrific burns.The Sun reports that while on a family getaway to Morocco, Toni Feeney's two kids asked to get henna tattoos. She agreed to let the boys get a Spiderman web and a dragon on their arms, thinking it would be harmless.But turns out the dye being used was toxic black henna, which later triggered a severe reaction that caused the boys' skin to develop painful chemical burns.Black henna contains PPD. It's the same substance found in black hair dyes, but henna pastes often have it in much higher concentrations than is legally allowed in the EU.Doctors have put the boys on antihistamines and antibiotics to keep any infections at bay, with instructions not to put anything on the wounds. Both are now recovering.Feeney has taken to Facebook to warn parents of the dangers of black henna tattoos, especially on young children.The toxic black dye has been known to cause permanent scarring and in rare cases, life-threatening anaphylactic reactions.It's been banned in countries like the UK, US, Canada, and Australia, but continues to be used countless holiday destinations worldwide.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 02:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/10/3672164/3672164_D9E12A1AB6D64C4082BD57F00722DF95_180810_3672164_Temporary_tattoo_leaves_UK_kids_with_horrific_bu_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/89C/5F3/89C5F3EF90EC4935B228FA5D8626938E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, henna tattoo, black henna, temporary tattoo, henna, chemical burns, PPD, toxic black henna, holiday henna]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674181</guid>
      <title>Herd of cows help police nab fleeing suspect</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEMINOLE, FLORIDA  Four felony suspects were on the run when the Sanford Police Department received help from a herd of cows, leading to the group's arrest, reports WKMG-TV.A woman and three other suspects were recklessly driving a stolen car when the police started following them.The woman, identified as Jennifer Kaufman, then decided to ditch the car and ran into a cattle field.It seems like the cows were not happy with Kaufman invading their territory, and started chasing her as well.The owner of the pasture mentioned in an interview to WKMG-TV that his cattle "panicked" because they didn't know who Kaufman was.The woman then ran away from the cows and climbed over a fence, where the police were waiting to arrest her.The other fleeing suspects were eventually arrested too.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 08:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/13/3674181/3674181_A4E80AD901EA439C9FE332F70F8A4EEC_180813_3674181_Herd_of_cows_help_police_nab_fleeing_suspect_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61E/FD2/61EFD2E97CD99BDA2A3B96330F58FE3C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Florida, cattle, cows, herd of cows,  fleeing suspect, suspect on the run, suspect fleeing police, suspect fleeing police runs into cattle field, cows chase suspect]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674164</guid>
      <title>NASA has launched an insane mission to 'touch the sun'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MERRITT ISLAND, FLORIDA  NASA has sent a probe to fly closer to the sun's surface than any man-made object has ever gone.Unlike other space missions, the Parker solar probe will have a long and complex orbit, since it's much more difficult to get to the sun, according to NASA.The earth travels 67,000 miles per hour in a sideways motion relative to the sun to avoid being pulled in by its strong gravitational forces. As such, any object travelling to the sun must cancel that motion.NASA's Parker solar probe must drop 53,000 miles per hour of sideways speed. In addition to being launched by the powerful Delta IV Heavy rocket, it will perform seven Venus flybys over a seven-year period, relying on the planet's gravity to draw its orbit closer to the sun.The probe is then set to fly through the heated solar atmosphere called the corona, to understand and be able to predict the behavior of solar winds.If all goes according to plan, the Parker solar probe will make its first close pass at the sun in November.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 08:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/13/3674164/3674164_15EE3357365E4C0FA6D6B59799567580_180813_3674164_NASA_has_launched_an_insane_mission_to__touch_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE1/E53/EE1E53D73D7D88A665AB134A18702050.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, NASA, solar probe, sun mission, parker solar probe, solar mission, rocket launch, delta heavy rocket, touch the sun, NASA mission, solar winds]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674085</guid>
      <title>Alabama beach volleyball players accidentally massacre baby birds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAND ISLAND, ALABAMA  Beachgoers on a small Alabama island may have unknowingly killed scores of baby birds.The group inadvertently disturbed the nesting grounds of a rare, protected bird.AL.com reports that least terns are small coastal birds that lay their eggs on depressions in the sand  something that leaves them vulnerable to a whole host of threats.One such threat came bouncing up this summer, collecting the grape-sized eggs and stacking them around a dome of sand to make way for a volleyball space.Thing is, least tern eggs need to be kept cool, not warm. So leaving them unprotected under the sun pretty much baked those chicks to death.The disturbing site was discovered over the Fourth of July Weekend by wildlife researcher Andrew Haffenden, who was conducting a bird survey for nonprofit Birmingham Audubon and had earlier spotted several tents and a net on the island.Haffenden and his group later put up ropes and signs around the nesting area, and alerted U.S. Fish and Wildlife.Despite the mass carnage and the storms that hit in late July, Haffenden says the current number of active nests indicate that it just might shape up to be a good year for the birds.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 06:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/13/3674085/3674085_7C44F6C395DE4A4FAC971683ABC62A39_180813_3674085_Alabama_beach_volleyball_players_accidentally_ma_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F38/445/F384450B93BF4C8AE784C98AFCF19107.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bird massacre, beach volleyball, protected birds, baked eggs, baby birds, dumb humans, idiots, man destroys nature, man ruins nature, nesting, nesting season, least terns, eggs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3675055</guid>
      <title>Turkey currency crisis sparks fears of global consequences</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANKARA, TURKEY  As Turkey grapples with a financial crisis, fears mount that its economic consequences will ripple through global markets.The Turkish stock market continued to fall Monday, with its currency trading as low as 6.97 to the dollar. The value of the lira has already dropped 46% since January, reports Reuters.Turkey had borrowed freely in recent years due to cheap rates in the U.S. and Europe, but debts are becoming unmanageable with the U.S. Federal Reserve’s new raised interest rates, according to the Washington Post.The lira’s fall has been made worse by President Erdogan’s insistence that the central bank keep interest rates low. Recent disputes with the U.S. has also prompted Trump to double tariffs on Turkish steel.Turkish borrowers currently owe $82 billion to Spanish banks, and $38 billion to French ones. These and other foreign banks are set to suffer big losses should the debt default.The Erdogan administration has blamed ‘foreign threats’ for the country’s financial turmoil, and has urged citizens to sell dollars and gold to support the lira.An action plan to stem losses is supposedly in the works. In the meantime, the central bank is taking steps to make short-term credit more accessible to banks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3675055/3675055_1EF76FBCDE8F4ECDA95AAAAC88C11208_180814_3675055_Turkey_currency_crisis_sparks_fears_of_global_co_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/41A/304/41A304D56D5E423D9BB95E6C2B8ED881.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,Turkey crisis,Turkey currency crisis,Turkey financial crisis,recession,Turkey recession,lira,Turkish lira,Turkey currency,Erdogan,global financial crisis]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674939</guid>
      <title>Hippo kills Taiwanese tourist in Kenya</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENYA  A hippo attacked a Taiwanese tourist over the weekend, according to the Kenya Wildlife Services.The attack occurred on Saturday night at Lake Naivasha, approximately 58 miles from the capital of Nairobi.  Chang Ming Chuang, 65, was with a coworker taking some pictures of the hippopotamus on the lake shores when the animal charged and bit Chang in the chest, according to the BBC. Chang was transported to the Naivasha DIstrict Hospital where he was pronounced dead. Chang's colleague, Wu Peng Te, 62, survived to ordeal and escaped with minor bruises.According to National Geographic, hippos are some of the most dangerous animals in the world. They can snap a canoe like a twig with their massive jaws.Around 500 people are killed in Africa every year by hippos, National Geographic reported.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3674939/3674939_3916B282FA884C859833AF5462566852_180814_3674939_Hippo_kills_Taiwanese_tourist_in_Kenya_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4C8/AE1/4C8AE12C86D878670C393DC8D7197DED.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hippo, hippo attack, hippo attack Kenya, Taiwanese tourist, Taiwanese tourist hippo Kenya]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674929</guid>
      <title>Ford got screwed in huge floor-plan financing fraud</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LUBBOCK, TEXAS  Ford Motor Credit filed more documents with the bankruptcy court last Friday claiming Reagor-Dykes Auto Group misrepresented sales-reporting data to Ford Credit. Ford claims this could be one of the largest floor-plan financing frauds in U.S. history, according to KCBD. Ford believes Reagor-Dykes was stretching out the time it was using to pay off vehicles it sold to customers. During a Ford Credit investigation, they discovered the auto group was selling vehicles on average of 55 days before reporting the car sales to Ford Credit. The documents also claims Reagor-Dykes fraudulently obtained double-flooring from Ford Credit, reported KCBD. Double-flooring is an illegal practice where a single vehicle is used as collateral for more than one loan. Ford Credit also says Reagor-Dykes secured inventory financing for vehicles it had already sold. By listing the vehicles as current inventory, Reagor-Dykes was then able to obtain additional financing. According to Ford, Reagor-Dykes "squandered more than $41 million on the current management's watch  through either their own fraud or gross mismanagement."  According to KCBD, Ford Credit filed the documents requesting the court appoint a trustee to recover and preserve assets for the liquidation of Reagor-Dykes and provide payment to creditors.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3674929/3674929_EB0062D7C3574FCDB48F42C048EC0586_180814_3674929_Ford_got_screwed_in_huge_floor_plan_financing_fr_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/200/C2A/200C2A5B4FA7D86485D08ABAB03C9AC5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Ford Credit, Reagor-Dykes Auto Group, Ford Reagor-Dykes, double flooring, Ford]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674837</guid>
      <title>Family returns from Carr Fire to find fish alive thanks to some help</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REDDING, CALIFORNIA  A family who was forced to evacuate because of the massive Carr Fire returned home to a fantastically fishy surprise.  The massive 190,000 acre blaze forced the family to leave their house without their family fish named Grant. The father had let his daughter know that Grant probably wouldn't make it through due to lack of food.    But according to a Cal Fire tweet, "Both were in for quite a shock when they returned home to a well-fed fish!"The Engine 1489 crew also left an attached note by Grant's fishbowl saying, "Fed your fish a few sprinkles. Sorry if we weren't supposed to." The Corning Police Department also left a notation saying they fed Grant again on August 1 at 10:33 a.m. The Carr Fire has already been raging for 3 weeks and destroyed 1,100 homes. Luckily, Grant's house wasn't one of them.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 08:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3674837/3674837_FBB8A14B161D4EFFBD1024B5E48DAC56_180814_3674837_Family_returns_from_Carr_Fire_to_find_fish_alive_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0D7/2F4/0D72F4687739C3ACEFFE40700ABC7300.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Redding fires 2018, California fires 2018, Grant the Fish, Carr Fire, CalFire, California fires]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674821</guid>
      <title>Emotional killer whale mother lets go of dead calf after 17 days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANADA    An orca has finally let go of her baby calf after taking it on a "tour of grief" for 17 days.The orca named Tahlequah  also known as J35  gave birth to a baby calf on July 24, unfortunately the baby only lived for half an hour, The Star Vancouver reports.The death of her baby calf seems to have triggered an emotional response in the whale, as she was seen carrying the infant whale with her during the day and night.Tahlequah was seen dropping the dead infant to catch fish to eat, reports CBC British Columbia.However, she was also seen diving into the water to bring the baby's body back whenever it slipped off her head.Researchers monitoring the whale said the mother whale was even seen pushing the dead baby along or holding its tail in her teeth, calling it "unprecedented" as they estimate the whale may have pushed the dead baby for around 1,000 kilometers. The Center for Whale Research released a statement saying the mother whale seems to be in good health.As for the baby, they assume the carcass may have sunk to the bottom of the sea.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 07:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3674821/3674821_8B1292BBAA5D4AF3B026862963EB4D66_180814_3674821_Emotional_killer_whale_mother_lets_go_of_dead_ca_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/99C/F03/99CF035FCC945BF8CAB95547D42BC277.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, killer whale, mother,killer whale carrying dead calf, baby whale, dead calf, newborn calf, 17 days, 1000 km, tour of grief, emotional whale, sea, animals, newborn animals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674767</guid>
      <title>Man at New Mexico compound training kids to shoot up schools</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMALIA, NEW MEXICO  The search for a missing boy led police to a remote New Mexico property, where they found something even more horrifying.CNN reports that 4-year-old Abdul-Ghani Wahhaj went missing in late November, and is believed to have been kidnapped by his father, Siraj Wahhaj.On Friday, authorities raided a makeshift compound near Amalia, New Mexico with no running water or electricity, and rescued 11 emaciated children aged 1 to 15.They found Siraj Wahhaj armed with an AR-15, revolver, four pistols, and ammunition, and arrested him and his accomplices, a man and three women.Court documents allege that Wahhaj was giving the children weapons training, and preparing them to commit future school shootings.The remains of a young boy were later found at the site, but authorities have yet to determine if the body is Wahhaj's missing son.The five suspects were charged with 11 counts of felony child abuse, and have pleaded not guilty.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 06:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3674767/3674767_A64CCA7B605A43CFAC970CC8F918A2EB_180814_3674767_Man_at_New_Mexico_compound_training_kids_to_shoo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/766/31B/76631BBBC470DCFD0A759DBA194EF7E5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, new mexico compound, siraj wahhaj, missing boy, starving children, weapons training]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674642</guid>
      <title>Prehistoric mega-shark teeth unearthed on Australian coast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAN JUC, AUSTRALIA  It's not quite the megalodon, but a jawful of sharp, serrated teeth provides rare evidence of a similarly ferocious mega-shark that once stalked the ancient waters down under.According to a press release from Museums Victoria, amateur fossil enthusiast Philip Mullaly discovered a set of sharp teeth sticking out of a boulder on Australia's Jan Juc coast. He contacted Museums Victoria, and further exploration revealed several more.The teeth belonged to the Great Narrow Jagged-Toothed Shark, which grew to over nine meters long  twice the size of a Great White.The prehistoric predator lived approximately 25 million years ago and are believed to have preyed on small whales and penguins.Shark skeletons are mostly made of cartilage, which doesn't fossilize well. Only single teeth and bits of vertebra are usually found, so multiple sets from a single shark is a rare find.Apart from the mega-shark, teeth from several Sixgill sharks were also uncovered, leading the team to believe a school of the bottom-feeding Sixgills may have feasted on the mega-shark's carcass.The fossilized teeth collection is with Museums Victoria, and will be on public display for six months.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 03:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3674642/3674642_F39936DF4D5F46B09BB309A33AE6AACD_180814_3674642_Prehistoric_mega_shark_teeth_unearthed_on_Austra_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F8A/626/F8A626028B80D9B79A9F873DE3FBA174.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, mega shark, prehistoric shark, shark teeth, shark teeth, great narrow jagged-toothed shark, megalodon, the meg, shark fossil, jan juc, museums victoria]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3674621</guid>
      <title>Scientists find that stomach viruses are able to travel together</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S.A.  A study published in Cell Host & Microbe found that different stomach viruses tend to be more contagious when the virus particles cluster together.The scientists conducted the study by analyzing stool samples from patients who had rotavirus or norovirus.They found out that stomach virus such as norovirus and rotavirus cluster together to form "packs" of up to 40 viruses.The virus clusters  called vesicles  are then covered in a protective membrane. The virus inside the clusters are also quick to replicate inside the membrane to form more virus particles.According to the study, the protective membrane protects the virus clusters from being noticed by the immune system.As the vesicles pass through the immune system and into the intestine, it quickly separates and infects one single cell with multiple viruses.In the study, scientists found that mice infected with clustered viruses became more ill compared to those that were infected with a single virus.The researchers noted as there are currently no vaccine to treat the vesicles, treatments to target the clusters, instead of individual virus particles, would need to be developed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 02:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/14/3674621/3674621_110EB3A0D6E94153A045FCA0CD1797CA_180814_3674621_Scientists_find_that_stomach_viruses_are_able_to_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/941/07F/94107FE8ED8A8359701B8109D986BD27.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Study, science, stomach viruses, rotavirus, norovirus, stomach illness, vaccine, antiviral drugs, virus clusters, virus, individual viruses, virus infections, vesicles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3675778</guid>
      <title>Bridge collapses during violent storm in Italy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ITALY   A bridge in Genoa has suddenly collapsed, resulting in a number of casualties, reports The BBC.In a video posted on social media, a section of the Italian bridge was seen falling during a violent storm.Vehicles such as cars and trucks were also seen falling from the bridge as it collapsed.The section of the bridge that fell was around 200 meters long, the BBC reports.Sections of the bridge were seen collapsing onto the railway lines and the river among other places.Officials involved in the rescue mission say at least 26 people have been killed as a result of the incident. There are still at least 15 people injured and some missing as well.It is still unclear as to why the section of the bridge collapsed, reports CNN.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 12:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/15/3675778/3675778_E16EE957883C484E84F8D1561293E048_180815_3675778_Bridge_collapses_during_violent_storm_in_Italy_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15E/4C9/15E4C99579E6A200C9687CEAD38905E2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Italy, bridge collapses, bridge, storm, violent storm, bridge collapse italy, bridge collapse genoa, bridge collapse in genoa italy,bridge collapse italy video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3675651</guid>
      <title>Saudi Arabia threatens Canada with 9/11-style attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIYADH, SAUDI ARABIA  The Saudis and the Canadians are in the middle of a strange diplomatic dispute  all of which was set off by a single tweet.The BBC reports that months after women in Saudi Arabia were finally allowed to drive, several female rights activists were arrested on unclear grounds.Canada's foreign ministry expressed alarm over the arrests and said as much in a tweet, while also calling on the kingdom to release the activists.That apparently ticked Saudi Arabia off, so much so they kicked out the Canadian ambassador, stopped all flights to Toronto, and cut off all new trade.Days later, a Saudi-affiliated account tweeted out a graphic of a 9/11-esque scenario showing an Air Canada plane heading toward the CN tower, with a thinly veiled threat to stop meddling. Yikes.Both sides are standing their ground for now. Top moose Trudeau chimed in to the spat by reiterating Canada's commitment to human rights. Yeah, maybe don't sell arms to human rights violators, then?Can't have it both ways, Justin. World don't work that way.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 09:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/15/3675651/3675651_A832C78BF0E842318345C0EC83FC9023_180815_3675651_Saudi_Arabia_threatens_Canada_with_9_11_style_at_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/82B/D80/82BD80EBA8744EE29BED2D93D00E6189.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Saudi Arabia, Canada, human rights, women rights, whipping boy, international criticism, raif badawi, samar badawi, Air Canada, Toronto Tower, Saudi Arabia activists]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3675581</guid>
      <title>Florida GOP candidate caught using completely fake diploma</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SARASOTA, FLORIDA  A Republican candidate for the Flo-rida House was actually dumb enough to lie about having a college degree, and then trumped that by posing with a fake diploma. According to WPLG, Melissa Howard is running for the 73rd House District, and intends to stay in the Republican primary race. “It was not my intent to deceive or mislead anyone,” said the deceiver in a statement on Monday. I made a mistake in saying that I completed my degree. What I did was wrong and set a bad example for someone seeking public service. I am staying in the race and intend to win and lead by example from now on.” Howard was called out last week by FLA News Online for lying about graduating from the Miami University in Ohio on her website.So what did Einstein do? She flew to Ohio and posted a picture of her and a “diploma.”Unfortunately, the diploma shows a degree that doesn’t exist at Miami University. It also has a fake signature from a dean from a different program. Miami University also clarified that Howard didn’t graduate.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/15/3675581/3675581_62910B01E909483C9B9C29C83F42E5C1_180815_3675581_Florida_GOP_candidate_caught_using_completely_fa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/EA4/966/EA4966EC2B5144C6917441FD0C12249F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,Melissa Howard Florida GOP,Melissa Howard fake diploma,Melissa Howard GOP candidate,fake college degree]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3675426</guid>
      <title>University of Chicago ditches ACT, SAT requirement from application</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  As colleges across the country compete for students, hundreds of universities have stopped requiring the SAT or ACT. Some of the toppest tierest, uber exclusive institutions of higher learning have joined the growing movement, like Pitzer College, Lewis & Clark College, Cornell - College, and Montana State University.   But when the University of Chicago announced in June that it was dumping the requirement, it became the first good school to say sayonara to the standardized tests.Supporters of the move say dropping the test requirement is meant to encourage more disadvantaged students, aka blacks and Latinos, to apply.The problem is that when you drop the SAT or ACT requirement, then Asians get screwed because many actually do well on the tests.  University of Chicago Dean of Admissions James Nondorf feels the initiative will help to “level the playing field” for first-generation and low-income students. And let’s not forget, those rich (no-so-smart) legacy kids also need some help. What happened to looking for the best and brightest?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 05:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/15/3675426/3675426_6EB9EA647DDA4D9B936E95831447DF97_180815_3675426_University_of_Chicago_ditches_ACT__SAT_requireme_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/FEF/0D7/FEF0D78B5DC64417A4F415F1EBFCC03F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,colleges dropping ACT requirement,colleges dropping SAT requirement,University of Chicago,University of Chicago dropping SAT requirement,University of Chicago dropping ACT requirement]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3675373</guid>
      <title>Child receives near-fatal virus from mosquito bite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH CAROLINA  A woman is making the plight of her 6-year-old son public after he contracted a deadly virus from a mosquito bite, reports USA Today.In a post on social media, LoriAnne Surrett talks about how Noah, her son, had to spend six weeks at the hospital to fight the La Crosse encephalitis virus.A person contracts La Crosse encephalitis when they are bitten by an infected mosquito. The virus can cause inflammation of the brain as fluids build up. According to the CDC, symptoms usually take up to one to two weeks to show up and may include fever and headaches. In more severe cases, symptoms may also include nausea, vomiting, even seizures. The CDC says the most effective way to reduce the chance of being infected with the virus is to use insect repellents which contain DEET, Picaridin or other similar ingredients.The CDC also says there is no specific treatment for La Crosse encephalitis as antibiotics aren’t effective against the virus.However if the illness is severe, it may be treated with supportive therapy, IV fluids along with respiratory support, which is how Noah was treated.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 04:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/15/3675373/3675373_518709B0636F468DAC4F01CA767FCD9D_180815_3675373_Child_receives_near_fatal_virus_from_mosquito_bi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/EEA/799/EEA799231A7C49AEB7196A6F4D91BFD4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,TomoNews,Satire,virus,mosquito bite,La Crosse encephalitis,inflammation of brain,infected mosquito,insect repellents,DEET,Picaridin,infected with La Crosse encephalitis,mosquito bite spreading virus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676541</guid>
      <title>San Fran forming Poop Patrol to keep sidewalks deuce-free</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  San Fran may be one of the richest cities in the U.S., but it's also one of the filthiest, which is why the city is launching a new clean up crew to rid the sidewalks of human waste.According to the SF Chronicle, the city has formed a new task force called the "Poop Patrol." In around a month, a team of five Public Works staffers will get the honor of roaming the lovely sidewalks of the Tenderloin and Civic Center or other areas known to be littered with deuces in a steam cleaner on wheels. The team will start scrubbing away in the afternoons, typically when human logs start getting dropped off. According to Public Works director Mohammed Nuru, "we're trying to be proactive. We're actually out there looking for it." Between Jan. 1 and August 13 of this year, the city already received 14,597 calls about human mud pies on sidewalks.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 12:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/16/3676541/3676541_E943891CF19F44C9AF95990C0A2D4F2A_180816_3676541_San_Fran_forming_Poop_Patrol_to_keep_sidewalks_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6D7/5E3/6D75E31AB7C948A2BDFBAA428019638A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, San Francisco, San Francisco dirty sidewalks, San Francisco dirty streets, San Francisco Public Works, SF bathrooms]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676503</guid>
      <title>Vaping can harm important immune system cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM, UNITED KINGDOM  Vaping can harm important immune system cells, according to a new study. Researchers from the University of Birmingham found e-cigarette vapor disabled vital immune cells in the lungs and increased inflammation, the BBC reported. The small scale study was led by Professor David Thickett, and the results published in the online journal Thorax. The experiment used a mechanical procedure to mimic vaping, using lung tissue samples from eight non-smokers. Scientists found the vapor caused inflammation and negatively affected alveolar macrophages, cells that remove harmful dust particles, bacteria and allergens. Changes in the lung tissue occurred over 48 hours, however the group advise that further research is needed to understand long-term health complications from vaping. Thickett said while e-cigarettes may be safer than traditional cigarettes, they could still be harmful if used long-term.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 11:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/16/3676503/3676503_BE74E44CB8924C228145428C40B890CB_180816_3676503_Vaping_can_harm_important_immune_system_cells_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9BD/588/9BD588CBC7BC95A7908C9A58DE651347.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, vaping, vaping immune system, e-cigarettes, vaping health risks, e-cigs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676382</guid>
      <title>Bashar al-Assad is YouTube advertiser-friendly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA/DAMASCUS, SYRIA  A TomoNews investigation reveals that YouTube ads are running on videos connected to the Syrian regime, as well as a channel claiming to be President Bashar al-Assad's official YouTube channel.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 09:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/16/3676382/3676382_03972093BF8243E79F0C44E431674035_180816_3676382_Bashar_al_Assad_is_YouTube_advertiser_friendly_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/072/7B0/0727B013AC5C1DC135D6C1DA93B19CCB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, youtube, syria, youtube advertising, bashar al assad, adpocalypse, refugee crisis, programmatic ads, advertisements, content creators, international affairs, google, alphabet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676156</guid>
      <title>Coral-algal partnership has been around since age of dinosaurs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STATE COLLEGE, PENNSYLVANIA  Reef algae are much older and more resilient than previously thought, and may well survive longer than expected.The BBC reports that corals rely on microscopic algae that live inside their cells to harness energy from sunlight, both for food and reef formation. The algae, in turn, receive nutrients and protection.This symbiotic relationship was once estimated to have begun 50 to 65 million years ago, but new research published in Current Biology indicates it started in the mid-Jurassic some 160 million years ago.This means the coral-algal partnership were around when dinosaurs roamed Earth. Even more shocking  they survived the catastrophic event that rendered dinos extinct.On top of being older, the algae is also more diverse. Genetic analyses reveal that lineages lumped into one genus can in fact be subdivided into at least 15 genera with hundreds or thousands of species.Warming waters are a concern for coral due to bleaching, in which the algae is expelled by the coral. But findings suggest some algal species may be more tolerant of heat.The resilience depends largely on the species, but could be meaningful as far as climate change goes.For now, scientists need to modernize coral symbiont taxonomy, to improve communication and pave the way for future research on reef corals.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 05:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/16/3676156/3676156_448FFAA0224B48B981B954AEF63EC2AF_180816_3676156_Coral_algal_partnership_has_been_around_since_ag_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/A5F/19A/A5F19ACF93894A888125F1046806B8F9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, coral, coral reef, coral bleaching, coral algal partnership, micro-algae, coral algae, coral algal symbiosis, symbiotic, zooxanthellae, age of dinosaurs, global warming, warming oceans, climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676149</guid>
      <title>Face transplant gives suicide survivor second chance at life</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CLEVELAND  A 21-year-old woman has become the youngest person in the U.S. to receive a full-face transplant three years after surviving a suicide attempt.National Geographic reports that Katie Stubblefield was 18 when she shot herself with a hunting rifle. The bullet went through her forehead, nose, sinuses, and jaw, and damaged her eyes.Doctors in Memphis managed to save her life, but weren't able to close her wounds. Stubblefield was later moved to the Cleveland Clinic in Ohio, where surgeons crafted her a new nasal passage, and rebuilt her jaw and skull using bone grafts and titanium.A distraction device was attached to her facial bones and tightened daily to move her eyes into better alignment.Once a suitable donor was found, doctors removed the face and transplanted it onto Stubblefield, connecting nerves and blood vessels in a grueling 31-hour procedure.She was discharged in August 2017 after a nearly three-month long recovery period, but will need to take anti-rejection drugs for the rest of her life.The brave survivor plans to attend online college and go into counseling, in hopes that she can raise awareness about suicide prevention.For now, she's continuing to undergo physical and occupational therapy, on top of seeing a speech therapist and taking Braille lessons.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 05:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/16/3676149/3676149_4372E08159044A4E959F7A9F59B4B226_180816_3676149_Face_transplant_gives_suicide_survivor_second_ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/334/8D9/3348D929ED504B333A1BDEE64520E2ED.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, face transplant, full face transplant, youngest fact transplant, reconstructive surgery, plastic surgery, katie stubblefield, cleveland clinic, experimental medicine, experimental treatment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677351</guid>
      <title>Weedkiller chemical found in kids breakfast foods</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  Glyphosate has been found in a number of breakfast items specifically targeted at children such as cereals, oats and snack bars, reports The Guardian.A report published by EWG's Children's Health Initiative says that according to lab tests, the foods were found to contain "a hefty dose of the weed-killing poison."Around three-quarters of the tested food samples were found to have higher glyphosate levels than what EWG believes is safe for children.Junk from big name brands such as Quaker, Kellogg's and General Mills were found to have some of the highest concentrations of the chemical.EWG also said they believe the federal limits are outdated and that the EPA should limit the amount of glyphosate used on food crops.A CNN guest said the EPA says people should avoid consuming more than 2 mg of glyphosate for every kilogram of body weight. He continued saying "nobody on Earth consumes anywhere near that amount of glyphosate" and claimed EWG was lobbying for the organic industry.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 13:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3677351/3677351_C4596371F6E84D2C920039FA6FC6D1C5_180817_3677351_Weedkiller_chemical_found_in_kids_breakfast_food_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D7E/EBC/D7EEBC70680923F9A2648AA3D5BE421C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chemicals, weed-killing chemicals, breakfast foods, breakfast, food, kids, food for kids, cereals, oats, snack bars, glyphosate, EWG, EPA, cancer-linked chemical, poison]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677339</guid>
      <title>US actually has measles outbreaks in 21 states</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  According to the CDC, there has been an increase of measles cases this year.The past few years has seen a rise in people who unfortunately think vital vaccinations cause autism, which they don't. Most of the people who got measles were reportedly unvaccinated.Measles includes symptoms such as high fever, red eyes, and a rash that begins on the face.The CDC says the virus is contagious as it stays in the airspace when someone with measles has coughed or sneezed. Ninety percent of the people who aren't immune to the virus will likely become infected.They also recommend getting the measles, mumps, and rubella vaccine to prevent measles.The disease is especially unsafe for children under the age of 5 or adults over the age of 20.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 12:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3677339/3677339_72EEC594DC704FC188B18F9E3656A87F_180817_3677339_US_actually_has_measles_outbreaks_in_21_states_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6A7/A37/6A7A37C84E729879E2D58DB1B68C841F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Measles, Measles outbreak, vaccination, vaccines, measles symptoms, Virus, contagious,  MMR vaccine, disease, measles vaccine, measles virus]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677268</guid>
      <title>Woman's lost contact lens found embedded in eyelid after 28 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUNDEE, SCOTLAND  Decades after losing her contact lens, a woman finally managed to find it  embedded right in her eyelid.CNN reports that a 42-year-old British woman noticed a slight swelling over her left eye that became large and painful in a span of six months, prompting her to see a specialist.Doctors conducted an MRI and discovered a small 6-millimeter cyst embedded in her eyelid.When the cyst was surgically removed, it broke open to reveal a hard contact lens inside, even though the patient had not worn any for 28 years.Her mother later recalled that the woman got hit in the left eye with a shuttlecock as a teen. The rigid contact she was wearing was assumed lost, but had apparently stayed in the eyelid for 28 years.It's still a mystery why the swelling and inflammation happened nearly three decades after the incident. The woman's left eyelid had been droopy for a long time, but had no other symptoms indicative of a trapped contact lens.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 11:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3677268/3677268_E05CB1589FD844029CEAC59B885D174D_180817_3677268_Woman_s_lost_contact_lens_found_embedded_in_eyel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3A7/6E6/3A76E65C0D8AA34CFC0CDB92421C4B5C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, contact lens, lost contact lens, cyst, eye cyst, swollen eyelid, droopy eyelid, contact lens in eye, contact lens mishap]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677232</guid>
      <title>Google is tracking you even with location history disabled</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  Think Google isn't keeping tabs on your whereabouts just because you told it not to? Yeah... nope.The company is under fire after an Associated Press investigation found it continued to track users even when their location history was turned off.A help page for location tracking tools on the website had previously stated that "with location history off, the places you go are no longer stored."But according to the report, while Google may not be displaying your movements on a timeline, it continues to keep an eye on your every move through services and apps.Google maps, for example, snapshots your location as soon as you open it. Browser searches and weather updates also save your phone's whereabouts.So is there a way to go off the Google grid? The answer is yes, but it involves diving deep into your settings to find and disable "Web and App Activity."If you're really uncomfortable with having your time and geo-stamped data in the big G's hands, you can manually delete it from the 'My Activity' page  but know that it's tedious and time-consuming.Trust Google to make deleting your data as complicated and confusing as they possibly can. Those are advertising dollars, after all.On the bright side, Google has at least updated their help page to be less misleading. It now clarifies that some location data may still be saved due to other services on a device.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 10:58:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3677232/3677232_B2DF371607724B498C26999572EBC2EA_180817_3677232_Google_is_tracking_you_even_with_location_histor_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/464/ABD/464ABDD8C63FA470BE5BA90CF810EAFF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, google, location tracking, location history, data, data privacy, web and app activity, how to stop google location tracking, data collection]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677184</guid>
      <title>Georgia police investigating $100,000 ramen heist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FAYETTE COUNTY, GEORGIA  A group of thieves in Georgia stole ramen noodles worth around $100,000, according to the Atlanta-Constitution Journal.A truck packed with the ramen was parked outside a Chevron store in Fayetteville, Georgia.Police believe a group of robbers may have stolen instant noodles, but they're not exactly sure why.There may have been up to 200,000 individual packs of ramen in the truck, reports the Star-Telegram.Authorities are still looking for the ramen robbers, telling people to keep their eyes peeled for a white trailer truck.Meanwhile, social media was clearly impressed by the cup-a-noodles caper.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 10:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3677184/3677184_2C440D2E44CC4A22B7665B7AEB64E0D7_180817_3677184_Georgia_police_investigating__100_000_ramen_heis_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B05/429/B054292B7527F498CEC75BFD9D947E70.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, noodles, ramen noodles, instant noodles, ramen noodle packs, heist, ramen noodles heist, police, investigation, trailer truck, ramen trailer truck, suspects, robbers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677179</guid>
      <title>Elephants protected from cancer by 'zombie gene'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Elephants hardly ever get cancer, and scientists have finally figured out why.According to research from the University of Chicago, over 17% of people worldwide die from cancer, compared to less than 5% for elephants, even though they have 100 times as many potentially cancerous cells.One reason for this is they have over 20 copies of the tumor suppressor gene p53 that stops DNA damage from turning into cancer, while humans and other animals only have one.Because the cells died as soon as damage was detected, there is zero risk of them ever becoming cancerous.The study found that p53 can also trigger an inactive pseudogene in elephants called LIF6 to come back to life. When cell damage is detected by p53, it activates the LIF6 gene, which in turn produces a protein that pokes holes in the target mitochondria and causes it to die.This genetic resistance to cancer isn't just seen in elephants. Smaller critters like naked mole rats and grey squirrels also have mechanisms that keep them tumor-free.By studying how these animals' genes work, scientists are hoping to figure out how to prevent or treat cancer in humans.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 10:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3677179/3677179_50C52609EA63415C89090D9C113DC453_180817_3677179_Elephants_protected_from_cancer_by__zombie_gene__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F40/531/F4053135F6C54552E3B5041AB618FF1D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, elephants, cancer, cancer research, zombie gene, why elephants don't have cancer, cancer mortality, tumor suppressor gene, p53, lif6]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3677108</guid>
      <title>YouTube cans Syrian government channels after TomoNews report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DAMASCUS, SYRIA / SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA  Syrian government-linked YouTube channels been removed following a TomoNews report about ads displaying on them.Yesterday a TomoNews investigation showed how Syrian government-linked YouTube channels were displaying advertisements from massive brands.Those channels were YouTube / PresidencySy and ORTAS Videos, a channel for the General Organisation of Radio and TV for Syria. Syrian government websites linked to both.U.S. sanctions prohibit American companies from providing services to Syria without obtaining a license from the Treasury Department. ORTAS is specifically listed on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons.Not long after TomoNews contacted YouTube and the U.S. government for comment, and shortly after we published our video, those channels appeared with the text: "This account has been terminated due to a legal complaint." For the record, TomoNews did not file a legal complaint. We just reported on the story.Another ORTAS-linked YouTube channel that was linking to live streaming channels has also been removed, with YouTube citing community guideline violations.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 09:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3677108/3677108_218DD4EBAB5840488E92F00F64EA81F7_180817_3677108_YouTube_cans_Syrian_government_channels_after_To_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F01/EB4/F01EB4A11B8F61E83C5B3278586506E3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, youtube, syria, youtube advertising, bashar al assad, adpocalypse, refugee crisis, programmatic ads, advertisements, content creators, international affairs, google, alphabet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676966</guid>
      <title>Kroger testing self-driving grocery deliveries in Arizona</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SCOTTSDALE, ARIZONA   Krogers said it will begin testing self-driving grocery delivery with technology partner Nuro at a Kroger-owned Fry's Food Store in Scottsdale. According to Reuters, the initial phase of testing will use Toyota Prius cars equipped with Nuro tech. Safety drivers will remain behind the wheel in case of an error or emergency.Nuro's R1 driverless delivery van, which has no seats, will hopefully hit the roads in the fall, according to the companies. The driverless delivery service will set you back $5.95 with no minimum order required, and it will only be available to addresses inside the store's zip code. One drawback for the typical 'Murcian however, is that customers will actually need to walk to the curb to get their delivered groceries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 06:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3676966/3676966_6AF3388F640843C99A34A50266D56C6D_180817_3676966_Kroger_testing_self_driving_grocery_deliveries_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B33/2C1/B332C133CCF08A8680DD1BD0ADB907C4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Kroger, Kroger self-driving, Kroger driverless grocery delivery, self-driving grocery delivery, Kroger autonomous delivery, grocery delivery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3676934</guid>
      <title>Blue light from digital devices could speed up blindness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOLEDO, OHIO  If you haven't already, it might be time to cut down on screen time, as new research shows blue light is slowly killing our vision.Fortune reports that digital devices like phones or tablets are constantly exposing us to blue light, which cannot be blocked or reflected by the eye's cornea or lens.Photoreceptor cells in the retina rely on molecules called retinal to sense light and trigger the firing of signals to the brain. Simply put, it's what allows people to see.But a new study from the University of Toledo has found that exposing retinal to blue light causes a toxic reaction that kills photoreceptor cells, which are incapable of regenerating.When introduced into other cell types, the retinal molecule produced the same deadly reaction when exposed to blue light, but not with yellow, green, or red light.Alpha tocopherol, a form of vitamin E, was found to reduce cell damage. But as vitamin levels decrease with age, prolonged blue light exposure may lead to macular degeneration- a leading cause of blindness.Researchers say it's best to limit exposure and avoid looking at devices in the dark.Though if you really can't stay away, at least invest in protective glasses that filter out UV and blue light.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Aug 2018 06:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/17/3676934/3676934_06E3594F962044229E4EFB536BDE8F20_180817_3676934_Blue_light_from_digital_devices_could_speed_up_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4D6/AFF/4D6AFFB987774A8809A68838758D0F23.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  blue light, blindness, bad for your eyes, vision, blinding, blue light exposure, macular degeneration, digital devices, blue light filter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3678830</guid>
      <title>Woman survives 10 hours at sea after falling from cruise ship</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CROATIA  A British woman on a cruise ship in the Adriatic Sea fell into the water approximately 60 miles off the coast of Croatia and reportedly spent 10 hours treading water before being rescued. The 46-year-old, who some local media identified as Kay Longstaff, said, "I fell off the back of the Norwegian Star and I was in the water for 10 hours, so these wonderful guys rescued me," in an interview with Croatia's state television network HRT. According to the Washington Post, she declined to tell reporters how she fell off the cruise ship. The cruise company is expected to examine closed-circuit camera footage in order to determine the events leading up to the incident. The company said the woman went overboard as the ship was headed to Venice. The ship was stopped and a search mounted after crew realized someone had fallen overboard. Croatian navy and coast guard were also alerted. The navy used a PC-9 aircraft and a patrol boat. Kay was spotted around 9:40 p.m. in the sea and rescued five minutes later.  She was taken to a hospital in Pula, Croatia and is in stable condition.According to the Guardian, the incident is under investigation and the British embassy in Croatia has been informed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 12:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/20/3678830/3678830_5F9B27C7B05F48D5BF95D9554CAFB005_180820_3678830_Woman_survives_10_hours_at_sea_after_falling_fro_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/09F/B55/09FB55C82440C7D096B80FF7A145629E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, woman falls off cruise ship, woman survives 10 hours at sea, cruise ship, cruise ship fall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3678670</guid>
      <title>Refugee charity ad appeared on official Assad YouTube channel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA - A refugee charity has suspended advertising with Google after their ad appeared on a video on Bashar Al Assad's YouTube channel.The news come after a TomoNews investigation last week showed how Syrian dictator Bashar Al-Assad's official channel was displaying ads from massive brands on YouTube. The list of companies appearing there and on another Syri was large, including Samsung, Lexus and even DonaldJTrump.comA video featuring Assad also displayed ad a from UK refugee charity, Sponsorrefugees.org. TomoNews reached out to them with with our findings."We were unaware our adverts were being placed on this channel," a spokesperson for the charity said in an emailed statement. "We have suspended advertising with Google Ads and have asked they clarify where our adverts will be placed and give us assurances that our adverts will only run on appropriate channels."The channel in question was YouTube.com/PresidencySy. Another channel, not displaying the refugee ad, but still showing ads from companies, was ORTAS Videos or the General Organisation of Radio and TV for Syria. Syrian government websites linked to both channels. To be clear, we don't know if the Syrian regime was making money from these advertisements.After we reached out to Google for comment on Thursday, those channels were soon shut down. Writing in an emailed statement a rep for the company said then: "We disable videos and accounts that repeatedly violate our Community Guidelines or Terms of Service and when we are required by law to do so."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 09:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/20/3678670/3678670_6C6A3210F5E84F759A2C87930A7B4C55_180820_3678670_Refugee_charity_ad_appeared_on_official_Assad_Yo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F76/3AF/F763AF50378946514A47BF26350CC454.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, syria, youtube advertising, bashar al assad, adpocalypse, refugee crisis, programmatic ads, advertisements, content creators, international affairs, google, alphabet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3678507</guid>
      <title>Trump's military parade could cost up to $92 million</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  U.S. officials estimate the cost of a military parade for President Trump could be up to $92 million.This is three times more than the original estimate by the White House, reports the Washington Post.Officials say the Pentagon would spend around $50 million to cover the costs of aircrafts, equipment, personnel etc.According to CNBC, the remainder $42 million would be paid for by other agencies such as the Department of Homeland Security.The parade would also likely be pushed to 2019, instead of the original date of Nov. 10 this year.Helicopters, fighter jets, transport aircrafts as well as historical military plane flyovers, all expect to be included in the parade.However, the size and scope of the military parade could still shift.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 04:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/20/3678507/3678507_EB5C6529F87B40939C0FA59CFA01FC8E_180820_3678507_Trump_s_military_parade_could_cost_up_to__92_mil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/00E/24C/00E24C7C1D1063C0CEA5EA02341900D3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, USA, military parade, military parade usa, military parade trump, Trump military parade, trump news, Pentagon, White House, $92 million, military parades costs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679487</guid>
      <title>Woman killed by alligator as she attempts to save her dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEAUFORT  COUNTY, SOUTH CAROLINA    A woman was walking her dog when the pair was suddenly confronted by an alligator, reports USA Today.Cassandra Cline was walking her dog around the lagoon of the Hilton Head Island community, when an 8-foot-long alligator suddenly appeared out of nowhere and went after her pet.Cline didn't hesitate to jump into to try to rescue her pooch.Unfortunately, she was no match for massive reptile, which turned on her instead, dragging her into the water. Cline's body was later found in the lagoon by emergency responders, reports CNN.The dog, however, miraculously escaped unharmed.The Beaufort County Sheriff's office said an autopsy would be conducted soon, adding that they are "shocked and heartbroken over this loss."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 10:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/21/3679487/3679487_4136E783B2FE43479B2C273C99B1BDC8_180821_3679487_Woman_killed_by_alligator_as_she_attempts_to_sav_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D00/EB8/D00EB8D9759B24C6ED829A2A7861E0BC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, alligator, alligator attack human,alligator attacks woman, dog, woman, lagoon, South Carolina, alligator attack in South Carolina, alligator videos, alligator strikes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679453</guid>
      <title>Woman gets mob of men to show up for mass Tinder date in NYC</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A self-proclaimed singer, actress and model from New York City managed to win Tinder over the weekend after she tricked hundreds of men into a massive dating competition. According to the Gothamist, Natasha Aponte was able to get a boatload of men to show up to Union Square on Sunday thinking they were going to be on a one-on-one Tinder date. According to CBS News, Aponte sent out Tinder texts inviting unsuspecting men with messages like, "Hey, I'm finally free, do you wanna meet up at Union Square for my friend's DJ set, we'll get a drink and we'll see what happens."With the cheese carefully placed, all Aponte had to do was wait. Hundreds of eager men started showing up as expected. That's when Aponte hopped on stage, protected by bodyguards, and informed everyone that they had all been invited for a chance to go on a date with her. She then proceeded to live swipe-right and swipe-left by calling out things she wasn't into, like Puerto Ricans, Trump supporters and guys with long beards.Then she actually had men line of for a race. Even crazier, a lot of guys actually did it. Turns out this may have all been a viral stunt as Aponte had producer Rob Bliss helping her out. Bliss was the one who helped make the now famous catcalling video from 2014.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 10:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/21/3679453/3679453_F7080CE742B3420EAE9A1D140BC74014_180821_3679453_Woman_gets_mob_of_men_to_show_up_for_mass_Tinder_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CA8/C7D/CA8C7D7AC214E14223B8EB93C953E10F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Tinder date, mass Tinder date, dating game, Tinder dating game, Natasha Aponte Tinder, Natasha Aponte mass Tinder date]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679339</guid>
      <title>Chinese man swallows 87 nails, 7 push pins after lovers' tiff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TONGZHOU, CHINA  A Chinese man is miraculously still alive after swallowing dozens of nails because of a lovers' quarrel.China Times reports that the 25-year-old was taken to the hospital after complaining of abdominal pain, which he claimed was from accidentally eating a steamed bun stuffed with nails.But when an X-ray revealed a large mass of nails in his stomach and a few more near his groin, doctors suspected something else had gone down.According to several media reports, the man had swallowed the nails one by one after getting into a fight with his girlfriend. He gave hospital staff a farewell letter for her before his operation, telling them to contact her if they can't get in touch with his family.Fortunately, doctors managed to taking out all 87 nails during a 4-hour surgery. The man had also ingested seven push pins, but these passed naturally though his digestive tract.Swallowing that many nails is obviously very dangerous, not only because it might puncture internal organs, but also because metal plus stomach acids could make for a very nasty infection.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 08:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/21/3679339/3679339_568402844A6147FAB6D6AF97559EE738_180821_3679339_Chinese_man_swallows_87_nails__7_push_pins_after_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D2C/D6B/D2CD6BAB989DE6F8FA071D2C9E084159.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man swallows nails, man eats nails, nails in stomach, nails, push pins, nail stuffed bun, bun stuffed with nails, surgery, suicide note, farewell letter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679247</guid>
      <title>Eating certain vegetables can prevent colon cancer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  While it's been well-established that vegetables have many health benefits, the mechanisms behind them have largely remained unknown.Now, new research from the Francis Crick Institute and Imperial College London offers concrete evidence that eating certain veggies can not only keep the bowels healthy - it also protects from cancer.According to the study published in the journal Immunity, aryl hydrocarbon receptor or AhR is a protein that acts as an environmental sensor, protecting the gut from inflammatory responses to the bacteria that live in it.Scientists studied mice that couldn't produce AhR, finding that they developed gut inflammation, which progressed to colon cancer.The key to stimulating AhR is I3C or indole-3-carbinol, which is produced when vegetables from the Brassica genus like cabbage, broccoli, or kale, is digested.Mice that were fed a diet rich in I3C didn't develop inflammation or cancer. Those with cancer that were switched to the diet also ended up with fewer, more benign tumors.The team now wants to see if the veggies have the same effect on people. They're hoping to do further experiments in organoids made from biopsies of the human gut, and eventually go on to human trials.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/21/3679247/3679247_D7927286E4DE41F2B0D1FA930A0EF241_180821_3679247_Eating_certain_vegetables_can_prevent_colon_canc_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/50A/DED/50ADED5D30372998F257ED46DBAA09D7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cancer, cancer research, anti cancer, cancer cure, cancer prevention, colon cancer, cabbage, vegetables, bowel cancer, superfood, healthy food]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679213</guid>
      <title>Flushing disposable contacts is adding to plastics pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  A new study by Arizona State University found that people discarding their disposable contacts by flushing them could be contributing to plastics pollution. In the U.S., approximately 45 million people wear contacts. The study found around 15 to 20 percent of wearers don't dispose of their old lenses in waste containers, and instead flush them down toilets or sinks.    The study, presented at the National Meeting and Exposition of the American Chemical Society, estimates between 1.8 to 3.4 billion lenses get flushed per year, equaling 20 to 23 metric tons plastics waste. Because the contact lenses are made with stronger plastics, they do not break down when exposed to microbes while going through a sewage treatment plant.Researchers found that the old contacts instead become smaller pieces and are prevalent in wastewater sludge after sewage treatment. The sludge is then deposited on land where lenses can then be washed into lakes and rivers where they are then by fish, birds or other animals.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 04:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/21/3679213/3679213_DD0BD3097E6C47549FF33AEE94C6F705_180821_3679213_Flushing_disposable_contacts_is_adding_to_plasti_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C07/0CD/C070CD47FEF7C48C59A8AACD35055A8F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, disposable contacts, plastics pollution, microplastics, flushing disposable contacts, contact lenses]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679150</guid>
      <title>Kevin Spacey's new movie only makes $126 on opening day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  Kevin Spacey's new film, "Billionaire Boys Club" has opened to a record low of $126, reports Fox News.The Hollywood Reporter is describing the film debut as "a career low at the box office," for Kevin Spacey.The movie is Spacey's comeback of sorts since he was accused of sexual misconduct in the wake of the MeToo movement."Billionaire Boys Club" only opened in 10 select theaters across the country on Friday.And this is after the movie was first released on video about a month ago.According to the Hollywood Reporter, if movie tickets cost around $9.27, it means fewer than six people showed up in each cinema.Spacey, who has won two oscars in the past, probably never expected his career to take such a drastic turn.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 03:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/21/3679150/3679150_61056D47D92642238366F20719A03E65_180821_3679150_Kevin_Spacey_s_new_movie_only_makes__126_on_open_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/B39/412/B39412C1C2984D8E8797D618FC7A1650.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, celebrities, Kevin Spacey, Kevin Spacey new movie, Billionaire Boys Club, movie, new movie, opening day, Me Too movement, sexual misconduct allegations, Kevin Spacey sexual misconduct allegations]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3680316</guid>
      <title>Man won't marry girlfriend offering him new car and $14,000</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HENAN, CHINA  In recent local news out of China, a Chinese woman's marriage proposal was turned down in a very embarrassingly public way.According to The Paper, the woman desperately wanted to marry her boyfriend, but wasn't able to quite get over his "cowardliness."So she devised a challenge for him.Standing atop the famous U-Shaped glass walkway at Fuxi Mountain in Henan while clad in a poofy, white wedding dress, she said she would marry him as long as he mustered up the courage to walk across the transparent bridge 350 meters up from the ground.Now if love wasn't enough to get him across that bridge, she sweetened the deal with a brand new car and about $14,000 in cash.But it appears even that wasn't enough, and although footage shows the man's friends pushing him and trying to talk him into crossing that figurative marital gangplank and literal glass walkway, he said no.Then he ran away, saying that the woman was being irresponsible and that she was putting their relationship at risk.Many are dismissing the entire event as merely a publicity stunt, but although staff members at the bridge admit to helping the woman execute her proposal, they said it was no stunt.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 13:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/22/3680316/3680316_C8A9232281EE4AF7B023884AE9B2F0A0_180822_3680316_Man_won_t_marry_girlfriend_offering_him_new_car__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FB6/219/FB6219946E48FD73C44101790F39245C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, marriage proposal gone wrong, marriage proposal fail, glass walkway, glass bridge, Fuxi Mountain, Henan province, China, Chinese couple, publicity stunt]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3680147</guid>
      <title>Robbers try to jack $75,000 from Texas woman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON  A woman was robbed in broad daylight at a gas station after withdrawing $75,000 from a bank.The theft took place around 10 a.m. last Friday at the Valero on Cypress North Houston at Highway 290, according to ABC 13. Video surveillance footage was released by the Harris County Precinct 4 Constable's office.  It shows the woman getting out of her car carrying a purse. As she tries to enter the store, a suspect pulls up in an SUV and rushes her from behind, and attempts to snatch the purse with 75 grand. The woman and the thief get into a violent struggle as a man from inside the store comes running out to help the woman. As all three people struggle on the ground, the woman manages to get up, but then another car pulls up with a second robber. Both thieves then start attacking the woman and the man from the store. At one point, one of the suspects gets into his car, and then backs the vehicle up over the woman. The robbers then proceed to make off with the cash. Authorities say the suspects had followed the woman from the bank after she made her large withdrawal. According to Harris County Precinct 4 Constable Mark Herman, one of the suspects has been arrested and the other remains at large. The woman was transported to the hospital where she is in critical condition.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 10:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/22/3680147/3680147_06958283350F4011904C205D6086C23E_180822_3680147_Robbers_try_to_jack__75_000_from_Texas_woman_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3BF/D29/3BFD29C2D91DFD259BD1E12F2C4106B0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, robbery, purse snatching, robbers snatch $75,000]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3680142</guid>
      <title>Woman's eyelids glued shut after failed eyelash extensions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHUKET, THAILAND  A woman who went to get some eyelash extensions left a salon with here eyes swollen shut after a botched procedure.Apparently the woman and her beautician weren't seeing eye-to-eye because the lady used super glue to attach the fake lashes instead of the proper cosmetic adhesives, according to Yahoo Sports. A video of the woman getting her eyelids fixed was posted on Facebook and has since racked up an eye popping 1.3 million views.Fara, the beautician that helped to woman get the glue and fake lashes off, said she's never seen a case like this. According to Sanook, Fara said when the woman came into see her the glue had already dried and her eyes were mad swollen. To remove the fake lashes, Fara first had to apply some solution to soften the glue, then she used a steel cuticle pusher to scrap the fake lashes away from her eyes. It's unclear where the woman got her super glue extensions done, but after this eye-opening experience, she probably won't be looking to go back anytime soon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 10:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/22/3680142/3680142_86CDBF7067494A72AA17E6E17A08A50C_180822_3680142_Woman_s_eyelids_glued_shut_after_failed_eyelash__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/444/410/4444109C7D4A3241AB60B3C3C8F97D34.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, eyelash extensions, fake eyelashes, eyelash extensions fail, eyelash extensions super glue, woman eyelids glued shut, eyelids glued shut]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679987</guid>
      <title>Chinese shoppers brawl in South Korean duty free shop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA  No one likes queue jumpers, but would you go so far as to beat one up? Well, these Chinese shoppers will.The Korea Times reports that two women from China were recently caught on camera having a hoedown outside a Lotte Duty Free in Seoul, South Korea.An employee told MailOnline that the pair started brawling after one of them went straight to the front of the line.Footage of the hullabaloo that was posted to Weibo and Miaopai shows a lady in a white shirt exchanging blows with a woman in black as a crowd looks on.When the lady in white takes her opponent to the ground, a man, presumably white's husband, stomps on the other woman's head. He's quickly pulled away by onlookers, but continues shouting that the woman was bullying his wife.The brawl supposedly lasted for five minutes before security came and broke it up.Needless to say, the trio isn't getting any sympathy from the internet, with netizens saying they're an embarrassment to China, and should be banned from travelling.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 07:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/22/3679987/3679987_27CBCD5DCA9D4A47B082E7CB4C42D364_180822_3679987_Chinese_shoppers_brawl_in_South_Korean_duty_free_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E01/98E/E0198EA5DEDF62EC86CD482FAC8783C9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, duty free fight, queue jumper, line jumper, korean duty free, shoppers fight, shoppers brawl, shopping fight, lotte duty free, epic fight]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679933</guid>
      <title>Massive magma cache found beneath California supervolcano</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONO COUNTY, CALIFORNIA  New research has found a huge cache of magma hidden underneath one of the largest supervolcanoes in the world.Forbes reports that California's Long Valley supervolcano erupted some 760,000 years ago, spewing out hot ash, lava, and toxic gas for 6 days that resulted in the formation of a massive caldera.Since 1978, a gradual uplift has been observed in the caldera center, likely from magma flowing into a chamber below the supervolcano.Using seismic tomography, researchers from the USGS California Volcano Observatory were able to show a more detailed view of the subsurface, which they published in the journal Geology.They discovered that the reservoir beneath the supervolcano contained 240 cubic miles of semi-molten magma, 27% of which was in a liquid state.An eruption would require at least 50% of the magma to be liquid, so there's no immediate threat.The bad news is, when Long Valley does eventually erupt, it's likely going to be a massive catastrophe similar to the one from hundreds of thousands of years ago.Since scientists aren't be sure how magma is distributed within the reservoir, normal eruptions are also a possibility, so they're keeping a very close eye on the caldera.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 06:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/22/3679933/3679933_2A0DBCB8A62C4E8DAFFBDEB01642DAB2_180822_3679933_Massive_magma_cache_found_beneath_California_sup_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8ED/A4C/8EDA4CF25956CBBF0ACC061F7271DAE5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, supervolcano, volcano, magma, magma cache, magma reservoir, long valley supervolcano, long valley caldera, california supervolcano, volcanic eruption, lava, hot lava, pyroclastic flows]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679896</guid>
      <title>Minds social network has its own token and just moved to Ethereum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CRYPTOWORLD  Minds, a blockchain based social network, has launched its own token to reward users for using the website in addition to moving the network to Ethereum.According to Heavy.com, Minds is an encrypted, open-source Facebook clone that claims to focus on free speech.  Users on Mind.com will earn tokens for contributing to the site, according to Heavy.com. Tokens can also be purchased on the site. In addition, users will also be able to promote posts using tokens. Minds users can also use the tokens to tip channels or to pay for subscriptions.  Minds CEO Bill Ottman says the platform receives 500,000 daily pages views and has 1.25 million registered users.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 05:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/22/3679896/3679896_1C803E25DFBC4868AFB5FE1DB2BAFB6D_180822_3679896_Minds_social_network_has_its_own_token_and_just__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6EB/F26/6EBF26BC646744CCF9A8A64B6B343DD4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cryptocurrency, digital currency, social media network, Minds social network, Ethereum]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3679891</guid>
      <title>These electric chopstick simulate different flavors on the tongue</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  According to a study published in Food Research International, a team of scientists have designed cutlery which could help to alter the taste of food and help to cut down on the amount of salt we consume. Human beings have the tendency to eat a lot of salt because it makes food taste good, even though too much salt isn't good for the body, reports IEEE Spectrum.Nimesha Ranasinghe, assistant professor at the University of Maine and director of the Multisensory Interactive Media Lab, came up with the idea of using utensils such as chopsticks and soup bowls to transmit the salty flavor to the tongue.Ranasinghe said he experimented with the amplitude, the frequency and with the placement of electrodes on different utensils.He designed a pair of chopsticks with electrodes embedded in the tips of the chopstick which would send taste sensations to the tongue once turned on.Ranasinghe said recent research shows all the regions of the tongue can detect all five taste senses, reports IEEE Spectrum.He told Newsweek the technology would be able to simulate different flavors such as sourness, saltiness, and bitterness with around 70 percent accuracy.The scientist has also experimented with different objects such as flavor-enhancing water bottles, straws, spoons, and even an Internet-connected cocktail glass aka a "vocktail."He admits the technology is still in its beginning stages, however he has hope that " ... one day virtual flavors will burst onto the tongue … "]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 05:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/22/3679891/3679891_163611A2AEF1498098D025CF157AEEFC_180822_3679891_These_electric_chopstick_simulate_different_flav_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CFA/B65/CFAB657B5ABB8A9283C22E596EFDB6B0.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, food, food flavors, chopsticks, electric chopsticks, electric taste augmentation, electrodes, simulated flavors, technology, sense of taste, tongues, taste sensation, five tastes]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3680968</guid>
      <title>Nvidia releases overpriced RTX 20 Series</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GERMANY  Nvidia unveiled its next generation RTX 20 Series graphics cards at the GeForce Gaming event in Germany. According to Forbes, before you blow a ton a dough on the RTX 2080 Ti or the RTX 2080, you might want to wait awhile for the prices to drop. Nvidia's newest GPU is built around real-time ray tracing. Ray tracing renders light in real-time when it interacts with surfaces, skin and objects. Ray tracing addresses billions of light sources in real-time which takes loads of computing power, but is able to make everything much more realistic. Even though this is a significant leap for GPUs, the exorbitant price tag may not justify the purchase as only around 20 games have been optimized for ray tracing. Nvidia is hoping suckers will pre-order the RTX cards for $799 a pop. The best bet though, would be to just wait.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 09:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/23/3680968/3680968_3840D3C28EBB4B54BD510EF1CF294EC1_180823_3680968_Nvidia_releases_overpriced_RTX_20_Series_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D16/D2A/D16D2AE5971D7F88C3DFA23CA4D0C07B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Nvidia, Nvidia RTX 20, Nvidia RTX 20 graphics card, ray tracing, Nvidia ray tracing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3680831</guid>
      <title>Walmart may soon let lazy 'Muricans shop in VR</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA  The company that made grocery shopping synonymous with fat scooters may be working on a way to make 'Muricans even lazier  if that's possible. According to Retail Dive, the geniuses over at Walmart have actually taken out two patents for a virtual reality showroom that customers can visit and buy Made-in-China garbage through VR headsets.Instead of visiting an actual brick and mortar store, Walmart thinks people will be dumb enough to throw on some clunky VR goggles so they can select items from virtual shelves, which will then be shipped to them. According to MediaPost, the VR rooms could be equipped with sensory feedback systems that could control temperature and release smells corresponding to the objects handled in VR. How many smells would Walmart have to develop for this?Even more useless, the sensors devices could also simulate wind, rain, heat, cold, snow and ice, because you run into all of those when shopping inside Walmart stores. Will Walmart actually implement any of these game changing ideas? One can only hope.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 07:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/23/3680831/3680831_300F393ABFBD46D5AB61F3EFC3B0EF4D_180823_3680831_Walmart_may_soon_let_lazy__Muricans_shop_in_VR_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/246/18C/24618C9CDD0B14925CE9B029709366A6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satirlookinge, Walmart, Walmart virtual reality, Walmart virtual reality patents, virtual reality, virtual reality shopping experience]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681941</guid>
      <title>Facebook finds Iranian accounts spreading misinformation online</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRAN  Facebook released a statement saying they have removed hundreds of accounts and pages after they were found spreading misinformation on the social networking site.Facebook says FireEye, a cybersecurity firm, alerted them about the Iranian accounts and pages.The Iranian efforts date back to 2011 and involved Facebook and Instagram.It eventually expanded to Twitter and Youtube as well, reports The Washington Post.Facebook says it removed a total of 652 pages, accounts, and groups which were linked to Iran.Facebook claims some of the accounts were linked to Iran's state-owned media.Apparently, the fake Iranian accounts used Facebook to organize events and purchase ads on the website.The accounts included themes such as "anti-Saudi, anti-Israeli, and pro-Palestinians." They also seemed to advocate policies that were favorable to Iran.Twitter said it had removed 284 accounts for "coordinated manipulation," saying the accounts appeared to have originated from Iran.According to reports from The Independent, the fake accounts were found to target users specifically in the US, UK, Latin America and the Middle East.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 10:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/24/3681941/3681941_6AA9D962702D4C549CFA338B8B0EA3DC_180824_3681941_Facebook_finds_Iranian_accounts_spreading_misinf_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/561/2CA/5612CAFD207CBE2E584FF6AB8E124F11.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Iran, misinformation, global misinformation operation, Iranian influence, disinformation, disinformation campaigns, social media, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Youtube, fake accounts, fake Iranian accounts]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681829</guid>
      <title>Police officer who was breastfeeding baby promoted</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERISSO, ARGENTINA  A police officer who breastfeed a hungry, abandoned baby has been promoted after a picture of her went viral.  According to CNN, Officer Celeste Jaqueline Ayala had recently become a mom. She was on patrol at the Sister Maria Ludovica children's hospital on August 14, when she heard a crying baby. According to Metro UK, she told local media she noticed he was hungry and putting his hand in his mouth, so she asked hospital staff if she could hug and breastfeed him. Ayala grabbed a chair and sat down outside the hospital ward and fed the little fellow. Her partner snapped a photo and posted it on Facebook, but it didn't really go viral until this week.  Because of her selfless and kind-hearted act, she's now been promoted to sergeant.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 09:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/24/3681829/3681829_9C7C529B14E64AA9BE46D025572C2B1F_180824_3681829_Police_officer_who_was_breastfeeding_baby_promot_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1E8/0DC/1E80DC81DBC156029EB5655C4F7D8305.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, police officer promoted, police officer feeding baby, argentina police officer feeding, hungry baby, feeding baby]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681654</guid>
      <title>Facebook found rating its users based on trustworthiness</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  Facebook has started giving scores based on trustworthiness of users on the social media site.According to The Washington Post,  Facebook has developed the ratings system over the past year and would be used to assign users a score from zero to one.Facebook has not disclosed what criteria they use to determine a user's scores, or whether the scores are used in any other way.Facebook claims the system was created in an effort to combat fake news.Facebook has given the option to allow users to report or flag problematic content on the site.However, they have discovered that some people were falsely reporting content just because they didn't agree with it.A spokeswoman from Facebook told The BBC, they are doing this to ensure the "fight against misinformation is as effective as possible."Users apparently have no way of knowing what their rating is, at least for now.Other tech companies such as Uber and Twitter also give their users scores and ratings. Even the Chinese government has a system in place in which gives its citizens a "social credit" score based on their behavior both online and off.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 06:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/24/3681654/3681654_0BF6D51B890C49028E28E0F3EB0CD384_180824_3681654_Facebook_found_rating_its_users_based_on_trustwo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/35A/A10/35AA108826D7889E8A791CA0FA81FC89.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Facebook, facebook users, rating users, social media, ratings system, misinformation, fake news, fight against fake news, content, scores, surveillance]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681649</guid>
      <title>This is how China could WIN at trade</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China is expanding its global influence via what some are calling a new 'Silk Road', but it is so much more than it seems.The Belt and Road project  which the Center for Strategic and International Studies says could cost anywhere between $1 trillion and $8 trillion  aims to connect trade between Asia, Africa and Europe with infrastructure that is built and paid for by China.According to consulting firm Dezan Shira, the project's financing mainly comes from Chinese state-owned investment funds and development banks, as well as the newly created Asian Infrastructure Investment Bank.The project also puts the stability of China and neighboring countries, such as Afghanistan, as a priority, according the European Council on Foreign Relations. This is tied to their fears of revolt from separatists in Xinjiang province. China worries they could find a base of operation outside its borders, and are using the project as a means to leverage regional security cooperation.Several governments questioned the timing of their of Chinese loans, and are now looking to renegotiate the financial terms, according to Project Syndicate.China has already acquired a 40 year lease on a deepwater port in Pakistan, as well as a naval-base in Djibouti. Future ports in Burma and Kenya may also hold promise for the country. This has led some analysts, such as professor Brahma Chellaney writing in Project Syndicate, to believe Beijing's actual aim is to create a network of naval bases via its Belt and Road trade routes.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 06:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/24/3681649/3681649_B48AD475CA0C405C850CA2D8A8F77FA3_180824_3681649_This_is_how_China_could_WIN_at_trade_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/928/33B/92833B08E2969461B87C1CD889D55941.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, belt and road, sri lanka, economics, international trade, global economy, asia, chinese navy, foreign relations, international business, trade routes, china economy, new silk road, Asian Infrastructure Investment Bank, world trade, economics, business, trade tariffs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3681496</guid>
      <title>NASA to install heat shields in the new Orion Spacecraft</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENNEDY SPACE CENTER, FLORIDA  According to reports from NASA, an uncrewed Orion spacecraft will be launched during the Exploration Mission-1, beginning a three week trip to space.NASA's Orion spacecraft is 16.5 feet in diameter, one of the largest of its kind.The base structure of the heat shield has titanium truss covered with layers of carbon fiber material known as composite substrate.Large blocks of Avcoat, an ablative material, were then bonded onto the shield's surface.Avcoat has been used in the past in Apollo's heat shields and the Orion Exploration Flight Test-1. However, this time blocks were used instead of the usual injecting method.The Orion spacecraft would be taken 40,000 miles beyond the moon and back to Earth.As the spacecraft re enters Earth's atmosphere, it would need to withstand temperatures of upto 5,000 degrees Fahrenheit. This is when the ablative material will wear away, and prevent heat from being transferred to the rest of the spacecraft.The NASA engineers plan to monitor how the Orion performs in outer space and if it works well, it may soon carry astronauts into space destinations such as the Moon and Mars.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/24/3681496/3681496_C1A5629726F744C4B88A567639DC56C7_180824_3681496_NASA_to_install_heat_shields_in_the_new_Orion_Sp_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ECC/B8B/ECCB8BB59496F76F0FA61A62C5B039E8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Space, Outer space, NASA, heat shield, Kennedy Space Center, spacecraft, Orion Spacecraft, NASA Orion Spacecraft, Orion NASA, astronauts, Avcoat, ablative material]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683638</guid>
      <title>Parasitic disease spread by 'kissing bugs' on the rise in the US</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  According to a statement from the American Heart Association, Chagas disease has been spreading from Central and South America to the U.S.Chagas disease is spread by a bug called the Triatomine bug, also known as the kissing bug, which carries a parasite called Trypanosoma cruzi.According to the CDC, the kissing bug gets infected by biting an infected animal or person.After getting infected, the bug carries the parasite in its feces.The infected bug then bites humans around the eyes or mouth, breaking into the skin.Initial symptoms of Chagas disease include fever, body aches, headaches, rashes etc, however the American Heart Association released a warning saying around 60-70 percent of people do not develop any symptoms of the disease.According to the CDC, the infection may result in cardiac complications or intestinal complications for some.The disease can only be treated with anti-trypanosomal medication.It also does not spread from person to person or contact with animals.The American Heart Association released a statement to increase global awareness of the disease in hopes of detecting the disease at an early stage.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 13:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683638/3683638_BD4B65BD3A894AD886E979ECA2ACDD33_180827_3683638_Parasitic_disease_spread_by__kissing_bugs__on_th_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/450/E19/450E194B4FFDFB08FFD2DAB83E5EB5A8.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Kissing bug disease, kissing bug, Triatomine bug, Chagas disease, Chagas disease symptoms, disease, infected animal, infected person, infected bug, Trypanosoma cruzi parasite, parasite, infection, illness, CDC, American Heart Association]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683539</guid>
      <title>What is glioblastoma, the brain cancer that killed John McCain?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AMERICA  Arizona Senator John McCain died Saturday from an aggressive form of brain cancer, glioblastoma. According to the American Brain Tumor Association, glioblastomas are brain tumors that appear in astrocytes, star-shaped cells that make up the supportive tissue of the brain. Glioblastomas are highly malignant and reproduce rapidly, and are supported by a large network of blood vessels in the brain. They rarely spread to other parts of the body. They are usually found in the cerebral hemispheres of the brain, but can appear anywhere in the brain or spinal cord. According to Popular Science, symptoms can range from general neurologic symptoms, such as headaches or seizures, to specific areas of the brain, like speech difficulty, weakness on one side of the body, or double vision.Glioblastoma is normally diagnosed through brain imagery and then surgery. Treatment includes surgery to remove as much of the tumor as possible, then radiation and chemotherapy.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 11:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683539/3683539_9CAD5B3523D646CFAA4323F3C9B05F96_180827_3683539_What_is_glioblastoma__the_brain_cancer_that_kill_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/297/ECE/297ECE785BBEF8F40245F648C544392A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, brain cancer, brain tumor, glioblastoma, Senator John McCain, GBMs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683365</guid>
      <title>NASA launches new laser to track Earth's melting polar ice caps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  NASA says it plans to launch an advanced laser instrument which would be used to monitor our planet's melting polar ice.NASA's new laser  Ice, Cloud and land Elevation Satellite-2 (ICESat-2)  would have the ability to collect more than 250 times the height measurements of polar ice compared to its predecessor.The laser also uses a new system called Advanced Topographic Laser Altimeter System (ATLAS), which would enable it send six beams of green light to the ground and to fire 10,000 times each second.The laser would also have the ability to measure ice on Greenland and Antarctica "within the width of a pencil," by capturing 60,000 measurements each second.It would also be able to time how long it takes for light photons in the green light to travel to and from Earth.NASA says ICESat-2 will get a more detailed view of the ice surface as it circles the Earth from pole to pole, measuring ice heights along the way four times a year.NASA says the mission is scheduled to last for three years and hopes this new technology will bring about new data about our planet's melting ice and how its changing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 07:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683365/3683365_4C880C88FD3347EA91A216F5D76DF836_180827_3683365_NASA_launches_new_laser_to_track_Earth_s_melting_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE6/5BA/FE65BADF054A32F478D8FE6F988E3CBE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, NASA, space, laser, space laser, ice, polar caps, antarctica, greenland, ICESat-2, ATLAS, Earth, melting ice caps, polar ice, polar ice caps melting, NASA announcement]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683341</guid>
      <title>World's biggest plane reveals new rocket lineup</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE, WASHINGTON  The makers of the world's largest plane have recently unveiled exactly how it plans to deploy satellites into orbit.According to a Stratolaunch Systems press release, its planned lineup of launch vehicles includes the Pegasus rocket, two medium-lift rockets, and a space plane.The small-payload Pegasus XL has a 370-kilogram capacity for either single or triple configuration.The Medium Launch Vehicle, or MLV, has a capacity of 3,400 kilograms. A three-core variant called the MLV-Heavy is being developed to carry nearly twice as much.The reusable space plane, codenamed 'Black Ice', is presently just a design study. It's meant to carry cargo to and from Earth, though a follow-on variant will be crew-capable.Rather than blasting off a launchpad, the rockets will be tethered to a massive twin-fuselage carrier, which boasts a wingspan of 385 feet. Once the plane gets to an altitude of 35,000 feet, the rockets drop and blast off into orbit.Assuming everything goes smoothly for Stratolaunch, we might be able to see the first Pegasus rocket launch by 2020, followed by the MLV in 2022.So far, the main aircraft carrier has done a taxi test, but has yet to go up in the air. It will also need to be tested and fitted for the rockets.All in all, seems like the company's got a lot of work to do.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 06:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683341/3683341_012DACF903AA471B9C9469D0A8A57E96_180827_3683341_World_s_biggest_plane_reveals_new_rocket_lineup_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/126/D82/126D828183887CD2AF297F1D00B18761.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, stratolaunch, world's biggest plane, world's largest plane, rocket, launch vehicle, air launch, space orbit, rocket fleet, launch vehicle, pegasus xl, mlv, mlv-h, space plane, black ice]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683288</guid>
      <title>US scientists approve electron-ion collider project</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON, D.C.  The U.S. National Academies of Sciences, Engineering, and Medicine has endorsed the development of a multi-million-dollar particle accelerator project.According to MIT News, the electron-ion collider will consist of two intersecting accelerators  one blasting a beam of electrons and the other a beam of protons or ions to nearly the speed of light.The beams are made to collide at intersecting points, which are surrounded by detectors to record the resulting interaction.Each collision generates virtual photons, particles of light that penetrate through the proton or nucleus to tease out the structure within, including the distribution of quarks and gluons.The proposed machine would be able to help physicists understand where the mass of a proton comes from, how it gets its spin, and how gluons work.Science Magazine reports that two facilities have submitted proposals to host the EIC. Brookhaven National Laboratory in Upton, New York has a proton accelerator, but no electron ring, while the Jefferson Lab in Newport News, Virginia has the electron accelerator, but will need a proton ring.The Department of Energy is currently building a $730 million facility for rare isotope beams, and may not be able to fund the proposed collider until after 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 05:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683288/3683288_C41F440E2B0F4196816507AAF3DDF812_180827_3683288_US_scientists_approve_electron_ion_collider_proj_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5AB/076/5AB076095E84C3E991F129BA171FF576.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, electron ion collider, EIC, particle accelerator, electron beam, protons, proton parts, electrons, proton mass, spin, physics, nuclear physics, jefferson lab, brookhaven national laboratory]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683276</guid>
      <title>Neanderthal-Denisovan hybrid discovered in Siberian cave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SIBERIA, RUSSIA  Scientists have found concrete evidence of interbreeding between different species of early humans.In 2012, a bone fragment from a teenage girl who died some 90,000 years ago was recovered from the Denisova cave in Siberia's Altai Mountains, according to a new study published in Nature.Analysis of the genome conducted at the Max Planck Institute for Evolutionary Anthropology revealed that the girl was a hybrid  her mother was a Neanderthal while her father was Denisovan.Denisovans are a hominin group distinct from Neanderthals and modern humans. Only a few of their bone fragments have been found, so their appearance and behavior remain a mystery.Researchers did find that this particular Denisovan had some Neanderthal ancestry, while the mother was genetically closer to Neanderthals in western Europe than to one who had lived in the cave earlier.Scientists knew from looking at the genetic patterns of ancient humans and homo sapiens that the different groups mated with each other, but the findings mark the first time a first-generation offspring of these pairings has been found.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 05:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683276/3683276_A760827993A841D0AAD1B67990A0CD03_180827_3683276_Neanderthal_Denisovan_hybrid_discovered_in_Siber_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/194/865/1948653F8E5AA1A1DA6CA00BDC59DE03.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, human hybrid, ancient human, interbreeding, neanderthal, denisovan, neanderthal denisovan hybrid, denisova cave, ancient teen]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683255</guid>
      <title>Rare flesh-eating sexually transmitted disease found in UK</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM   A rare sexually transmitted disease which causes the genitals to break out into flesh eating ulcers has been found in the UK for the first time, reports The Lancashire Post.The STI is called Donovanosis, and is usually found in tropical regions such as southeast India, Guyana and New Guinea.The infection usually occurs in the genital area, however it could also appear around the nose, mouth, and chest.If a person goes without treatment, the ulcers could increase in size.Shamir Patel, a pharmacist,  told Liverpool Echo, that antibiotics could potentially be used to treat the disease.He said the STI is a "rare and nasty condition" which causes lesions and skin disintegration as the flesh basically eats itself and "literally rot away."However, he said the disease is going untreated in the early stages due to to it being so uncommon in the UK.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 04:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683255/3683255_167C335E2798416C95F962AB5395AEB9_180827_3683255_Rare_flesh_eating_sexually_transmitted_disease_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F09/E6D/F09E6DD8F2A09355E5439840B676A3F5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, STI, STD, ulcers, flesh-eating ulcers, UK, STD symptoms, sexually transmitted disease, disease, genitals, infection, tropical areas, antibiotics, bacteria, skin disintegration, lesions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683172</guid>
      <title>Drug tunnel found under old KFC restaurant in Arizona</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN LUIS, ARIZONA  Authorities in Arizona discovered a nearly 600-foot long drug tunnel running between a former fast food restaurant and a private residence in Mexico. According to KGUN, suspect Jesus Ivan Lopez Garcia was pulled over on August 13 after police saw him loading several plastic containers into a trailer outside of an old Kentucky Fried Chicken restaurant. Lopez was found to be in possession of 239 packages of various narcotics, including 261 pounds of methamphetamine, 14 pounds of cocaine, 30 pounds of white heroin, 13.7 bounds of brown heroin and 6.8 pounds of fentanyl. Police say the total street value of the drugs was over $1 million.    After obtaining a search warrant, agents searched Lopez's home and the old KFC and found the entrance to the tunnel in the kitchen of the former fast food restaurant. Homeland Security Investigations told KYMA, the tunnel was 22 feet deep, 5 feet tall and 3 feet wide. It extended 590 feet underground to a home across the border in San Luis Rio Colorado, Mexico where it came up to a trap door underneath a bed.   Garcia is now facing federal charges that include conspiracy to possess with intent to distribute methamphetamine and cocaine.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 02:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/27/3683172/3683172_2E1F7CC00ABB464EB24B73F72965453A_180827_3683172_Drug_tunnel_found_under_old_KFC_restaurant_in_Ar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4AE/870/4AE8707392820CBDBE75DC2D6D52DFAE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tunnels, tunnel, former KFC tunnel, US Mexico border, US Mexico border tunnels]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684156</guid>
      <title>UK Border Force detector dogs celebrate 40 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  The Border Force detector dogs in the UK are celebrating 40 years of sniffing out medication, drugs among other things to protect UK borders.According to Border Force - Gov.UK, different breeds such as Labradors, German Brief Haired, Pudelpointers, Slovak Pointers and more are usually trained to work as detector dogs.Over the years, around 700 different detector canines have been trained by Border Force officers.According to reports, it takes around three to ten months to coach a detector canine.A canine's ability to smell is up to 10,000 times more acute than a person's, reports PBS.Detective canines have discovered items such as half a billion pounds in cash money, 900 million cigarettes, and 450 tons of tobacco.The dogs are even able to sniff out fake passports due to the difference in the kind of ink used to make them, as well as differentiate between various currencies of money.UK Immigration Minister Caroline Nokes says detective canines have "an unbelievable sense of scent, workability and loyalty [which] make them a useful asset.."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 10:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/28/3684156/3684156_F5086B4678954096BB007A9C1FA4E262_180828_3684156_UK_Border_Force_detector_dogs_celebrate_40_years_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E64/8D9/E648D90064019FFB274DFD7846F3F5CC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, animals, UK, dogs, border patrol, UK borders, detector dogs, paw patrol, border force, Border Force detector dogs, dogs sniffing out drugs and weapons at border, dog nose, acute sense of smell, man's best friend, detector canine, canines]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684105</guid>
      <title>US Navy re-launches 2nd Fleet in response to Russia expansion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORFOLK, VIRGINIA  The U.S. Navy has officially reactivated the Cold War-era Second Fleet in response to increased Russian military expansion. The fleet was originally set up in the beginning of the Cold War, with the main objective of supporting NATO against the Soviet Union. According to Politico, the move comes amid a recent surge in Russian submarine activity in the Atlantic. According to CNN, NATO and U.S. officials have said that Russian naval activity is at its highest since the end of the Cold War. The 2nd Fleet located in Norfolk, Virginia, which was deactivated in 2011, will be assigned ships, aircraft and Marine landing forces that can be deployed along the East Coast and in the North Atlantic. Vice Adm. Andrew "Woody" Lewis, who took command of the new headquarters last Friday, said he and his staff will "aggressively and quickly rebuild this command into an operational warfighting organization. According to CNN, officials say the Atlantic fleet will work with naval units like Naval Forces Europe and the Fourth and Sixth Fleets while focusing on joint, integrated training and operations in "high-end of naval warfare." The fleet will once again support NATO and the NATO Joint Force Command for the Atlantic which will be located in Norfolk as well.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 09:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/28/3684105/3684105_AC51F24A4431401E9B24E6CF3C93F04D_180828_3684105_US_Navy_re_launches_2nd_Fleet_in_response_to_Rus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A6B/E6D/A6BE6D4396DEFF4233956F09EA751796.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US Navy, US Navy re-launches, 2nd Fleet, Atlantic 2nd Fleet, US Navy 2nd Fleet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3683889</guid>
      <title>Earth's magnetic poles can flip much faster than we think</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN / CHINA  New research has found evidence that Earth's magnetic poles have shifted rapidly once before, and could lead to a global catastrophe should it happen again.Forbes reports that the earth is surrounded by a magnetic field that shields the planet's surface from charged particles constantly being emitted by the sun.This field can switch directions  a phenomenon known as geomagnetic reversal. It is believed to unfold slowly over thousands of years, with the last full reversal occurring 780,000 years agoAccording to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Science, research teams from Taiwan and China analyzed a Sanxing Cave stalagmite that grew over a 16,000 year period. Variations in the rock's magnetic minerals revealed a huge polarity shift 98,000 years ago that occurred in just 144 years.Previous studies have suggested that the magnetic field could weaken by about 90% during a reversal, which will greatly impact power grids and modern electronics.Unfortunately, pole shifts can't be predicted, and we can only hope it happens far enough in the future to when humanity has come up with certain technologies to avoid significant damage.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 04:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/28/3683889/3683889_3B57F4215AAC49D7A87F6569AC2920A3_180828_3683889_Earth_s_magnetic_poles_can_flip_much_faster_than_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5BF/464/5BF46433437E96AC50207D579F41C66C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, magnetic field, earth magnetic field, magnetic poles, Earth magnetic poles, geomagnetic reversal, pole reversal, pole switch, pole flip, magnetic reversal, magnetic switch]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3685020</guid>
      <title>Mystery woman in handcuffs seen ringing doorbells in Texas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTGOMERY COUNTY, TEXAS   A woman was seen ringing doorbells of different Texas houses late in the night before disappearing on August 24, reports CNN.Surveillance footage shows the woman barefoot, wearing a T-shirt and what appear to be handcuffs, looking nervous while ringing the doorbell several times.One of the homeowners shared their experience with KPRC, saying they were asleep when they heard doorbell ring around 20 to 30 times.She said her husband got up to check who was at the door, but no one was there. It seemed like the woman just disappeared.The Montgomery County Sheriff Office said they are investigating the "suspicious incident."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 12:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/29/3685020/3685020_34CD17DCFE8A43688278C4A4A7E39F3C_180829_3685020_Mystery_woman_in_handcuffs_seen_ringing_doorbell_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2DA/E66/2DAE66D5CB2B03E5CFCA3833E695177D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Texas, woman, mystery woman,mystery woman texas, mystery woman rings doorbell, police search, houses, ringing doorbells, mysterious woman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684925</guid>
      <title>Militaries from Russia, China and Mongolia take part in war games</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Russia, China and Mongolia will this year take part in a large, joint military operation dubbed "Vostok-2018".According to the Moscow Times, Russia is sending 300,000 military personnel as well as 1,000 aircraft and two naval fleets to the exercise. China is sending 3,200 troops, along with aircraft, and 900 pieces of military hardware, reports Xinhua. Mongolia's contribution to the event is unknown, the BBC reports.Xinhua reports that the Chinese and Russian cooperation in the event is being hailed as proof of expanded ties between the two countries.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 10:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/29/3684925/3684925_5F15C6865E464DFBAD8E862314424820_180829_3684925_Militaries_from_Russia__China_and_Mongolia_take__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/165/E95/165E95FC30000F16385E70C4BA3E8AF3.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Russia, China, Mongolia, Navy, Aircraft, air force, Vostok 2018, East 2018, military, east asia]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684918</guid>
      <title>Brest friendly dolphin causes French swimming ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BREST, FRANCE  A mayor from the city of Brest on the northwest coast of France has banned swimming and diving on local becauses of an over-friendly menace  Zafar the dolphin.  According to the BBC, Zafar has been putting on quite the show for the children by swimming and playing with bathers and kayakers. The problem now is the dolphin seems to be getting a bit too frisky for the French. Officials have warned that Zafar is looking for close contact with swimmers.The 10 foot dolphin at first was playing with kayakers in Brest harbor, but then moved south towards the city.According to Le Telegramme, Zafar has been rubbing up against boats and swimmers, and even in shallow water. Last month, one swimmer needed assistance after Zafar wouldn't let her get back to shore. Another kayaker said the dolphin actually leapt over his head, while another Spanish vacationer complained about being confronted by Zafar, who seemed really anxious to interact. Zafar then one upped himself when he launched a woman out of the water into the air with his nose.  Mayor Roger Lars has banned swimming and diving in areas where the dolphin is spotted, as well as approaching within 50 meters of Zafar.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 10:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/29/3684918/3684918_3B08B785246F4E478408E87764C51897_180829_3684918_Brest_friendly_dolphin_causes_French_swimming_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C85/5FC/C855FCDE42BE7180B13C55E635C2B1AC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dolphin, over-friendly dolphin, frisky dolphin France, Zafar the dolphin, Zafar dolphin Brest France]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684716</guid>
      <title>New "holy grail" weight-loss pill to help in the fight against obesity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  A new study published in the New England Journal of Medicine has found promising results for a weight-loss drug in the U.S.Researchers say lorcaserin, also known under the trade name of Belviq in the U.S., [c][d]is the first drug for weight-loss that does not increase the risk of heart issues.Half of the 12,000 participants in the study were given lorcaserin, which is designed to suppress appetite, while the other half were given a placebo.The drug is supposed to be taken twice a day and will would stimulate brain chemicals to bring about a feeling of fullness.However, the researchers noted that side effects such as headaches and nausea may also be caused by the drug.After 40 months, the study found that the participants prescribed lorcaserin were three times more likely to lose 5 to 10 percent of their body weight compared to those taking a placebo.  However, according an editorial published in the New England Journal of Medicine, patients are advised to use the drugs on a "cautious basis" based on their needs.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 06:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/29/3684716/3684716_1AAD9631B8674449A3CD405165FD25A0_180829_3684716_New__holy_grail__weight_loss_pill_to_help_in_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/177/12A/17712A6392E0B5793EF8E9AD8694D88E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US, study, weight-loss pills, drugs, medicine,lorcaserin, Belviq, lose weight, obesity, obesity in America, obesity epidemic, fighting obesity,  placebo, stimulate brain chemicals, suppressing feelings of hunger, fat, body weight,feeling of fullness]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684703</guid>
      <title>DoD officials mulling cosmic operations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. military is exploring how to take its operations into space.According to a U.S. Department of Defence document, military officials are exploring four components for a proposed Space Force. One of these is a Space Development Agency for primarily research and development.The next would be a Space Operation Force. According to the DOD, this would "develop, field and integrate space capabilities into multi-domain warfighting."Thirdly the U.S. government would explore a Services and Support component for logistical and administrative purposes.The fourth component the DoD are looking at is a U.S. Space Command to lead conflict operations in space.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 06:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/29/3684703/3684703_A70034CFDEA74107B135633C922AE54A_180829_3684703_DoD_officials_mulling_cosmic_operations_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CC0/90C/CC090C7E84E31406C3A512C2078FEE8F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space force news, us space force news, space force, space corps, space defense, science and technology, pentagon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684614</guid>
      <title>China using debt-trap diplomacy to spread its global dominance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  China has been accused of leveraging massive loans to smaller, developing countries in order to take over assets and construct military bases in said countries. In a practice referred to as "debt-trap diplomacy" or "debt colonialism," huge loans are given to countries that will be unable to repay, forcing smaller countries to give up major concessions when the loans default, according to The Center for Global Development.  Countries like Pakistan, Djibouti, Fiji, Montenegro, Maldives, Kyrgyzstan and Laos all owe China large amounts of money. Last year, Sri Lanka owed more that $1 billion in debts to China, so it was forced to hand over a port to Chinese government-owned business on a 99-year lease. Infrastructure loans to build roads and ports linked to the "Belt and Road" initiative to have led to countries owing millions or billions in debt, often accounting for large percentages of the countries' GDP.China may be looking to leverage its debt in the Pacific in order to increase its military footprint in the South Pacific, The Times reports.In April, China informed Vanuatu it had intentions of building a military base. According to the Sun, Vanuatu owes $246 million to China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 04:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/29/3684614/3684614_69A5152BD0C74A209280BE8E095463C0_180829_3684614_China_using_debt_trap_diplomacy_to_spread_its_gl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/89E/6BA/89E6BAA7AFD4B6008C8BA80F15DED720.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China debt, China debt-trap diplomacy, debt colonialism, Belt and Road initiative]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3684604</guid>
      <title>Remains of 4,000-year-old lost city discovered in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHIMAO, CHINA  Archeologists have discovered the remains of a 4,000-year-old lost city on a ridge above China's Tuwei River.  Researchers found a massive step pyramid that is at least 230 feet high and stretches 59 acres at its base and published the results in the journal Antiquity, according to Live Science. According to archeologists, a city flourished around the pyramid for five centuries, and at one point encompassed an area of 988 acres. Researchers have named the city "Shimao." The pyramid was built out of a loess hill, and had 11 steps tapering as they ascend. It was guarded by an inner and outer wall. According to the researchers, atop the pyramid "were extensive palaces built of rammed earth, with wooden pillars and roofing tiles, a gigantic water reservoir, and domestic remains related to daily life." The researchers believe the ruling class lived on top of the pyramid, where artisanal or industrial crafts were produced. The remains of several human sacrifices were also discovered at Shimao.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2018 04:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/29/3684604/3684604_6F65C94F198C46DD8DC4E573AEE12E50_180829_3684604_Remains_of_4_000_year_old_lost_city_discovered_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B29/8FF/B298FFA3AFECFC63951FBB00BF74960F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China lost city, China lost city discovered, China lost pyramid discovered, China Shimao lost city]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3685763</guid>
      <title>Procter &amp; Gamble actually thinks it can trademark LOL, NBD and WTF</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CINCINNATI, OHIO  Get ready to LOL because the innovators over at Procter & Gamble have actually applied to trademark acronyms that are super common when texting. According to the BBC, if approved, terms including “LOL” (Laugh Out Loud), “NBD” (No Big Deal) and even WTF could be used to market P&G junk.The company plans to use the terms to market soap, detergents and air fresheners to millennials, who don’t waste time with P&G garbage.P&G registered the trademark applications with the US Patent and Trademark Office in April. The household cleaning crap company seems to think that if someone under 35 sees a product branded with some slang they’ll shell out the money. LOL. The applications haven’t yet been approved. You can already picture the commercials. A young cisgendered millennial walks into the bathroom and drops a huge log. OMG that smells. NBD isn’t going to clean that up.  That’s going to need some WTF … LOL that worked amazing. P&G is the best.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/30/3685763/3685763_D2ECCE8CF92D432889F012AE8AEC58A1_180830_3685763_Procter___Gamble_actually_thinks_it_can_trademar_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/130/55C/13055CF49FF941CD9D394C202A5965E2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,Procter & Gamble,P&G LOL,P&G NBD,P&G wants to trademark LOL,Procter & Gamble trademarks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3685690</guid>
      <title>Serial 'dine-and-dash' dater now could be going to jail</title>
      <description><![CDATA[USA  At least eight women have come forward to accuse a man of eating and drinking during their separate date and leaving without paying, forcing the women to foot the bill, reports The Washington Post.Apparently, Paul Gonzales would meet these women on dating apps and invite them for dinner.One of the women told the Washington Post, Gonzales then proceeded to order lavish meals such as four lobsters and expensive wine as well as souffle.And just before he was done eating he make an excuse and said he needed to make a phone call.The woman said she waited for a while until she decided to ask the waiter if he saw her date. The waiter said he left.According to BBC News, Gonzales defrauded the women of more than $950 and could face up to 13 years in prison.Gonzales has been charged extortion and grand theft, though he has pleaded not guilty.One of the women said she was "ecstatic" and said she "hopes he gets what he deserved."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2018 11:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/18/08/30/3685690/3685690_D9F1398FD3384B00B954A900AD7011DD_180830_3685690_Serial__dine_and_dash__dater_now_could_be_going__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/637/346/637346C089C6B03B233D582C76D38D10.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, date, dating, dine and dash, dine and dash dater, dine and dash date, dine and dash date caught, footing the bill, restaurant, expensive food, dating apps, dinner]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
