<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dcterms="http://purl.org/dc/terms/" xmlns:openSearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS Feed for Watchup</title>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 19:31:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3837754</guid>
      <title>French mayor offers free Viagra to boost village birth rate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTEREAU, FRANCE  A French mayor has come up with an interesting solution to solve underpopulation in his town. The Telegraph reports that the number of babies had been going down in the village of Montereau, south of Paris. Its population was a measly 650.Falling birth rates was not good for the local schools, which would have to shut one or two of its four classes if there weren't enough students. If that happens, the town's kids have to travel to neighboring areas to be educated.To try and solve the population problem, Mayor Jean Debouzy pledged free Viagra for all the couples in Montereau to help get things up and ready.According to the decree, "pills will be handed out to couples between 18 and 40 in order to give them every possible chance to conceive and thus preserve the schools." A tall order!He also wanted to give special one-off bonuses for anyone who birthed a baby, as an incentive.Whether or not the mayor is actually allowed to give out the blue pills is unclear, since it can only be obtained in France with a doctor's prescription. But the townsfolk don't seem to chomping at the bit for Viagra, either. Not one of them has made a dash for the performance enhancing pills since the decree was issued last Thursday.If anything, though, the mayor says the Viagra ploy will at least be a good way to get people to talk about the school issue.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 19:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/01/3837754/3837754_8B1D7EF6A98047EBAC12D207C94679CC_190601_3837754_French_mayor_offers_free_Viagra_to_boost_village_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, low birth rate, low population, Viagra, free Viagra, French mayor, Montereau, desertification France, desertification]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3837752</guid>
      <title>7 dead, 21 missing after tour boat capsizes in Budapest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUDAPEST, HUNGARY  At least seven people are dead and 21 others missing after their tour boat capsized in Hungary.The Guardian reports that 33 South Koreans and two Hungarians were onboard a sightseeing boat called The Mermaid for an hour-long tour on Budapest's Danube river Wednesday night, despite poor weather.CCTV footage released by police shows the Mermaid and a 443-feet-long cruise ship called the Viking both travelling North on the river.""While approaching the pillars of the Magrit bridge, the Mermaid steered left into the path of the larger ship, and was hit from behind.According to the head of Budapest's disaster management office, the Mermaid capsized and sank just seven seconds later. The BBC reports that witnesses saw people in the water screaming for help.Seven people have been rescued, including one that was pulled from the water two miles south of the accident site. Seven are confirmed dead, while 21 others are still missing. CNN reports that none were wearing life jackets.According to police, rescue efforts were hampered by the rain and fast current on the Danube. Authorities have extended the search for the missing far downstream, even into Serbia, where the Danube flows, according to the L.A. Times.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 19:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/01/3837752/3837752_ECAB0B69AB0641CA9E45B8571AC66211_190601_3837752_7_dead__21_missing_after_tour_boat_capsizes_in_B_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hungary boat accident, budapest boat accident, budapest boat crash, budapest boat tragedy, tourist boat, tour boat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3837440</guid>
      <title>Michigan cop rescues toddler from oncoming dump truck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALCONA COUNTY, MICHIGAN  A cop in Michigan is being praised after rushing to save a 2-year-old child from a passing dump-truck, Fox News reports.Sgt. Joseph Richards was on patrol when he noticed a child walking on the street.Dash cam footage shows him quickly rushing over to the girl and picking up her up just as a red dump truck rushes past.According to Michigan police, the truck driver tried to stop as soon as he saw the girl but didn't brake in time.In a statement, police said, "If not for Sgt. Richards' quick action, this incident would have ended in tragedy."The child's mom told the cops she had lost track of her daughter just before it all went down.The lucky child was returned to her family, who lived across the busy roadway.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/05/31/3837440/3837440_1CD4DDEABED24C9FAF792A20C15F52AD_190531_3837440_Michigan_cop_rescues_toddler_from_oncoming_dump__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, michigan police, toddler, dash cam video, michigan roadway, police saves toddler who wanders onto a busy road, red dump car, hero stories, hero stories real life, michigan cop hero, michigan cop, everyday heroes, cop saves two-year-old girl, cop saves life, cop saves kid, cop saves kid from busy roadway, michigan cop saves toddler]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3837360</guid>
      <title>Tiananmen Square: 30 years on</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEJING  30 years ago peaceful protests for democratic reform quickly turned into bloodshed as Chinese armed forces turned their weapons against their own. This is a timeline of what led to the Tiananmen Square massacre.On April 17, 1989, roughly 100,000 students gather in the heart of Beijing to protest for economic reform in China and in remembrance of Hu Yaobang, a former communist party chairman and reformist who had died just two days prior. In the days to come, students are quickly joined by workers, public officials, and intellectuals, calling for an end to authoritarianism. According to Reuters, on April 22, thousands of students assemble in Tiananmen Square to officially memorialize Hu, despite government warnings. They attempt to deliver a petition containing their demands for reform to government officials. The petition is rejected. On April 26, the People's Daily, a Chinese state-run newspaper, retaliates by publishing an editorial accusing protestors of being anti-party and anti-socialist. The letter sparks even more protests and unrest from the public. On May 19, then-party chief, Zhao Ziyang, and then-premier, Li Peng, meet with student protestors at Tiananmen Square. Zhao asks them to retreat but the negotiations are unsuccessful. He is later purged for failing to stop the protests. The following day Li declares martial law in certain areas of Beijing. On May 30th, students raise a 10-meter statue in Tiananmen Square made of paper-mache and foam dubbed the "Goddess of Democracy" modeled after the Statue of Liberty.  On June 4th armed Chinese troops enter Tiananmen Square and begin to violently take down demonstrators using tear gas and bullets. The square is cleared of protestors by the following morning.Later the same day an unknown protestor stops a tank convoy by defiantly standing in front of the leading tank.  Archive footage shows the man climbing up the tank and attempting to speak to the tank commander. He is later removed by other protestors.In a broadcast on June 6th, Chinese State media states the death toll was roughly 300 with only 23 students confirmed dead. However, witnesses claim deaths are probably in the thousands. In China today, Tiananmen never happened.  Remembering the massacre is in itself an act of rebellion and any information about the events that occurred is either censored or non-existent. According to Reuters, Chinese internet company censors are now relying on AI technology to erase any text, images or videos related to the Tiananmen massacre. A censor working for Beijing Bytedance told Reuters, quote, "We sometimes say that the artificial intelligence is a scalpel, and a human is a machete." end quote. To this day, Chinese authorities have not released Tiananmen's official death toll.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 07:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/05/31/3837360/3837360_08636F01EFB54CF4AE98B3064BFF1742_190531_3837360_Tiananmen_Square__30_years_on_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, tiananmen square, tiananmen 1989, tiananmen sqyare protests, tiananmen square massacre, tianenmen square video, tiananmen square tankman, tiananmen square incident, tiananmen square tank, china beijing tiananmen square, tiananmen square video, china, beijing, deng xiao ping, ccp, china, beijing]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838194</guid>
      <title>China threatens to cut U.S. off from rare earths</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  China claims it could use rare earths to hit back in the trade war with the United States.According to Reuters, Chinese state propaganda warned that Beijing could cut the U.S. off from rare earths. According to the Associated Press, the Trump administration has imposed 25 percent tariffs on $250 billion in Chinese imports and is planning to tax the $300 billion in imports that have so far been spared. Trump also threw down the hammer by putting Huawei on a blacklist that bars U.S. companies from supplying the Chinese company without government approval. CCP tabloid Global Times warned that China has lots of ways to retaliate, including cutting off the supply of rare earths. According to Reuters, rare earths are a group of 17 chemical elements used in high-tech consumer electronics to military equipment.According to Merrill Lynch research, China produced 78 percent of the world's rare earths last year.  The U.S. used to be the world's leading producer of rare earths, but the incredible pollution that comes with mining the elements caused production to move overseas. According to Reuters, some trade analysts expect an acceleration in bringing new rare earth mining capacity online in California and Australia if China does throw its rare earth Trump card.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 02:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/02/3838194/3838194_CAFD5E84B9104CB5A1B2D2D90D889E1B_190602_3838194_China_threatens_to_cut_U_S__off_from_rare_earths_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US China, US China trade war, China rare earths, Trump vs China, Trump trade war, Trump China tariffs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838191</guid>
      <title>Kim Jong-un executed, purged top negotiators after Hanoi summit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL  Kim Jong-un has cleaned house after the failed Hanoi summit by executing North Korea's special envoy to the United States on spying charges and purged the country's top nuclear negotiators.The New York Times reports that according to South Korea's largest daily Chosun Ilbo, envoy Kim Hyok-chol was executed by firing squad in March at the Mirim airfield in a Pyongyang suburb. According to the newspaper, Kim faced a charge that he was "won over by the American imperialists to betray the supreme leader."The South Korean paper said four other officials from the North Korean Foreign Ministry were also permanently dirt napping, without mentioning how they got the juicy details. According to Reuters, the team was responsible for carrying out working-level negotiations for the second U.S.-North Korea summit in February, so Kim blamed them for its collapse. The Chosun Ilbo also reported that Kim Yong Chol, a senior official who had been U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo's counterpart before the summit is now relaxing in a forced labor and ideological reeducation camp. According to the report, Shin Hye Yong, the interpreter for Kim Jong-un at the Hanoi meeting is also said to be enjoying a all-inclusive stay at a political prison camp for apparently making a translation mistake.Experts say that Fats is most likely using the purge to take attention away from internal turmoil and discontent. Well, he definitely gives a new meaning to the wordFIRED.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 02:26:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/02/3838191/3838191_BDD6757EE4E54A2685E1FCC96DBB42C8_190602_3838191_Kim_Jong_un_executed__purged_top_negotiators_aft_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Korea, Kim Jong-un, Kim Jong-un purge, Kim Jong-un Hanoi summit, North Korea vs US]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838960</guid>
      <title>Astronomers fear SpaceX 
satellites will block stars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA  Starlink is planning on deploying thousands of satellites into Earth's orbit and astronomers are concerned.Real-life Tony Stark, Elon Musk, is known for his radical technological ventures. Remember when he sent out a Tesla Roadster into earth's orbit, just for kicks?His most recent plan, however, is much more impactful  to provide the entire world with internet access. SpaceX plans to do so by sending out low-orbiting satellites into orbit, effectively creating a network that they've dubbed Starlink. Starlink promises to provide a stable connection to users around the world with minimal delay.Last week, SpaceX confirmed the deployment of 60 Starlink satellites into Earth's orbit and that's just the beginning. Getting our Wi-Fi from space sounds pretty cool, but for Starlink to work as promised, thousands of satellites need to be deployed and that is concerning to some experts, particularly astronomers.  According to a report from the New York Times, having thousands of satellites reflecting light in space could disturb astronomer's view of the night sky. Whenever a satellite passes by a telescope's field of view when it is taking a long exposure shot, it destroys the whole image. This in itself is not a big issue, scientists have learned to work around the occasional satellite but Starlink could be tripling the number of satellites in orbit in the years to come.  Experts aired their worry on social media. Planetary astronomer, Alex Parker, warned his followers saying, quote, "If SpaceX launches all 12,000, they will outnumber stars visible to the naked eye." Some Twitter users replied, stating that the satellites were not a cause for concern as they would only be visible during certain times of the day. Even Elon Musk himself chimed in saying, "Precisely, sats will be in darkness when stars are visible." Dutch archaeologist, Marco Langbroek clapped back at  Musk with a video he took which showed Starlink satellites crossing above the night sky in Leiden, Netherlands. The satellites clearly overshadowing neighboring stars.In his tweet, he explained to Musk that the satellites might be invisible in winter but not during summer. Adding quote, " they are visible throughout the night at middle latitudes like Europe." Musk didn't reply. The Times reports that the radio frequencies these satellites emit are also a cause for concern. Radio stations used by astronomers are located in remote areas to avoid interference from other cell towers. If Starlink deploys all its satellites, these radio quiet zones will cease to exist. According to Musk though, there's no reason to panic. In a tweet, he explained they would avoid using certain frequencies so as to not disturb radio astronomy. In another tweet, Musk justified the Starlink Satellites saying, quote, "There are already 4,900 satellites in orbit, which people notice ~0% of the time. Starlink won't be seen by anyone unless looking very carefully & will have ~0% impact on advancements in astronomy."So, next time you look up and wish upon a star, just know that you might inadvertently be wishing upon a SpaceX satellite.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 14:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838960/3838960_1DA4D124C7FC4B278028EF9026B7BADA_190603_3838960_Astronomers_fear_SpaceX__satellites_will_block_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, spacex, starlink, internet, starlink internet, starling spacex, elon musk starlink, satellite internet network, SpaceX internet plan, spacex launch, spacex starlink, starlinks, space based internet, elon musk internet, elon musk internet plans, internet satellites, starlink internet satellites, internet satellites in space, space internet, internet from space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838957</guid>
      <title>Japan has created the ultimate summer umbrella</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Japan has the perfect solution to summer heat. A Fanbrella.  Have you ever wished that your umbrella could protect you from the blazing summer sun while at the same time shower you with a fresh mist and blow cool breeze onto your sweaty brow? Well, look no further. Japan has got the answer. Meet the Fanbrella. As you've probably guessed by the name, it is the Japanese lovechild of a fan and an umbrella. According to Thanko, the company behind this marvelous invention, apart from having fans installed, the Fanbrella also has an attachment at the bottom of its handle where the user can connect a water bottle. Just press a button, and voila, the fans blow out a cooling mist. All you need is a bottle with an opening of 1.1 inches in diameter.  The Fanbrella runs on four Double-A batteries which will get you about five hours of blissful freshness.If you're tempted to purchase the Fanbrella just know that it is only available in Thanko's online shop for 5,980 yen which translates to roughly $55.42. In the meantime, if you're going out and the heat is unbearable, remember to stay hydrated and seek shelter inside your closest air-conditioned convenience store.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 14:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838957/3838957_C51E2EEADAB64339B06B986FBAE94C29_190603_3838957_Japan_has_created_the_ultimate_summer_umbrella_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, fanbrella,  japan umbrella, japan thanko umbrella, japan fanbrella, fanbrella japan, fanbrella, cool gadgets, crazy gadgets]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838887</guid>
      <title>Global food production is already being affected by climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS  A new study has found that climate change is already affecting production of the world's top crops in certain regions. According to a University of Minnesota-led research published in PLOS ONE, barley, cassave, maize, oil palm, rapeseed, rice, sorghum, soybean, sugar, and wheat are the world's top 10 crops. Together, these provide 83 percent of all calories produced on cropland.Researchers analyzed weather and reported crop data to evaluate the potential impact of observed climate change, and found that some areas were faring far worse than others.Findings indicate that observed climate change caused significant yield variation in the crops, from a 13.5 percent decrease for oil palm to a 3.5 percent increase for soybean. Overall, this resulted in an average reduction of one percent of consumable calories from the top 10.The impact on global food production in Europe, Southern Africa, and Australia are mostly negative. It is generally positive in Latin America, and mixed in Asia, and North and Central America. There are decreases in crop production in half of all food-insecure countries, as well as in certain rich, industrialized nations in Western Europe.On the other hand, climate change has also increased the yields of certain crops in some parts of the upper midwest United States.The findings are especially relevant to the UN's Sustainable Development Goals of ending hunger and limiting the effects of climate change, and has major implications for food companies, traders, and the regions where they operate. More importantly, the study shows that change is already happening, and not just something to worry about in the future.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 11:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838887/3838887_D2E1BA9EDC3B4CE8A7396D74926B8D05_190603_3838887_Global_food_production_is_already_being_affected_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, climate change, global warming, food production, effects of climate change, climate change effects, climate change crops, world crops, global food production, top 10 crops, world top crops]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838857</guid>
      <title>Google could be facing major probe from Justice Department</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The Trump administration's Justice Department is preparing to open an antitrust investigation into Google, according to the Wall Street Journal. According to Bloomberg, the move comes after the Justice Department reached an agreement with the Federal Trade Commission on who gets to put the screws to the tech juggernaut. According to two anonymous sources familiar with the matter, the probe would fall to the department's antitrust division. According to Bloomberg, American antitrust officials are coming under increasing pressure from bipartisan lawmakers and advocates for tougher enforcement of tech giants like Google and Facebook. The FTC, earlier this year, set up a task force to look at the conduct of tech companies and their past mergers. Trump along with other Republicans have often complained that Facebook, Google and Twitter suppress conservative views. Bloomberg reported that one area the DOJ probe will insert itself in is Google's control over the digital advertising market. According to eMarketer, Google has a strangle on 37 percent of the U.S. digital ad market, and Facebook is number two with 22 percent. According to the New York Times, political leaders and consumer advocacy groups have criticized U.S. regulators for dragging their feet against monster tech companies. The New York Times reported that, Google, Facebook and Amazon have faced some hefty penalties from a bunch of European regulators for antitrust and privacy issues. In the meantime, save yourself the headache and just use the most sophisticated and lighting quickest search engine to ever existInternet Explorer.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 10:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838857/3838857_14F361185F464620A633F30859E55F37_190603_3838857_Google_could_be_facing_major_probe_from_Justice__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Google probe, DOJ Google probe, Google antitrust probe, Trump DOJ Google probe, Department of Justice Google probe]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838814</guid>
      <title>Twitter blocks Chinese dissidents ahead of Tiananmen annivesary</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO  Twitter suspended a large number of Chinese dissident accounts just days before the most politically sensitive period of the year in China.The New York Times reports that June 4 marks the 30th anniversary of the bloody crackdown on pro-democracy protesters in Tiananmen Square.In China, Big Brother keeps the seal extra tight on 'that sensitive period in June,' which means several extra doses of censorship from the Great Firewall.    So when the accounts of prominent and long-time critics of the Beijing government suddenly dropped off the face of Twitter, everyone assumed it was the Chinese censors.According to the New York Times, over a hundred users got the cut- from human rights lawyers, activists, and nationalists, to even college students.The reasoning made sense, since Beijing's internet po-po had been carrying out a campaign way before June 4 that targeted Chinese Twitter users, who often used VPNs to work around China's Twitter block. But as it turns out, it wasn't China- or so says Twitter. Supposedly, the purge was all part of routine Twitter efforts to "stop spam and inauthentic behavior." According to TechCrunch, the company claimed in a statement that Chinese authorities hadn't mass reported the accounts. Instead, it seemed Twitter was cleaning CCP bots and accidentally suspended a whole lotta anti-CCP accounts.That doesn't quite make sense, and people online think so too.Yaxue Cao, founder and editor of the U.S. based publication "China Change" said in a tweet she thinks something else is going on, and speculated that the "routine process" may have been abused by someone on the payroll.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 09:28:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838814/3838814_46EEEB6E08114D999839874E129B1583_190603_3838814_Twitter_blocks_Chinese_dissidents_ahead_of_Tiana_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, twitter, tiananmen, tiananmen anniversary, chinese dissidents, chinese politics, chinese political activists, twitter take down, twitter users, china twitter]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838760</guid>
      <title>11-foot alligator breaks into home and gets "the good stuff"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CLEARWATER, FLORIDA  An 11-foot alligator smashed its way through a homeowner's window in Clearwater, Florida.The Tampa Bay Times reported that it was 3:30 a.m when 77-year-old homeowner, Mary Wischhusen was on her way to the bathroom when she heard the crash through her kitchen window.Wischhusen locked eyes with the alligator and said, quote, "all I had was a vision of a huge head...a gigantic head looking at me saying, 'Hey.'"She called the authorities and fled to her bedroom to hide, where she, quote, "went on the computer and played games to settle down.According to Channel 3000, the gator was pulled out of the same window it came through and had caused considerable damage to the homeowner's drywall, a large glass table and several bottles of wine.Wischhusen asked, "I don't know why he wanted my red wine, but he got my red wine, the good stuff.Concerned about the fragility of her wine, she queried, "the next gator might like white wine".Channel 3000 reported that The Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commons was forced to put the gator down.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 07:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838760/3838760_1A3713EC98B643E8A0365E9AF99A83AC_190603_3838760_11_foot_alligator_breaks_into_home_and_gets__the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Florida, Aligator, break-in, Gator, red wine, smash, FWC, alligator in kitchen, gator in kitchen, alligator attacks, alligator breaks into house, alligator clips, wine, alligators in Florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838747</guid>
      <title>Man pays $21,700 property 
deposit with bottles of coins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JINAN, CHINA  A man in China filled up 16 water bottles with loose change to pay for the initial deposit on his house, the South China Morning Post reports.According to local newspaper the Qilu Evening News, the man accumulated the coinage over a number of years via his work as a seafood vendor in the northern Chinese city of Jinan.So he decided to fill up the water bottles with around 150,000 RMB, which is around US$21,700, in coins, then hauled them to the real estate office for his down payment.One of the staff told the Qilu Evening News that they received a call from the man, asking if he could make the initial payment using coins. They thought he was joking.Video footage shows the staff sitting on the floor and counting all the change  one penny at a time. It took 26 people four hours to tally all the coins.There's no word yet on how the man plans to make the rest of the house payment.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 07:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838747/3838747_410B4B70F12C402C824D5F4431ECA40D_190603_3838747_Man_pays__21_700_property__deposit_with_bottles__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, china, jinan china, chinese street vendor, chinese grocery store, jinan street vendor, china water bottles, man in china fills water bottles with coins to pay for a house,  150,000 yuan, RMB, payment methods in china, house down payment, crazy stories from china , man makes down payment on house using coins]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838672</guid>
      <title>UN unveils new measures to combat Ebola crisis in DR Congo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KINSHASA, DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO  The Ebola epidemic has already killed 1,200 people in the Democratic Republic of Congo and is currently at risk of spreading to nearby countries, according to the World Health Organization.According to the U.S. based Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Ebola typically affects humans and nonhuman primates. The infection is spread through viruses within the Ebola virus group.The virus is transferred to humans through contact with the fluids of dead wild animals, such as bats, according to the World Health Organization. Ebola is then transmitted among humans through direct contact with contaminated body fluids.Symptoms of the virus include fever, headache, sore throat rashes and, in severe cases,  internal or external bleeding.According to the WHO website, the UN is adapting a new strategy to identify and treat people as soon as possible. They are also said to be providing access to vaccinations.The 2018 Democratic Republic of Congo outbreak is the second largest Ebola epidemic in history and, according to Forbes, is the country's tenth outbreak since 1976.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838672/3838672_BEE00CFBEDA643809F7E85BFE3DC8BEA_190603_3838672_UN_unveils_new_measures_to_combat_Ebola_crisis_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ebola virus, virus, viral outbreak, Congo, DR Congo, ebola outbreak, congo ebola outbreak, ebola outbreak in congo, ebola outbreak in congo 2019, ebola outbreak news, ebola outbreak congo 2019, DRC ebola outbreak, ebola cases]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838638</guid>
      <title>China achieves military goals, slows building in South China Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH CHINA SEA  A top U.S. military official says China has slowed construction and island-building in the South China Sea as it has achieved its immediate military goals for the region.The South China Morning Post reports that during a presentation at the Brookings Institute, General Joseph Dunford claimed Chinese President Xi Jinping had reneged on a promise in 2016 to then-President Obama not to militarize the South China Sea.Despite overlapping claims by several different countries, Beijing asserts ownership of the South China Sea based on historic rights. In recent years, it began a massive building program to reclaim land in the disputed region by increasing the size of existing reefs or creating new islands.According to the Council on Foreign Relations, China has constructed ports, military installations, and airstrips on islands in the Paracels and Spratlys. Woody Island, in particular, has been militarized through the deployment of fighter jets, cruise missiles, and a radar system.According to Dunford, building on the Chinese-claimed islands has been slowing, likely because they have been developed to the point where they can provide the military capability required by the Chinese.He warns that future expansion in the area must be checked with clear and collective action, and not necessarily with a military response, as diplomatic and economic tools can also be used to hold people accountable.While the U.S. has no official position on territorial claims in the disputed South China Sea, it periodically conducts freedom of navigation operations to challenge Beijing's claims and maintain open sea lanes.This entails passing close to China-claimed reefs, which draws the ire of the Chinese.The South China Morning Post reports that China had recently begun construction on its third aircraft carrier, which is expected to expand its ability to launch larger and more varied aircraft.Beijing's military build-up has led Washington to develop long-range missiles that can be launched beyond the range of Chinese missile defence systems.The U.S. is likewise adapting its naval strategy to deal with a rival that may challenge its ability to navigate globally.According to Dunford, there is also a need to improve military communication between the U.S. and China. Over the past decade, the U.S. has tried and failed to establish regular communication between top military officials to improve understanding, something analysts attribute to a cultural difference.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 04:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838638/3838638_5F2157E6B9174DF78250AA56259AD08E_190603_3838638_China_achieves_military_goals__slows_building_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, south china sea, us china, artificial islands, south china sea militarization, freedom of navigation, spratlys, paracels, paracel islands, disputed islands]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3838605</guid>
      <title>Researchers find 'Forbidden Planet' in Neptunian Desert</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE   Astronomers have discovered a Neptune-like exoplanet called NGTS-4b in the Neptunian Desert region of a star, according to a study published in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society. This is the first time this type of exoplanet has been found in a star's Neptunian Desert region, CNN reports. Neptunian Desert refers to the area close to stars where no planets similar to Neptune's scale can be found. Stars send out strong radiation to this area. This causes planets to lose their gaseous atmosphere. They usually evaporate, leaving behind a rocky core.According to the new research, NGTS-4b was spotted using a ground telescope called Next Generation Transit Survey.The exoplanet, nicknamed, "The Forbidden Planet," is three times the size of Earth and has a radius that is only 20 percent smaller than Neptune. The exoplanet has temperatures of up to 1,000 degrees Celsius.Space.com reports the new exoplanet orbits a star named NGTS-4, which is around 920 light years away from Earth. The exoplanet completes orbits of the star every 1.3 days, according to a University of Warwick press release.Astronomers believe the exoplanet could have moved into the Neptunian Desert region at some point in the past one million years.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 03:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/03/3838605/3838605_74742623370B43B68387D5E2AEF384A4_190603_3838605_Researchers_find__Forbidden_Planet__in_Neptunian_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space, space exploration, astronomy, neptune, neptunian desert, forbidden planet, neptune forbidden planet, exoplanet, neptune exoplanet, NGTS-4b, forbidden planet neptune, NGTS-4, neptunian desert zone, Next-Generation Transit Survey telescope, exoplanets 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839334</guid>
      <title>China tests submarine-launched ballistic missile in Bohai Bay</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOHAI BAY, CHINA  The Chinese People's Liberation Army successfully tested its new submarine-launched ballistic missiles on June 2. According to Defence Blog, the test launches took place past 4 a.m. at Bohai Bay near China's Shandong province. Hong Kong's Ming Pao Daily reports that the PLA gave the public a 3-minute heads up before suddenly restricting access to waters at 2:30 a.m.  Eyewitnesses in Liaoning, Shanxi, and Shandong claimed to have seen long missile tail fins, but weren't given any sort of explanation by the authorities.Defence blog reports that the SLBMs being tested were allegedly JL-3 third generation solid fuel missiles, which have an intercontinental range of 12 to 14,000 kilometers, and can carry up to 10 independent warheads.According to Jane's Missiles and Rockets, the JL-3 is meant to arm Beijing's next-generation Type 096 nuclear-powered ballistic missile submarine class- due to enter service in the late 2020s.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 08:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/04/3839334/3839334_580A39379747480AB3883B4BD9EA0808_190604_3839334_China_tests_submarine_launched_ballistic_missile_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, ballistic missile, ballistic missile test, submarine launched ballistic missile, SLBM, Chinese SLBM, missile test, China missile, China next gen missile, JL-3, JL3, Bohai Bay, China weapons]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839299</guid>
      <title>Woman's suspected brain tumor is actually a parasite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIDDLE TOWN, NEW YORK   A New York woman was suffering from symptoms that led doctors to believe she had a tumor, but it turns out she was hosting a parasite, WCYB News reports.Rachel Palma's symptoms were terrifying. She couldn't sleep, and when she did she had awful nightmares. Palma started to have trouble speaking and her right hand would suddenly stop working. According to WCYB News, the 42-year-old even made phone calls she couldn't remember making. She was rightfully concerned but several visits to the ER showed no specific cause for her bizarre behavior. Finally, a doctor performed an MRI which showed damaged tissue on the left side of her brain about the size of a marble.  The initial prognosis was that it was most likely a brain tumor, or at least that's what neurosurgeon Dr. Raj Shrivastava expected. Fortunately for Palma, she had no brain tumor. Instead, doctors found an egg. Yes, an egg. Dr. Jonathan Rasouli, chief neurosurgery resident at the hospital where Palma was treated, described it to WYCB news as, "this very firm, very well encapsulated thing. It looked like a quail egg."Turns out, the egg contained a baby tapeworm. A parasite. Palma had a parasite growing in her brain. As disgusting as it sounds this was the best case scenario for Palma. The egg was effectively removed and Palma is now parasite free.The medical term for this alien-like parasitic infection is neurocysticercosis and, according to the Centers for Disease Control, it is usually contracted when you swallow microscopic tapeworm eggs which can be found in raw pork. Citing the CDC, WCYB News reports that 1,000 people are hospitalized for this type of infection each year in the U.S. Raouli also told the outlet it was "super rare" in the country. If the infection is caught on time, it can be handled with antibiotics.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 07:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/04/3839299/3839299_93185A06A10C448DBD4DCB84483B2A33_190604_3839299_Woman_s_suspected_brain_tumor_is_actually_a_para_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, woman parasite in brain, parasite in brain, brain parasite, tapeworm, brain tapeworm, tapeworm invades brain, tapeworm in brain, tapeworm egg in woman]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839208</guid>
      <title>Apple plans to get rid of iTunes and replace it with 3 other apps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN JOSE, CALIFORNIA  Apple has announced plans to kill off the iTunes app during its annual Worldwide Developers Conference while simultaneously stating that the company will launch a series of apps to replace it.Apple had removed content from its iTunes facebook and instagram pages just before the company made the big announcement.According to Business Insider, starting this fall, iTunes will basically be split into three different apps: Apple Music, Apple TV and Apple Podcasts.Apple said the company will start offering the new apps in the next software update called macOS Catalina.All previously downloaded or purchased music will be transferred onto the music app. The tech giant will still offer an iTunes Music Store for those looking to purchase songs.Apple says its new TV app will provide more than 100,000 shows and movies that users can either purchase or rent. Apple's TV app will also consist of its very own streaming service, Apple TV Plus, which is set to be unveiled this fall.As for its new standalone Podcast app, users will be able to choose from more than 700,000 shows without having to visit the Podcasts section of iTunes on the Mac.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 05:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/04/3839208/3839208_9125F03999C546FA9EECC56D91E85BF7_190604_3839208_Apple_plans_to_get_rid_of_iTunes_and_replace_it__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, apple, itunes, apple itunes, apple kills itunes, apple to end itunes, technology, itunes shuts down, apples gets rid of itunes, itunes killed off, itunes music player, music technology, itunes shutting down, apple to replace itunes, apple gadgets, itunes app, apple redesigns music app]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839923</guid>
      <title>CRISPR gene-edited babies may have shorter lives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERKELY, CALIFORNIA  A new study shows that alterations on the CCR5 gene could shorten life expectancy and increase vulnerability to certain diseases. Last year, Chinese scientist He Jiankui revealed he had successfully edited the CCR5 gene in the embryos of twin girls using CRISPR/Cas9 technology.By altering this gene, he expected the twins would be protected from contracting HIV, however, new studies show he might have inadvertently shortened their life expectancy as well. According to the study published in Nature Medicine, scientists analyzed the DNA of 400,000 volunteers, some of which had mutated CCR5 genes. Results showed that individuals with non-working CCR5 were 21 percent less likely to live to age 76. Apart from increased mortality rates, results also showed that altering the said gene could also make individuals more susceptible to influenza and the West Nile virus. The problem with mixing around genes is, you never know what you're going to get. An MIT Technology review states that genes have many functions, so blocking one part of them may bring the intended results, but also unexpected outcomes. To the dean of Harvard Medical School George Daley, the experiment is an ethical and scientific failure. He told NPR, "Even when we think we know something about a gene, we can always be surprised and even startled, like in this case, to find out that a gene we thought was protective may actually be a problem."To other experts, this is just part of the scientific process. Speaking to NPR, George Church, a professor of genetics at Harvard, said that new technological developments are expected to come with unforeseen consequences, adding, "The first monoclonal antibodies were nearly deadly. The first gene therapies were indeed deadly. All kinds of means of transportation were and still are deadly. It's all about benefits versus risks."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 09:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839923/3839923_123AC9DDD26241D1987521834BA3BD45_190605_3839923_CRISPR_gene_edited_babies_may_have_shorter_lives_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, China, crispr babies, crispr china, crispr gene editing, 
Chinese scientist, chinese scientist gene edited babies, chinese scientist genetically edited babies, CRISPR, CRISPR technology, gene-editing, DNA, editing DNA, world's first genetically edited babies, CRISPR-cas9, CCR5, altering human DNA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839910</guid>
      <title>China issues U.S. travel warning over harassment by officials</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C. / BEIJING  China is warning its citizens against travelling to the United States, citing instances of visitors being harassed by U.S. officials, and frequent shootings.ABC News reports that China's foreign ministry as well as Chinese embassies and consulates in the U.S. sent out the warning, which urges their people to step up safety awareness and preventive measures.According to the Associated Press, U.S. law enforcement agencies have allegedly subject Chinese visitors to interrogation, interviews, and other forms of what it calls "harassment."In a separate alert, China's Ministry of Culture and Tourism sent out a warning over frequent robberies, thefts, and gun violence in America, and urged Chinese students abroad to fully assess the travel risks.The travel alert is valid until December 31, and comes amid a worsening trade dispute between Washington and Beijing.According to AP, Chinese travel to the U.S. is falling after over a decade of rapid growth - partly due to the additional visa checks.Travel from China also fell by 5.7 percent in 2018, marking the first time since 2003 that Chinese travel to America went down from the previous year.China had held a similar travel warning last summer, which prompted the Americans to shoot back with their own warning about travelling to China.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 09:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839910/3839910_1D3D5FC63D4B45F486DCF00972CE1411_190605_3839910_China_issues_U_S__travel_warning_over_harassment_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, us travel warning, china travel warning, us harassment, chinese tourists, chinese visitors, china travel alert, chinese tourism, us tourism, us tourists]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839846</guid>
      <title>U.S. mulling antitrust probes into Silicon Valley's big four</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. government is considering investigations into whether Silicon Valley's big four tech giants are misusing their market power, Reuters reports.The Federal Trade Commission and the Department of Justice will divide oversight of Amazon, Apple, Facebook and Google. The FTC will take Amazon and Facebook, while the Justice Department will watch Google and Apple. According to Reuters, the next step for the two government agencies is to decide if they should begin formal investigations.Separately, CNET reports Congress is launching its own antitrust investigation into competition in the digital marketplace. The probe, led by Democratic representative and House Antitrust Subcommittee chairman David N. Cicilline, will, among other things, explore "whether the dominant firms are engaging in anti-competitive conduct," according to a news release on the Congressman's website. The House probe will also determine if current antitrust legislation and enforcement is sufficient, CNET reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 07:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839846/3839846_148B3412856A422E903EEAF8F5698B0E_190605_3839846_U_S__mulling_antitrust_probes_into_Silicon_Valle_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, USA, us, tech giants, amazon, apple, facebook, google, tech giants antitrust, blocking tech giants, antitrust probe tech giants, antitrust probe news, tech companies, powerful tech companies, tech companies too powerful, tech giants investigation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839810</guid>
      <title>Chinese shoppers go crazy for new Uniqlo Line</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA  It seems the Americans aren't the only ones trashy enough to behave barbarically to get those sweet, sweet deals.A series of videos have surfaced showing Chinese shoppers break out in total anarchy for a new line-up of clothes from Uniqlo.The Japanese fast-fashion brand recently teamed up once again with artist/designer Brian Donnelly, otherwise known as Kaws. Apparently, Kaws has become rather popular in Asia. The Chinese are hardly known for their patience and self-restraint, especially when it comes to waiting in line.The videos show Chinese customers squirming under security barriers, torpedoing through aisles, yanking garments off mannequins, destroying in-store displays and even breaking out into some form of primitive fisticuffsjust for some clothes?According to the South China Morning Post, thanks to the popularity of Kaws, a shirt that costs 99 yuan or 14.32 US dollars, is being resold online for 115 US dollars online.According to What's on Weibo, some netizens claim these manic consumers aren't really taken in by the brand, rather, they simply love the competition.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 06:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839810/3839810_AB3B0BB4551E43E8B3EE053AE5AC5524_190605_3839810_Chinese_shoppers_go_crazy_for_new_Uniqlo_Line_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, Chinese go crazy, shoppers go crazy for Uniqlo, Chinese shoppers go crazy, fashion, Chinese consumers, Uniqlo, Kaws, Kaws Uniqlo, Uniqlo Kaws China 2019, fights]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839741</guid>
      <title>Malaysia is cashing in on Chinese durian craze</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR  Malaysia is tapping into the Chinese market as it opens its doors to frozen durian imports, reports Bloomberg.  Durian. People who haven't tried it have most certainly heard of it, or at least smelled its famously pungent odor. To some, this strange fruit smells like used diapers, but for Malaysia, they carry the smell of dollar bills. According to Bloomberg, Malaysia has been giddy to cash in on China's durian-craze ever since the Chinese General Administration of Customs opened its doors for imports of frozen whole durian fruit on May 30.  Turns out, Chinese people love durian. They're mixing it with ice cream, cakes, and even pizza.  Bloomberg reports China imports 300,000 metric tons of durian annually, 90 percent of which comes from Thailand. Malaysia wants a piece of that durian pie.  Lucky for them, according to NPR, China has taken a liking to the Musang King, a durian variety produced by Malaysia. Channel News Asia reports that 300 grams of Musan King sells for roughly $48 on Chinese online shopping site Tmall.  Malaysian celebrity chef, Zamzani Abdul Wahab, told NPR that Musang King is quote, "the best because the color is golden yellow, the flesh is sweet with a slight bitterness at the end that makes it the most special one, the most special breed of all." Sounds good to us. But are Thai durian's that different from Malaysian ones? According to Malaysia's deputy minister of agriculture, Sim Tze Tzin, definitely. He tells NPR that their durians are all about quality, not quantity. His analogy for it was, quote, "It's just like Thais are selling beer, we are selling champagne. Good quality champagne." Thai durian producers might need some aloe vera for that burn. Malaysian newspaper, The Star, reports that 67 farms have registered for durian production. On paper, this all sounds good, but environmentalists are concerned about what could happen if the demand for durian continues to increase. Malaysia has already witnessed the environmental destruction that comes from the demand for palm oil and rubber and experts now fear that this too can be a side effect of durian production.Forest researcher, Lim Tek Win, told NPR he believes greed could drive people to develop durian plantations in natural forest reserves.Lim warned that if there are no clear policies when it comes to where durian plantations are allowed, then biodiversity and loss of habitat could be a real concern in the years to come.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 04:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839741/3839741_2D287332E05F4A359F50F60CEBBC639C_190605_3839741_Malaysia_is_cashing_in_on_Chinese_durian_craze_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, malaysia durian, malaysia sells durian, chinese market, china durian demand, china malaysia business, china durian, china durian market, thailand durian]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839714</guid>
      <title>U.S. visa applicants now required to disclose social media info</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  As if the application form to get a U.S. visa wasn't lengthy enough, the State Department now wants all applicants to include all their social media deets.According to the New York Times, the new policy that started Friday requires visa applicants to the United States to submit information on any social media accounts they've used in the past five years.This information would allow authorities access to locations, photos, birthdates, milestones, and other personal data typically shared on social media.CBS reports that immigrant and nonimmigrant visa forms have already been updated to reflect the change, which is expected to affect over 15 million foreigners who apply to enter the U.S. each year.The new forms list several social media platforms and ask the applicant to provide account names they've had over a five-year-period. There's also an option to volunteer details on platforms not on the list. Apart from social media identifiers, applicants are also now required to provide email and phone number histories, international travel and deportation status, and whether any family members have been involved in terrorist activities. These extra details were once only required for an estimated 65,000 people a year that were identified for extra scrutiny, like those who travel to regions controlled by terrorist organizations. The State Department claims the new rules are simply a way to confirm identities and ensure a tighter vetting process.There are exemptions, but only for diplomatic or official visa applications.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 03:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839714/3839714_56828BBCAF144702A4E657EBCC9FAE05_190605_3839714_U_S__visa_applicants_now_required_to_disclose_so_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US visa, US visa application, social media, social media screening, US visa application form, US immigrant visa, US visitor visa, visa application]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839692</guid>
      <title>Texas is outlawing 
traffic light cameras</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEXAS  Texas is saying adios to red-light traffic cameras.Gov. Greg Abbott of Texas slammed the brakes on redlight cameras and signed a bill to ban them. According to the Houston Chronicle, it will go into effect on September 1st.The bill will put a stop to the cameras which normally fine drivers $75 for running reds.According to Fox 7, those opposed to the cameras claim they're un-American and violate privacy. And let's be honest, they're just annoying.  Advocates of the cameras include local law enforcement who insist they make a real difference in the areas they're installed.An interview with NBC 5 heard the chiefs of both Bedford and Plano police departments say, "We have seen a dramatic reduction of intersection accidents That means less people are getting hurt traveling our roadways".The Houston Chronicle reported that some critics label the cameras as a money grab. And at 75 bucks a pop, they do have somewhat of a point. Supporter of the bill Senator Bob Hall, said, "It does not have to do with safety".]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 02:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839692/3839692_8D50AA2D19634A7494E668B4D6B9AFD6_190605_3839692_Texas_is_outlawing__traffic_light_cameras_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Texas, Texas bans red-lights, red-light ban, red-light camera, speed camera, traffic, road laws, banned, outlawed, red light law, Gov. Greg Abbott, bill, House Bill 1631, photographic traffic signal enforcement systems]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3839664</guid>
      <title>'Purged' North Korean official appears next to Fatty at concert</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  A top North Korean official who had been reported as purged over the failed Hanoi nuclear summit with the U.S. was shown in state media on Monday kicking it next to Kim Jong-fats at a concertdoh.   According to the Associated Press, North Korean publications released photos of Kim Yong Chol sitting next to Dear Leader and other top goons at a musical performance by the wives of the Korean People's Army officers.  A report by Pyongyang's official speakerbox the Korean Central News Agency listed Kim Yong Chol in attendance at the musical event of the century. In a pretty creepy description of the event, KCNA said it, "impressively represented the ideological and mental features of KPA officers' wives, who make every moment of their life honorable with ardent yearning for the leader." According to AP, last week, South Korean newspaper Chosun Ilbo cited an unidentified source in reporting that Kim Yong Chol had been tossed into a hard labor and re-education for the botched Hanoi summit. Chosun Ilbo also reported that five other officials were executed by Fatty. Those guys have not shown up in any North Korean reports. Who knowsmaybe THEY ended being the lucky ones.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:18:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/05/3839664/3839664_9F07B73BAE76435785ABEB2AEEEFE657_190605_3839664__Purged__North_Korean_official_appears_next_to_F_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Korea purged official, North Korea, Kim Jong-un, Kim Yong Chol, Kim Yong Chol purge report]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840724</guid>
      <title>Metal thieves make off with rail bridge in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MURMANSK, RUSSIA  Some crafty thieves in Russia have managed to steal an entire bridge because why the hell not?The BBC reports that a criminal case has been launched after local prosecutors say unknown perps removed the main central span of a rail bridge in the Russian arctic region of Murmansk.The stolen metal is 23 meters long and weighs 56 tonnes. It was likely taken to be sold for scrap metal, which is a common problem in Russia.Residents noticed the bridge's disappearing act back in May. Photos on Russian social media site VK shows the bridge with its central section already gone.But chunks can still be seen on the river, which suggests the structure was first taken down before being taken apart.The Znak news website reports that the damage caused by the grand theft to the local company that owns it is 600,000 roubles, or roughly $9,000. According to state newspaper Rossiyskaya Gazeta, the bridge had been disused, and the tracks lifted long ago. Back in its heyday, it was used to transport concentrated rare earth elements from a nearby plant, but became useless after the plant went bankrupt and closed shop in 2007.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 15:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840724/3840724_D2D0820041F34134A65A607A631B15D7_190606_3840724_Metal_thieves_make_off_with_rail_bridge_in_Russi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, stolen bridge, thieves steal bridge, metal thieves, bridge thieves, bridge robbers, railway bridge, murmansk, russia bridge, russia stolen bridge]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840457</guid>
      <title>Ford slapped with $23.6 million fine in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA  Ford's joint business venture in China is being fined millions of dollars for violating antitrust laws, amid escalating tensions between the U.S. and China. CNN reports that China's State Administration for Market Regulation served Changan Ford with a fine of 162.8 million yuan for setting minimum resale prices on its cars in Chongqing. That's about $23.6 million, and equivalent to four percent of Ford's sales in Chongqing in 2018.Chinese regulators claim the company's actions took away dealers' pricing autonomy, restricted competition, and damaged consumer interests.Ford responded by saying it respects the regulators' decision, and is taking corrective action.China's move on the American automaker is just the latest punitive action in the trade war between Washington and Beijing.The U.S. had put Chinese tech giant Huawei on a list of companies deemed to be undermining American interests, and U.S. firms were barred from using the tech giant's telecom gear. China later announced it was coming up with its own foreign company blacklist, and has already zeroed in on FedEx after Huawei claimed it diverted two packages intended for the China office to the U.S.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 08:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840457/3840457_58177EBDF2204504AED03644D77F6659_190606_3840457_Ford_slapped_with__23_6_million_fine_in_China_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Ford, China, Changan Ford, China fines Ford, Ford China, antitrust violation, antitrust laws, China antitrust laws]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840380</guid>
      <title>White &amp; red meat have the same effect on your cholesterol levels</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OAKLAND, CALIFORNIA  New research has found that white meat isn't necessarily a healthier alternative to red meat.White meat was found to have the same effect on cholesterol levels as red meat, according to a new study in The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition.To conduct their study, researchers randomly assigned 113 participants to a high saturated fat diet  or a low saturated fat groups.They also went through three different diets: a red meat diet, a white meat diet and a non-meat protein diet. The red meat diet mainly used beef while the white meat diet consisted of chicken and turkey. Legumes, nuts, grains and soy products were used during the non-meat protein diet.Results show that both red and white meat caused an increase of LDL cholesterol levels in participants, despite the amount of saturated fat in the diet.Conversely, the study found that eating a plant protein diet had the best benefit for cholesterol.LDL cholesterol is known as the "bad" cholesterol as it builds up in the arteries and could potentially cause a heart attack or a stroke, according to CNN.Senior author of the study, Ronald Kraus, was quoted by a University of California San Francisco news release as saying, "When we planned this study, we expected red meat to have a more adverse effect on blood cholesterol levels than white meat, but we were surprised that this was not the case."He noted that there may be other effects of red meat consumption that could be responsible for heart disease, adding that the effects should be explored in more detail.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 07:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840380/3840380_D3F7CA54CB4F438D8B2B941C517250E1_190606_3840380_White___red_meat_have_the_same_effect_on_your_ch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, white meat, red meat, red beef, cholesterol level, eating red meat, red meat bad for you, red meat and cholesterol, white meat raises cholesterol, white meat red meat cholesterol, white meat unhealthy, white meat red meat cholesterol, cholesterol, diet, poultry meat, beef, chicken]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840368</guid>
      <title>Man wins $344.6 million Powerball with fortune cookie numbers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CUMBERLAND COUNTY, NORTH CAROLINA    The answer is, 1 in 292.2million, but what's the question?You guessed it, the odds of winning the jackpot are about 1 in 292.2million.A fortune cookie helped smash those odds when a North Carolina man rejoiced after finding out he had won $344.6 million on a Powerball jackpot, which is the largest payout in the state's history. According to USA Today, Charles W. Jackson, the 66-year-old prize winner had chosen his numbers from a fortune cookie his stepdaughter had given him a couple of years ago.He called his wife to tell her about his winnings but admitted he didn't realize how much he had won or even if he had gotten all the numbers, she told him to, "check google".CBS 17 reported Jackson saying, "After I hung up with her I jumped back in there and looked and I said, 'dang I got em all'".After taxes, Jackson walks away with a cool $158 million. He said he planned to donate money to charity, give $1 million to his brother, and take a trip to Vietnam. Jackson continued, "I hope it don't change me a lot.... I'm going to try not to change my life. I'm still going to wear jeans. Maybe newer ones."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 07:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840368/3840368_D0967623A4A044D1B32DF8343D624300_190606_3840368_Man_wins__344_6_million_Powerball_with_fortune_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Carolina man wins the lottery, man wins the lottery with fortune cookies numbers, fortune cookies numbers win the lottery, North Carolina man wins  $344.6 million, Lottery winner, Powerball winner, North Carolina, Lottery, Biggest lottery win in state history]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840359</guid>
      <title>Leaked video shows Joe Biden preaching 'I voted for a fence'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLUMBIA, SOUTH CAROLINA   A leaked video from 2006 has surfaced showing former vice president Joe Biden at the Columbia, South Carolina, Rotary Club saying things about Mexico that we would hear from Trump a decade later.Biden was quoted as saying: "Folks, I voted for a fence, I voted, unlike most Democrats  and some of you won't like it  I voted for 700 miles of fence. But, let me tell you, we can build a fence 40 stories high  unless you change the dynamic in Mexico."In the video, Biden can then be heard saying that he thinks the American people should be punished for hiring illegals.Biden continues to spread his policies about the room as he goes on to talk about "corrupt Mexico" and the "tons" of drugs that come through the border.The comments in the video may come as a blow to his current presidential campaign and a shock to his supporters. Then again, he has been under fire recently for being a handsy creep.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 06:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840352/3840352_268400876F5B479F9CE69299850B6B60_190606_3840352_Leaked_Video_Shows_Joe_Biden_Preaching__I_Voted__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,joe biden kid sniffer,joe biden,leaked video,joe biden leaked video,joe biden controversies,joe biden 2020 presidential run,mexico,fence,wall,trump,joe biden 2020,joe biden 2006,Rotary club exposed,creepy joe,creepy joe biden,joe biden fence]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840345</guid>
      <title>Apple is charging $1,000 for a monitor stand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN JOSE, CALIFORNIA  Consumers online are outraged after Apple announced its Mac Book Pro monitor will be sold separately from its stand. The cost of the stand? $999.Apple is known for its ridiculously costly products that Apple fanboys will no doubt line-up to buy no matter how useless they are, but this time even loyal consumers did a double take. At its annual Worldwide Developer Conference in San Jose this week, John Ternus, the company's hardware engineering VP, was going about new Apple products while the audience responded with the customary "oohs" and "aahs" of excitement. First, he unveiled the new Mac Pro desktop with a price tag of $6,000 coupled with its PRO Display monitor priced at just $4,999. Expensive? Of course. But Apple managed to get away with it since it flashes a 32-inch 6K Retina display, among other extra features.  But then, the third announcement came. If you wanted to say, put your monitor on a stand as one usually does, you had to pay $999 more for the Pro Stand. That's another grand for a stand. Needless to say, the audience's excitement quickly turned into disbelief.You'd think a $5,000 dollar computer monitor would already come with its stand, but as we are all aware of by now, Apple will slap extra price tag wherever it deems possible.Apple offered the Pro Stand as if it was some sort of optional purchase. I guess if you're short $1,000 you could technically lean your 5 grand monitor against a wall or make your own DIY stand or something? But the Pro Stand must be worth the price, right? Well, according to its specs, which Apple detailed in a press release, the stand allows users to tilt and rotate the monitor as well as adjust its height. Truly, groundbreaking. Never heard of a monitor stand that did that before. The good thing is people aren't falling for Apple's shenanigans and called out the tech giant for being so blatantly greedy.Twitter user Vishnu Narayanan took a shot at Apple's CEO saying, "If I had a $1000 to spend on something useless, I would buy a #ProStand and ship it to @tim_cook. He lacks a spine. He prob' need a stand. @Apple"Others saw Apple's new product as a business opportunity, Twitter user James G. offered his services saying, "Just so everyone knows: I will hold your computer monitor whenever you want me to for $997.  #Apple #ProStand" This guy might be onto something.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 06:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840345/3840345_5E446E524C774192B60596FE1BE7E9A3_190606_3840345_Apple_is_charging__1_000_for_a_monitor_stand_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, apple, apple pro stand, apple mac book pro, apple stand 999, apple pro stand 999, apple price, apple pro stand price, apple stand price]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840282</guid>
      <title>Woman draws gun in heated karaoke argument in Texas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS  A woman who was packing actually pulled her piece on a guy inside of a Mexican restaurant over a karaoke disagreement, according to an arrest affidavit. According to police, 41-year-old Doris Vallejo-Godoy was with her girlfriend at the bar in the La Catedral del Marisco restaurant, when she got in it with some dude at the karaoke machine. According to Statesman, the affidavit said words were exchanged and the man apparently called Vallejo-Godoy some names.  So she did what any karaoke veteran would doshe pulled her pistol out to calm the guy down, without pointing it at him. Wellthat's what she told the police anyways. The man however, said that after the argument, karaoke clown busted him in the face, pulled the weapon out and pointed it directly at him.   According to Statesman, a waitress then tried to grab Vallejo-Godoy from behind, but she got loose and then turned around and pointed the gun at the waitress's stomach and threatened her. The girlfriend eventually managed to calm her down, at which point they were about to pay and leave. That's when the po po arrived and busted Vallejo-Godoy.Einstein was charged with aggravated assault with a deadly weapon, a second-degree felony.  Authorities said she also didn't have a concealed handgun license and was charged with unlawful carrying of a concealed weapon.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 04:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840282/3840282_22647522BE6E4378AFACC035384A1DF9_190606_3840282_Woman_draws_gun_in_heated_karaoke_argument_in_Te_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, karaoke, karaoke machine, karaoke argument, Vallejo-Godoy, Vallejo-Godoy karaoke argument]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840278</guid>
      <title>Gut bacteria could affect the way meds work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW HAVEN, CONNECTICUT  Science may have found the reason why meds don't always work the same way with different people, and turns out it's all in the gut.According to a study published in Nature, Yale researchers identified human gut microbes that can process more than 150 therapeutic drugs.The team tested the ability of 76 kinds of bacteria to alter the structure of 271 oral drugs that range from hormones to antiviral meds. To do this, the bacteria were incubated in test tubes with nutrient and drug solutions for 12 hours. 176 of the 271 drugs ended up being modified by at least one bacterial strain, and each strain was found to have modified 11 to 95 different drugs. After then pinpointing the genes responsible for these drug-metabolizing abilities, researchers found wide variations in the number of these genes in healthy people.This could explain why some guts metabolize drugs quickly, while others process the same meds more slowly, or not at all. Study co-author Maria Zimmermann-Kogadeeva said it's possible to use the genetic makeup of an individual's gut flora to predict how he or she will respond to medication."The  researchers hope their study is a useful first step in understanding how microbiomes contribute to drug response, and perhaps shed light on its role in processing non-drug compounds like dietary nutrients or environmental agents.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 04:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840278/3840278_002C4940FFFE425EA568FB504A36D181_190606_3840278_Gut_bacteria_could_affect_the_way_meds_work_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, gut bacteria, gut microbes, drug efficacy, meds, medical treatment, medicine, drug response, drug metabolism, drug effects]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840234</guid>
      <title>Experts say Planet Earth is quickly losing its topsoil layer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EARTH  Earth's topmost layer is slowly eroding away due to the effects of overgrazing and conventional farming methods.According to the Guardian, nearly half of the world's topsoil has already disappeared.The lack of cover crops, over-tilling, and the use of pesticides have all contributed to soil degradation. This has caused farmlands to be stripped of important nutrients, minerals, and organisms which typically help in plant growth.This layer is essential to food production, as the Guardian reports that 95 percent of food on our planet is grown on topsoil.According to estimates from the United Nations Food and Agriculture Organization, earth could run out of topsoil as quickly as 60 years from now.It could take around 500 years for healthy topsoil to cultivate but it could take less than a century for it to degrade, according to The Guardian.If the topsoil does disappear, vegetables and other foods grown in the soil could possibly contain lower vital nutrients.Healthy topsoil will be a necessity in order to feed a growing population, as the world's population is set to reach around 9 billion people by 2050.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 02:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/06/3840234/3840234_11D1CEA21D7C4026A6CF549BF31F7445_190606_3840234_Experts_say_Planet_Earth_is_quickly_losing_its_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, earth, planet, planet earth, top soil, earth's topsoil almost gone, soil, rebuilding soil health, earth topsoil, earth topsoil degrading, organic matter, soil nutrients, topsoil loss, losing topsoil, earth is losing topsoil, agriculture, earth could soon run out of topsoil, intensive farming, lack of nutritious top soil, erosion, overgrazing, healthy soil, degraded soil]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3841226</guid>
      <title>Chinese farmer pushing $300,000 BMW steals livestock for gas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LINSHUI COUNTY, CHINA  A bird-brained farmer in China was busted for actually stealing chickens and ducks from villages just so he could pay for gas for his reasonably priced $290,000 BMW. According to the Chengdu Business Daily, police say the 50-year-old farmer had been stealing birds from farms in Linshui county, Sichuan province since April.Looks like the Chinese Warren Buffetminus all the moneylives in a multistory villa, but had to turn to thieving poultry after running into some financial problems. Apparently, the $290,000 Bimmer[b]  is quite the gas guzzler, so Scrooge McDuck hatched up a scheme to steal ducks and chickens under the cover of night fall. According to police, the farmer would take his motorcycle out late in the middle of the night. Why not the BMW? Oh yeahno gas. Using surveillance footage from rural roads, authorities finally identified the thief. They almost caught him on May 22, but his luxury ride was faster than the clunkers the Chinese police were driving, so he flew the coup. He was eventually arrested by authorities.Looks like he was taking the chickens and ducks back to his farm, so he could then raise them.  He would then sell them to potential buyers, and then go buy gas for his BMW.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 15:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/07/3841226/3841226_F8DF1F3F0A7F40D5B8EDC555B818B360_190607_3841226_Chinese_farmer_pushing__300_000_BMW_steals_lives_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese farmer with BMW, farmer with BMW can afford gas, farmer steals chickens to pay for BMW gas, farmer steals chickens ducks]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3841143</guid>
      <title>Multiple Cobra sightings in Taipei</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI  The Taiwanese cobra has been spotted twice this week by locals who were just trying to get some sightseeing done.The venomous snake was first sighted on a hiking trail in central Taiwan, Taiwan News reports.In a video posted by the Taichung City Tourism Bureau, the cobra was seen waiting right by a tourism marker.As soon as the cameraman tries to get closer to it, the snake immediately turns its head and stares menacingly at him.A warning was posted along with the video, urging the public to "watch out for snakes in tall grass."A second cobra was spotted just days later near a swimming pool in a park in Taipei.Observers were quick to share photos of the snake on Taiwanese online messaging board PTT.The sudden increase of venomous cobras around the city may be due to the recent hot weather, according to Taiwan's Tourism Bureau.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/07/3841143/3841143_C5F791F5E8AF4538BB5D8E823423053F_190607_3841143_Multiple_Cobra_sightings_in_Taipei_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, taiwan, cobra, cobra sighting, taiwan cobra sighting, giant cobra, giant cobra on the loose, taiwanese cobra, Naja atra, giant taiwanese cobra, cobra sightings taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3841033</guid>
      <title>U.S. announces $2 billion arms package to Taiwan, China upset</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  The U.S. is preparing an arms sale package of more than $2 billion worth of tanks and weapons to Taiwan.Reuters reports that according to four people familiar with the negotiations, an informal notification of the proposed sale has been sent to the U.S.Congress.According to Reuters, three of the sources said the potential sale included 108 General Dynamics Corp M1A2 Abrams tanks, in addition to anti-tank and anti-aircraft munitions. Taiwan is badly in need of upgrading its existing U.S. made tank inventory, which includes M60 Patton tanks. Two of the sources told Reuters anti-tank munitions included 409 Raytheon Co and Lockheed Martin Corp-made Javelin missiles worth as much as $129 million. According to Reuters, one source said the congressional notification also included 1,240 TOW anti-tank missiles worth $299 million, as well as 250 stinger missiles with a $223 million price tag. Taiwan's Defense Ministry confirmed the weapons request, and said the sale was proceeding normally.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 09:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/07/3841033/3841033_03AE9DE2D29F4143ACD671FA40E13269_190607_3841033_U_S__announces__2_billion_arms_package_to_Taiwan_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, U.S. Taiwan arms package, U.S. Taiwan arms sales, Taiwan M1 tanks, Taiwan U.S. tanks, Taiwan]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840998</guid>
      <title>Australian media headquarters raided by federal police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY    According to the Australian Broadcasting Corporation, the Australian Federal Police, or AFP, raided its headquarters last Wednesday. ABC states police raided the company over a 2017 series of stories called the Afghan Files. The articles were based on leaked military reports and revealed incidents of Australian troops attacking unarmed civilians and children.  The previous day, they raided the home of  Annika Smethurst, a journalist with News Corp, for a story she had published in April 2018 where she claimed the Australian government was contemplating giving spy agencies more access to surveillance. In a press release, the AFP stated the search warrant carried out against ABC was, quote, "in relation to allegations of publishing classified material, contrary to provisions of the Crimes Act 1914." However, journalists believe the raids are being used to intimidate whistleblowers and journalists.ABC's investigations editor, John Lyons, tweeted a picture of the AFP's search warrant which asked for access to journalist's notes, internal and external correspondence, story pitches, and diaries among other internal data. Lyon also tweeted that the warrant allowed the AFP to "add, copy, delete or alter" material in the company's computers. He added, quote, "All Australians, please think about that: as of this moment, the AFP has the power to delete material in the ABC's computers." The AFP's actions were condemned by other international news outlets. The BBC tweeted out its support for ABC calling the raid "an attack on press freedom" adding it was worrying Australian media was being targeted for, quote, "doing its job of reporting in the public interest."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 07:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/07/3840998/3840998_2F945069A1E845E5BED6F56196805BE7_190607_3840998_Australian_media_headquarters_raided_by_federal__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, abc offices raided, australian police, abc australia, annika smethurst, freedom of press, journalist raid, abc raid, afp raid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840989</guid>
      <title>If you're drinking bottled water, you're drinking microplastics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VICTORIA, CANADA  A new study by the University of Victoria in Canada has found that you could potentially double the amount of microplastic particles you ingest by drinking bottled water.The researchers mentioned in the study that they focused on the American diet to calculate the amount of microplastic particles present in food items such as honey, seafood, salt, sugar and tap water.According to the study, boys and men ingested and inhaled approximately 81,000 and 121,000 microplastic particles a year, respectively.While girls and women were exposed to roughly 74,000 and 98,000 plastic particles annually.The researchers determined that the amount of microplastics present in the body was related to how one typically consumes water.Individuals who drank bottled water could be ingesting an additional 90,000 microplastics in a year, according to the study.In comparison, those who only consumed tap water only ingested an additional 4000 microplastics annually.The authors of the study concluded that the overall consumption of microplastics for Americans is likely to be much higher.However, there are some limitations to the study. According to CNN, Professor Richard Limpitt at the National Oceanography Centre in the UK, criticized the study saying that the authors failed to differentiate between nanoplastic particles and microplastic particles.Adding that the size of the plastic particles has a "massive impact on the data presented and the conclusions reached."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 07:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/07/3840989/3840989_AC67CDF0C9F144F8B6D64EB6CEDDEC10_190607_3840989_If_you_re_drinking_bottled_water__you_re_drinkin_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, microplastics, plastic particles, microplastics pollution, plastic bags, plastic pollution, plastic pollution, microplastic particles, plastic waste, plastic litter, bottled water, bottled water microplastic particles]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3840957</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman earns $4,000 a month making bird nappies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGSU, CHINA  A woman in China is earning a cool $4,000 a month from selling bird nappies online.According to China Daily, 25-year-old Zheng Han is a former nurse from Jiangsu Province who quit in 2014 to focus on her online store on Taobao, which is one of the largest e-commerce platforms in the country.Zheng first started selling decorative costumes for birds, before going into the bird diaper market for friends who wanted a better way to deal with doo doo. She looked online and found that bird diapers were already a thing in the U.S. but were both poorly designed and pretty expensive at 29 to 58 bucks apiece.So Zheng designed her own diapers, making it a point to make them convenient and practical. Her current version has gone through eight or nine upgrades, and features a cotton outer layer and an inner canvas layer that's waterproof A small sanitary pad or make-up sponge is put in before use. There's also velcro in case the feathered folk need adjustments.Each diaper sells online for 200 yuan or about $3. Zheng says she used to get an order every three or four days, but now has over 1,000 orders a month, even from abroad.Her clientele includes bird lovers from as far away as Australia, the U.S., Canada, Singapore, and the UAE.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 06:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/07/3840957/3840957_10EEB8AE95F34A1FA4664CBBAD29BF5E_190607_3840957_Chinese_woman_earns__4_000_a_month_making_bird_n_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bird diapers, bird nappies, animal diapers, diapers for birds, handmade diapers, diapers, online seller, nursing, nurse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842592</guid>
      <title>Kim Jong-un executes general by tossing him in piranha tank</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG  It appears that North Korea's Kim Jong-un has decided to go full out Bond villain by having one of his generals offed by tossing him into a piranha-filled fish tank. According to the Daily Star, Fats sent down the order after the general was accused of plotting a coup. The Daily Star reported that the giant fish tank was built inside Ryongsong Residence, one of Kim's presidential palaces, after the dictator ordered his underlings to come up with some new ways of execution. Looks like the general's arms and torso were introduced to some knives before the meet and greet with the piranhaswell, more like EAT and greet.The Daily Star reported that sources said it was unclear if the general succumbed because of the fish, his wounds, or drowning. Kim's super fun fish tank is filled with hundreds of piranhas imported from Brazil.According to the Daily Star, since taking power in 2011, Kim has sent at least 16 senior aides on permanent vacations from the land of the living. Hundreds more North Korean citizens have also been given permanent dirt naps.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 23:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/11/3842592/3842592_CBB8E25EAB494B7D80707C0614CF7E42_190611_3842592_Kim_Jong_un_executes_general_by_tossing_him_in_p_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Kim Jong Un, North Korea, North Korea Kim Jong-un, North Korea general coup, North Korea general coup plot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842477</guid>
      <title>South Korean coffee shop uses robot baristas to brew coffee</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA  A coffee chain in South Korea has come up with the idea of replacing human baristas with robotic baristas.The robot takes orders via a mobile app or a kiosk and is able to make fresh coffee in just under a minute, according to the Associated Press.Once the coffee is ready, a 4-digit code is sent to the customer so that it can be used to open the pick-up box containing the coffee.The robot baristas are wired with 5G technology to offer faster services, reports The Korea Times.Dal.Komm Coffee seems to be doing quite well as it currently has 45 robot-equipped coffee shops across the country, as reported by the Associated Press.The futuristic robot barista is able to brew 90 coffee cups an hour, or as many as 300 cups a day. The coffee shops have managers who monitor the robots via surveillance cameras and sensors.While some may find the new technology to be "fun" and "convenient," others might prefer to have a human connection with their barista.Not surprisingly, this new tech is proving to be extremely popular with the millenials, as most prefer to do everything on their smartphones.The developers of the barista robots said they are planning to launch a faster, smarter version of the robot that will be able to recognize customer voices and movements later this year, The Associated Press reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 14:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/10/3842477/3842477_7FA3979D37F24CCCAB4B0752B0C5914D_190610_3842477_South_Korean_coffee_shop_uses_robot_baristas_to__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, south korea, robot baristas, robot baristas in south korea, robot barista seoul, robot technology 2019,  robot technology south korea, automation asia, Dal.komm Coffee, dal.komm coffee korea, dal.komm coffee beat robot, automated coffee shop, robotic coffee shop,  robot barista]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842471</guid>
      <title>Chinese warships load up with Australian baby formula</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY  It appears that three Chinese warships spotted in Sydney Harbor on Monday morning were there for an ultra-highly classified military operationthey were dispatched to pick up some milk.Photographs taken by the Australian show elite Chinese soldiers carrying boxes of Australian baby formula from a van, in addition to tons of whitening sheet face masks.According to the Australian, People's Liberation Army hacks were seen loading dozens of A2 platinum and Aptamil formula aboard the mighty fighting vessels. Ever since China's poison baby formula scandal in 2008, Chinese consumers have snatched up U.S., Australia and Europe made baby formula like they are the latest Jordans. But now in the midst of Trump and Beijing's trade war, Chinese authorities are trying to wean consumers off better quality baby formula, by improving made in China formula. Surewhat could possibly go wrong?Because of the massive Chinese demand, many Australian supermarkets and pharmacies often experience formula supply shortages.   According to News.com.au, Chinese websites that deal in black market baby formula, buy it abroad and then sell it in China for super inflated prices. Who knows, maybe Beijing's South China Sea fake islands scheme is just part of some master baby formula smuggling ring.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 14:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/10/3842471/3842471_70B98A8E0642472994DCD513AD1455C4_190610_3842471_Chinese_warships_load_up_with_Australian_baby_fo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese warships Australian baby formula, Chinese soldiers load Australian baby formula, Chinese soldiers load whitening face masks, China baby formula, China Australian baby formula]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842452</guid>
      <title>Liquid water may have erupted from Pluto's icy volcanoes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  A new study suggests that scientists may have found proof of liquid water being spewed out of Pluto's volcanoes. Ammonia was found on Pluto's surface, according to a study published in Science Advances.This has led scientists to believe that the dwarf planet's volcanoes may have recently erupted with liquid water.Scientists found evidence of ammonia in areas where tectonic activity had previously taken place. They discovered this by analyzing data from NASA's New Horizons probe which flew by Pluto in 2015.According to the researchers, ammonia was mixed in with water from Pluto's underground ocean. Subsequently, liquid water erupted through cracks and vents.Scientists are calling this cryovolcanism, as reported by Space.com.Lead author of the study Cristina Dalle Ore, told the website that radioactive heat from Pluto's ores causes the planet's interior to be warmer than its surface. This allows the ammonia to be liquid despite Pluto's frigid temperatures.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 13:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/10/3842452/3842452_4ED043D3655342B0BC30B86B4E5347A1_190610_3842452_Liquid_water_may_have_erupted_from_Pluto_s_icy_v_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space, space exploration, pluto, pluto volcano, volcanoes on pluto, ice volcanoes on pluto, pluto ice volcano, icy pluto, dwarf planet, liquid water pluto,  planetary science, planetary discoveries, ammonia pluto, evolution of life, pluto, cryovolcanism]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842304</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters march against China extradition bill</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  More than a million people marched in Hong Kong to protest a controversial new law that would allow suspects to be sent to China for trial.According to the South China Morning Post, the bill will allow Hong Kong to decide case-by-case whether to transfer suspected criminals to territories it doesn't have formal extradition deals with, including Macau, Taiwan, and mainland China.The government claims the proposed bill would plug loopholes so that Hong Kong would not be a safe haven for criminals. But critics say it will instead undermine Hong Kong's semi-autonomous legal system and allow China to take anyone in Hong Kong for political reasons or business offenses.According to CNN, protesters wearing white and waving placards gathered at Victoria Park in central Hong Kong on Sunday afternoon.While walking three kilometers to the Legislative Council, they chanted "shelve the evil law" and "anti extradition to China" and called for Chief Executive Carrie Lam to step down.Organizers say 1.03 million people joined the march, which would make it the largest demonstration the city has had since it was handed back to China in '97. Hong Kong police claim the number is closer to 240,000.The BBC reports that clashes later erupted between demonstrators and cops. Police in riot gear used batons and pepper spray on some who tried to break into the Legislative Council complex.At least seven were arrested, according to Hong Police posts on Twitter.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 09:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/10/3842304/3842304_2449004DC10340DEA065B5C8CE7C0DC4_190610_3842304_Hong_Kong_protesters_march_against_China_extradi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China extradition, China extradition bill, China extradition, Hong Kong, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, mass protest, HK mass protest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842248</guid>
      <title>Canadian researchers complain
dodgeball is dehumanizing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER, CANADA  Remember elementary schoolwhen you'd pelt a ball into someone's face in the name of sport? Well, according to The Washington Post, Canadian researchers from three universities claim dodgeball actually dehumanizes peers and is used as a catharsis for students. Professor at the University of British Columbia, Joy Butler branded dodgeball as a tool of "oppression" and said, quote, "the message is that it's okay to hurt or dehumanize the other". And, "dodgeball is the only game where the human being is the target..." no other games focus on it.According to CTV News, another anti-fun professor David Burns said, "if you practice ganging up on people, over time you'll esteem ganging up on people. If that's what you want, then dodgeball is an excellent tool to that end."The researchers claim that the annihilation of your opponent during dodgeball creates unsafe conditions within an area that's supposed to encourage positive development. A paper on their study is set to be published in the European Physical Education Review.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 07:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/10/3842248/3842248_56E6FE25FC2E4C018A979726A373197C_190610_3842248_Canadian_researchers_complain_dodgeball_is_dehum_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Canada, dodgeball, Canada dodgeball, British Columbia, dodgeball bullying, bully, dehumanizing, researchers complain dodgeball is dehumanizing, sports, school]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843148</guid>
      <title>HK leader to push ahead with extradition bill despite protests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Hong Kong Chief Executive Carrie Lam announced on Monday that she has no plans to withdraw a controversial plan to allow extradition to China, despite mass protests against it.According to The New York Times, the Hong Kong government has proposed an extradition bill that will allow case-based transfers of suspected criminals to territories it does not have agreements with, including Taiwan, Macau, and China.The administration wants to pass the bill before July, to allow for the extradition of a Hong Kong man wanted for murdering his girlfriend in Taiwan.The Guardian reports that opponents of the bill say it is being pushed by the Chinese government, setting off fears that Beijing will be able to use it to extradite political activists, dissidents, and other opponents in the city.On Sunday, over a million people marched the streets of Hong Kong to oppose the extradition plan. The mostly peaceful protest turned violent after midnight, after police with batons and pepper spray clashed with demonstrators attempting to occupy areas around the Legislative Council complex.Despite the opposition, the government has no plans to change the bill's wording or withdraw it from legislation.Lam has reasoned that it is necessary to prevent Hong Kong from turning into a fugitive haven, and claims there are human rights safeguards in the bill that meet international standards, and are in place to protect the city's unique freedoms.According to the Guardian, China's Foreign Affairs Ministry said it supports Hong Kong in passing the bill. In a Monday editorial, state-owned China Daily defended the extradition plan and blamed "foreign forces" for creating chaos in Hong Kong.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843148/3843148_426FE73F98DD46B28308ED528C133508_190612_3843148_HK_leader_to_push_ahead_with_extradition_bill_de_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong protests, HK protests, HK mass protest, Hong Kong mass protest, China extradition, China extradition bill, China extradition law, HK extradition, Carrie Lam, Hong Kong]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843144</guid>
      <title>NASA to open International Space Station to paying customers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISS  According to the BBC, NASA will be opening the International Space Station to commercial ventures, including space tourism.Starting 2020, there will be two private space missions per year, each for stays of up to 30 days.Travelers will be ferried to the ISS by two companies hired by NASA  SpaceX using its Crew Dragon capsule, and Boeing with the Starliner it's currently building.These companies would choose the clients and be responsible for determining crew composition, and making sure the private astronauts meet the medical and training requirements for spaceflight.The L.A. Times reports that apart from a $58 million roundtrip ticket, tourists will need to pay $35,000 for each day spent at the station. Use of the station's toilets and life support system costs $11,250 per day, while the daily charge for crew supplies such as food, air, and medical supplies is $22,500.The AFP reports the International Space Station isn't owned entirely by NASA, having been built starting in 1998 with Russia. The U.S. though, paid for and controls most of the orbiter's modules.While NASA had previously banned commercial use of the station, the Russian space agency has long embraced space tourism. In 2001, U.S. businessman Dennis Tito paid Russia $20 million to be the first space tourist on the ISS.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 17:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843144/3843144_2D65F2638DB64A5C918CC480DC54D834_190612_3843144_NASA_to_open_International_Space_Station_to_payi_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, NASA, ISS, international space station, space tourism, space tourists, space station, private astronaut, private space trip]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843088</guid>
      <title>Man who filmed viral arrest is jailed on parole violation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYRACUSE, NEW YORK  A man who filmed a violent police arrest that went viral has been jailed on parole violation charges, public records show. According to CNY Central, 21-year-old Yamil Osorio was arrested by parole officers on Monday, three days after he filmed a forceful police arrest that has sparked protests from anti-police brutality activists. The video shows 23-year-old Shaolin Moore being dragged out from the driver's seat after police allege he refused to get out of the car. According to police reports, the cops had asked Moore to step out of the vehicle over a loud music complaint. The report states police had previously recovered drugs and a firearm in the same area and feared Moore could be carrying a concealed weapon. Footage shows two police officers holding Moore against the floor, while one of them strikes him in the head three times. In the report, the officer claims it was to "distract him and get his arms behind his back."  The video ends after a third officer notices Osorio recording and walks to the passenger side, demanding Osorio stop filming. Records show Moore had previously served almost three years in state prison for third-degree burglary and was released in June of last year. Syracuse Police Chief Kenton Buckner said the officers in the video are still on duty despite protests calling for those involved to be suspended. Buckner added that the officers would be interviewed as part of an internal investigation.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 15:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/11/3843088/3843088_AA0DBD728A194DDEBA747DE625F463AF_190611_3843088_Man_who_filmed_viral_arrest_is_jailed_on_parole__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, syracuse police, osorio syracuse, shaolin moore syracuse, syracuse police, police brutality, police brutality, police brutality protest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843028</guid>
      <title>China overly slippery glass slide accident leaves 1 dead, 6 injured</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGXI, CHINA  Flying down an insanely long glass slide with just a pinch of rain? Sounds like a solid plan. According to a report on Miaopai, one person was killed and six others injured last week after falling off a glass slide at a tourist spot in Guangxi.The visitors to the site in Pingnan county slid down a 260-meter-long slide sitting on nothing but a cloth pad while wearing some cheap gloves that apparently were supposed to act as breaks.  Let's just say things went downhill after that. Because of the rain, the slide was way too slippery, which caused one man to hit the guard rail and break right through it, launching him off the slide 7 plus meters away. Six other people that followed him were also injured.Unfortunately, the man succumbed due to head injuries. The other people were treated for various other bumps and bruises. All the victims were apparently part of the same family. Police have arrested the owner of the ride and are currently investigating the cause of the accident. Our guess? It was probably gravity. Looks as if the glass slide failed to get proper approval from the required departments when it opened last September. That's reassuring.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 13:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/11/3843028/3843028_B115555F9EAC4C45AC8D41BAA15E08C0_190611_3843028_China_overly_slippery_glass_slide_accident_leave_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, glass slide, china glass slide, China Guangxi glass slide, China long glass slide, China slides]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843010</guid>
      <title>6-year-old hair stylist still crushing it with the scissors in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SUINING, CHINA  On the lookout for a new do? Bangs or no bangs? A perm possibly? Well head over to the Sichuan city of Suining and pop in to see stylist Jiang Hongqi. Oh yeahhe's also only 6-years-old. According to Miaopai, Jiang's parents run a hair salon. At 4-years-old, they started taking him to the salon with them.  There he would watch his parents wash, cut and dry customers' hair. Looks like the hair doesn't fall far from the head because little man soon discovered he had quite the knack for styling. He started out just washing and drying people's hair, but has since moved up to slicing and dicing men and women's hair. The 6-year-old styling sensation can also cut and do his own hair.Jiang also has been known to make a house call or two for those looking for a quick trim. His slick scissor skills have made him quite the online sensation in China with over a million followers on Chinese video app Kuaishou.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 13:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/11/3843010/3843010_7DE047746093488F92332440484C5C1D_190611_3843010_6_year_old_hair_stylist_still_crushing_it_with_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China 6-year-old hair stylist, China 6-year-old barber, 6-year-old hair stylist, China kid hair stylist]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842858</guid>
      <title>Converting plastic into usable fuel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY, UTAH  Renewlogy, a private waste management company, has found a way to turn plastic into fuel.The company is able to process around 10 tons of plastic waste on a daily basis to convert into fuel, according to Renewlogy's website.Plastic waste is shredded into smaller pieces and then put into a oxygen-free reactor. The machine is then heated up. This causes the carbon molecules present in the plastic to break down into smaller molecules, essentially turning plastic into usable fuel.Renewlogy explained on their website that gases created from the process would be captured and recycled to prevent any toxic gas emissions.According to the company, the byproduct of the carbon molecules are then converted into naphtha, which is commonly used to create virgin plastic, diesel fuel, and other petrochemical products. The company claims that less than 10 percent of plastic has ever been recycled.According to Renewlogy's website, plastic production is forecasted to double in the next decade.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 09:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/11/3842858/3842858_647C87B1290E466F95D28B15DE9AC84D_190611_3842858_Converting_plastic_into_usable_fuel_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, renewlogy, renewlogy video, renewlogy plastic to fuel, usable fuel, plastic, turning plastic into fuel, plastic fuel, Renewlogy technology, recycling plastic, recycling plastic to fuel, recycling plastic to produce fuel, plastic waste, plastic waste recycling, plastic waste to fuel, plastic waste solutions]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842759</guid>
      <title>Woman mistakes emergency exit
for toilet and delays flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANCHESTER, UNITED KINGDOM  Passengers onboard a flight from Manchester to Pakistan were left feeling down in the dumps when a woman mistakenly opened the plane's emergency exit thinking it was the can, causing a seven-hour flight delay.The plane was on the runway when the female passenger elected to use the toilet despite the seatbelt signs being lit. It's unclear how the woman was able to open the emergency exit without being stopped by the cabin crew. As a result, the plane's emergency slides deployed.  According to The Express Tribune, Pakistan officials blame a lack of airline staff for the incident. The Guardian reported that when the woman was questioned on why she opened the emergency door, she said that she thought it was the toilet. A spokesperson for Pakistan International Airlines, also known as PIA, told The Express Tribune that, "there was no threat of any kind." PIA followed protocol and offloaded disgruntled passengers with some taking to Twitter to express their dissatisfaction.The Sun reported that the flight was pushed back from its scheduled departure of 9:20 p.m on Friday to 5 a.m on Saturday.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 07:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/11/3842759/3842759_8C76BDA8A7274C569CC78BE6F80983BA_190611_3842759_Woman_mistakes_emergency_exit_for_toilet_and_del_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plane delayed, woman delays plane with toilet mistake, emergency exit, Manchester, Pakistan, flight delay, PIA, passenger mistakes emergency exit for the toilet, passenger mistakes emergency exit for bathroom, passenger mistakes exit for toilet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3842624</guid>
      <title>Total solar eclipse to be visible from Chile on July 2</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COQUIMBO, CHILE  Another total solar eclipse is coming in 2019.Bloomberg reports that according to NASA, the total solar eclipse on July 2 will start off  the coast of New Zealand, and reach its peak 1,000 kilometers north of Easter Island, lasting four minutes and 33 seconds.A total eclipse occurs when the sun, moon, and Earth are in a direct line. It's only visible from a small area  those who see it are in the center of the moon's shadow when it hits Earth.Parts of Chile and Argentina will be in the path of totality, but only for a brief window of time.The Independent reports that viewers in San Juan, Argentina can expect to see 36 seconds of totality, while those in La Silla, Chile may be able to view it for one minute 53 seconds.According to Bloomberg, a partial eclipse will be visible in Brazil, Ecuador, Uruguay, and Paraguay if weather permits.Chile's Elqui Valley is one of the few spots on land to view the total eclipse from, and over a quarter of a million visitors are expected on the days surrounding the eclipse.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 03:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/11/3842624/3842624_331F74EB0742491D9580381276A4EAEF_190611_3842624_Total_solar_eclipse_to_be_visible_from_Chile_on__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, solar eclipse, eclipse, total solar eclipse, chile eclipse, july 2 eclipse, 2019 total solar eclipse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843597</guid>
      <title>Facebook's massive Texan solar farm project explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  Facebook is partnering up with Longroad Energy, a renewable energy developer, to build a massive solar farm in Texas. Called The Prospero Solar project, the Associated Press reports, the farm will occupy 18 square kilometers. This is more than five times the size of New York City's Central Park.According to Engadget, the solar farm will have a capacity of 379 megawatts. This is part of Facebook's plan to use renewable energy to power its data centers. Facebook's data centers are used to store images, videos and other user information.Engadget reports that Facebook is already using renewable energy for 75 percent of its business, as of last year. According to Facebook Sustainability, the company intends to become 100 percent energy efficient by 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 13:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843597/3843597_AE50D5245ED447278A2830D7AD056749_190612_3843597_Facebook_s_massive_Texan_solar_farm_project_expl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, facebook solar farm, solar farm, sustainability, going green, solar power, solar energy, renewable energy, Facebook data centers, facebook data center sustainability, facebook solar project, The Prospero Solar project, facebook solar farm texas]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843593</guid>
      <title>Chinese exporters dodging tariffs by using Made in Vietnam labels</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VIETNAM  As the trade war with the U.S. and China continues, some Chinese exporters are now trying to cheat their way around Trump's tariffs. According to Bloomberg, Vietnam said on Sunday that is discovered dozens of fake product-origin certificates and illegal transfers by Chinese companies trying to dodge U.S. tariffs. Bloomberg reports that this is the first time an Asian government has publicly called out China since trade tensions have ramped up between the world's two largest economies. In a statement from Vietnam, the country pledged to increase penalties on trade-related fraud amid concerns that Chinese exporters are illegally rerouting orders to skirt past Trump's $250 billion tariffs on Chinese goods.Some of the examples the shady behavior noticed by the Vietnamese government include Chinese goods changing packaging to say "Made in Vietnam" before certificates of origin are processed. Vietnam also said U.S. customs officials uncovered Chinese plywood being sent to the U.S. through a Vietnamese company.   According to Bloomberg, U.S. trading partners including Vietnam are being urged to crack down on illicit exports in order to avoid getting slapped with some Trump tariffs themselves.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 13:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843593/3843593_0E45746DC02B432EAC3D66F9511D9666_190612_3843593_Chinese_exporters_dodging_tariffs_by_using_Made__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, US China trade war, China exporters Vietnam labels, Chinese exporters Vietnam labels, fake Made in Vietnam labels, Trump tariffs]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843571</guid>
      <title>Argentinian bees make nests from plastic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA  New research from Argentina's National Agricultural Technology Institute shows that solitary bees are making nests out of plastic packaging.Scientists set up 63 trap nests around crop fields for the wild bees between 2017 and 2018. Three of the nests were used by bees.Citing the study, ScienceAlert reports that two were built from mud and petals, while the third one had three cells made from plastic.The first two cells were created out of thin, light blue plastic. The third was crafted from a thicker, white plastic. The researchers found that the bees had created them by cutting the materials into different shapes and then stacking them on one another.The first cell contained a dead larva. The second one seemed to have had a bee grow into adulthood while the third cell was incomplete.In a Spanish-language press release translated using Google Translate, lead author of the study Mariana Allasiano said the research would demonstrate the adaptive flexibility that certain species of bees would have in the face of changes in environmental conditions.The research was published in the April 2019 issue of the French journal, Apidologie.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843571/3843571_46261376B82740DEA3F3F9F05C60AAA0_190612_3843571_Argentinian_bees_make_nests_from_plastic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, bees, wild bees, plastic, plastic waste, plastic waste solution, wild bees building plastic nests in argentina, argentina, solitary bees, solitary bees argentina, bees building nests with plastic, bees plastic nests, bees making nest out of plastic, plastic bee nest]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843560</guid>
      <title>Canada to ban single-use plastics by 2021</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTREAL, CANADA  Canada is finally joining the anti-plastic movement.Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau announced on Monday that Canada will ban harmful single-use plastics as early as 2021.While the specific products to be outlawed have yet to be decided, CNN reports that bags, straws, cutlery, and stirring sticks may be included.According to DW, Trudeau said plastic producers will be held responsible for the full life cycle of their products, and that manufacturers and the companies using the products will need to provide recycling plans.The government would also work with the companies to establish targets on waste.The BBC reports that currently, less than 10% of plastics are recycled in Canada.Each year, the country throws away 3 million tonnes of plastic waste, which end up in landfills and incinerators, litter beaches and parks, and pollute bodies of water.According to the Canadian government, over a million birds and 100,000 sea mammals are injured or die globally each year when they mistake plastic for food.Trudeau claims that banning single-use plastic will not only reduce pollution and protect the environment, but also create 42,000 jobs in the recycling and recovery industries.Canada's anti-plastic crusade comes after the EU and the United Kingdom passed similar bans in late March and May, respectively.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 12:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843560/3843560_823AA7D0E2204FC3AE36752B95354940_190612_3843560_Canada_to_ban_single_use_plastics_by_2021_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, plastic ban, single use plastics, plastics ban, plastic pollution, canada plastic ban, canada single use plastics, plastic waste, harmful plastic waste, Canada plastic ban 2021]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843525</guid>
      <title>Man survives falling 800 feet into Oregon's Crater Lake caldera</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CRATER LAKE NATIONAL PARK, OREGON  A man miraculously survived a short 800-foot tumble down into the Crater Lake caldera on Monday, authorities say.Oregon Live reports that according to park officials, the man was at Crater Lake National Park with some coworkers near Rims Village.A park spokeswoman said that man apparently jumped onto some snow, and that's when the super long slip 'n slide began.The guy then slipped and kept sliding...and sliding...and sliding. WELLyou get the picture. The man finally came to a stop 800 feet into the caldera. According to a park press release, the Coast Guard's North Bend Sector got a call around 3:47 p.m. about the fall. According to Oregon Live, emergency rescue crews climbed down into the caldera, reached the man and walked him down to the shoreline.That's where a U.S. Coast Guard helicopter was able to fly down and pick him up. The Coast Guard chopper then landed in a nearby parking lot, so the man could be transferred to an AirLink Critical Care Transport helicopter. He was then flown to Bend for treatment.Park officials say the man was able to get in and out of the helicopter basket on his own.  In May, the park warned visitors that rocks and snow near the edge of the caldera were unstable and could give way without warning. At least people are paying attention to the warnings.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 10:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843525/3843525_5F23D7CC2CD24204B521DDD969ADE039_190612_3843525_Man_survives_falling_800_feet_into_Oregon_s_Crat_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man survives fall, man survives 800-foot fall, man falls into Crater Lake caldera, man falls Crater Lake, man survives Crater Lake fall]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843357</guid>
      <title>Deepfake Zuckerberg video
tests Facebook's policies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  A deepfake video of Mark Zuckerberg giving a Black Mirror-like speech was posted to Facebook-owned Instagram.The video portrays Zuckerberg sitting at a desk addressing his public in a very ominous manner.The video falsely shows him saying, "Imagine this for a second: One man, with total control of billions of people's stolen data, all their secrets, their lives, their futures...I owe it all to Spectre. Spectre showed me that whoever controls the data, controls the future."Vice reported that a spokesperson for Instagram said it will not be removing the video, instead, it will be following the same policy Facebook applied to a doctored video of House Speaker Nancy Pelosi.Facebook previously refused to take down a viral faked video of Pelosi, looking smashed out of her head. This move has somewhat forced Facebook's hand to maintain the same level of standards for the Zuckerberg video.The video, made by artists Bill Posters and Daniel Howe in collaboration with the advertising company Canny, used footage from a real video back in September 2017 that saw Zuckerberg address Russian election interference on Facebook.According to CNN, the Pelosi video was not a deep fake, as it was made using traditional video editing techniques, unlike the Zuckerberg video that used sophisticated AI that manipulated the CEO's face to make it look as if he said something he didn't. Zuckerberg's voice is replaced with an actor's.According to the Washington Post, Zuckerberg has tried to contact Speaker Pelosi to explain how his company handles misinformation, so far, Pelosi hasn't returned his calls.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 07:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843357/3843357_ECE55D633DC944F282FA4408AA70E6BF_190612_3843357_Deepfake_Zuckerberg_video_tests_Facebook_s_polic_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Facebook, Mark Zuckerberg, Deepfake, deepfake videos, Mark Zuckerberg deepfake video, Instagram leave deepfake Zuckerberg video online, Nancy Pelosi drunk video, debunking, drunk, fake news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843259</guid>
      <title>Gulf of Mexico's 'dead zone' may be largest in history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GULF OF MEXICO  The Gulf of Mexico could have a dead zone almost 8,000 square miles in size due to this year's record-breaking rainfall in the American Midwest, according to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.Citing scientists' predictions, the NOAA says the dead zone could be one of the largest on record. Dead zones, also referred to as hypoxic zones, have low-oxygen levels that are deadly to marine life.These occur as nutrients present in fertilizers, such as nitrogen and phosphorus, are washed into rivers due to annual rainfall. Nutrients present in the river water runoff then cause algae to grow in ocean water, as fresh water doesn't mix with the ocean's due to its density.Louisiana State University ocean ecologist, Nancy Rabalais, told National Geographic that animals such as shrimp and fish will swim away from hypoxic zones when oxygen levels drop below two parts per million.Farmers are starting to adopt practices such as making less use of fertilizers and using more cover crops to decrease nutrient runoff, as reported by National Geographic.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 04:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/12/3843259/3843259_214B6F45C27F4191AEE568967F79229B_190612_3843259_Gulf_of_Mexico_s__dead_zone__may_be_largest_in_h_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dead zone, gulf of mexico, gulf of mexico dead zone, hypoxic zone, American corn belt, gulf of mexico dead zone video, gulf of mexico dead zone 2019, midwest, midwest rainfall, mississippi river, dead zone nutrients runoff, 8000 mile dead zone, hypoxia dead zone, hypoxia gulf of mexico]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844059</guid>
      <title>Police fire rubber bullets at Hong Kong extradition protesters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG  Police goons have fired rubber bullets and tear gas at demonstrators protesting against a new bill that would allow extradition to China. According to the BBC, protesters blocked important roads around government buildings and hurled bricks and projectiles at police. Hong Kongers are worried the new "law" would allow Beijing to target its political opponents and with China's total lack of human rightsthey are right to be concerned. The BBC reported that the CCP's puppet, Hong Kong Chief Executive Carrie Lam, condemned the "organized riots."Officials say 72 people have been injured so far in skirmishes, with two men in critical condition. Of course, the Hong Kong government has said its still backing the bill and it's expected to pass its final rubber stamp vote on June 20. Thank Beijing for that. It has promised legally binding human rights safeguards and other measures it says should allay concerns. Human rights safeguards with Xi Jin-pooh's approval?According to the BBC, the protests have been for the most part peaceful, but ramped up when demonstrators tried to storm government buildings. Unsurprisingly, there's been almost no media coverage of the Hong Kong protests in China. Search results either come up Hong Kong officials have said its courts would have the final say over whether to grant extradition requests, and that suspects accused of political and religious crimes will not be extradited. Let's not be naive, clearly the CCP is the one making all the decisions, and they WILL have the final say.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 11:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/13/3844059/3844059_9FEFE5569F03426DBAE84BB68404F95A_190613_3844059_Police_fire_rubber_bullets_at_Hong_Kong_extradit_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3F5/AA2/3F5AA253B5F5B09DBDCD690A35CBFDA5.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Hong Kong protests, Hong Kong extradition bill, Hong Kong China extradition bill, Hong Kong, Hong Kong demonstrators, HK extradition bill]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843924</guid>
      <title>Ancient human nomads linked to modern populations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANA RIVER, RUSSIA  A new study sheds light on how ancient human migration in Northeastern Siberia is linked to human populations today.  In a new paper published in the journal Nature, scientists studied the population history of Siberia by analyzing DNA from the remains of 34 ancient individuals from sites in northeastern Siberia, northern East Asia, and southwestern Finland that date back 31,600 to 600 years. They then compared them with DNA of ancient and modern humans from Eurasia and North America. Results show the first human groups to arrive in the region were the Ancient North Siberians which are now extinct. Later on, two more migratory waves came from East Asia, the third of which was a group named Neo-Siberians. Modern Siberians can trace their ancestry back to this group.  Scientists also discovered a new group of humans they've named Ancient North Siberians by extracting DNA from teeth that belonged to two unrelated children whose remains were found near Siberia's Yana River at a location called the Yana Rhinoceros Horn Site. They believed these would have ties with early native North Americans, however, they appear to be unrelated. DNA collections indicate native North Americans came as a result of bonding between East Asians and a population distantly linked to Ancient Northern Siberians which occurred roughly 20,000 years ago.  Although the Ancient North Siberians are now long gone, Dr. Martin Sikora, first author of the paper said, "These findings have changed a lot of what we thought we knew about the population history of northeastern Siberia but also what we know about the history of human migration as a whole."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 07:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/13/3843924/3843924_F3048716A6674EA4BE473DD2829F8BAB_190613_3843924_Ancient_human_nomads_linked_to_modern_population_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EF6/6A7/EF66A7D73ED904E71ECABEEED3D2D414.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, human species, ancient humans, new species, ancient species, human ancestors, siberia, Ancient North Siberians, ancient human species]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3843905</guid>
      <title>Sneezing attack causes SUV to flip and catch fire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BELLE MEADE, TENNESSEE   A 42-year-old man rolled his ride when he suddenly broke out into a sneezing frenzy behind the wheel in Tennessee.  ABC 11 reported that the driver, who was in a white Ford SUV, told police that he was traveling down the road when he started sneezing and then just lost control and flipped his car.According to News 2, the allergy attack caused him to run off the road and hit a culvert beside Percy Warner Golf Course.  Thankfully a group of golfers and construction workers acted swiftly and rolled the car back over, allowing the trapped man to get out of the vehicle. The Charlotte Observer reported that just moments after, the vehicle burst into flames that spread along the windshield. By phone, the man told News 2 what had happened, quote "I just started sneezing  my allergies were flaring, and I started sneezing  It felt like my front right tire went out all of a sudden  I was spinning, and it was over on its side."ABC 11 said that the man escaped with barely a scratch.The man continued, "Are you kidding me? I just flipped this car, and I'm walking away with a bruise?"]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 07:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/13/3843905/3843905_2E4C05EC8C71478594719D0B345DB93D_190613_3843905_Sneezing_attack_causes_SUV_to_flip_and_catch_fir_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5A7/9EF/5A79EF45A9807351C7368A1D3F51F089.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man escapes crash after having sneezing attack, sneezing blamed for car crash. Allergy attack causes car crash, car accident, vehicle accident, sneezing car accident, Tennessee, golf course]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844733</guid>
      <title>Oil tanker attacks: US suspects Iran involvement</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GULF OF OMAN  The U.S. government reckons Iran is responsible for two suspected oil tanker attacks in the Gulf of Oman this week, the BBC reports.On Thursday, two oil tankers were sailing through international waters south east of the Strait of Hormuz when a fire broke out onboard. This was followed by an explosion.The Front Altair was carrying 75,000 tons of naptha and was heading from the United Arab Emirates to Taiwan, BBC News reports.The second oil tanker, the Kokuka Courageous, was believed to be carrying around 25,000 tons of methanol. The ship was travelling from Saudi Arabia to Singapore.Citing Iran's state news agency Irna, the BBC reports that the first incident occurred on the Front Altair when it was 46 kilometers off the Iranian port of Jask.The second took place an hour later, when the Kokuka Courageous caught fire around 51 kilometers off Jask.The president of Kokuka Sangyo, the Japanese company that owns Kokuka Courageous, said he believes the ship was hit by a shell. Managers of the vessel added that the ship was damaged "as a result of a suspected attack."Taiwan's state oil refiner CPC Corporation suspects that the Front Altair was hit in a torpedo attack, according to the Guardian. The CPC was chartering the tanker.Citing the vessel's owners, CNN reports all crew members were evacuated safely onto another cargo ship.According to Reuters, U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo told reporters that the U.S. believes Iran was behind the attacks. "This assessment is based on intelligence, the weapons used, the level of expertise needed to execute the operation, recent similar Iranian attacks on shipping, and the fact that no proxy group operating in the area has the resources and proficiency to act with such a high degree of sophistication," Pompeo said, according to Reuters.Iran denies they were involved in what happened. As reported by the BBC, a statement by the Iranian mission to the United Nations, said:  "Iran categorically rejects the U.S. unfounded claim with regard to 13 June oil tanker incidents, and condemns it in the strongest possible terms."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 14:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/14/3844733/3844733_3344D0093F3F417EA3D1B4BE056B90E9_190614_3844733_Oil_tanker_attacks__US_suspects_Iran_involvement_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6E8/531/6E85316F9CC82F2E5B28FE8D7D661773.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Gulf of Oman, Gulf of Oman explosions, Gulf of Oman tanker, Oman, Middle East, Strait of Hormuz, iran, USA, gulf of Oman attack, iran vs usa, iran oil tanker, Kokuka Courageous tanker,  Front Altair]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844609</guid>
      <title>Huawei to build mother Russia's 5G network</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW  Huawei has been taking quite the pounding ever since being blacklisted by President Trump, but it appears mother Russia is throwing them a lifeline.  According to the Verge, the Chinese tech company announced a 5G development deal with Russia's biggest mobile operator MTS. The AP reported that the deal was inked last week in Moscow as Chinese Emperor Winnie the Xi and Russian beefcake bro Vladimir Putin looked on. According to CNN, Huawei has been caught in the escalating trade war between 'Murica and Tiananmazing China. CNN reports Trump has been waging a war against Huawei, by banning it from U.S. 5G networks and cutting it off from American software and components it needs for its smartphones and network equipment business. Washington has been warning its friends to restrict or ban the use of Huawei tech in their 5G networks, because Beijing could use it for spying. Luckily for Huawei, Tootin Putin isn't worried about security concerns. According to CNN, MTS said the deal would cover the development of 5G technologies and the launch of 5G pilot networks in Russia this year and in 2020.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 11:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/14/3844609/3844609_E4500C6BAFD84AC2A8549B5BCAD8D8F2_190614_3844609_Huawei_to_build_mother_Russia_s_5G_network_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61F/289/61F2891DAE45C0B3E0D835151290443F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Russia Huawei 5G deal, Huawei MTS 5G deal, Huawei 5G technology, Huawei blacklisted, Huawei ban]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844431</guid>
      <title>NASA to launch a mission to explore a metal asteroid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  NASA is readying for a mission that will launch in 2022 to explore the metal asteroid Psyche. Scientists think Psyche may once have been a Mars-sized planet that had its outer crust blasted off billions of years ago by violent asteroid collisions, according to NASA's website.Psyche is located in the main asteroid belt in our solar system between Mars and Jupiter. Researchers believe Psyche is composed mostly of iron and nickel, similar to Earth's core.Psyche will carry scientific instruments including a magnetometer to measure the asteroid's magnetic field and a spectrometer to detect what exactly the ancient asteroid is made out of, according to NASA.A multispectral imager will take high-resolution images of Psyche to distinguish between metals and silicates.The probe will be launched in August 2022 and is expected to reach the asteroid by Jan. 31, 2026.Through this mission, scientists hope to gain a better understanding of how our solar system was formed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 07:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/14/3844431/3844431_1120C4100D7545ACBE44A0BC57FB9808_190614_3844431_NASA_to_launch_a_mission_to_explore_a_metal_aste_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7F6/E6C/7F6E6CD4D0FEDD8A40ED881B8E595BBA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa, space, space exploration, nasa space, solar system,  asteroid Psyche, nasa probe, nasa spacecraft, nasa psyche, nasa psyche project, pysche planet, psyche dwarf planet]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844367</guid>
      <title>Paris' plans for Eiffel Tower area revamp unveiled</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  The city of Paris has announced plans to revamp the area around the Eiffel Tower and turn it into a pedestrian-friendly garden.The 72 million euro project was designed by London-based Gustafson Porter + Bowman, according to the Guardian.The plans include, transforming the area's Trocadro Gardens[ac][ad][ae] into a green amphitheater space for tourists.According to French television network France 24, the Pont d'Iena[af][ag] bridge would be turned into a green walkway where pedestrians could walk or cycle across it. The bridge will also connect with gardens on opposite sides of the River Seine[ah][ai].Private vehicles would be restricted, with only public and emergency transport allowed onto the bridge.The second phase of construction, on the opposite side of the tower, will commence after the 2024 Olympics and is expected to be finished in 2030.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 06:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/14/3844367/3844367_1EE32A798F5D4B68A2AAA5F33FFDC43D_190614_3844367_Paris__plans_for_Eiffel_Tower_area_revamp_unveil_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE3/85B/CE385BE1E48737C6F2757174DA9706E1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, eiffel tower, paris eiffel tower, eiffel tower garden, garden renovation france, garden renovation eiffel tower, eiffel tower renovation, eiffel tower revamped, paris garden eiffel tower, paris infrastructure, paris garden, paris walkways, eiffel tower garden project,  Gustafson Porter + Bowman, green design, green space, paris green space, paris green corridor]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844322</guid>
      <title>Chinese guy swallows keys during bender, has them taken out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA  A Chinese man on what must have been one hell of a bender got so blitzed he swallowed his keys, and then totally forgot about it. According to Pear Video, the man apparently was out last Thursday night and throwing 'em back, when at some point his house key and apartment building key fob ended up down the old windpipe. Pear Video reported that he woke up the next morning and felt sick, but had no idea why. If there were only a key to help solve the puzzle. Chinese reports then said the guy got himself to a hospital in Dongguan complaining of chest pains.After an X-ray and endoscopy, Dr Xu Zhe at Dongguan People's Hospital found the keys stuck at the lower part of the dude's esophagus, almost to his stomach. Dr. Xu told reporters the man had been so hammered the night before he didn't even realize he had swallowed them. For some odd reason, he didn't feel any discomfort when the keys were taking a trip down his windpipe. He was placed under general anesthesia, and then had a successful operation to remove the keys.No word if he's gotten into his place yet.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 04:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/14/3844322/3844322_63312C3FE54F418A94CB6F82937394E5_190614_3844322_Chinese_guy_swallows_keys_during_bender__has_the_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EAC/6D3/EAC6D34541E83CEECD11E6E3873175B4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, man swallows keys, man swallows house key, man swallows key fob, Chinese man swallows keys, guy swallows keys]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3844274</guid>
      <title>103-story high glass floor at Willis Tower shatters under visitors' feet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Visitors at the Willis Tower got a sky-high scare after one of the SkyDeck's glass ledges shattered on Monday.According to CNN, the SkyDeck features clear observation boxes 103 stories up, that give tourists spectacular views of Chicago.On Monday, visitors experienced a heartstopping moment after the glass began to crack right under their feet.Witness Jesus Pintado captured the terrifying scene on video, showing the glass floor of the ledge splintered into tiny pieces.It's not the first time a SkyDeck ledge has cracked, either. People were panicking just as hard when the same thing happened in May 2014.The ledge itself can hold up to five tons, and is composed of three layers of glass each about one half inch thick and coated with a protective layer.The Willis Tower told CBS the glass that splintered was the protective layer, which acts more or less like a screen protector. It posed no immediate danger, and was replaced later that night.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 03:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/14/3844274/3844274_D85B3AAC8D22477C89898CD7D75C1EDB_190614_3844274_103_story_high_glass_floor_at_Willis_Tower_shatt_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/822/329/82232942B009393EF0081038FF1EDC76.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Willis Tower, skydeck, glass floor cracks, skydeck ledge, glass cracks, glass floor shatters, Chicago tower, glass observation deck]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3845291</guid>
      <title>Tofu plunges from high-rise, smashes woman's windshield</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIAMUSI, CHINA  Not only is tofu a great source of protein containing all nine essential amino acidsit can also do wonders for your ride. According to Miaopai, a woman from Jiamusi in Heilongjiang province returned to her parked car and found her windshield had been smashed, but not by a rock or some vandals. Instead, on top of the shattered glass was a big old pile of soft, mushy white tofu.Miaopai reported that the owner of the car, a woman named Zhang, thinks the tofu in question took its fatal plunge from one of the high-rise apartment buildings by the parking space. Unfortunately, no surveillance cameras were able to catch the tofu's last moments, so finding its owner may prove to be a bit of a challenge. If only China had some type of tofu-recognition technology in place to catch the bandits. Perhaps all this facial recognition that Beijing is playing around with is barking up the wrong tree. Tofuthat's where it's at.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 02:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/16/3845291/3845291_2F28B28952EA4E56AB0291965B331C03_190616_3845291_Tofu_plunges_from_high_rise__smashes_woman_s_win_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/581/638/58163877295A3FF4DD8B390894157E32.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tofu smashes windshield, tofu smashes car windshield, tofu windshield, falling tofu shatters windshield, falling tofu]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3845896</guid>
      <title>F-35 fighter jets continue to have glitches, other issues : Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  American F-35 fighter jets currently have 13 deficiencies including loss of flight control in certain cases, according to documents acquired by Defense News.The documents reveal that after completing certain unspecified maneuvers, pilots of the F-35B and F-35C fighter jets were not always able to completely control the pitch, yaw and roll of their aircraft.Citing the documents, Defense News reports the two fighter jets are also compelled to limit their airspeed in order to avoid structural damage to the stealth coating.If a tire suddenly blows out on the F-35A and F-35B fighter jets, this could potentially destroy its hydraulic brake lines.F-35C jets may have a green glow appear on their helmet mounted display at times, making it challenging to land on aircraft carriers, according to Defense News.Other issues include the F-35 erroneously reporting that a battery has failed under cold weather conditions and sudden cabin pressure spikes which can cause extreme pain in the ear.Mat Winter, the U.S. Defense Department's F-35 program executive, told Defence News that nine out of the 13 problems are likely to be corrected or receive a downgrade in its status before the government decides to move on with full-rate production at the end of this year.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 09:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/17/3845896/3845896_2E0462A1C20E49DFA768C171BE2F893A_190617_3845896_F_35_fighter_jets_continue_to_have_glitches__oth_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD5/F59/FD5F5979C5AEA8764AF65FB57D82AE85.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, pentagon, F-35, F-35 problems, f35 problems 2019, f 35 fighter jet problems, F-35 program, F-35B, F-35C, F-35 flaws,  F-35 design flaws, pentagon F-35, Lockheed Martin F-35 Lightning II Joint Strike Fighter, Lockheed Martin fighter jets, F-35 weapon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3845882</guid>
      <title>A magnetic field may be keeping Milky Way's black hole at bay</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON   A magnetic field at the center of our galaxy may be keeping a supermassive black hole at bay.According to their website, NASA believes they now know why the supermassive black hole at the center of our galaxy is suspiciously dormant in comparison to others in different galaxies.New research from NASA's Stratospheric Observatory for Infrared Astronomy, or SOFIA, is helping scientists understand the difference between a highly active black hole and a relatively inactive one.The results from SOFIA and its far-infrared camera, or HAWC+, have given them large amounts of data about the magnetic field at the center of the Milky Way and its role in making the Sagittarius A* black hole so tranquil.NASA stated that like most black holes if the magnetic field funnels the gas directly into it, the black hole is active because of its mass consumption of gas. However, the new observations using HAWC+ reveals that the magnetic field at the center of the Milky Way channels the gas so it flows into an orbit around the black hole, making the black hole calmer because it's not ingesting any gas that would ultimately create new stars.Principal investigator and lead author of the study Darren Dowell said, "the spiral shape of the magnetic field channels the gas into an orbit around the black holethis could explain why our black hole is quiet while others are active."According to NASA, the new observations using HAWC+ helps understand how the material in the atmosphere of a supermassive black hole interacts with its host, and also to help to answer the long-established question of why the black hole in the center of our Milky Way is fainter in comparison to those in other galaxies.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 08:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/17/3845882/3845882_F6F6653C3EB44CB6BE78797F1D3D3FA8_190617_3845882_A_magnetic_field_may_be_keeping_Milky_Way_s_blac_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F07/B8D/F07B8DC968F136E6E577DF5AC9669EEE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, NASA, massive black hole, Milkyway galaxy, magnetic field, supermassive black hole stopped, SOFIA, HAWC+, black hole magnetic field, magnetic field black hole, supermassive black hole, space]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3845868</guid>
      <title>Cops used 'reasonable force' in Willie McCoy shooting, says report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VALLEJO, CALIFORNIA  An independent consultant hired by the city of Vallejo has found police use of deadly force in the shooting death of rapper Willie McCoy 'reasonable.'According to the San Francisco Chronicle, the report released on Monday revealed that officers fired 55 shots in 3.5 seconds at McCoy, who sat barely awake in his car outside a Taco Bell. The Guardian reports that the incident sparked outrage on a national level, and prompted  scrutiny of the Vallejo police's frequent use of deadly force, and history of misconduct and abuse.But in the report, paid 'expert' and retired police officer David Blake concluded the 55 rounds fired by six cops in 3.5 seconds was reasonable based on his "training and experience as a range instructor, as well as through applied human factors psychology."He claimed each cop had probable cause to believe McCoy posed an immediate threat, adding that "officers aren't required to wait until a weapon is pointed at them to take the necessary steps to save their lives."The McCoy family has called the report biased, saying it was especially unwarranted since body cam footage revealed officers saying the gun in the car had no magazine in it.  They even commented that even if it were loaded, it likely only had a single bullet. The family's attorney, Melissa Nold, criticized the report and Blake, who she says gets paid to defend the cops when they shoot people. He previously investigated the 2008 Stephon Clark shooting and concluded the officers had probable cause to fire at the unarmed man.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 08:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/17/3845868/3845868_A96EAADC9CCD4916BE91537D0A0BB6E7_190617_3845868_Cops_used__reasonable_force__in_Willie_McCoy_sho_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CC2/CA7/CC2CA7CCC3179BD9F6D9DE4D309D4CEE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Willie McCoy, Willie McCoy shooting, David Blake, Vallejo shooting, Vallejo police station, reasonable force]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3845866</guid>
      <title>Biden lied about marching in the civil rights movement</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW HAMPSHIRE  Presidential candidate and former vice president Joe Biden lied about his involvement in the Civil Rights Movement when he first tested his presidential message to a New Hampshire audience in 1987, according to a report in the New York Times. The report states that despite his advisors reminding him on more than one occasion of one tremendous flaw in his speech, the fact that he never actually marched during the Civil Rights Movement, he assured them that he understood  but kept telling the story anyway.The New York Times also reported that his rashness as a candidate caught up with him by that September as he was also accused of plagiarizing his speeches. And according to the Los Angeles Times, Biden exaggerated his academic achievements during his campaign in New Hampshire, saying he "ended up in the top half" of his class in law school at Syracuse, although records indicate he finished near the bottom.The New York Times report continued, quoting Biden as saying: "I've done some dumb things  and I'll do dumb things again." during a stop-the-bleeding news conference at the Capitol.Thirty-two years later and Biden's back in the race for the third time and it seems he will say and do just about anything to win.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 08:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/17/3845866/3845866_6BED7B3DC81347A0BFA0670671666514_190617_3845866_Biden_lied_about_marching_in_the_civil_rights_mo_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/283/207/2832074E33A914473BBF3A0D7F4C0DAC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Joe Biden, Biden caught lying about marching in the Civil Rights Movement, Civil Rights Movement, Presidential Elections, 2020, Joe Biden lying, Biden lies about marching in Civil Rights Movement, Presidential speech]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846562</guid>
      <title>Ex-Army soldier opens fire outside Dallas federal courthouse</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DALLAS  A masked gunman was fatally shot on Monday after open firing on a federal building in Dallas.The Dallas Morning News reports that according to witnesses, gunman Brian Clyde parked his car at a street corner in front of the Earle Cabell Federal Building in Dallas.He then ran and began shooting at the building at 8:40 a.m.According to the publication, security personnel on the first floor pushed people to the ground as Clyde fired shots outside.The 22-year-old former army soldier was shot while exchanging gunfire with federal officers who responded to the incident. He died at the scene.Police inspected Clyde's 2003 Nissan Altima, and found a suspicious device, which they then detonated using controlled explosions.Authorities say they are looking into a motive for the attack, and are actively looking into Clyde's social media presence.His Facebook page was taken down Monday afternoon, but online posts included rants about the U.S. government, and photos of ammunition, according to CBS DFW.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 10:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/18/3846562/3846562_5DB3ECE4BBCE48A3AB5A72DE7369EAEB_190618_3846562_Ex_Army_soldier_opens_fire_outside_Dallas_federa_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F1C/306/F1C30684EEE6A48D855D8F0B359C0309.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, dallas court shooting, dallas courthouse shooting, dallas shooting, dallas federal building shooting, dallas federal building, earle cabell building, brian clyde, army veteran]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846485</guid>
      <title>Shoppers run for their lives as Chinese escalator crumbles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LUZHOU, GUANGXI / CHINA  Yet again, a Chinese escalator has tried to kill someone, and unfortunately this isn't' out of the ordinary.According to Sina, on June 15th, a shopping mall in Luzhou, Guangxi saw two shoppers run in absolute terror as a shoddy escalator collapsed behind them.The video from the mall's surveillance cameras shows the pair of shoppers stepping onto the escalator only to see it crumble beneath their feet, forcing them to run upwards to safety.The escalator is currently being repaired. Fortunately, no injuries were caused by the incident.Unfortunately, not everyone is this lucky. The South China Morning Post reported on another escalator incident back in 2015 involving a 30-year-old mother and her two-year-old son.The horrific incident saw the mother push her son to safety before she was pulled into the exposed mechanism and tragically killed.Of all the things to be made in China, escalators aren't one to take a risk on.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 09:16:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/18/3846485/3846485_C851B57E9E134AAE9D727BDC032B7926_190618_3846485_Shoppers_run_for_their_lives_as_Chinese_escalato_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BFA/EEF/BFAEEF93686C5450553F5625F5075A35.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, Chinese, China escalator accident, China escalator mall accident, Chinese escalator mall, accidents, Chinese escalator accidents, tragedy, incident, Chinese escalator incident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847169</guid>
      <title>Woman trashed apartment before falling 16-stories down trash chute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON  A woman in Portland is in the hospital after trashing her neighbor's luxury condo and then throwing herself down a garbage chute from the 16th floor.Steven Lofton told The Oregonian that the woman had been in a 'manic and crazed' state when she pounded on his door around lunch on Monday.When he opened the door, she rushed in and went wild, throwing and breaking things and absolutely trashing his apartment.She eventually ran back out to the hallway and began physically fighting with her boyfriend, whose condo is on the same floor. At this point, Lofton says he closed the door and called the cops.Police believe the woman then climbed into the garbage chute on her own, and proceeded to plunge 16 stories down.Rescuers later found her unconscious and with a bad head injury in the building's trash collection area, and took her to the hospital. Fire officials had no update on her condition as of Tuesday afternoon.According to Lofton, the unnamed woman didn't live in the building, but was known on the floor since she and her man had loud fights and physical altercations.Residents had raised their concerns about the couple to management several times, though it seemed nothing had been done to address the issue.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3847169/3847169_0953E328299E49EC934D34979346048A_190619_3847169_Woman_trashed_apartment_before_falling_16_storie_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AEF/744/AEF744101D885F8B2E241E9ED4C34F80.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, woman falls into garbage chute, garbage chute fall, manic woman, crazed woman, the civic portland, woman trashes luxury apartment]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847159</guid>
      <title>What are ghost nets?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONOLULU  The International Union for Conservation of Nature, or IUCN, describes ghost nets as a silent menace threatening the world's marine species. Here's what makes them so bad. Ghost nets as commercial fishing nets that have been abandoned, lost or discarded at sea.They are made from a strong plastic and can remain in the water for a long time.Ghost nets float with ocean currents and trap plastic and other debris, as well as fish and crustaceans  a process known as ghost fishing.Fish caught in the nets often act as bait, luring larger predators like turtles, sharks and dolphins, who eventually become entangled themselves.When a drifting net becomes too heavy due to its catch, it may eventually sink to the seabed, where smaller ocean dwellers feed on the entangled creatures.This, along with natural decomposition, reduces the weight of the net so that it floats back up to the surface, where it then restarts its destructive cycle.In addition to this, ghost nets can also cause damage by smothering reefs and introducing invasive species and parasites into coral reef habitats.The United Nations Environment Programme estimates that over 600 to 800,000 metric tonnes of ghost gear enters the ocean annually. Some are lost during storms, and some dumped deliberately.Nick Mallos, director of the Trash Free Seas Program at Ocean Conservancy, says ghost nets are the most deadly form of marine litter.Efforts being made to lessen their impact include clearing drifting nets and promoting the use of biodegradable fishing gear. But there is no quick-fix solution, and certain practices, such as illegal fishing, remain a block to progress.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 11:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3847159/3847159_39612373543C446B93F92B378ED89577_190619_3847159_What_are_ghost_nets__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9F0/170/9F0170135D7AD40E8956DBCB82209C66.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ghost net, ghost nets, ghost fishing, silent killer, fishing nets, marine animals, commercial fishing, marine life]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847054</guid>
      <title>Domino's to use self-driving vehicles for pizza delivery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON  Domino's is teaming up with Nuro, a robotics company, to use automated vehicles to make pizza deliveries in Houston, Texas starting later this year.According to a press release by Domino's, the unmanned car is called R2. It will be used to make deliveries to a selected number of customers who place their orders online.Customers would be able to track the driverless vehicle on Domino's app. Once the pizza is delivered, customers would be able to unlock the self-driving pizza delivery pod via a PIN code provided by the company. This isn't the first time Domino been testing out autonomous vehicle technology.According to the Houston Chronicle, the company had previously tested out self-driving cars, drones and even rovers in an effort to make automated pizza delivery a reality.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 09:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3847054/3847054_1E34546495A0410DBD4E14169FCB9D9D_190619_3847054_Domino_s_to_use_self_driving_vehicles_for_pizza__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0C4/A50/0C4A505230B5642A19C6F763FC73E495.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Domino's, dominos technology, Domino's pizza, Domino's pizza self driving car, domino's pizza self driving delivery car, domino's pizza self driving delivery, domino's pizza self pizza delivery,  dominos technology, domino's pizza technology, high tech delivery car, self driving vehicles 2019]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847025</guid>
      <title>Granddaughter goes 
no. 2 on public bus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING    Asia One reported that there have been many occurrences in recent years of Chinese tourists causing outrage for letting their children relieve themselves in public and this time... it's no different.According to Asia One, two Chinese grandparents in Beijing pulled out a portable potty and plastic bag to let their granddaughter excrete on the bus.The dumping of the child's feces into the plastic tub caused outrage and resulted in a quarrel between passengers when a woman became offended by the public defecation and smell. In the video, the woman and the grandparents draw their phones to film one another while the act is in midstream.The woman posted the video to Weibo and explained how the grandparents refused to take their granddaughter off the bus. The woman posted, 'at first I said to myself to let it go since she was a little kid after all. But later I had to complain as there was a smell. The old couple began to curse me and criticized me for not showing sympathy for a kid.'According to the South China Morning Post, netizens were divided in opinion and expressed their objection on both sides.In the same report, it stated that there was a similar incident In February when a woman was photographed letting her son urinate on the floor of the Forbidden City in Beijing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 09:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3847025/3847025_5A6515A32A6C498294D2BA132CDA1F9B_190619_3847025_Granddaughter_goes__no__2_on_public_bus_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/063/EAB/063EAB6FD8E1FBC625D0D084784BD49B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, girls poo's on a public bus, Chinese public urination, Chinese tourists, Chinese defecate in public, toilet, Chinese girl poops in public, public defication, poop, chinese go to toilet in public]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846998</guid>
      <title>A Chinese woman rides cows because horses cost too much</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANCHENG, JIANGSU / CHINA     According to The Beijing News, an equestrian Chinese woman has started riding cows, because horses are too expensive.The woman surnamed Xue from Jiangsu province says she loves to ride horses but they cost too much money, so of course, she switched to cows.Xue noticed that two of her three family cows were quite fast. She now trains them first in the morning by taking them for a steady walk.She says that she practices riding her cows every day and even places weighted sacks over the cows, sacks that she makes sure weighs more than she does.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 08:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3846998/3846998_F4610C91137E4A7EA2A1345CC50503C9_190619_3846998_A_Chinese_woman_rides_cows_because_horses_cost_t_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CC2/FCC/CC2FCCBA84C7A1D82CA1C8458F80C269.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese woman rides cows, Chinese woman rides cows because horses are too expensive, Asia, China, Chinese woman. Chinese woman cow skills, Jiangsu]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846857</guid>
      <title>Cryptocurrency mining could be contributing to climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MUNICH  New research from the Technical University of Munich has found that the amount of computing power needed to mine bitcoin produces roughly the same amount of carbon emissions as a major city like Las Vegas.Bitcoin miners have to solve many complex mathematical problems to generate bitcoins, according to the study. This process requires large amounts of electrical power, in turn increasing carbon emissions.The scientists determined that the virtual currency consumed about 46 Terawatt hours of energy as of November 2018. This is equivalent to around 5,650,411 tonnes of coal."They wanted to find out where the cryptocurrency miners were located, how much energy was consumed and how much carbon emissions were produced as a result.The study found that 68 percent of bitcoin mining takes place in Asia, with 17 percent taking place in Europe and 15 percent in North America. Researchers estimate that mining cryptocurrency creates more than 22 million tons of carbon emissions per year.This is roughly equivalent to the amount of carbon emissions produced by developing nations such as Sri Lanka or major world cities such as Vienna or Las Vegas.In a Technical University of Munich press release, lead author of the study and TUM PhD candidate, Christian Stoll explained that there were bigger factors contributing to climate change.He added, "However, the carbon footprint is big enough to make it worth discussing the possibility of regulating cryptocurrency mining in regions where power generation is especially carbon-intensive."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 04:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3846857/3846857_9B516C2C10C94D9588C589875DD31ED9_190619_3846857_Cryptocurrency_mining_could_be_contributing_to_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5C0/C48/5C0C48A1C1C8842CC4EECF3989FFAA0E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cryptocurrency, money transfer, virtual currency, bitcoin climate change, climate change, bitcoin mining, bitcoin climate impact, bitcoin accelerates climate change, bitcoin mining climate, bitcoin mining climate change, bitcoin transactions, bitcoin processing power , cryptocurrency mining, cryptocurrency climate change]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846812</guid>
      <title>The U.S. is sending 1,000 more troops to the Middle East</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIDDLE EAST  The Pentagon is set to send 1,000 additional soldiers to the Middle East amid rising tensions with Iran, CNN reports.In a statement from the U.S. Department of Defense, Acting Secretary of Defense Patrick Shanahan announced that the troops would address "air, naval, and ground-based threats in the Middle East."The announcement comes after two oil tankers were attacked in the Gulf of Oman last week. The U.S. suspects Iran was responsible, claims that Tehran denies.Shanahan said, "The recent Iranian attacks validate the reliable, credible intelligence we have received on hostile behavior by Iranian forces and their proxy groups that threaten United States personnel and interests across the region."The deployment would include troops for additional surveillance and intelligence gathering, The Associated Press reports, citing U.S. officials.The move is part of a military package shown to U.S. leaders last month that includes Patriot missile batteries, aircraft and ships, according to the Associated Press.Shanahan downplayed the announcement and said "the United States does not seek conflict with Iran." He explained the action was taken to protect U.S. military personnel and interests in the region.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 03:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3846812/3846812_8493A926B31A4F8AB52567ACA4CDCDB3_190619_3846812_The_U_S__is_sending_1_000_more_troops_to_the_Mid_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/335/017/335017CE10AC0B3C770D3B805FB54C67.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, USA, Iran, Middle East, US forces, US military, iran vs usa, usa middle east, usa vs middle east, usa sending troops to middle east, us iran, us troops, us troops middle east, us iran latest news]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846802</guid>
      <title>Faulty fire switch on Boeing Dreamliners spark safety concerns</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C.  A crucial fire-fighting system on Boeing's fleet of 787 Dreamliners was found to have the potential to malfunction, sparking fears among airline pilots.The Guardian reports that Boeing warned airlines using the 787 Dreamliner that the switch used to extinguish engine fires has failed in a 'small number' of instances.According to Boeing's airline alert, long-term heating can cause the fire switch to remain locked so it can't be used to release the two extinguishers in each engine.Boeing claims the risk of fires is low. But a pilot told The Observer that should the switch malfunction during an engine fire, there's no manual override to deploy the extinguishers, and therefore no way of putting the fire out.The Federal Aviation Administration admitted the malfunction is a risk to the flying public, but decided not to ground the fleet. Instead, it issued an airworthiness directive and required airlines to inspect the switches every 30 days.According to the Observer, the pilot community says Boeing's attitude to the risk is upsetting, especially in light of recent issues with the 737 Max. The FAA has declined to comment on the pilots' concerns, saying only that it invited feedback from the airline industry back when its directive was proposed in February.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 03:15:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3846802/3846802_1749B041057D43C59C3EF7558E9A5E32_190619_3846802_Faulty_fire_switch_on_Boeing_Dreamliners_spark_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/674/581/674581E167E1F8B93928CB1270F71D2C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Boeing, Boeing 787, B787, Dreamliner, Boeing Dreamliner, Boeing safety, Boeing safety, Boeing safety fears, FAA]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3846785</guid>
      <title>NASA to use Starshade technology to hunt for new exoplanets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  NASA has announced plans to use starshade technology to search for new planets beyond our solar system.Two spacecraft would be used in a future starshade mission, according to the space agency's website.One would be a space telescope that would look for planets while the other probe would be carrying the starshade.NASA said the starshade technology would be used to block starlight. This would allow the telescope to get a clear view of any new orbiting planets in space.The spacecraft carrying the starshade would fly 40,000 kilometers in front of the planet-hunting telescope.NASA explained that this technology would only work if the two spacecraft stay are aligned to within one meter of each other. If there is a greater distance between the two, this would allow light from star to seep into the space telescope's view.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 02:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/19/3846785/3846785_9A81B87A61544B059318B2A9F7325328_190619_3846785_NASA_to_use_Starshade_technology_to_hunt_for_new_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/492/229/49222912E9B810A5D9E4C3459F7BEF5E.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, nasa, space, exoplanet, starshade, nasa starshade, nasa starshade project, starshade technology, nasa alien planet discovery, future starshade mission, starshade nasa, WFIRST, coronagraph, space exploration, starshade mission, space technology, starshade in space, nasa starshade technology]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847823</guid>
      <title>Tesla drivers keep falling asleep behind the wheel on autopilot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA  If you're one of those people who has trouble falling asleep, you might want to consider getting a Tesla. According to Electrek, several different Tesla drivers have been caught snoozing at the wheel while on Autopilotbecause what else are you going to do if you don't have to steer. NBC 4 reported that last week a driver was caught on camera completely passed out cruising down the 405 Freeway in L.A. with something tied around the steering wheel.   Electrek reports that the "something" was probably a device designed to trick Autopilot into sensing that someone is gripping the wheel. The man must have counted some serious sheep because he was on self snooze for at least 30 miles. Another slumbering Tesla driver was then caught last Friday driving in the Bay Area during heavy rush hour traffic with sleep mode fully engaged. The 16-second clip was posted up on Reddit. Tesla drivers are told that they should remain alert and ready to take control at anytime while using Autopilot.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 13:39:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847823/3847823_BF3900B800694BFE8E022F7A168B8C74_190620_3847823_Tesla_drivers_keep_falling_asleep_behind_the_whe_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DD4/423/DD442347BE429B700FD1715AE34D0E2C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Tesla driver, Tesla autopilot, Tesla driver sleeping, Tesla driver sleeping on autopilot]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847814</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman arrested for stomping on sea turtle nest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  A Chinese woman was arrested by Miami Beach police on Saturday morning for being a cold, heartless hag and charged with molesting or harassing marine turtles or their eggs. According to the Miami Herald, 41-year-old Yaqun Lu, who is currently living in Michigan, was seen by police and bystanders stomping all over the nest with her bare stanky-old feet.The Miami Herald reported that the nest was in a closed-off, protected area ringed by a double perimeter of eight wooden stakes and yellow tape. There was also a sign that said "Do Not Disturb" posted by the nest. So what did Lu do? She walked up to the nest, grabbed a wooden stake and started jabbing at the nest and then proceed to step all over the nest like a truly worthless human being. According to the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission, sea turtles are federally protected by the U.S. Endangered Species Act of 1973 and Florida statutes that make it illegal to harm or harass sea turtles, their nests or hatchlings. According to the Miami Herald report, Lu was taken to jail and is being held on a $5,000 bond. Miami Beach po po said the Miami-Dade State Attorney's Office and the Chinese consulate in Houston were notified of Lu's arrest. And as for the turtle eggs? Police say they were undamaged by Lu's despicable act.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 12:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847814/3847814_C7A6DD2D127747B18DC5A432372A3244_190620_3847814_Chinese_woman_arrested_for_stomping_on_sea_turtl_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/331/20D/33120DEBD95DF6B4AABD070A9A5293F1.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese woman, Chinese woman arrested, Chinese woman steps on turtle nest, Chinese woman turtle nest Florida]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847673</guid>
      <title>Alabama cops rescue methed-out attack squirrel during bust</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATHENS ALABAMA  Cops carrying out a drug bust in Alabama on Monday found not only a bunch of Breaking Bad and ammo on the property, but also an 'attack squirrel.' According to AL.com, deputies found the bushy-tailed critter inside a cage. They'd been informed prior to the raid that the animal was being fed speed to keep it aggressive.The Sheriff said in a press release that there was no way to safely test the little rascal for meth, so officers followed advice from state conservation officials and released it in a nearby wooded area.A man on the property was arrested on drug charges, but the actual resident, 35-year-old Mickey Paulk, wasn't home during the search.He's still on the lam, with outstanding warrants charging him for possession of a controlled substance, possession of drug paraphernalia, and possession of firearms.On Tuesday, Paulk came out on Facebook Live to deny the attack squirrel charges, saying he never fed it ice since it would've been fatal.He also appeared in the video petting a squirrel, claiming it's the same one deputies released.The cops say they can't really confirm this, but if a man can have one squirrel, he sure as heck can have two, maybe more, so who knows?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 10:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847673/3847673_379C85AF8B634B73BA95041A9716C80D_190620_3847673_Alabama_cops_rescue_methed_out_attack_squirrel_d_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5FA/6DA/5FA6DAA20D06E2CFD18C353EA934A741.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, attack squirrel, pet squirrel, squirrel on drugs, squirrel on speed, methed up squirrel, drugged squirrel, viral video]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847641</guid>
      <title>Facebook to launch controversial cryptocurrency by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA  The social network is coming out with a Bitcoin-style cryptocurrency, and let's just say not everyone is on board.Facebook on Tuesday announced plans to launch its own cryptocurrency in 2020. The digital currency, called Libra, is backed by a reserve of financial assets, making it less volatile than other cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin.The social giant won't have direct control over Libra. Instead, it will be serviced by the Libra Association, an independent nonprofit headquartered in Switzerland. Its founding members include companies like Uber, Visa, MasterCard, and PayPal, among others.""The association's main functions are to validate transactions on the Libra blockchain, and manage the reserve the digital currency is tied to.A digital wallet for the new cryptocurrency, called Calibra, is also being launched, and will be available on Messenger, WhatsApp, and as a standalone app.Calibra will allow users to send Libra to anyone with a smartphone, and in the future may be used to pay for purchases on the app or to various vendors for day-to-day transactions.According to Facebook, the Libra blockchain is pseudonymous, allowing users to hold more than one address not linked to their real-world identity.It claims financial data on Libra transactions will be kept separate from user ad profiles, and that Calibra account information will not be used to improve ad targeting on Facebook-owned platforms.With Facebook's track record thus far, it's understandable that more than a few are wary of this new venture. CNBC reports that Democratic Rep. Maxine Waters said in a statement that the company is "continuing its unchecked expansion and extending its reach into the lives of its users."Citing a lack of regulatory framework for cryptocurrency, she has requested the company pause work on Libra until Congress and regulators can examine the issues and take action.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 09:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847641/3847641_BF860B4C05A74E52BE9051FD644DB3EC_190620_3847641_Facebook_to_launch_controversial_cryptocurrency__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B9E/208/B9E208760F1F30C49AF9B23EED780173.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, libra, facebook libra, cryptocurrency, facebook cryptocurrency, facebook digital currency, libra cryptocurrency, calibra, calibra digital wallet, facebook calibra, bitcoin]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847552</guid>
      <title>Lame Chinese parents sue tattoo parlor for son's ink</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGSHAN, CHINA  Parents from eastern China successfully sued a tattoo parlor for getting their teenage son kicked out of school for caking his body in ink and for what they say, infringing on his rights.The South China Morning Post reported that a court in Jiangshan, Zhejiang province ordered the parlor to pay out over 20,000 yuan or $2,900 in compensation.The parlor had to return the 1,000 yuan the boy paid for the tattoos, 5,000 yuan for medical fees, and 15,000 yuan in compensation for apparent mental "loss."The unnamed guy got his first tattoo in 2016 of some super cool and definitely not tacky dragons and demons, and by September 2017 his school demanded he gets them removed, concerned that his image would have, quote "a major impact on the appearance of the school."The dad of mini Ozzy Osbourne said he'd hoped that introducing his fist to face several times would prevent more tattoos.The son said, "the more they beat me, the more tattoos I want', a counterproductive walloping, who would've guessed it."Last year the Chinese Communist Party saw a campaign to clean up society and told the police to watch out for people with animal tattoos and quote, "exaggerated" jewelry because they were, "typical of black evil forces".]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 08:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847552/3847552_26D3240F5DAE45419946E157758D2B23_190620_3847552_Lame_Chinese_parents_sue_tattoo_parlor_for_son_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese parents sue tattoo parlor for getting their son kicked out of school, Chinese parents sue tattoo artist, communist party, China, Chinese, Asia, Tattoo   sued, court rules in favor of Chinese parents who sue tattoo parlor, Chinese parents, tattoos]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847460</guid>
      <title>Uber unveils first look
at flying taxi, uber air</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MISSION BAY, SAN FRANSICO   On Tuesday the ridesharing company for the first time offered a look at the inside of its aviation product, Uber Air.On its website, Uber says Uber Air is envisioned as a zero-emission electric air vehicle service, available at the push of a button and created by the company in a bid to ease road congestion.According to the Verge, the interior was designed in partnership with French aerospace company Safran.Four passenger seats are turned outwards to the window in rows of two. Behind the second row is room for storing passenger luggage.The craft is illuminated in blue light and, according to Forbes, it has seats upholstered in aerospace-grade 'ultra leather,' a tough, low-friction material for passengers to easily slide in and out of.According to Forbes, initially, the designers had envisioned a cabin more fitting to the customer's needs with charging points, cupholders, and digital screens. But Ian Scoley, a vice president at Safran's design studio, told Forbes: 'We realized for an 8-minute flight, that's all irrelevant.' Uber states on its website that it aims to demonstrate flights in 2020 and for the service to become commercially available in 2023.Dallas and Los Angeles will be the first places to offer this service commercially, with Melbourne being the first city outside of the U.S. to host trails.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 05:48:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847460/3847460_8CEEFB6272D04773A5F16C5D3ECCD934_190620_3847460_Uber_unveils_first_look_at_flying_taxi__uber_air_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F35/0A8/F350A8FC36BDF9F7BA869599AA17671B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Uber, Uber Air, Uber Air taxi, Uber Air vehicle, zero emissions, Safran, Uber driver, Safran aerospace, public transportation, aviation, electric vehicle, road congestion, traffic]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847448</guid>
      <title>Man gets tangled by customs for 34 singing finches in hair curlers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK  A man got tangled up with customs officials at JFK Airport on Sunday for trying to smuggle 34 singing finches from Guyana into 'Muricastuffed in hair curlers.NBC 4 New York reports that according to a complaint filed by federal prosecutors in Brooklyn, 39-year-old Francis Gurahoo of Connecticut hatched a hair-brained scheme to sneak dozens of finches in his carry-on. Prosecutors say the little birds are used in singing contests in Brooklyn and Queens where bets are placed on to see which finch has the best Bieber-esque pipes. According to the complaint, contests were held in public places like parks where two finches would karaoke the crap out of themselves in front of a judge who picks the best voice. The complaint states that birdbrain HATCHED a plan to sell his suitcase of finches for around $100,000, which comes out to about $3,000 for one tiny singer.  Unfortunately there was no word if Bird Boxhead was planning on HAWKING the 34 hair curlers too.           According to CNN, U.S. Customs and Border Protection says it nabbed smugglers carrying almost 200 finches in airports in 2018.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 05:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847448/3847448_1B0DC1E63E0849639A55FFB05DA8DF74_190620_3847448_Man_gets_tangled_by_customs_for_34_singing_finch_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E7D/BC7/E7DBC77ECF1F43B66E9A8D7AC97A55B7.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, singing finches, finches, finch singing contests, Brooklyn finch singing, Queens finch contests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3847443</guid>
      <title>Cop saves suicidal jumper with kind words and a hug</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHANDLER, ARIZONA  A 26-year-old man who climbed over a highway overpass railing with intent to jump is luckily still around thanks to a kind-hearted officer. According to the Chandler police, the man had climbed over a protective railing on a pedestrian bridge spanning the Price Freeway when Officer A. Little arrived on scene. Police bodycam footage of the incident on the evening of March 28, 2019 was posted to Facebook by the Chandler Police Department.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 05:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/20/3847443/3847443_5A49F908F16D4CEA9A43D5989B4CC2AD_190620_3847443_Cop_saves_suicidal_jumper_with_kind_words_and_a__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC5/07D/DC507D7187696B8B6F3155D1E875ACFC.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, good cop, cop saves jumper, cop saves the day, nice cop, cop saves jumper hug]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848464</guid>
      <title>Winnie the Xi in Pyongyang to kick it with Kim Jong-fats</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG  Emperor Winnie the Xi popped over to Pyongyang on Thursday and was treated to a 21-gun salute at the airport and a whole bunch of balloons. According to the BBC, President Pooh's trip marks the first Chinese state visit to North Korea in 14 years. The BBC reports this is the fifth time the two dictators have kicked it together in 15 months, but the first pow wow to take place in the funner Korea. The two pals are expected to chat about economics and nukes. According to the failing New York Times, Pooh and Fatty are engaged in separate disputes with President Trump. China and 'Murica have been going at it over trade, while Washington has a problem with Pyongyang's nuclear weapons. The fake news media went on to say American officials expect Xi to try and play middleman by forcing Kim on the nuclear issue to gain leverage with Trump before next week's G20 in Japan.  According to the BBC, tens of thousands of peopleno doubt by their own free will  lined the streets to welcome King Xi to North Korea on Thursday morning. China's official propaganda arm Xinhua news said the two fun-loving leaders met for talks, but provided nothing else. Everyone's coming out swinging, but who will be the last man standing?]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 15:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/21/3848464/3848464_1998A6B5BD76467AB914980D1CB929B9_190621_3848464_Winnie_the_Xi_in_Pyongyang_to_kick_it_with_Kim_J_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3AF/215/3AF215C2D0940F99C38CC9CC15331E80.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, North Korea, Xi Jinping North Korea trip, Xi Jinping in Pyongyang, China North Korea relationship, Xi and Trump, Kim and Trump]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848399</guid>
      <title>Arctic Ocean to get new underwater fiber optic cables</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARCTIC  Finland-based Fiber optic infrastructure company Cinia and Russian telecommunications operator MegaFon have joined hands to build a fiber optic cable across the Arctic Ocean.The Arctic Fiber project is planned to be launched in three phases.As per Submarine Cable Networks, there would be a fiber optic cable line between Nome and Prudhoe Bay in Alaska in Phase 1. During Phase 2, the cable would be extended west into Asia, down to China and Japan. In Phase 3, the cable would be branched into the Lowest Northwest Passage into Canada and onto the United Kingdom.According to IEEE Spectrum, the cables would reduce latency between European, Asian and North American users.The magazine notes that there are other undersea cables stretching across the northern Atlantic to Europe, then through the Mediterranean. They cut across the Indian Ocean and go up through the South China Sea before finally spanning the Pacific to the U.S. west coast.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 12:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/21/3848399/3848399_1EBF2847AA6541A2939D7464A0BB0469_190621_3848399_Arctic_Ocean_to_get_new_underwater_fiber_optic_c_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C77/386/C77386C4FE54DB0845DBAA613179027B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Arctic, arctic ice melting, arctic ice melting news, climate change, arctic cables, arctic cable route, fiber optic cable route arctic, Cinia, MegaFon, arctic fiber optic cable, Arctic Connect Cable, arctic telecommunications cable, arctic sea, arctic undersea cable infrastructure, arctic undersea cable, arctic fiber project, undersea infrastructure, arctic ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848394</guid>
      <title>Honeybee colonies on the decline in the U.S., report finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLLEGE PARK, MARYLAND  A nationwide U.S. survey has found that bee colonies are dying off due to harsh winters.The report by Bee Informed Partnership, a non-profit group led by the University of Maryland, surveyed around 4,700 beekeepers managing around 320,000 bee colonies during the 2018 to 2019 winter season.Researchers found that beekeepers lost an estimated 37.7 percent of honeybee colonies in the past year alone.This is the highest number of winter losses recorded by the non-profit group for honey bees ever since they started 13 years ago.Entomologists from the group told the Guardian that parasites such as varroa mites could be causing an increase in colony losses due to the viruses they carry.Adding that, pesticides used to remove the mites seem to be becoming less effective.Beekeepers have been making efforts to split healthy bee colonies in order to duplicate them, according to the newspaper.Other problems beekeepers need to deal with include bees dying off due to disease, pesticide use and habitat loss.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 12:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/21/3848394/3848394_5411A46433594CE0936075799EEC4318_190621_3848394_Honeybee_colonies_on_the_decline_in_the_U_S___re_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/50E/149/50E1496A6CBC5F3F2F3104E8B78AA4FA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Colony Collapse Disorder, CCD, honey bees, bees, honeybee colonies, bee population, bee population 2019, bee population decline, beekeepers, US beekeepers, honeybees decline US, bees decline stats, bee population decreasing, what is happening to the bee population, honey bee population decline]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848222</guid>
      <title>Bad phone posture leads to 'horn bone' growth in skull</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA  New research from Australia has found that excess usage of smartphones causes a horn-like bone spur to grow at the back of the skull.These bones spurs, also known as enthesophytes, are abnormal bony projections that can form at the attachment of a tendon or ligament.The University of the Sunshine Coast study found that the bone spurs were 10 to 30 millimeters thick.Scientists sampled more than 1200 people between the ages of 18 to 30 and found that around 41 percent of the participants had developed a bony lump at the back of their skull.Further testing such as MRI scans and blood tests were performed. These confirmed that the bone spurs were not a result of genetic factors or inflammation.Enthesophytes are typically seen in older people with poor posture and are the bones response to stress, according to the study.Researchers explained that in this case the abnormal growth forms due to long-term pressure on the skeleton, as the head shifts forwards while we use smartphones for extended periods.According to the study, the bone deformation could cause chronic pain. Carrying the head forward also causes other problems such as neck stiffness and headaches.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 09:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/21/3848222/3848222_885BD7C267CB48DDB6236E620B9A3D2E_190621_3848222_Bad_phone_posture_leads_to__horn_bone__growth_in_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AFB/282/AFB282448D500425F1A9B7A5D982A6A2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, australia, smartphones, tablets ,smartphone usage, smartphone usage  effects, bad effects of smartphone,  technology effects on skull, horn-like bone growth, human evolution, skull deformation, human skeleton, effects of technology on human skull, human skeleton evolution, bone growth]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3848938</guid>
      <title>Zoo money stolen by armed robbers, not eaten by gorilla</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KANO, NIGERIA  The Nigerian po-po is dismissing claims that $22,000 in zoo funds ended up as gorilla chow, saying the news is 100% fake, since the zoo doesn't even have a gorilla.Reuters reports that when 6.8 million Naira, or about $22 grand, disappeared from the Kano Zoological Gardens in northern Nigeria, local media went wild reporting that a cash-eating gorilla was the culprit.In reality, the perps who made off with the zoo's gate fees were armed robbers, which, given the country's widespread corruption, isn't really uncommon.The zoo's managing director said there isn't a single gorilla at the zoo. Even if there was, it's not like a monkey could just break into a safe and pull off a heist. It's likely the tall tale was cooked up by the hooligans to cover up their theft.Speaking of hooligans, the Daily Post reports that 10 zoo staff members are being investigated by police, and have already been arrested and detained.Amazingly, it's not the first time a crime was pinned on a nonexistent animal culprit. Last year, a Nigerian clerk got suspended after telling auditors a snake ate $100,000 in cash.Not the most convincing liars, these ones.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 17:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/23/3848938/3848938_4AB0D0968A6342589D3929662D3ADBD4_190623_3848938_Zoo_money_stolen_by_armed_robbers__not_eaten_by__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/766/698/766698A07141921313600E1221612413.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cash eating gorilla, money eating gorilla, gorilla steals cash, gorilla steals money, rogue gorilla, armed robbery, junk journalism, fake news, kano gorilla, nigeria zoo robbery]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849773</guid>
      <title>Florida city gives in to hackers' $600,000 ransom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIVIERA BEACH, FLORIDA  Some cyber criminals are getting one heck of a payday thanks to the desperate folks of Riviera Beach, Florida. According to CBS12, a local government employee made the mistake of clicking on a malicious email link in early June that ended up paralyzing the entire city's computer systems.The outage forced the police and fire departments to go analog and write down hundreds of daily 911 calls. Fixing and insuring the computers will cost upwards of a million bucks, so in desperation, Riviera Beach commissioners voted to use the city's insurance to pay the ransom of 65 Bitcoins, which comes out to about $592,000.Assuming the criminals don't double cross them, the city will regain access to data that was encrypted in the attack.Even with their ransom-paying plans, Riviera Beach says they're still planning to investigate the attack. Yeah, a lot of good that does.Either way, you can be sure hackers all over America are going to take this as encouragement to hack.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 15:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/24/3849773/3849773_81BCCF884CB64885863CC2CCBAA1CA8A_190624_3849773_Florida_city_gives_in_to_hackers___600_000_ranso_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0F2/F6C/0F2F6C3DBF80AFE074C2C302F491AAE4.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, ransomware, hackers get paid, ransom, bitcoin ransom, cyber attack, cyber attack ransom, ransom payment, city pays hackers]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849738</guid>
      <title>At least 11 dead in Hawaii skydiving plane crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONOLULU, HAWAII  A skydiving plane crashed in Hawaii over the weekend leaving behind no survivors, reports the Honolulu Star Advertiser. The incident is said to be one of the worst civilian disasters in Hawaiian history.The aircraft was a Beechcraft BE65-A90 and was operated by the Oahu Parachute Center, according to the Honolulu Star Advertiser.The crash took place near Dillingham Airfield in Honolulu at 6:30 P.M. on Friday soon after takeoff, according to Hawaii News Now.The television station cites witness Steven Tickemyer as saying that the aircraft dived down before the crash and was engulfed in flames as soon as it hit the airfield's fence line.Honolulu Police told the Star Advertiser that the victims included three men aged 27, 28 and 29, two women aged 26 and 27, plus six other men whose ages weren't revealed.Authorities are still investigating the cause of the plane crash, reports Hawaii News Now. In a tweet, Honolulu Mayor Kirk Caldwell said: "I am closely following the tragic developments out of Dillingham Airfield this evening. At this time our thoughts and prayers are with the family and friends of the victims."Elsewhere, Hawaii News Now reports friends and family of the victims have started laying flowers at the site of the crash to mourn the dead.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 13:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/24/3849738/3849738_0B46406BA63C4983BB00185300132F72_190624_3849738_At_least_11_dead_in_Hawaii_skydiving_plane_crash_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BBA/125/BBA125873E9F86B74157CFA918365677.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, hawaii, hawaii skydiving crash, hawaii plane crash, hawaii skydiving accident 2019, honolulu plane crash, hawaii skydiving plane crash, skydiving, skydiving accident, skydiving victims, skydiving plane crash, skydiving accident]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849712</guid>
      <title>Man tinkling off bridge causes injuries on Berlin tour boat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERLIN  Several people were hurt after a tinkle-happy man in Germany relieved himself off a bridge, right onto a boatload of tourists.According to the Berlin Fire Department, the Friday night incident began after an unidentified man went for a wee from the 4-meter-high Jannowitz Bridge, just as a tour boat passed underneath. The golden showers triggered a commotion on the boat, causing people to jump up and hit their heads on the underside of the low lying bridge.Four people got lacerations on their heads and had to be taken to the hospital.The Independent reports that the three women and one old man were discharged after receiving treatment.Police, meanwhile, are still on the lookout for the bridge tinkler, according to the DW, but have already filed charges against him and his "abnormal behavior."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/24/3849712/3849712_B4A6E3D91D584292B3EC7FC5B7AE85FF_190624_3849712_Man_tinkling_off_bridge_causes_injuries_on_Berli_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8FA/FD3/8FAFD3DAA4B750C4BC4108C6AC86067A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, berlin bridge, berlin tourist boat, man wees off bridge, man tinkles on tourists, tourist boat, tour boat]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849616</guid>
      <title>Woman passes out on plane, wakes up to an empty aircraft</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TORONTO  Imagine being so invisible that everyone, including the cabin crew, just switch off the lights, lock the plane up for the night and leave you inside.That's exactly what happened to Tiffani Adams on an Air Canada from Quebec to Toronto on June 9.The BBC reported that when Ms. Adams woke up, she was freezing, still buckled into her seat and that everyone had gone.Ms. Adams managed to call a friend to let her know where she was when her phone died less than a minute into the SOS call.Unfortunately, she was unable to charge her phone as all the power to the plane was shut off.The Independent reported that the woman made her way to the planes main door, opened it and was met with a 50ft drop. She then sat with her legs dangling out of the aircraft while sending out a distress signal using a flashlight she found onboard.Ms. Adams luckily spotted a random baggage handler who was passing the plane and flagged him down. He was reportedly shocked to see her and questioned how the heck they left her on the plane.In the Facebook post shared by her friend, Adams said she's been "terrified" and is having recurring nightmares since the incident and now has trouble sleeping.  She also said she wakes up anxious and afraid she's been locked up someplace dark.An airline spokesperson confirmed the incident to the Independent and that Air Canada is looking into it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 09:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/24/3849616/3849616_416B5D00842141038260CBF554A913F3_190624_3849616_Woman_passes_out_on_plane__wakes_up_to_an_empty__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/634/C6A/634C6A882C68EDB4DB12AD879FCBC005.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Air Canada, a woman falls asleep on a plane and wakes up alone, Woman abandoned on a plane, a woman wakes up alone in a dark and cold plane after she fell asleep during her flight, Air Canda woman falls asleep, Air Canada woman wakes up alone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849509</guid>
      <title>China deploys J-10 fighter jets to disputed South China Sea island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WOODY ISLAND  Military aircraft have recently been spotted on a Chinese-controlled island in the contested South China Sea, in the first known deployment of fighter jets there since 2017.CNN reports that to a satellite image from ImageSat International shows China has deployed four Chengdu J-10 fighter jets to Woody Island in the Paracels.Analysts told CNN that both the placement of the jets out in the open, and the equipment accompanying them indicate they were on the disputed island for up to 10 days.The planes were also not carrying external fuel tanks, suggesting they were to be refueled on Woody Island.According to a former operations director at the U.S. Pacific Command's Joint Intelligence Center, the deployment is a statement that China can extend their air power reach over the region.With the J-10 aircraft's combat range of up to 500 miles or 750 kilometers, this puts the South China Sea and other vital shipping lanes well within reach.Former Australian Air Force officer and current Griffiths Institute fellow Peter Layton speculated that it could also be early training deployment to get the J-10s ready for an ADIZ declaration.An ADIZ or air defense identification zone would require aircraft flying over the disputed waters to first notify Beijing.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 07:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/24/3849509/3849509_6D7DF4B722E247B89885612C5BEA2460_190624_3849509_China_deploys_J_10_fighter_jets_to_disputed_Sout_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F5E/DE4/F5EDE481FA63E36D3CD68372DAD5519A.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, South China Sea, Woody Island, China fighter jets, J10 fighter jet, artificial islands, Paracels, Paracel Islands, China, china military aircraft, China military]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849374</guid>
      <title>London Heathrow's expansion plan explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  Heathrow Airport has unveiled a proposal to expand its airport, including plans to open a new runway by 2026.This would be the London airport's third runway. The new runway will be 3,500 meters long and would be located in the north-west area of the airport.According to architectural designs released by Heathrow Airport Expansion Consultation website, the proposed runway would be turned into a bridge as it passes over the M25, a motorway around London.According to the BBC, expansion plans include building one single site for cars to park at. The new site would be built at the northern part of the airport on an unspecified date.By 2050, the airport also plans to unveil a new terminal that would integrate indoor and outdoor spaces. Additional plans include creating a low carbon-emissions zone and reducing noise pollution in the area.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 02:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/24/3849374/3849374_12245E0D87F543EA9763668687A894E1_190624_3849374_London_Heathrow_s_expansion_plan_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0F2/E7E/0F2E7ED0908A8A914E154230C8C12BEB.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Heathrow airport, London heathrow airport, london heathrow airport expansion, london heathrow airport expansion project, Heathrow airport third runway, heathrow airport new terminal, heathrow airport third runway plans, airport expansion london]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3849366</guid>
      <title>Iran shoots down U.S. military drone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN   Iran shot down a U.S. military surveillance drone over the Strait of Hormuz on Thursday.This is the first time Iran has directly attacked the U.S. military, The Associated Press reports.Iran says the U.S. Navy RQ-4A Global Hawk was flying over its territorial airspace while the U.S. says the plane was flying in international airspace.Both countries released coordinates of where the military drone was flying during the incident, CNN reports.Iranian Foreign Minister Javad Zarif tweeted a timeline of the incident. He said the U.S. aircraft took off at 00:14 and was targeted at 04:05 as it violated Iranian airspace.A Khordad-3 medium range air defense missile was used to shoot down the American military drone, according to Iran's Tasnim News Agency.Iran's Revolutionary Guard commander General Hossein Salami said the country had shot down the drone to send a warning to the U.S, according to CNN.As soon as the incident took place. U.S. President Donald Trump tweeted, "Iran made a very big mistake!""We do not have any intention for war with any country, but we are fully ready for war," said Salami, the Associated Press reports, citing a televised press address.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 02:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/24/3849366/3849366_E95FC1D1AD3B45209364CC1AFE0C3483_190624_3849366_Iran_shoots_down_U_S__military_drone_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F64/FE2/F64FE248D2C5629F191F925CBCFE9AAF.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire,  iran vs usa, Middle East, Strait of Hormuz, iran, USA, usa middle east, usa vs middle east, us iran drone, us iran latest news, iran shoot down us drone, iran shoots down drone, iran news today, iran shoots down us surveillance drone]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850318</guid>
      <title>Ocean Cleanup device redeployed to Great Pacific Garbage Patch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PACIFIC OCEAN  A floating device designed to trap plastic trash in the ocean has been upgraded in a second attempt to clean up the Great Pacific Garbage Patch.The Guardian reports that the Ocean Cleanup project's system 001 is a floating 600-meter long U-shaped barrier that is meant to collect plastic debris in the ocean.The project's main goal is to clean up the Great Pacific Garbage Patch, a massive island of garbage in the Pacific Ocean between California and Hawaii.Last September, System 001 was towed from San Francisco to the Patch, but problems arose during its first cleanup attempt.While the system managed to catch plastic waste, it struggled to maintain sufficient speeds and was unable to retain the collected trash. The floating boom also broke apart under constant wind and waves, reports the Guardian.According to Ocean Cleanup, an upgraded design dubbed System 001/B is currently being redeployed to the patch.New features include the attachment of inflatable buoys in the opening, which will tow the system forward, propelling it using the force of the wind.Should the buoys fail to speed it up, an alternative option is to attach a parachute-like sea anchor that will turn the system around and bring the speed close to the speed of the water.As the project found out, the speed of the system doesn't actually matter. What's crucial is consistency, since it's fluctuations in the speed that prevent plastic from staying in the system.The screen was brought forward in order to eliminate the rail connection that caused the boom fracture, and the heavy stabilizing frames removed to ease the load on the pipe. The size of the barrier has also been reduced by a factor of three, in order to speed up procurement, assembly, and towing.Ocean Cleanup CEO Boyan Slat had previously said he hopes to deploy 60 of the systems, which could remove half of the accumulated plastic in the Patch in five years.It's unclear though how these system issues, or what Slat calls "unscheduled learning opportunities" will impact that timeline.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/25/3850318/3850318_425E24CB95BD4321811C6C3D354E728F_190625_3850318_Ocean_Cleanup_device_redeployed_to_Great_Pacific_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url=""/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, great pacific garbage patch, pacific garbage patch, ocean cleanup, plastic pollution, ocean plastic, ocean garbage, pacific ocean cleanup, pacific ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850245</guid>
      <title>Cat sneaks into washing machine, survives full wash cycle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. PAUL, MINNESOTA  A Minnesota feline dodged a major CATastrophe after sneaking into a washing machine and then getting stuck in the washer for a full cycle. According to Fox News, Stefani Carrol-Kirchoff was washing some clothes last Wednesday when her one-year-old cat Felix hopped into the machine while the door was open. According to CNN, Carroll-Kirchoff shut the washer without checking. She set the machine to express washwarm water, cold rinseand left. Who knows how many lives Felix used up during his extended rinse, but it clearly wasn't his time to go. After the cycle was finished thirty-five minutes later, Stefani noticed the clothes were still wet, so was just about to shut the door againwhen she heard a meow and noticed a single white paw protruding out from the wet laundry. CNN reported she quickly got the soaking wet cat out and called her father, who raced them to the Animal Emergency and Referral Center of Minnesota. Felix's lost his vision temporarily and had pneumonia from all the water in his lungs, but he's a champ and is recovering. He can now see and has started eating, although he still remains on oxygen. According to the vets, it's just a matter of time before Felix makes a PURR-fect recovery.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 12:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/25/3850245/3850245_1C7604A88F0F47B8BACCE2865F937B2C_190625_3850245_Cat_sneaks_into_washing_machine__survives_full_w_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4C2/9C2/4C29C250E8F6BA88B5F0019809E2C2E2.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, cat in washer, cat in washing machine, cat survives full wash cycle, cat survives washing machine, cats]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850238</guid>
      <title>One pilot dead as two fighter jets collide in northeastern Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MECKLENBURG, GERMANY  Two military jets collided in northeastern Germany on Monday while on a mission for the German air force, Deutsche Welle reports.The two aircraft crashed before 2:00 P.M. local time in northeastern Germany near Lake Mueritz, which is north of Berlin.Three Eurofighter jets took off from Laage Air Base, according to Germany's public international broadcaster, Deutsche Welle .The trio was part of the German military's Tactical Air Force Wing 73, which specializes in air defense.The two pilots ejected from their fighter jets and launched their parachutes. One of the pilots was found alive, hanging on a tree canopy. The other pilot was found dead, with human remains being found in the area by the police.Part of the plane wreckage was found in the surrounding area of Malchow, Deutsche Welle reports.The German broadcaster cites reports as saying that the wreckage had caused fires that were extinguished.In a statement, Germany's Minister of Defence Ursula von der Leyen said that they would launch an investigation into the incident.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/25/3850238/3850238_CFB7158D384D48EC9AEFCAAB5D7110E8_190625_3850238_One_pilot_dead_as_two_fighter_jets_collide_in_no_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/865/8A6/8658A6AACA2829C74E53580A1051DC60.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, german air force, germany, fighter jets, eurofighters, german military jets, Laage Air Base, germany military, Eurofighter jets, plane wreckage, german fighter jets 2019, german fighter jets 2019, Tactical Air Force Wing 73, military eurofighter typhoon]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850221</guid>
      <title>London may soon get a new wooden skyscraper</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON  PLP Architecture and Cambridge University's Department of Architecture unveiled a proposal in 2016 to build London's first wooden skyscraper.The building would be made out of timber and includes mid-rise terraces.The 300-meter tall building is planned to be constructed in central London alongside the Barbican housing estate, according to the architecture firm's website.The skyscraper could house up to 1,000 new residential homes in a 1 million square feet space. The wooden structure would also be made to meet fire regulations set in place for existing concrete and steel buildings.If everything goes according to plan, the building would become the second tallest building in London after The Shard, Inhabitat reports.Researchers explained in a University of Cambridge news release that wooden structures could potentially have multiple benefits such as wood being a renewable source, cost reduction and making the building more lightweight.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/25/3850221/3850221_1E6109C110DA4504A0D10E007994698E_190625_3850221_London_may_soon_get_a_new_wooden_skyscraper_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/75C/C68/75CC6812A750F117343ADCDEFFF8402B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, London skyscraper, wooden skyscraper london, timber building london,  tallest timber building london, skyscrapers, tall skyscrapers, unique skyscrapers, timber structures, wooden skyscraper united kingdom, timber structure construction]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850179</guid>
      <title>Girl gets stuck in claw machine after climbing inside for doll</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA  A determined little girl in China got herself into a bit of a jam after climbing inside a claw machine through the prize flap on mission to grab a Pikachu doll. According to Pear Video, the mother told police she had her hands full at the time watching two toddlers when her oldest daughter slipped off and made her way over to the game at a Dongguan shopping mall. Funny thing about kids, if there's a hole or space big enough to fit, they're definitely going all in. Getting out is a different story. Luckily, another shopper at the mall spotted that the girl probably was in need of some help, so she called the police. Footage from the scene shows the girl just chilling calmly while officers and mall staff worked on getting her out. After about 30 minutes she was all good to go. Police told reporters that she got out from the claw machine unharmed.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 10:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/25/3850179/3850179_E533E263CD99492E872FBE7FA477B3DF_190625_3850179_Girl_gets_stuck_in_claw_machine_after_climbing_i_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3F7/3E6/3F73E661C30F5E6A8BF47E0237F21D30.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, claw machine, grabber machine, person trapped in claw machine, dongguan claw machine, China claw machines, China]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850031</guid>
      <title>Tokyos' wooden skyscraper plans explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO  Japanese company Sumitomo Forestry has announced plans to build the tallest wooden skyscraper in the world in the city of Tokyo by 2041.The skyscraper would be 350-meters tall and will mark the company's 350th anniversary.The hybrid structure would be made from 90 percent wood and 10 percent steel, according to a press release by the company.The building would use around 185,000 cubic meters of wood. This would allow the structure to remove approximately 100,000 tons of carbon dioxide from the air as well as encourage reforestation.The exterior of the building will be made out of a braced tube structure which would be able to protect the structure in case of an emergency.According to Inhabitat, the building will be covered in greenery and will allow sunlight to enter its interior.Once complete, the structure will be the tallest building in Japan as well as the tallest wooden tower in the world.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 07:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/25/3850031/3850031_296AC06834124E70A3E3D1CA7DF43AA8_190625_3850031_Tokyos__wooden_skyscraper_plans_explained_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D7C/D42/D7CD42CC2AC67B8AE7A30922C03868E6.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, tallest wooden skyscraper, sumitomo forest company, mega projects, skyscraper construction, wooden skyscraper, wooden skyscraper japan, tokyo wooden skyscraper, sumitomo forestry, japanese skyscrapers, timber skyscraper, timber structures, timber structure construction]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850866</guid>
      <title>What happened to Iran Air Flight 655?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STRAIT OF HORMUZ, IRAN  July 3, 2019 marks the 31st anniversary of a largely forgotten atrocity carried out and then covered up by the United States - the U.S. Navy shootdown of a civilian airliner in Iran."The Washington Post reports that Iran Air Flight 655 took off on the morning of July 3, 1988 from Bandar Abbas International Airport, for what would have been a 28-minute flight to Dubai.""At the time, U.S. Navy guided missile cruiser USS Vincennes was pursuing Iranian patrol boats in the Persian Gulf, and entered Iranian territorial waters to open fire.""The Vincennes detected the Iran Air aircraft as it was climbing 12,000 feet and transmitting IFF squawks in Mode 3, a signal that identified it as a civilian aircraft.""Despite this, the Vincennes attempted to contact the plane on the military frequency. After receiving no response and supposedly mistaking the airliner for an Iranian F-14 Tomcat, ship captain Will Rogers gave the order to fire two SM-2MR surface-to-air-missiles.""One of the missiles hit Flight 655, destroying the plane and causing the wreckage to fall into the water below.""There were no survivors. All 290 passengers on board were killed, including 66 children."In a 2014 Slate article, former Boston Globe defense correspondent Fred Kaplan claimed American officials told various lies to pin the blame on the Iranian pilot.During the first press conference on the incident, Admiral William Crowe, then chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said the plane had been descending at a high speed and was headed directly for the Vincennes. A 53-page incident report issued by the Pentagon in August 1988 found that almost all the initial details cited by senior officials to blame the pilot were wrong. Even so, it concluded that Rogers and his officers acted properly.Iran maintains that the shooting was done deliberately, and later sued the U.S. in the International Court of Justice.America never formally apologized, expressing only 'deep regret.' It did, however, agree on a settlement with Iran, paying $131.8 million in compensation, $61.8 million of which went to the victims' families.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 16:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/27/3850866/3850866_35EE9302E8E54684A72D77EF0EC1F785_190627_3850866_What_happened_to_Iran_Air_Flight_655__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/880/922/88092257CDBCA123D3B512299075FC64.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Iran Air 655, USS Vincennes, Iran Air, Tanker War, Iran Air Flight 655, US vs Iran, forgotten US history]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850807</guid>
      <title>Giant squid caught on video for the first time ever in U.S. waters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GULF OF MEXICO  A kraken-esque giant squid was captured on video for the first time ever off U.S. waters in the Gulf of Mexico.The rare footage was released by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration last week and shows a juvenile giant squid swim toward the camera in a 28-second long video. NOAA said the squid was about 10 to 12 feet long and was found around 100 miles southeast of New Orleans on June 19. According to CBS News, the squid appeared to wrap its tentacles around the NOAA's underwater stealth camera called the Medusa before making a quick getaway into the darkness. According to the NOAA, the Medusa uses red lights that are invisible to creatures at deeper depths. The NOAA said the camera was able to draw the attention of the squid due to an "e-jelly" lure which emulates the bioluminescence of jellyfish.  CBS News reported that scientists with NOAA were looking to explore the deepest parts of the Gulf to study the effects lack of light has on animals at depth.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 14:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/26/3850807/3850807_D0F2DA999F464D00B72DE47709C18B09_190626_3850807_Giant_squid_caught_on_video_for_the_first_time_e_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D26/814/D2681401A66B57D676602D25BA605220.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, giant squid, NOAA giant squid, giant squid Gulf of Mexico, juvenile giant squid]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850685</guid>
      <title>Slug throws Japanese rail into chaos</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KYUSHU, JAPAN  Everyone knows the Japanese are sticklers for punctuality, and their trains are no different. But just last month, the high-speed rail in Kyushu was thrown into absolute chaos after a tiny slug triggered a massive power failure.CNN reports that the outage happened at 9:40 a.m. on a Thursday, aka rush hour, or otherwise known as the worst possible time.It affected lines operated by JR Kitakyushu, which led to 26 trains being cancelled and over 12,000 passengers getting delayed.An inspection of the network's electrical equipment later revealed the culprit: a two to three centimeter-long dead slug. The slimy little bugger had gotten in through a gap in the power box, and burned to death after touching an electrical cable  which then triggered the mass power outage.Wildlife effing up the power isn't terribly uncommon, but it's usually collisions caused by animals like deer. Slugs  not so much.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 10:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/26/3850685/3850685_D2336CA684B24A5A9A52DD2D221B01A1_190626_3850685_Slug_throws_Japanese_rail_into_chaos_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/960/29D/96029DC0D72359655E9A8AD60D001E5F.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, japan rail, slug power failure, power failure, japan high speed rail, JR kitakyushu, kyushu power outage, japan power failure, japan power outage, slug]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850650</guid>
      <title>Woman bungee jumps to deliver colleagues' lunches</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA   A Chinese woman is impressing the internet community with her no-nonsense, speedy approach to mealtime.Wan Tiandi is a worker at Wansheng Dream Ordovician Park, an adrenaline junkie's paradise. Here she is bungee jumping off a mountain to feed her coworkers.According to the South China Morning Post, Wan makes the near-1000ft bungee jump because it's more efficient and a lot faster.In the past when her colleagues received the lunches, they were already cold, which, hey-presto, gave birth to this totally sensible idea.Due to the geography of the park, what would be an over 30-minute drive down the mountain, now takes mere minutes.The report also said her colleagues praised her for working hard to deliver the hot food.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/26/3850650/3850650_ADD83D667AA346ACAE815634C8070441_190626_3850650_Woman_bungee_jumps_to_delivery_colleagues_lunche_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C06/E93/C06E93FB281BD753183F63A64D1E5B7B.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews,Satire,China,Chinese woman bungee jumps to feed coworkers,bungee jumping,bungee jump,food delivery,a Chinese woman bungee jumps to delivery her coworker's lunch]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3850618</guid>
      <title>Huge reservoir of freshwater discovered beneath Atlantic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  Scientists have discovered a massive freshwater aquifer hidden beneath the Atlantic.According to a study published in Scientific Reports, Columbia University scientists used an electromagnetic receiver to survey offshore groundwater deposits below the Atlantic Ocean.The results reveal a reservoir of freshwater stretching from the coast of New Jersey to Massachusetts, extending out about 50 miles to the edge of the continental shelf. The reservoir begins some 600 feet below the ocean floor, and bottoms out at 1,200 feet.Researchers theorize that toward the end of the last ice age some 15 to 20,000 years ago, the world's water was locked in ice. Much of what is now the underwater U.S. continental shelf was exposed due to lower sea levels.When the ice melted, sediments formed river deltas over the shelf which trapped freshwater in scattered pockets. Sea levels then rose later on.The aquifer is not stagnant, and is likely fed by subterranean runoff from the land. It is also freshest near the shore, and becomes saltier farther out, suggesting that it gradually mixes with ocean water over time.Because of this, the water would first need to be desalinated before people can use it.While there's no need to dip into this reservoir at the moment, there may be other existing aquifers that could potentially represent a resource in drier regions like southern California, Australia, the Middle East, or sub-Saharan Africa.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 08:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/26/3850618/3850618_B38071284B12436DBC5FD4F89A37441A_190626_3850618_Huge_reservoir_of_freshwater_discovered_beneath__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E8B/F15/E8BF156CB6080A55007640627220C6E9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, freshwater reservoir, freshwater store, atlantic freshwater, atlantic freshwater reservoir, aquifer, atlantic aquifer, freshwater under the ocean, atlantic ocean]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851399</guid>
      <title>Kim Kardashian trademarked the word 'Kimono'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES  Kim Kardashian has decided to trademark the name "Kimono" for some new underwear lineonly one problem, just ask the Japanese. On Tuesday, Kim dropped a load on Instagram to announce the new shapewear line blurting out, "finally I can share with you guys this project that I have been developing for the last year. I've been passionate about this for 15 years. Kimono is my take on shapewear and solutions for women that actually work."It's a shame at 38 years of age, Kardashian isn't aware that words have meanings. Apparently, none of the people around her do either.  Kimonos are traditional loose long-sleeved robes typically tied with a sash that only date back to 15th Century Japan.  According to the BBC, they are considered the national dress of Japan and are now mostly worn during special occasions. According to the L.A. Times, the human butt also filed trademarks for "Kimono Body," "Kimono Intimates," and "Kimono World."There was immediate backlash from people that understand words and from quite a few Japanese people, hence the hilarious hashtagKimOhNo.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/27/3851399/3851399_38E2382F915848FE8CC41E9755162D5D_190627_3851399_Kim_Kardashian_trademarked_the_word__Kimono__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/78E/A75/78EA75D3A0EE4E840D7849A479195558.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Kim Kardashian, Kim Kardashian Kimono, Kardashian Kimono backlash, KimOhNo, Kardashian appropriation]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851371</guid>
      <title>Chicago's 80-story tall wooden skyscraper plans explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO  Architectural firm Perkins and Will, along with engineers Thronton Tomasetti and the University of Cambridge conceptualized a wooden skyscraper to be built along the Chicago River in 2017.Called the River Beech Tower, the 80-story high tower would be part of the Chicago's River Beech project.The team would only use real and commercially available timber materials for construction, according to the firm's website.The structure would consist of a diagrid system on its exterior. This would take advantage of the timber's natural axial strength, reports ArchDaily.The building would include 300 residential apartments as well as various skyparks that would feature in its interior for visitors and residents. The green spaces would be visible from the outside through the building's wide windows.The River Beech Project will consist of ten other buildings, a green space as well as a river walk, according to Travel and Leisure.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 12:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/27/3851371/3851371_D7179813F01E4DC5811A94CCAAD0C22F_190627_3851371_Chicago_s_80_story_tall_wooden_skyscraper_plans__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EAB/A1B/EABA1BA77DD14EB24E55E7DD60ECA33D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, architecture, wooden structures, wooden buildings, wooden skyscraper, wooden skyscraper chicago, chicago's first wooden skyscraper, chicago skyscrapers, skyscrapers, tall skyscrapers, unique skyscrapers, timber structures, eco-friendly buildings]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851360</guid>
      <title>Mt. Everest is turning into a big open toilet and garbage dump</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KATHMANDU, NEPAL  Mount Everest has turned into a massive open toilet littered with garbage after a record number of rich douchey climbers visited the world's highest mountain this season. According to the Associated Press, at the top of the world, one can find depleted oxygen cylinders, food wrappers, rope and other junk scattered all over. A Nepalese government cleanup crew is now tasked with clearing everything from abandoned tents to a literal boatload of butt loads from an estimated 700 climbers, guides and porters. The AP reports that exhausted climbers struggling with the altitude and battling nausea often leave the heavy tents behind rather than carry them down.An estimated 30 tents have been left Everest's highest campsiteCamp 4and as much as 11,000 pounds of trash.  But apparently the biggest threat to Everest now is the nearly 17,000 pounds of Number Twos dropped this season at Camp 2, which is two levels higher than Base Camp. And because some climbers don't use makeshift toilets, and instead just dig a hole in the snow, as temperatures rise, that waste gets then washed down to Base Camp where people use melted snow for drinking waterEwww.      Mountaineering groups have been pushing the Nepalese government to come up with regulations on how to properly dispose of human waste. Some climbers use biodegradable bags that have enzymes that break down the doo doo, but those are expensive and have to be imported from the States.  In the meantime? Maybe just make all those rich climbers carry their own crapall of it.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 12:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/27/3851360/3851360_621562D575C74802BA0676C5B291CE83_190627_3851360_Mt__Everest_is_turning_into_a_big_open_toilet_an_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D02/980/D02980A88503B9B69C8BE1C84F07DF05.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Mt Everest, Mt Everest garbage, Mt Everest abandoned tents, Mt Everest toilet, Mt Everest waste problem]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851338</guid>
      <title>Amazon Prime Day will be two days this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MURICA  Americans can never seem to buy or consume quite enough useless garbage, but luckily Amazon Prime Day is just around the corner and the cherry on top is that it will run for two entire days this year. Amazon announced that Suckers Daysorry, Prime Daywill kick off at midnight on Monday July 15, and run for 48 fun-filled shopping hours.   The e-commerce monstrosity claims it will include more than a million deals around the world on a bunch of stuff you definitely don't need, but will probably buy.  According to CNN, Prime Day was first launched in 2015 to celebrate the company's 20th anniversary and was modeled after Black Friday. CNN reports that Prime Day has since morphed into Amazon's annual summer show of force in the shopping world. Most importantly, Amazon uses the discount holiday to jam its own junk down people's throats like Alexa , the hot, hot Fire tablet or the Echo speaker. Prime Day is also used to trick people into signing up for Prime, Amazon's $119-annual free shipping program.  Amazon has promised to unveil special deals for Prime Day and launch new products especially for Prime members in anticipation for this year's shoppocalypse. So do whatever you have to do. Donate blood, refinance your mortgage, sell some organs or maybe even a kid or two. Whatever you dodon't miss Prime Day.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 11:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/27/3851338/3851338_F99F33E7FE404DEFB0DF33F444FAE7FC_190627_3851338_Amazon_Prime_Day_will_be_two_days_this_year_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7AA/44B/7AA44B1DF1DE17B466B608ADAB1FD8BA.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Amazon, Amazon Prime Day, Amazon Prime Day 2019, Amazon Prime Day sales, Amazon Prime Day deals]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851105</guid>
      <title>French inventor sells pills to make your farts smell like roses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GESVRES, FRANCE  A French inventor has dedicated the past decade or so of his life to one thing and one thing only: making your toot smell good.According to the Mirror, Christian Poincheval created a bizarre product called Pilule Pet  scented fart pills for those of us who parlez no Francais. The nearly septuagenarian Poincheval, who calls himself the Cunning Imp, says the idea came about after a particularly windy dinner with friends made an unforgettable stench.He began developing his pill in 2007, and now has a range of 'em in several different scents, from chocolate to roses, and even ginger.The Imp claims the pills are made from organic stuff like blueberries, fennel, and seaweed, and is the result of lengthy research and trials. Hmm, wonder how many nasty farts he had to sniff before he got it?The pills have been on sale for over a decade, retailing for roughly21 bucks for a bottle of 60. They're especially popular around Christmas, it seems.It's not just for humans anymore, either. Le Cunning Imp has also come up with a powder for pets so you don't have to endure your dog's suffocatingly horrible gas. Win win!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 07:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/27/3851105/3851105_20CE84D6FE5D44E5A5DE339AE52BE793_190627_3851105_French_inventor_sells_pills_to_make_your_farts_s_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2DF/0ED/2DF0ED1AE8E0ED4D289A80DE958E5A27.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, scented fart pills, scented flatulence pills, smelly gas, smelly farts, fart pill, french fart pill, lutin malin, cunning imp]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851066</guid>
      <title>Total Solar eclipse to appear 
over in South America in July</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH AMERICA  A total solar eclipse is set to take place on Tuesday, July 2, across South America.A total solar eclipse occurs when the moon covers part of the sun facing Earth, according to NASA.According to Space.com, the eclipse will start at the east-northeast of Wellington, New Zealand and make its way across the Southern Pacific Ocean. The eclipse will appear over central Chile, and is expected to last for 2 minutes and 36 seconds. It will continue east-southeast through to central Argentina and Uruguay.A partial solar eclipse will also appear over other South American countries such as Panama, Costa Rica, and part of Nicaragua.This year's solar eclipse will be 70 percent longer than the solar eclipse that took place across the continental U.S. in 2019, reports Astronomy.com.A total solar eclipse usually occurs around every 18 months, according to NASA.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 05:49:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/27/3851066/3851066_4DC5319EF2904C919FDBAFBA2E3A89A6_190627_3851066_Total_Solar_eclipse_to_appear__over_in_South_Ame_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD9/808/FD9808C84792D26F14F9EC955DE46679.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, south america, solar eclipse, solar eclipse in south america, solar eclipse explained, south america eclipse, solar eclipse, eclipse, total solar eclipse, july 2 eclipse, 2019 total solar eclipse, solar eclipse 2019 july 2, total solar eclipse july 2nd 2019, july 2nd 2019 solar eclipse]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3852164</guid>
      <title>Woman arrested for stomping on sea turtle nest busted again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI  A cold-hearted Chinese woman who was charged with stomping on a protected sea turtle nest has been arrested yet again. CBS Miami reports that 41-year-old Chinese citizen Yaqun Lu was originally arrested on June 15 in Miami Beach.According to an arrest report, officers saw Lu stomping on a marked-off sea turtle nest and using a wooden stake to poke it. According to CBS Miami, police say the area was clearly marked off and had a double perimeter in addition to a warning sign. Lu is looking at a felony charge of molesting marine turtles or eggs. Sea turtles are protected under federal and state law. According to the Miami Herald, Lu was back in court on Tuesday after she was arrested AGAINthis time after being nabbed at the airport for trying to go to Panama. Lu was out on a $75,000 bond, and was due in court for that charge on Wednesday. CBS Miami reported that leaving the country was something she was prohibited from under the terms of her bond from the first arrest. Her lawyer said that Lu had bought the ticket prior to her first arrest. Wellmaybe she should have canceled her trip after the first visit to the slammer? Lu is currently being held at the Turner Guilford Knight Correctional Center with no bond. Luckily, since Lu's first arrest, the Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission was called out to reestablish the safety perimeter around the turtle nest.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 16:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/29/3852164/3852164_827D9B0CCEE94F78819864CF476EB966_190629_3852164_Woman_arrested_for_stomping_on_sea_turtle_nest_b_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/428/787/42878776D7CCD9533C3E044BEC7539D9.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, Chinese woman stomping on turtle nest, Chinese woman arrested, Chinese woman arrested turtle nest, Chinese woman arrested leaving country, sea turtle nests]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851883</guid>
      <title>Electrocuted man returns from the dead after 20 minutes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LIVONIA, MICHIGAN   20-year-old Michael Pruitt was helping his step-dad at work when he had his life zapped from him after he touched a live wire with a ladder.In a press release from Beaumont Hospital, Pruitt said, "I remember being electrocuted while holding that ladder and shaking, and then nothing." He was immediately... overcooked.According to Fox26, the homeowner called 911 and started CPR. Livonia firefighters were there within four minutes and continued with CPR and tried a shock with the defibrillator while taking him to Beaumont Hospital in Farmington Hills.By the time he arrived, he had no signs of life but Dr. Angel Chudler wasn't discouraged.In the press release, she said, "they brought in this perfect young man who had no vital signs. I said to my team, 'We're bringing him back.' And then, I said to him, 'You better come back!'"They shocked his heart but to no avail. Dr. Chudler then got super serious and turned up the defibrillator to eleven, jolted him again and shockingly, two minutes later: heartbeats.Clinical nurse Yasmeen Bachir said, "When he became conscious again, he was like the Hulk, grabbing the railings and shaking the bed with huge strength. It took the entire care team to hold Michael."Pruitt's big toes were burned from the inside where the high voltage electricity exited his body. They're now bandaged and healing.Pruitt joked, "when my folks ask me to take out the garbage now, I've been trying to use my painful big toes as an excuse not to do it,"]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 09:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/28/3851883/3851883_B568E3B39D2643A89B460A6243A978C6_190628_3851883_Electrocuted_man_returns_from_the_dead_after_20__2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F00/5D0/F005D050B4D0EFDB68B7E53D6AB9FEDE.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, electrocuted man returns, man electrocuted at work, man comes back to life, man electrocuted, Beaumont  Hospital]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851807</guid>
      <title>Hubble space telescope spots 'electric soccer balls' in space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE  The Hubble Space Telescope have identified electrically-charged molecules in space that are shaped like soccer balls. According to NASA, Buckminsterfullerene or Buckyballs, are molecules made of 60 carbon atoms arranged in a hollow sphere, in the rough shape of a soccer ball.Buckyballs, which are also called C60, has been found on Earth in some rare cases, in rocks and minerals or in soot created from high-temperature combustion.Though Buckyballs have been seen in space before, scientists using the Hubble Space Telescope recently discovered for the first time ionized C60 within the interstellar medium or ISM.The C60 becomes ionized when ultraviolet light from stars strips off an electron from the molecule, giving it a positive charge.The ISM is the diffuse matter and radiation that exists in between solar systems, which was previously considered too harsh an environment to sustain complex carbon-based molecules.Though most of it contains helium and hydrogen, it contains many other compounds that have not been identified.Researchers say they will continue searching the universe to see where else they can locate C60+. The Epoch Times reports that at the moment, observations seem to be pointing to a widespread presence in the Milky Way.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/28/3851807/3851807_EB3703726DA847EF8D5E05265C4E805C_190628_3851807_Hubble_space_telescope_spots__electric_soccer_ba_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/29B/A89/29BA8947F5464494C82DA23EC0673B5C.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, space soccer balls, buckyballs, space buckyballs, buckminsterfullerene, C60, hubble space telescope, hubble telescope, tiny electric soccer balls, carbon molecules, interstellar medium, ISM]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851786</guid>
      <title>Scientists use  3D printing to make hair farms for human hair</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY  Scientists have discovered a new way to grow human hair in the lab using 3D-printed molds.According to a Columbia University news release, researchers used 3D-printing to create a plastic mold with long, thin extensions half a millimeter wide, and designed to mimic the natural microenvironment of human hair cells.Once human skin is engineered to grow around the mold, hair follicle cells are seeded in and topped by keratin-producing cells.They are then fed a cocktail of growth factors that stimulates hair growth. This includes JAK inhibitors, which were found to reawaken resting hair follicles in mice when applied on the skin.Researchers had previously discovered a pathway called JAK-STAT in the stem cells of resting hair follicles that keeps them in a dormant state. By controlling pathway activity, JAK inhibitors can trigger follicle growth.According to the Columbia researchers, human hair follicles appeared after three weeks and started creating hair.The technique will be especially useful for hair restoration surgery, which currently relies on the redistribution of follicles from one part of the body to another.Using this new method, scientists can create "a grid of hairs that are patterned correctly and engineered so they can be transplanted back into that same patient's scalp."Hair follicles grown this way could allow for an unlimited supply, with no need for donor hair grafts.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/28/3851786/3851786_D44A30FD71544E578AE7CF7CFDDC0240_190628_3851786_Scientists_use__3D_printing_to_make_hair_farms_f_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BAA/437/BAA437823FCCE2DEF54EF8F3194D2F27.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, 3D printing, 3D printed mold, 3D printed hair farm, hair farm, hair mold, hair loss, baldness cure, baldness breakthrough]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851762</guid>
      <title>Hybrid wooden skyscraper proposed for Vancouver</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER, CANADA  Architecture firm Perkins and Will announced plans in May 2019 to build the tallest hybrid wooden skyscraper in the world in Vancouver.The building will be called Canada Earth Tower and is expected to be built in the city's Central Broadway Corridor in collaboration with private developer Delta Land Development, which has yet to submit a formal rezoning application.Bruce Langereis, president of Delta Land Development, told online newspaper the Daily Hive that the building's exterior, structural columns and floor plates would be made out of cross-laminated timber, a material that can be manufactured with a fire-resistance of 30, 60 and 90 minutes, according to industry site GreenSpec. The building would also include a concrete core with an elevator and an emergency staircase.The skyscraper could rise up to 40 stories high and include approximately 200 residential apartments in a 339,300 square feet space, according to ArchDaily. Sections of the tower would also include an outdoor garden for residents.A horse-shaped complex would lie at the bottom of the building. Developers plan to transform the space into a place for retail stores, restaurants and offices.The building would include other green designs such as energy-efficient air and water pumps, natural ventilation and insulated roofs, the Daily Hive reports.]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/28/3851762/3851762_75EF1B4F9DDD4AAFBD704B27E05F444D_190628_3851762_Hybrid_wooden_skyscraper_proposed_for_Vancouver_2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B62/E19/B62E197450F3EAED49FD28509152E746.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, skyscraper, wooden skyscraper, hybrid timber tower, hybrid timber tower vancouver, world's tallest hybrid timber tower, wooden skyscraper canada, timber skyscraper, timber structures, Canada Earth Tower, canada earth tower vancouver]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3851604</guid>
      <title>China hacked eight different service providers: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING  Hackers from China's Ministry of State Security were found breaking into eight different computer service providers around the world, according to a Reuters report.This was an attempt to steal commercial secrets from the service providers' clients, Reuters reports, citing sources familiar with the case.Hewlett Packard Enterprise, IBM, Fujitsu, Tata Consultancy Services, NTT Data, Dimensions Data, Computer Sciences Corporation and DXC Technology were all victims of Chinese cyber attacks.According to the Reuters report, the global hacking campaign is known as "Cloud Hopper," and is believed to have been going on for years. The report says Chinese hacking group APT 10 or Advanced Persistent Threat 10, carried out the attacks for the Chinese Ministry of State Security.Reuters reports that they did this by sending out a phishing email to trick company employees into downloading malware or giving out their passwords. Once gaining access to clientele networks, hackers identified commercially sensitive data to encrypt and exfiltrate.In a statement to Reuters, China denied the accusations and said: "The Chinese government has never in any form participated in or supported any person to carry out the theft of commercial secrets."]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 04:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/06/28/3851604/3851604_37B9EFF8A4F3424DA3C3D5DFBD918F14_190628_3851604_China_hacked_eight_different_service_providers___2600.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
      <media:thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7DA/42D/7DA42D39A20CDE55826D32A6CD516B7D.jpg"/>
      <media:keywords><![CDATA[TomoNews, Satire, China, hacking, chinese cyber attacks, chinese cyber espionage, China cyber espionage, Chinese ministry of State security, technology service providers, Cloud Hopper, cyber espionage,  cyber attacks from China, chinese hackers, chinese cyber attacks, Cloud Hopper attacks, APT 10, Chinese cyber spies]]></media:keywords>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
