<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/delta-flight-forced-to-turn-around-because-of-bird-in-cockpit-3517600</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Delta flight forced to turn around because of bird in cockpit 3517600]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT — A Hot-lanta bound Delta flight was forced to hang a u-ey after the crew found a bird flying around the cockpit. 
Before the flight, the pilot happened to see a sparrow fly into the cockpit, causing the flight to be delayed as crew and maintenance workers searched for the little feathered fellow. 

After a delay and unsuccessful search attempt, the pilot decided to take off. 
Wouldn't you know it, shortly after the aircraft took off, the sparrow reappeared again in the cockpit, so the pilot decided to turn the plane back around. 
After getting back to Detroit Metro Airport, crews were finally able to grab the little guy and get him off the plane. 

In the end, after a considerable delay, the flight eventually made its way down to Atlanta. No word on what flight the sparrow ended up taking. 3517600]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMARMXABK2PFMDRRBNJFZLBHMEAETF37AAAWPTKSKRBFCDRAAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/41A/57C/41A57C7178544383A58142B6FB35B082.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bird in cockpit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bird in delta cockpit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delta connections]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delta detroit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delta detroit bird cockpit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bird on plane]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-firefighters-rescue-man-from-jumping-off-a-roof-3517540</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese firefighters rescue man from jumping off a roof 3517540]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WENZHOU, CHINA — Firefighters in eastern China recently rescued a heartbroken man just in the nick of time to prevent him from making a fatal mistake.

According to Chinese media The Paper, on December 27th an unnamed man in Zhejiang province's Yueqing[c] city was seen alone on the rooftop of an apartment. After getting a call about the situation, city police and firefighters arrived at the scene and tried to talk the distraught man down. However, he resisted and decided he'd rather leap off instead. Luckily, the firefighters and police possessed some quick reflexes and grabbed the man's arm before he went too far over the edge.

After being pulled back to safety, the man reportedly held onto a firefighter and wept, and later embraced his parents when they rushed to the scene.

The man later told the media he was sorry for his foolishness, he had thought about how his parents would react if he had gone through with it. And if he didn't already feel bad enough, local police warned the man that he could be punished for disrupting the peace and for wasting public resources. 3517540]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKWMDCTAIGAEYAXLFIWX9BAMEAS7U34KWLW5URFKEBWEBRCAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EE0/913/EE091328DD0F4B749E7E21129A9AA8A9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ firefighters saving man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ firefighters saving lives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ firefighters rescuing lives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man on rooftop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man rescued by firefighters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rescued from rooftop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wenzhou]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zhejiang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/home-invading-ninja-squirrel-attacks-two-cops-3517529</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Home-invading ninja squirrel attacks two cops 3517529]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BROCKFORD, NEW YORK —  Officers investigating an errant squirrel at Brockport, New York property last week got a taste of the rodent's mad ninja skills.

The cops were called after the squirrel entered the premises uninvited.

According to the local police department's Facebook page, the home-invading squirrel was caught and released without injury. 3517529]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLWCDAJAAFREYCCLJIAR9JAMICBVSC9AWIRXHZCKBIFCBZBBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F80/85E/F8085E681DB949A89AAA7501955F9CA1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>37</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ caught on camera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel goes nuts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel vs cops]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police animal rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel takes on cops]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel in house]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel in kitchen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ when squirrels break in]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/solar-expressway-gets-road-tested-in-china-3517427</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Solar expressway gets road-tested in China 3517427]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JINAN, CHINA — The People's Republic of China is testing a 1-km solar expressway in Jinan. 

Solar panels covering 5,875 square feet were laid on the expressway, reported Chinese state media outlet Xinhua News.

According to Inhabitat, the expressway consists of three parts: insulation on the bottom, the solar panel in the middle and weight-bearing transparent concrete on the top.

Xinhua reports that the road can generate enough power for 800 homes. 3517427]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFKAKTKEHR7X3DLFJRR9BHGNKB5RILKMCFPTADAEBAPVCRAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/51A/C43/51AC43BB46BA491386E6EC4F0675EE89.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>38</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar road]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar highways]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar expressway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar road in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar news]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/better-treatment-for-alzheimer-s-in-10-years-predicts-neuroscientist-3518438</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Better treatment for Alzheimer's in 10 years, predicts neuroscientist 3518438]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOSTON — Alzheimer's currently has no cure, but breakthroughs in research could lead to better treatment in just 10 years.

In an interview with WBUR, British neuroscientist Joseph Jebelli claims memory loss comes with age, but forgetting what certain everyday things are for could signal a more serious problem.

Healthy brains shrink by about 10 percent between ages 50 and 80. Brain cells shrivel up slightly, reducing contact between each cell and causing them to function more slowly.

In patients with Alzheimer's, toxic proteins cause a buildup of plaques and tangles in the brain, which causes cell death. Current medication only treats the symptoms, and can delay them for six months to a year.

Researchers have been looking into ways of using sleep to treat the disease, since the brain uses cerebrospinal fluid to clean away the plaques and tangles during sleep.

Scientists are also considering neural stem cells as a treatment for Alzheimer's, believing that the cells can be activated to generate new neurons — allowing the brain to heal itself.

Jebelli believes the future of Alzheimer's treatment lies not in an outright cure but in being able to manage and control the disease enough to keep its symptoms at bay. 3518438]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIFVC3XBIARIWKALEBARLD4M6JEXETZLSKR5URKASJA5AKTLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6FB/2E7/6FB2E7C0BD3C4B078B4B707D024725E2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cure for alzheimer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  alzheimer's cure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ memory loss]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sleep treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neural stem cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's symptoms]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-the-hell-is-the-keto-diet--3518380</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What the hell is the keto diet? 3518380]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — The diet that has been gaining in popularity reportedly can help those practicing it burn 10 times as much fat as a standard diet. 

The ketogenic — keto — diet was first introduced in the 1920s to treat epilepsy and diabetes, Business Insider reported. 
It involves eating only 50 grams of carbohydrates a day, roughly one plain bagel or a cup of white rice. The USDA recommends people eat 225 to 325 grams of carbs a day. 

On a keto diet, the body switches into starvation mode and burns excess fat stores for fuel.

On the diet, healthy fats make up 80 percent of daily caloric intake, while protein intake should be 20 percent. 

For comparison, the average American gets 50 percent of calories from carbs, 30 percent from fat and 15 percent from protein, according to the CDC.  

The human body breaks down carbs into glucose, to be used for energy or stored in the liver and muscles as glycogen. 

When carbs are taken out of the diet, the body burns up glucose reserves and then breaks down stored fat into fatty acids. These fatty acids move to the liver and are converted into ketones.

The brain and other organs use up ketones in a process called ketosis. 

Some studies have found a low-carb, high-fat diet could may promote weight loss, improve focus, and hold off age-related diseases. 3518380]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIBWXDRILEAACWRUBIBFR7LWNAEBXST9KEDWPHTWKMDA5AT7AD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6FB/2E7/6FB2E7C0BD3C4B078B4B707D024725E2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ketogenic diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ keto diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high fat low carb diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high healthy fat]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cold-weather-bomb-may-hit-u-s-east-coast-this-week-3518338</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cold weather bomb may hit U.S. East Coast this week 3518338]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[U.S. EAST COAST— A meteorological phenomenon known as Bombogenesis, or a cyclone bomb, may occur off the eastern U.S. coast this week. 

According to CNN, this occurs when an area of low pressure drops by more than 24 millibars in 24 hours. The result is a bomb cyclone.

Meteorologists predict that one could hit the U.S. on Wednesday or Thursday. 3518338]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IFMD3VBIGRAWKCLNJR36JCMMESTEC2AJLFZUZGKRARZVIDAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1FE/10D/1FE10DD76C58430B90A8890EACAD6247.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>33</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is a bomb cyclone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is a weather bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bombogenesis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us east coast]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new york cyclone bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boston cyclone bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weather bomb]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chocolate-could-be-gone-forever-by-2050-3518331</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chocolate could be gone forever by 2050 3518331]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA — Scientists say chocolate is in danger of disappearing as early as 2050 due to global warming. 

Researchers from the University of California are now working with the Mars company to save the cacao plant from disappearing, Business Insider reported. 
Warmer temperatures and drier weather conditions will soon threaten the world's cacao plants. 

Cacao can only grow within a narrow strip of rainforested land about 20 degrees north and south of the equator, where temperature, rain and humidity are relatively constant year round.   

Over half of the world's chocolate currently comes from two west African countries: Côte d'Ivoire and Ghana.  

Rising temperatures over the next few decades will make those regions unsuitable to grow cacao.

Berkeley scientists are now using a technology known as CRISPR to modify of cacao plant DNA in order to see if it can be made to survive in different climates. 

Researchers hope to be able to develop cacao plants that don't wilt or rot at their current elevations under warmer conditions. 3518331]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLAIDTSBSQRCBATBNJRX9DUGEBETFKZKFPAXUZHKRER7ARDAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6E8/A16/6E8A16A14BB54190846C0950E7572166.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chocolate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cacao]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cacao shortage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cacao global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chocolate could disappear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cacao plant]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/google-s-new-sunnyvale-campus-plans-revealed-3518157</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Google's new Sunnyvale campus plans revealed 3518157]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SUNNYVALE, CALIFORNIA —Search giant Google is set to acquire five acres of land to build new offices on the site of an old U.S. Air Force Base.
  
The company will construct a Google campus that'll include two large office buildings at the site. According to San Jose newspaper The Mercury news, one of these buildings will be five stories high.

Concept designs illustrate how the office design incorporates floor to floor, inclining slopes.The Mercury News reports this will allow workers to get from floor to floor via walking, cycling or rollerblading.

Google says the new premises could house 4,500 employees. 3518157]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIDRMAIILWPR5CZ7KFLWXK2BGFJVZSAQKRBRZTIAABKAVA3RAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E4C/50C/E4C50CF176324A2DB56034725D66524F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google sunnyvale campus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google campus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ silicon valley campus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google hq]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google office]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sunnyvale]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/aliens-won-t-friend-earth-because-of-zoo-theory--3518066</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Aliens won't friend Earth because of 'zoo theory' 3518066]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE FINAL FRONTIER — Aliens aren't talking, calling or Snapchatting with us puny Earthlings because they do not want to interfere with our development.

That's according to a 1973 theory by MIT astronomer John Ball. Alien civilizations may consider us a developing species and Earth our space sanctuary, writes Big Think, reporting on the theory. Aliens won't come near us because we might get a disease from them or vice versa.

The theory also reckons advanced alien civilization may have a pact whereby they don't interact with less developed life forms so as to not hinder their development. 3518066]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DFMXRFLRGWKBKCBBLATKBHMIDBIUT7KNLR3GKYAZARAVRDAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F90/C66/F90C66F2A2B84BBEAE717F45CA612F33.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth contact with aliens]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zoo theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ john ball]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radio astronomy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is zoo theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ is zoo theory right]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ do aliens exist]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-wants-to-put-a-lander-on-the-dark-side-of-the-moon-this-year-3518027</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China wants to put a lander on the dark side of the moon this year 3518027]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — China will reportedly attempt to land on the far side of the moon later this year, a feat never attempted by any other spacefaring nation.  

According to the Guardian, the People's Republic will launch two missions known as Chang'e 4. The first will see a satellite stationed some 60,000km from the lunar body to act as a communications relay between Earth and the moon. The second mission will see China attempt to land a spacecraft on the far side of the moon. 

If successful, Chang'e 4 could see China become the first nation to ever to navigate to that area of the moon. 3518027]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZAFMXRELIGWKBIULRAR77LSMZEV5RZNAFIWZHAKAACWZVKYKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/40D/B5E/40DB5EFFECF143739F9D4172CCEFE8C3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>43</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ far side of the moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chang e 4 mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china goes to space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china lunar mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china on the moon]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/smartphone-apps-use-mics-to-record-what-tv-ads-you-watch-3519372</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Smartphone apps use mics to record what TV ads you watch 3519372]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Hundreds of smartphone apps could be tracking their users' television viewing habits.

According to The New York Times, various game apps use software named Alphonso, a program which collects television viewing data via smartphone microphone, reported the Times. The paper found the software on various apps designed for children.

Alphonso says users can opt out of this and is made clear before users download an app. The company told The Times its disclosures comply with federal trade guidelines.

Alphonso Chief Executive Ashish Chordia told the Times around 1,000 games, messaging and social apps use Alphonso software. He didn't tell the paper which apps or how many users Alphonso keeps track off. 

The Alphonso company website says the software uses automated content recognition to identify what ads and programing a user is watching within a fraction of a second, in a completely anonymous fashion. The company collects this data for advertisers, reported the Times. 

Alphonso can also pinpoint what people are watching via audio signals in TV ads. The software can also track what films via people watch at the cinema based on audio snippets provided to the company from film studios, reported the Times, citing Alphonso Chief Executive Ashish Chordia. 

The company also gathers data from TiVO, televisions, and streaming devices from other manufacturers, reported the Times. This, the Times reports, can be combined with characteristics such as age, sex and income via large data companies. 3519372]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIAAADRIKNKR5VITBIDAZ7UVGJKB3EC3LRAAZUAHABKWZBTTAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1AB/E56/1ABE569D4C964DDC9F6C0672A206EED5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ is my phone listening to me]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ is my phone tracking me]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[phone tracking ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tv ads smartphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alphonso software]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ am i being tracked]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-2-500-virtual-assistant-could-worsen-japan-s-population-crisis-3518990</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[$2,500 virtual assistant could worsen Japan's population crisis 3518990]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Japan otakus may be like the prospect of intimacy with anime holograms, but the country's population problem may have just gotten worse.

Japan has a baby shortage, thanks in part to young Japanese who are shunning romantic relationships in favor of a two-thousand dollar holographic wife, reports Business Insider.

Gatebox is technically a virtual assistant like Amazon Alexa, but instead of a disembodied voice, you get Azuma Hikari, a character that's exceedingly cutesy and likes to talk.

It helps fill in an intimacy void, with the virtual character providing companionship without all the trappings of a messy, human relationship.

It even sends you messages throughout the day like a normal friend, or you know, wife.

All in all, Gatebox seems like a reasonably pleasant alternative to those of us who don't interact well with actual people.

Except, virtual relationships don't result in babies that help ease a declining birth rate, so while that void of intimacy may be filled, consider the population going, going, and soon, gone. 3518990]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVBRAYAHKBKWZBTEBWPAVKL3GSKV5UZMKAARVUTYANKFVCANKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/718/898/7188987EAFB14F1EAD0E34B9C4D835FC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gatebox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan birth rate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virtual companion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virtual assistant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hologram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ azuma hikari]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon alexa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aging population]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ low birth rate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vinclu]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-gets-cut-short-by-elevator-in-china-3518818</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman gets cut short by elevator in China 3518818]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI, CHINA — Looking at your phone instead of watching where you're going is always a solid plan, especially in the land of man-eating elevators.

A woman in Shanghai was walking into a Made-in-China elevator on June 21, 2017, when it malfunctioned and starting moving up even before the doors closed. 

Engrossed by her phone, the woman had no clue, so she tripped and face-planted into the lift. Too bad her right leg wasn't able to get on in time.   
The elevator then went up three floors — leaving the woman's right leg waiting for the next lift.  

The woman is seen at the end of the video lying on the floor waiting for help to arrive. 3518818]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIWVCAJAIHRRBKAL5AF792FMNIBRSIKK2IWXG3WAFKARX3TLE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6D9/DD6/6D9DD6FE41564CA39B3FF3BC5E68B175.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Made in China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China elevator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China elevator malfunction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China elevator incident]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-accidentally-blew-up-one-of-its-cities-with-a-missile-3519995</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea accidentally blew up one of its cities with a missile 3519995]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG — North Korea fabulously blew up one of its own urban cities by accident during one of its ballistic missile tests last year.

According to the Diplomat, last April when Kim Jong-Un shot off a Hwasong-12 intermediate-range ballistic missile, it couldn't even deliver a short-range. 
Instead it crashed in the city of Tokchon, located about two hours from Pyongyang. 
Everyone in the world at the time knew the test was a failure, they just didn't know how spectacularly. 
The missile was launched from North Korea's Pukchang Airfield, but things then went immediately south as the it flew 24 miles to the northeast blowing up industrial or agricultural facilities in Tokchon. 
In the meantime while North Korea is busy annihilating itself, what's Orangina doing? Bragging about the size of his bigly button. 3519995]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACAAXZCKNJWVAI7L2KA79BAMJKBZSCZK5DFRUZGK2KAVXT6KE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/65E/815/65E8153A61DB43D7805606233C9A152B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North Korea missile test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North Korea failed missile test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North Korea failed ballistic missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Tokchon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-trials-first-portable-bionic-hand-with-sense-of-touch-3519830</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman trials first portable bionic hand with sense of touch 3519830]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROME — An Italian woman has become the first woman to try out the first bionic hand with a sense of touch that can be worn outside a laboratory.

BBC reports that scientists in Rome have unveiled a portable bionic hand which uses sensors and electrodes to restore a sense of touch, trialing the technology on Almerina Mascarello who lost her hand in an accident 25 years ago.

Sensors on the prosthetic hand detect whether an object being held is hard or soft, and send electrical signals to a portable computer.

The signals are converted into sensory impulses and sent to electrodes implanted in the upper arm, which then relay it to the brain.

The process happens in real time, and Mascarello claimed she felt the sensation spontaneously, as though it were her real hand. Unfortunately, she had to give back the prototype once the six-month trial period ended.

Scientists are now working on miniaturizing the electronics and making the technology clinically usable. 3519830]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2LFXXZEAEEFVVAUBSKAZKDYMJJSVSZKABJRZGICANJAXC3RBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1AC/48C/1AC48CE82B16AD1544C321DA19EA4E76.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bionic hand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bionic limb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthesis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthetic hand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthetic limb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amputee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sensation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sense of touch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bionics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bionic technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sensors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electrodes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/blue-moon-total-lunar-eclipse-to-light-up-night-sky-on-jan-31-3519767</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Blue moon total lunar eclipse to light up night sky on Jan. 31 3519767]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SKY AT NIGHT — Earth will witness its first blue moon total lunar eclipse in over a century at the end of January, 2018. 

According to Space.com, east and central Asian countries in central, along with Indonesia, New Zealand and much of Australia, will get a quality view of the celestial event. Hawaii, Alaska and northwest Canada will also be able to witness it.

The last blue moon total lunar eclipse took place on March 31, 1866, reported Space.com, citing reference book Canon of Lunar Eclipses. 3519767]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIBRAYAAKSJW3AZULSPA39USMEEVTSAQABKA5UALAWJR5WAPAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D0F/96E/D0F96EB6029925A35BF8CF4179876D9F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue moon 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total lunar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eclipse 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ where to see blue moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue moon in sky]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eclipse 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eclipse 2017]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-doesn-t-want-the-world-s-recycled-plastic-garbage-3519762</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China doesn't want the world's recycled plastic garbage 3519762]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — China's ban on importing recycled plastic garbage is causing trash to pile up recycling facilities around the UK. 

China imported 7.3 million tons of waste plastic in 2017 from the U.S., the EU, the UK and Japan, Conversation reported.  
But starting this year, it is now banning 24 categories of recyclables and solid waste.  
Britain alone sends around two thirds — about 500,000 tons — of its recycled plastic garbage to China every year. 

Recycling companies are now scrambling to find other markets for their recyclables, the Telegraph reported.  

Some UK recycling firms are now looking to Malaysia and Vietnam, however, both those countries have capacity issues. 
Unless other alternative markets can be found, the plastics will have to be sent for incineration or dumped in a landfill. 3519762]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMCFGDTSKMAA7BRVL5CWTLSFG2JEZERMKIBW3HKWK2LRVD3TKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A91/F05/A91F05A83F15BE4CE0F2141BAA850F18.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China plastic ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China recycled plastic ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK plastic garbage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK recycled plastic garbage]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-f-35b-fighter-jets-could-see-action-this-year-3519755</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New F-35B fighter jets could see action this year 3519755]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The F-35B jet may see action this year as models of the plane are deployed to boats in potential conflict hotspots.

According to Marine Corp Times, the jet will join U.S. Marine vessels in the Pacific and Middle East.

Engadget reports that the F-35B is noted for its technological prowess, in particular  short takeoff and vertical landing (STVOL) process. This allows it to operate from vessels and bases with not built, or unable to accomodate for current aircraft.

Engadget reports that the Marines plans to purchase 353 models of the b-variant and 67 of the aircraft carrier oriented c-variant. 3519755]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRCACCIGKNJARCZVB6IWR9LVGVEETET6ABPRXFABA5AFVVRBKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AF9/A0F/AF9A0F77CD647880D039A39B38DF9D1F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f-35c]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f-35b]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f35 jet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f-35 lightning ii]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f-35 lightning ii in action]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f-35 lightning ii vertical take off]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f-35 lightning ii flyby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is the f-35 lightning ii]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ f35 plane]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-is-the-ripple-currency-exchange--3519697</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What is the Ripple currency exchange? 3519697]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Thanks to the Bitcoin craze, cryptocurrencies are being thrust into the limelight- and now it's Ripple's time to shine.

According to CoinMarketCap, Ripple is currently the second most valuable digital currency on the market, second only to Bitcoin. It's both a payment network and a cryptocurrency. It uses blockchain technology, but is differentiated from other platforms by its ties with legitimate financial institutions, reports CNN Money.

Ripple's currency is known as XRP and is not mined by users. The company has control, initially creating 100 billion coins, with 38 billion currently in circulation.

The rest of the coins will reportedly be released into the market gradually- up to a billion XRP tokens a month.

Other cryptocurrencies have a stored value and can be used to buy goods and services. But XRPs mainly cover transaction fees as an anti-spam measure, and are destroyed soon after.

Ripple's main purpose is to facilitate global money transfers. Banks take 3 to 5 days to process cross-border payments, but transactions on the Ripple network are cleared in only 4 seconds.

The platform also boasts low fees, and can handle up to 1,500 transactions per second, compared to only seven on Bitcoin.

By and large, the core function of Ripple is markedly different from other cryptocurrencies available in the market. Whether or not it's a good investment is another thing entirely. 3519697]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZAAMXTVK6KWXVKABWIR5K2FMECB5UT9AVAR5URLAWJAZAC4KD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/005/511/00551154F2B8442CA82605F2AB86A462.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ripple]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xrp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ripple currency exchange]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ payment network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ripple network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ripplenet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cross border payment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global payment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global transactions]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-raw-water-craze-is-going-to-come-out-badly-3519687</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The raw water craze is going to come out badly 3519687]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — What is raw water you ask? It's unfiltered, untreated, unsterilized water collected from natural springs. 

Raw water fans are worried about contaminants such as chemicals and lead in municipal water and additives such as fluoride.  
 
It's also ridiculously expensive. In SF, it can cost $61 dollars for a 2.5 gallon jug of raw water that could also give you raw cholera. Yay!

Besides cholera, the clearest stream water can still be filled with animal doo doo, Hepatitis A and E. Coli. 3519687]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFKACTKEDACBRVBNPWZ6DXMAAVZRC9KVDAVFICAMEFRVRAKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/73E/F14/73EF14798FC14B4497827EBA31FCD30E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raw water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raw water trend]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raw water craze]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tap water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Live Water]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sydney-dubbed-the-hottest-place-on-earth-after-temps-soar-to-47-3c-3521848</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sydney dubbed the hottest place on Earth after temps soar to 47.3C 3521848]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SYDNEY — The U.S. northeast may be experiencing record-breaking low temperatures, but in the land down under, Aussies are melting from the sweltering heat.

The Sydney Morning Herald reports that Sydney became the hottest place on Earth on January 7, with temperatures in the western suburb of Penrith reaching 47.3 degrees Celsius.

It was a few degrees shy of breaking the record for hottest day in the area — a 47.8 degree temperature recorded in Richmond in 1939. 

The hot weather combined with strong winds increased bushfire occurrences, prompting certain areas to issue a total fire ban prohibiting open air fires, welding, barbecues, and throwing lit cigarettes, among others.

The heat caused higher-than-normal ozone levels, prompting a forecast of poor air quality, which could affect those with respiratory problems.

Extreme temperatures also affected train track infrastructure, and contributed to power outages, which affected roughly 3,000 properties throughout Sydney.

The next few days are expected to be cooler compared to Sunday's scorcher, but still relatively hot. 3521848]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNNFPCIBAEAAKWRYBMDRT6DWNFIBXRTZKFIAVHCTA5CFEDRFLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/654/494/654494DB0F034EBEA1CB4BFBDBF6EC3E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hottest place]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sydney hottest day]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sydney heatwave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ australia heatwave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nsw heatwave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ australian summer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total fire ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bushfire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ozone pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blackout]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ power outage]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ukraine-s-getting-some-very-effective-anti-tank-missiles-3521820</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ukraine's getting some very effective anti-tank missiles 3521820]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KIEV, UKRAINE—Ukraine is set to receive anti-tank missiles from the U.S.

In December, the U.S. government approved a 2014 request from Ukraine to receive FGM-148 Javelin manportable anti-tank guided missiles, reported Jane's 360. 

The missile has two attack modes and is controlled from a a reusable command launch unit, according to Military.com.

It can be fired directly at a target in direct attack mode. The javelin also has a top attack mode, where it attacks targets from above. 3521820]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANNAAXCSAFLWIWRSLMDRRLBFGEDB5RC6A6KF5UTTAMBWAAIKKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FAA/CBB/FAACBBC39E9E46FC800DD3ED8EB8668B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ javelin missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ javelin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ukraine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fgm-148]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anti-tank missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ javelin missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ javelin missiles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ javelin v tank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ military technology]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-survives-being-snatched-by-hungry-eagle-3521693</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dog survives being snatched by hungry eagle 3521693]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LEHIGH VALLEY, PENNSYLVANIA — A brave dog is lucky to be alive after being snatched by a bird out looking for its next meal.

WFMZ reports that little Zoey had been playing in the backyard one snowy day, when she was spotted by an American bald eagle.

Immediately, the hungry predator swooped down and snatched the 8-pound bichon frise with its talons. Her owner's brother, who had been looking after her and the other dogs, was sent into a panic.

Zoey's owners searched all over the area.for her, but weren't successful.

Thinking their pet dead, the family put out a post on Facebook, asking for help to at least locate the pup's body so they could bury it.

Zoey though, miraculously survived and was found some 4 miles away. Her rescuer nursed her back to health and later located her owners via the public post.

Zoey has since been happily reunited with her family, though it may take a while before she ventures outside again. 3521693]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFIWCAKUBIDA3CATLBJAR9U3GRASRST2A6KWMTZKKFIWEDZAKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3F6/B75/3F6B75A66E24490D8FB191E0AC6EED12.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog snatched by eagle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hungry eagle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal survival]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ family dog saved]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pet dog saved]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hungry eagle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bichon frise]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/pulse-emitting-device-helps-those-suffering-from-ringing-in-their-ears-3521642</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Pulse-emitting device helps those suffering from ringing in their ears 3521642]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANN ARBOR, MICHIGAN — A new device may hold the key to silencing the persistent ringing sufferers of tinnitus often hear.

Tinnitus is characterized as a persistent ringing, or similar noise, that can heard in the ears. It affects around 25 million Americans, according to U.S. government information from the National Institute on Deafness and Other Communication Disorders. 

It isn't a disease, but a symptom of something wrong in the auditory system. This can be anything from ear wax in the canal, hearing loss to more serious conditions such as diseases of the heart and blood vessels.

The device, designed by University of Michigan researchers, works by emitting timed sounds and low-strength electrical pulses that direct damaged nerve cells back toward normal functionality. 

According to a University of Michigan news release, researchers tested the device on animals and 20 human patients for four weeks. The human patients were divided into two groups, one with a real device and one that only produced sounds. 

After four weeks the group with the real device reported an improved life quality with the sound usually generated by tinnitus having decreased.

Details of the device and research were published in the journal Science Translational Medicine. 3521642]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IWADAFBIDRABZVLMBAZ9SGGIEVXERKA6JF3U3TANKFIVTXAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3E6/54D/3E654DC09781490F98572BE82BF2BEB0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ What is that ringing in my ears]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tinnitus sound therapy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tinnitus research]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tinnitus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ear health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ auditory system health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tinnitus technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ university of michigan]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/don-t-tell-trump-the-u-s-doesn-t-actually-have-a-nuclear-button--3521620</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Don't tell Trump the U.S. doesn't actually have a 'nuclear button' 3521620]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — In the event the U.S. were to launch a nuclear attack, the president does not hit a nuclear button.
Instead, a mid-level military officer usually travels with the president at all times, who carries the Presidential Emergency Satchel also called the The Football, Popular Mechanics reports.
Inside the satchel is a black book with a list of strike options, a three-by-five-inch card with presidential authentication codes to confirm his or her identity; a list of secure presidential bunkers and instructions for using the Emergency Broadcast System.
In the event the president chooses the nuclear option, he consults with his advisers on what contingency plans to activate from the black book. 
Next, the president's identity is confirmed to strategic nuclear forces by reading a code off the three-by-five-inch card, known as The Biscuit.
The president's orders are then passed down the chain of command to U.S. bomber, missile and submarine crews around the world. 
The system is made to be fast, but also has some measures in place to mitigate impulsiveness. 3521620]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLRCDRCBSLAEV3FKADF7LUUGJJBTEC5AIDF3HAEAMARRVACKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/683/500/683500AFAEAB4796907E88FDDD190FE1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Presidential Emergency Satchel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ The Football]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ The Biscuit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear launch procedures]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear football]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear button]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/aliens-unfortunately-aren-t-causing-tabby-s-star-to-flicker-3521601</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Aliens unfortunately aren't causing Tabby's star to flicker 3521601]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — Scientists say they now have an explanation for why Tabby's Star flickers — space dust. 

Thanks to a Kickstarter crowdfunded astronomy project, a team of 200 scientists now believe a cloud of dust particles is causing the star to appear to flicker, the Washington Post reported. 

KIC 8462852 — the official star name — is best known for its sudden drops in brightness, according to Science News. 
Researchers reported that Tabby Star grew dimmer in blue wavelengths than in red ones, Science News reported. 

The dimming is most likely being caused by dust particles less than a micrometer in size.
The researchers will next try to determine where the dust originates from. 3521601]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAFPYCTLMAFAAASLFIFT7JBMADETSC5KFKWXH3SA2LAPBIEAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C2B/803/C2B8035803904B01AA74C4F23893FA71.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tabby's Star]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ KIC 8462852]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tabby Star's flickering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tabby Star's dimming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space dust]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-world-s-coral-reefs-are-dying-much-faster-than-you-think-3521544</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The world's coral reefs are dying much faster than you think 3521544]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE DEEP BLUE — Warming waters are hurting the world's coral reefs almost five times more than they did 30 years ago.

New research, published in the journal Science, says that hotter waters caused by global has impaired reefs by causing them to bleach more frequently than they did in the 1980s.

The study looked at 100 coral reefs and found that the frequency of bleaching had gone from once every few decades, to once every six years.

According to the U.S. National Ocean Service, coral reefs are sessile animals fixed in place.  Bleaching occurs when the reef reacts to stressful changes in temperature, light, nutrients and other conditions. This makes the animal eject the symbiotic algae in their tissue and turn pale white. 

Corals can survive and even recover, but continued bleaching eventually leads to death.
  
Corals reefs are critical to the world's fish population and are important for tourism, coast protection against heavy storms, typhoons and even tsunamis. According to the World Wildlife, corals account for almost US$30 billion each in goods and services 3521544]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6JWKACWBABAZVR9LJPA5KD4MEDSXRILAFKA3FACKFIATAZGKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1DC/8F6/1DC8F68B4E454F808E2404622A7D5AAB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral reef bleaching]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral reef bleaching dangers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ are coral reefs animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ are coral reef plants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change coral reefs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral reef science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral bleaching]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-biggest-offshore-wind-farm-to-be-built-in-the-north-sea-3521520</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's biggest offshore wind farm to be built in the North Sea 3521520]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH SEA — A sand bank in the North Sea could be home to a vast offshore wind farm by 2027 — possibly the world's largest.

The Guardian reports that a Dutch energy company is planning to build a massive offshore wind farm on Dogger Bank in the North Sea, which will include an artificial island equipped with a runway, harbor, and other facilities.

The turbines harness wind energy to generate alternating current, which will be sent via cables to the island. Since alternating currents incur power losses when transported over long distances, converters on the island will change it into direct current before transmitting it to the UK, Belgium, the Netherlands, Germany, Denmark, and Norway.

The current largest offshore wind farm, the London Array, can produce 630 megawatts of power. The Dogger Bank project, if it comes to fruition, is set to produce over 30,000 megawatts.

Energy company TenneT will likely shoulder the 1.5 billion-euro cost of building the island hub, and source wind farm developers to install the turbines. 3521520]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFKRGX3UB2KFPAZULNIRK6DWNABV5FAKABLWMGAHAEFWAB3YBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/729/4D0/7294D0FC9DAD4CD493F709F408C4F808.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ offshore wind farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's biggest wind farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biggest wind farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind turbine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ London Array]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dogger bank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dogger sand bank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TenneT]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-aims-for-total-surveillance-with-facial-recognition-technology-3522534</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China aims for total surveillance with facial recognition technology 3522534]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — Facial recognition is popping up all over China, as the government looks to technology to keep track of its people and what they're up to.

According to the Washington Post, Chinese apartments equipped with keyless entry use cameras to scan and verify residents' faces. But although convenient, the technology is also being used by authorities to monitor individuals and identify alleged 'bad guys' and persons of interest.

The project, called 'Sharp Eyes', intends to connect public security cameras with those in private compounds and buildings, to form a nationwide surveillance and data-sharing network.

Sharp Eyes' aim is to compile information on citizens, including criminal and medical records, travel and purchase history, and social media use, and link it to a face and identity card.

Its name derives from a Communist slogan, and is linked to Chairman Mao's attempts to get citizens to spy on each other.

Supposedly, the system can track suspicious behavior to help eliminate crime, which in China can be anything from homicide to speaking out against the government.

Ultimately, the goal is for total surveillance, and in a country where being an ethnic minority or an activist can get you flagged, that prospect is frightening. 3522534]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AWKDTWKEBR5YZXBWJA77D4GVBV5UZLA5CA5HZKK2LRVWTSAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F7C/1E4/F7C1E474791B4D82BCF4AAE172D11665.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial recognition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surveillance state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sharp eyes project]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china surveillance system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social credit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sesame credit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big brother]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ privacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spacex-to-put-tesla-roadster-on-board-its-most-powerful-rocket-3522356</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[SpaceX to put Tesla Roadster on board its most powerful rocket 3522356]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TITUSVILLE, FLORIDA — SpaceX is set to launch the world's most powerful rocket into deep space, and with it a most unusual cargo: Elon Musk's own car.

Space reports that the Falcon Heavy rocket features three Falcon 9 engine-cores that are powered by 27 Merlin engines.

The powerful rocket has 2,500 tons of thrust on liftoff, equal to 18 Boeing 747s at full throttle. Its maiden flight is scheduled for late January.

The Falcon Heavy is designed to get large payloads into space, and opens up the possibility of sending manned missions to the moon or Mars. But Instead of putting in concrete or steel blocks to act as mass simulators, the payload will be a red Tesla Roadster.

A lot of risk is associated with the rocket, which could blow up on ascent. If successful, the Tesla Roadster will be sent into Mars orbit, where it will remain for a billion years.

On top of this, SpaceX is also aiming to land and recover all three of the Heavy's first-stage cores. 3522356]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSNFPAAGBIARAAISBAAR5K2BMVBSKS33KJKRZTIGAACWMVIBAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/748/368/748368C1D2AC464BAD4E185F30EEBD70.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spacex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falcon heavy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falcon rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space X rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elon musk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tesla]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tesla roadster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ payload]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Boeing 747]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep space orbit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's most powerful rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ powerful rocket]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gang-of-wild-turkeys-harassing-rocky-river-mail-carriers-3522350</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gang of wild turkeys harassing Rocky River mail carriers 3522350]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROCKY RIVER, OHIO — A big mess of wild turkeys are preventing mail carriers from delivering the mail west of Cleveland.  

The Rocky River branch of the U.S. Postal Service let the city know that carriers in some parts of the city wouldn't be able to deliver the mail because of the hostile turkeys, according to Cleveland.com.

For the past three weeks, around 25 to 30 homes haven't been getting any mail thanks to the aggressive turkeys. 

Mail carriers unfortunately don't have anything to scare the turkeys off, so people have had to end up going to the post office to get their mail. 

Unfortunately the city can't go all guns and glory on the feathered foes due to a city ordinance. 

The city has instead told residents not to leave out any kind of bird food. Too bad Thanksgiving is over. 3522350]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNFPCCUBIARRY3EKECRILDXMMABREC3A5DWRU3WKNIFAAIFKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2A4/51E/2A451EE973674B25907B3637DA91BFCA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wild turkey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wild turkey stop mail carriers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wild turkey mail carriers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[brood of wild turkeys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[mail problems]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[postal service]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kodak-announces-kodak-coin-and-bitcoin-mining-plan-3523426</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kodak announces Kodak coin and Bitcoin mining plan 3523426]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROCHESTER, NEW YORK — Kodak shares are now soaring after the company announced plans to get into the cryptocurrency business.

BBC reports that Kodak is launching an image rights platform with its own blockchain. Photographers register their images and instantly get paid per use with the company's own virtual currency, called  Kodak coins.

To guard against copyright infringement, Kodak software will continuously search the web for violations and take care of licensing.

The company is set to host an initial coin offering on January 31.

Kodak's other initiative is the Kash Miner, a bitcoin mining rig box equipped with processors and a fan, that uses the same amount of electricity as a continuously-running hair dryer.

The machines will be rented out to customers for two years, with an upfront payment of $3,400, plus 50% of all proceeds generated by the machine from mining Bitcoin.

According to the company, customers should be able to earn more than $300 a month, or $9,000 overall.

Still, many are skeptical. Some critics believe Kodak is merely getting into cryptocurrency to raise stock prices. Whether that really is the case — guess we'll soon find out. 3523426]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMCAMYIBK6LFMD3DBADAXKD4GFLSXRRLK2IWMGADANLWEBAKAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/842/95C/84295CCC7D0F4BB086D27805736855DE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kodak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kodak coin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blockchain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blockchain technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin mining]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photography]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ copyright]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kodak Kash Miner]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/steve-bannon-out-at-breitbart-after-fire-and-fury-blowback-3523368</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Steve Bannon out at Breitbart after Fire and Fury blowback 3523368]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — Steve Bannon is stepping down as executive chairman of Breitbart News. 
It's been a roller coaster of a ride for former Breitbart head, to former chief strategist to President Stable Genius, back once again to former Breitbart head.
Things were all sunshine and rainbows for the former kingmaker until Fire and Fury was unleashed across bookshelves after the most consensual president of our times gave it the old Streisand treatment. 
In the book, Trump comes off like, really smart with Bannon having nothing but praise for the Drumph team. 
Conservative mega-donor and minority Breitbart owner Rebekah Mercer was less than pleased, but especially with Bannon's lukewarm apology — which he took five days to issue.
SiriusXM was also serious when they axed its relationship with Bannon. 3523368]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJKWEAAAAZBAXBRVBSJAZ7LRMRDSRSK9KNPWZG3YAZBRAAIALD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3C1/E28/3C1E28D1C6AA4D6AA96DE6C52A90EE01.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Steve Bannon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Steve Bannon Breitbart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Steve Bannon fired]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Steve Bannon Fire and Fury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bannon Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump Bannon]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/crazy-wild-boar-goes-on-rampage-in-restaurant-in-korea-3523287</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Crazy wild boar goes on rampage in restaurant in Korea 3523287]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GUMI, SOUTH KOREA — CCTV footage recently released shows a restaurant in eastern South Korea descended into chaos when a wild boar decided to rampage through it on New Year's day. 

On the evening of January 1, a wild boar broke into a local eatery in Gumi, North Gyeongsang[b] Province when everyone was still immersed in the New Year's festivities.

Panic quickly ensued as the boar even tried biting one of the customers, perhaps to get back at them for the many delicious pork dishes served there?

Luckily, no one was hurt, and the swine was later kicked out of the eatery by the customers. 3523287]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEBWXYIDKAFWMAKDLNIRXKJHGZBB7FC9A2PATUTSARFWCAZJKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/74F/D68/74FD680F49B342C7A557226FB5B7B997.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild boar goes crazy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild boar videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild boar chasing people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boar running]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chased by boars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chased by wild boar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korean restaurant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gumi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ South Korea]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/oprah-could-be-our-next-president-3523007</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Oprah could be our next president 3523007]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — Oprah Winfrey is thinking about throwing her hat in the ring in 2020 according to two of her close friends, CNN Money reported. 

Oprah gave a moving speech at the Golden Globes on Sunday night, which has now led to speculation she could make a run for the White House. 
According to sources, several of Oprah's inner circle have been urging her to make a run. 
It's just talk for now, but all that talk is already dominating the headlines and social media. Right after her Golden Globes speech, #Oprah2020 began trending. 
 
But Oprah lacks political and military experience. Obviously that no longer matters.
Well, it should. When is America going to realize that we don't need TV stars pretending to be president. 
Another problem is that the Democrats literally have no one in the chamber to go up against Small Hands in 2020.

More importantly, who should Oprah pick for her VP? Lebron or Steph? 3523007]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACFPYZCK5DWIBCHLJLFT7D3M2KSTET9LWIFPFKWK6IAIV3TAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/674/90D/67490DF475854EBBB38F05540FACB58D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Oprah 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Oprah for President]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Oprah Winfrey President]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Oprah Winfrey Golden Globes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Oprah Winfrey 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[#Oprah2020]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/meet-shannon-ihrke-ex-marine-and-full-time-lingerie-model-3524085</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Meet Shannon Ihrke, ex-Marine and full time lingerie model 3524085]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO, ILLINOIS — Shannon Ihrke is the former Marine-turned-model whose Instagram account has racked up over 70,000 followers.

Ihrke is the spokesmodel for a popular radio station in Chicago — 97.9 the Loop, she works as an MMA ring girl, and she's posed for publications like Maxim. 

Despite these milestones, Ihrke's most important honor was her four years in service for the United States Marine Corps. She joine the Marines when she was only 19, and said it was the best decision she has ever made. 

Ihrke said the Marines gave her a reason to stay motivated, set goals for herself, and to push herself when things got tough. Being a woman in the Marines, she said she had to constantly prove herself or work twice as hard as the guys in order to get their respect.

After four years, Ihrke called it quits and changed her plans to become a lingerie model. 3524085]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLAPXAHAJIWMVZSLVDR79BCGIBS7ET7KFKFPUAFAVARPVK7BE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/420/FF6/420FF6E535E24030B5A4C2BFE642843E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shannon Ihrke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot marines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shannon Ihrke marines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram models]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram marines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine model]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US marine]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/astronaut-mistakenly-tweets-that-he-grew-over-3-inches-after-21-days-3523952</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Astronaut mistakenly tweets that he grew over 3 inches after 21 days 3523952]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION — A Japanese astronaut has grown nearly an inch taller after launching into space 21 days ago.

Japanese astronaut Norishige Kanai mistakenly tweeted this week that he had grown 3.5 inches after spending 3 weeks on board the International Space Station. He later corrected that claim to 0.8 inches.

Astronauts spines often expand in space due to the lack of gravity, reports the BBC. This results in a height increase. The height returns to normal after the astronaut returns to Earth. 

Astronauts can also experience a loss of bone minerals and muscle mass. 3523952]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NFVCTVBZGAIVZXBJKRX9URNBLSIURIKBJWZGIGKZDWAYAEBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DA1/BB7/DA1BB7CD868F4E72A371C8675106A46B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space effects on the human body]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space human body]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taller from space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ international space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Norishige Kanai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ISS]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/idiot-leaves-hatch-open-causes-nuclear-submarine-to-flood-3523911</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Idiot leaves hatch open, causes nuclear submarine to flood 3523911]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VISAKHAPATNAM, INDIA — A very expensive submarine in India has been out of commision for at least ten months, all because someone in the damn navy forgot basic training.

The Hindu reports that the INS Arihant is the country's first nuclear-powered submarine. It's equipped with torpedos and ballistic missiles, and cost a whopping $2.9 billion.

Back in February, some genius left an external hatch open while the submarine was at harbor, inevitably causing seawater to pour in once it dove underwater.

The vessel's entire propulsion chamber got flooded as a result of the human error, and led to severe damage.

Water had to be pumped out of the submarine and the pipes replaced, since they were exposed to corrosive seawater.

The navy at least knows not to risk using damaged pipes to supply pressurized coolant to a nuclear reactor. Now if only they can improve basic training. 3523911]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNJFXCZJAZGRKATABVCW7KBGMNKSKSK3KIARZGIFANJRXXCWBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CBB/A8E/CBBA8EDDC91C4E72AAB758879F1570F1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ idiot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ INS arihant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arihant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear submarine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ india submarine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ india nuclear submarine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear sub]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human error]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupidity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ india navy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/louisiana-teacher-cuffed-arrested-for-blasting-superintendent-s-raise-3523893</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Louisiana teacher cuffed, arrested for blasting superintendent's raise 3523893]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KAPLAN, LOUISIANA — A Louisiana teacher who voiced her opinion against a superintendent's new contract was arrested during a school board meeting. 
Teacher Deyshia Hargrave brought up the issue of low teacher pay and increasing class size, and wondered if a pay bump for the superintendent was really the best thing, NBC News reported.   

Hargrave is an English teacher at Rene A. Rost Middle School in Kaplan, Louisiana.
Board members were about to call a vote to give superintendent Jerome Puyau a $30,000 pay bump. What? A thirty grand increase for a superintendent?  

In a 12-minute video posted online, Hargrave calmly addresses the board only to be humiliatingly handcuffed and arrested. 

The teacher was tossed into Abbeville City Jail on charges of resisting an officer and remaining on premises after being forbidden there, arrest records show. 3523893]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAARCCTTKWLRIWKDLSIRV74YGVBBVF35LWJWVUTRA6KFKAK5KF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/14C/60F/14C60F98DD9546E88C61C9CFB7070F82.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Louisiana teacher arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Deyshia Hargrave arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Vermilion Parish School Board]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jerome Puyau]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/change-in-irn-bru-sugar-recipe-prompts-panic-buying-spree-3523828</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Change in Irn Bru sugar recipe prompts panic buying spree 3523828]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GLESGA — Scots are panic buying Irn bru, Scotland's national soft drink, after its manufacturer announced plans to half the beverage sugar content.

According to BBC, Scots are stockpiling the beverage ahead of the change later this year. Manufacturer AG Barr says Scots won't be able to tell the difference, but nearly 40,000 people have signed an online petition begging them not to change it.

The legendary beverage has been a Scottish cultural mainstay since it was first introduced in 1901. The move comes ahead of new legislation by the UK government that will tax high-sugar as part of bid to combat obesity. 3523828]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NWMXTVB5AFIAZVL2IFT74YG2LVRR37AEAW7TZCAMDFCXILBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/223/CBB/223CBB522923478199B83E97B06524BA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ irn bru sugar tax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ recipe change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ irn bru recipe change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ag barr]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ barr]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ irn bru]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-connects-impaired-fertility-in-men-with-everyday-painkillers-3523817</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study connects impaired fertility in men with everyday painkillers 3523817]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The National Academy of Sciences has found that some painkillers can negatively impact male reproductive organs.

According to CNN, aspirin, paracetamol and ibuprofen can brought about a condition known as compensated hypogonadism in young men. This condition is linked to weakened fertility, depression and increased risk of stroke or heart failure. 

Previous research demonstrated that the painkillers impacted the testicles of male babies when ingested by mothers during pregnancy, CNN reported. 3523817]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLFXDABAIGREVZ9BRBA57BAMFJVXEANA2LRVUTYKBLACCKVAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1EA/2D4/1EA2D4E9DB404399811DC7483852269F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infertility]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infertile men]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ compensated hypogonadism]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ibuprofen side effects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pain medication side effects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paracetamol side effects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aspirin side effects]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-coral-sowing-technique-could-help-with-reef-restoration-3523798</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New coral sowing technique could help with reef restoration 3523798]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CURACAO — Researchers have found a new way to restore dying corals, using a method similar to how farmers scatter seedlings onto a field.

With the world's corals deteriorating at an alarming rate, and restoration often slow and laborious, a team of scientists from nonprofit group Secore International has come up with a better approach to sowing corals.

According to Secore, the new method involves harvesting coral larvae and planting them on tetrapod-shaped cement substrates. In a few weeks, the larvae will turn into coral polyps which can be sown on the reef. The seeding units don't require manual attachment and only need to be wedged into reef's crevices. One day, they can be sown from boats or by underwater drone.

Twelve months after the sowing, the scientists found at least one coral growing on half the units.

They believe the technique can sow 10,000 corals in just 50 working hours, compared to the hundreds or even thousands of hours needed for common restoration methods.

The team is currently working to refine each step of their novel sowing approach. 3523798]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAFXXTTKRGWIWIVLJJFX7U4GFIBZEAQA2JF7U3SKFJWPVZKBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6BF/DE9/6BFDE93A981245CB9BBF8CAC0B89F665.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ corals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral sowing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sowing corals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral planting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral reefs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral bleaching]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral restoration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ substrates]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ golf ball corals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral larvae]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral spawning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ curacao]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-how-alligators-survive-the-icy-winter-3525160</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's how alligators survive the icy winter 3525160]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OCEAN ISLE BEACH, NORTH CAROLINA — A video released Monday shed light on the unique way alligators adapt to icy winter conditions. 

The Charlotte Observer reports that in the video, alligators in Shallotte River Swamp Park in North Carolina were seemingly frozen inside a pond, with only their snouts visible above the ice.

Alligators are ectothermic, which means they don't generate their own body heat, and rely on the environment to regulate their internal temperature. Most gators live in temperate climates. But occasionally, a bomb cyclone brings in an icy winter and the scaly creatures have to deal.

When temperatures reach freezing, gators are known to stick their snouts out of the water before the surface ices over.

This allows them to continue breathing as they lower their body temperatures and metabolism, falling into a hibernating state in a process known as brumation.

Once it becomes warm and the water thaws, the cold-blooded animals will slowly begin thermoregulating their body temperatures.

Days after the frozen gator video made its rounds online, an update was posted showing the gators now out and about, though apparently still grumpy from their winter nap. 3525160]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMCAGCRBKNJAGWIVBBIRXK2BMREB7RCRKEBRXFKXKZBR3VZFAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2C5/4A0/2C54A0FC0CDFCCF41E949F9EC9FEB68D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frozen alligators]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frozen gators]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alligator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gator hibernation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gator brumation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hibernation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brumation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reptile hibernation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reptile brumation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cold blooded]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ectothermic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north carolina]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/elon-musk-attended-a-banging-party-by-accident-3524728</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Elon Musk attended a banging party by accident 3524728]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Elon Musk attended a party at a Silicon Valley investor's house that got a little out of hand. 
The Tesla and SpaceX CEO said he attended the now infamous sex party at investor Steve Jurvetson's residence, but that he didn't see anything naughty. 

Apparently, Musk thought it was going to be a costume party. He was at the party for a few hours and bounced around 1 a.m. after talking some shop. 
The party was mentioned in a Vanity Fair piece from Emily Chang's new book Brotopia. In Chang's account, an anonymous Jane Doe said she saw a bunch of people cuddling and was offered some powdered goodies. 
In November, Jurvetson parted ways with his venture firm Draper Fisher Jurvetson and took leave from the boards of Tesla and SpaceX, following an internal investigation. 3524728]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWKWXAIHAIFARBKFBRDF794YMACSTEZQLRCF5GZLAIDAMBADLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/523/4EB/5234EB37346A4F0F91F1651A02529BB5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Elon Musk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Space X]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tesla]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Steve Juervetson]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Elon Musk party]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Elon Musk attended party]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/lawsuit-claims-google-employees-block-conservative-staff-members-3524723</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Lawsuit claims Google employees block conservative staff members 3524723]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO —  Googlers detest working with white conservative dudes, that's according to the allegations made in a new discrimination lawsuit.

The suit was filed by ex-Google staff James Damore and David Gudeman, both are white male conservatives.

Damore wrote a 10-page internal memo titled Google's Ideological Echo Chamber, with citations, slamming the company's diversity policies. That triggered an internal debate within Google and the memo somehow got leaked to the media. Damore was subsequently fired.

Damore and Gudeman's lawsuit, if true, details a company culture where employees can block and actively avoid working with staff over political leanings. It also claims Googlers created a blacklist of big conservative media dudes not allowed on Google property.

The lawsuit also tells of two employees — one who identifies as a yellow scaled wingless dragonkin, and the other as an expansive ornate building — doing presentations at Google.

The lawsuit also claims the Big G's internal forums has little on straight couples but is lit up with alternative lifestyles including furries and polygamy. It's worth bearing in mind here that this all coming from fired staff, and that Google — as massive as it is — is still a private company from San Francisco, California.

And it's not just these dudes who are suing them. 

Several women have filed a joint suit against them citing gender pay discrimination nd Google is also the subject of a  U.S. Department of Labor investigation over whether it has breached equal pay laws. 3524723]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFEYKTKEBWIBCELFLRV7UUGICSIUTRKWKAXGKSAWIAAVIBKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D57/ECB/D57ECB3AFF4E4538A69FD4A30402DE24.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>102</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ james damore]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google diversity memo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ james damore google lawsuit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ damore vs google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ james damore gender]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google memo]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bbc-s-carrie-gracie-resigns-as-china-editor-over-gender-pay-gap-3524656</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[BBC's Carrie Gracie resigns as China editor over gender pay gap 3524656]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — The BBC has always been at the forefront of diversity and inclusion, especially when it comes to the diversity in pay.

Using the latest in diversification algorithms, the Beeb calculated it would be fair to have only a third of its top-earning on air stars be women last year — and to really keep it diverse — make the top seven earners all gentlemen.     

One of the BBC's top journalists, Carrie Gracie, resigned from her China editor post in protest, writing an open letter slamming the corporation for its 'secretive and illegal' pay culture. And as a side bonus, Gracie gets to move back to London. 

On that note, BBC, if you guys are looking for a new China editor with experience and only the highest journalistic standards — the Taiwanese Animators ARE available. 3524656]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIAWCCIIKZAAAAZWKEARKLBFNBKS7SZKKBJA3TABA6IAMWZNKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1D1/657/1D16574F370A4C3992A1461A867683C7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>86</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BBC gender pay gap]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BBC News top earners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BBC top earners list]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Carrie Gracie BBC]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Carrie Gracie BBC China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Carrie Gracie resigns China editor]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bbc-s-carrie-gracie-resigns-as-china-editor-over-gender-pay-gap-3524651</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[BBC's Carrie Gracie resigns as China editor over gender pay gap 3524651]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — The BBC has always been at the forefront of diversity and inclusion, especially when it comes to the diversity in pay.

Using the latest in diversification algorithms, the Beeb calculated it would be fair to have only a third of its top-earning on air stars be women last year — and to really keep it diverse — make the top seven earners all gentlemen.     

One of the BBC's top journalists, Carrie Gracie, resigned from her China editor post in protest, writing an open letter slamming the corporation for its 'secretive and illegal' pay culture. And as a side bonus, Gracie gets to move back to London. 

On that note, BBC, if you guys are looking for a new China editor with experience and only the highest journalistic standards — the Taiwanese Animators ARE available. 3524651]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2LWMDZEAADRMATHBMDA37JAMMBVZERKK6PFZTZCAACFPDZAKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6CE/169/6CE1695EEDB84396915C005B04E140F0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>86</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BBC gender pay gap]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BBC News top earners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BBC top earners list]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Carrie Gracie BBC]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Carrie Gracie BBC China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Carrie Gracie resigns China editor]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-found-in-dumpster-is-recovering-but-needs-a-home-3524621</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dog found in dumpster is recovering but needs a home 3524621]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT, MICHIGAN — A dog in Detroit, Michigan that was abandoned inside a dumpster has made an incredible transformation and is now looking for a permanent home and family. 

In a Facebook post from the Detroit Dog Rescue, a pit bull named Oscar was found in September, 2017 with another dog inside of a dumpster. Both dogs had scars, infections and parasites, including heartworm, a parasite that can cause heart failure in dogs.

In the latest update, Oscar has made an incredible recovery, and has moved on to a foster home for further recovery. Fortunately, the other dog, a German Shepard, has already been adopted. 3524621]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDWXYIBKAFFIVA9BBLRK7JHMECVZFC7KWKWZFAGAZAWMDZFAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7D4/319/7D4319AEDAEC44B380465B89654B57AB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal rescue story]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal rescue video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heartworm disease in dogs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog rescued from dumpster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heartworm disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canine heartworm disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ detroit dog rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ detroit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ michigan]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/99-of-north-gbr-sea-turtles-now-female-thanks-to-global-warming-3524603</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[99% of north GBR sea turtles now female thanks to global warming 3524603]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GREAT BARRIER REEF, AUSTRALIA — Rising temperatures have caused a major downturn in male turtle populations in the northern Great Barrier Reef.

A new study, published in the journal Current Biology, has found that 99 percent of sea turtles in the Pacific Ocean biggest green sea turtle rookery are female. Researchers say this is due to warming global temperatures.

According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, a sea turtle's sex is temperature dependent. Males are born at around 27.7 degrees centigrade, while females are born at around 31 degrees centigrade.

According to National Geographic, an area further south holds a ratio of two females to one male sea turtle.  Worldwide is around 3 to 1, reports National Geographic, citing research looking at 75 rookeries worldwide. 3524603]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAARIDICK2KRIBTALFIFZ7JHMMAB3R37ABKR3GRFANJRZWZBBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/574/AF0/574AF05C7FB043DCB32E854588FAA880.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gender climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sex climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turtle sex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turtle gender]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming sex change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming heating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby sea turtle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea turtles hatching]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-triggered-deadly-debris-flows-in-california--3526750</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What triggered deadly debris flows in California? 3526750]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MONTECITO, CALIFORNIA — More than a dozen are dead after a torrent of mud and debris swept through California's Santa Barbara County last week.

The Ventura County Star reports that this deadly and shockingly common occurrence is called a debris flow, though it's also commonly called a mudslide.

Often at risk for debris flows are mountainous areas that have been ravaged by wildfire. Fire kills vegetation and nutrients in the soil, causing it to become hydrophobic or water-repellant.

During intense rainfall, water that would normally be absorbed into the ground instead saturates it and causes the earth to liquefy into a flowing river of mud.

Debris flows grow in size as they pick up boulders, trees, and other debris, and are powerful enough to uproot or destroy entire neighborhoods.

Many of the deaths in Montecito reportedly occurred while most residents were asleep, after heavy rain fell in a short period of time around 3:30 a.m. 3526750]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNFPAADBVAATAKEBBJF7LDRGFJBKRRKKZDRXHKYKRCAGVZEAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3AB/B8D/3ABB8D6F78D543C9B9B21BFCAA5003C6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ debris flow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mudslide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mudflow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wildfire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ california debris flow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hydrophobic soil]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disaster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ natural disaster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fire flood cycle]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/plane-skids-while-landing-and-almost-winds-up-in-black-sea-3526700</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Plane skids while landing and almost winds up in Black Sea 3526700]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TRABZON, TURKEY— A plane carrying 168 passengers and crew nearly wound up in the Black Sea after skidding during its landing at the weekend.

Pegasus Airlines flight PC 8622 ran into problems while landing at Trabzon airport on Turkey's northern Black Sea coast on Saturday evening. Several media indicate the runway was freezing or icy. 

The Boeing 737-800 skidded and went down a cliffside beside the runway. Photos of the aftermath show the aircraft close to the Black Sea.

The airline said in a statement all of the passengers and crew were without injury and disembarked the aircraft safely. 3526700]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNWEDTUBRCRPXCDLNKF7L4RGMDB3EAIKZBW3UCWK5CFEWRIAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/500/13F/50013FA487AE472F98948F9513878578.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ landing goes wrong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane skids off runway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane landing turkey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ landing goes wrong turkey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane landing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pegasus airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trabzon landing]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/false-missile-threat-alert-for-hawaii-was-human-error-3526617</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[False missile threat alert for Hawaii was human error 3526617]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HONOLULU, HAWAII — An emergency alert notification was blasted across Hawaii warning of a inbound ballistic missile on Saturday — fortunately it was only a false alarm. 
Residents and tourists got quite the message after a worker accidentally hit the wrong button. 
BALLISTIC MISSILE THREAT INBOUND TO HAWAII. SEEK IMMEDIATE SHELTER. THIS IS NOT A DRILL, the alert read. 
The Hawaii Emergency Management Agency immediately hopped on Twitter to let everyone know it was a false alarm.
Looks like the error happened during a shift change when the button was mistakenly pressed sending the warning out on TV, radio and cell phones. 

A second alert was sent 38 minutes confirming the first alert was a false alarm. 3526617]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDAIYKUKFJWIACABBIA79UTGVEETECRKBPFTFABAWLFAAIEKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AE9/FBD/AE9FBD995BDB4A7BBBC01432373BA9C8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hawaii]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hawaii missile threat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hawaii missile threat false alarm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hawaii false alarm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hawaii missile false alarm]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/stage-i-of-taipei-s-circular-metro-line-to-open-in-june-of-this-year-3526461</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Stage I of Taipei's circular metro line to open in June of this year 3526461]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIPEI, TAIWAN — Construction is underway for a circular metro line that passes through the densely populated areas of Taipei and New Taipei City. The line will connect with the existing lines of the Taipei Metro system.

The Circular line — or Yellow line — is an elevated, medium-capacity rapid transit system. All stations are designed with natural lighting, transparency, and spaciousness in mind.

Stage I of the line is about 15.4 km (9.6 mi) long and consists of 14 stations. Dapinglin station, an existing underground station on the green line of the Taipei metro will serve as a transfer station for the circular line.

The circular line will connect Dapinglin station in southern New Taipei City to New Taipei Industrial Park, in the western part of the city. 

Jing'an, Banciao, Touqianzhuang, will also serve as transfer hubs to train station and other MRT lines, while New Taipei Industrial Park connects passengers to the Taoyuan Airport MRT line. 

The Circular line's 17 driverless trains each consists of four carriages with a total of 68 carriages manufactured by Hitachi Rail Italy

To ensure safety and punctuality, CBTC radio signaling systems will be installed on board to allow train traffic to be managed via telecommunication. 

International architect Emmanuelle Moureaux, who specializes in large-scale color projects, has been commissioned to design the color scheme for the stations and carriages. 

Constructed by Taiwan's RSEA Engineering Corporation, stage I broke ground seven years ago at a reported estimated cost of US$1.8 billion(NT$54.7 billion). 

Stage I of the circular line is scheduled to open to the public in June 2018. 3526461]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNFMY3TBVAWMDCALNJAZ6LUMMDBXRRIKVDA3TIFAEFRPWRAAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B26/46D/B2646D188A1746ED8F2624EC0D07E2AC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>110</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan circular line]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan circular line first stage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan circular line construction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan mrt ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan mrt line]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan public transportation technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ department of rapid transit systems]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chelsea-s-%C2%A31-bn-stadium-plans-may-get-halted-over-right-to-light--3526432</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chelsea's £1 bn stadium plans may get halted over 'right to light' 3526432]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A family cottage has halted development on Chelsea Football Club's new stadium in an upmarket area of London.

Plans for redevelopment of their Stamford Bridge stadium has been suspended as it may block a local home's right to light, reports the BBC. 

As the name suggests, that's a right for English landowners to receive light on their property.  The concerned household believe say the new stadium could affect sunlight and daylight. 

Plans for the £1 billion pound project got the go ahead last year from London authorities last year.  

Officials will meet on Monday to discuss how to proceed, the BBC reports. The new stadium would be capable of hosting 60,000 fans. 3526432]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNNRPDIBBSIAIYAVL6PW7LDSMRDSZSRMKJLF5HRFK6JWIB3RAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D01/ECB/D01ECB66E969417898E5106F6B12B9A6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chelsea new stadium plans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new chelsea stadium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chelsea stadium plans 3d]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chelsea football club]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stamford bridge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chelsea right to light]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-ice-sheets-near-martian-surface-3526416</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds ice sheets near Martian surface 3526416]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE RED PLANET — Researchers have discovered ice sheets on Mars, according to a new study in the journal Science.

The research looked at data from spacecraft on eight locations on Mars and found large swathes of ice.

The sheets are said to be located near the surface, as well as close to depths of 100m. Researchers also found cliffs made up of water ice.

According to Science, the ice sheets could be useful for future missions to Mars. 3526416]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5BRCXTWKSLFGDIWKBJAX7D4MZEBXR34LWJWMGIEKZAWPAKRKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F6E/E7F/F6EE7F1C0BE040D7BB9E3BFB78D1EEFE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>39</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water on mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice on mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars ice sheets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mission to mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars research]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/philippines-volcano-threat-level-increased-to-critical--3527526</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Philippines volcano threat level increased to "critical" 3527526]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LUZON, PHILIPPINES — Eruptions of steam and ash from an active volcano has made more than 3,000 people flee their homes in the Philippines.

According to CNN,  the Mayon Volcano on Luzon island in the Philippines began erupting on Sunday.  Officials moved the alert level to 3 at the weekend, saying there was an increased tendency towards hazardous eruption in weeks or days. There are 5 alert levels in total. 

Authorities suspect the crater glow at the peak points to the growth of a new lava dome and beginnings of lava flow towards the southern slopes. 

Level 3 is considered critical, Cedric Daep, head of the Albay Provincial Disaster Risk Reduction and Management Office told Reuters. 3527526]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IAPYCVA2PFCCCHKBPFRL4XGMEBKRC3LWJFPGTYBSIFKAACKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BAF/608/BAF6080D9A0547A995C0C521CF6968B1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>40</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mayon volcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ volcanic eruption]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luzon volcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ philippines volcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lava eruption]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ volcanoes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cranberries-lead-singer-dolores-o-riordan-dies-at-age-46-3527403</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cranberries lead singer Dolores O'Riordan dies at age 46 3527403]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Cranberries lead singer Dolores O'Riordan died suddenly on Monday in a London hotel room. She was only 46.

The BBC reports that no details have been released regarding the cause of death, which is as yet unexplained.

According to the Washington Post, O'Riordan's musical career began in 1990, when she answered a newspaper ad from Limerick City band The Cranberry Saw Us, and got hired as their lead singer.

The group eventually changed their name to The Cranberries, and rose to international fame in the mid-90s with hits like 'Linger' and 'Zombie'.

But despite shining in the spotlight, O'Riordan struggled with fame, and reportedly battled mental health issues behind closed doors.

In 2003, a decade after they shot to mainstream success, the band separated to pursue individual careers.

O'Riordan collaborated with other musicians before then launching a solo career with two albums.

By 2009, the band had reunited, and was doing well. O'Riordan's personal life, though was decidedly not. She got a divorce, and was diagnosed with bipolar disorder after being involved in an air rage incident.

The Cranberries had been set to go on tour after releasing a new album in 2017, but had to cancel performances in Europe and North America, citing O'Riordan's back problem, reports CNN.

Fans around the world are mourning the loss of such an iconic singer, and are sending condolences to her ex-husband and three daughters. 3527403]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCFIACVKIHR3XTFBIDFR7LSGFJB5SAIKWKRVGIDAIDAPARGAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/370/5B2/3705B24676C5412B8DA24E626440E5A7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cranberries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the cranberries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dolores o'riordan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ singer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cranberries singer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lead singer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ irish music]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rock band]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mental health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bipolar disorder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ linger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zombie]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uae-says-qatari-jets-intercepted-two-commercial-flights-3527362</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UAE says Qatari jets intercepted two commercial flights 3527362]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED ARAB EMIRATES — The United Arab Emirates said on Monday Qatari air force planes had intercepted two civilian aircraft en route to Bahrain, however Qatar denies the allegations. 

The UAE, along with Saudi Arabia, Bahrain and Egypt, imposed travel, diplomatic and trade restrictions on Qatar in June 2017, accusing it of funding terrorism, Reuters reported. 

The UAE General Civil Aviation Authority said two Emirati airliners carrying 277 passengers were met by Qatari fighter jets while flying between UAE and Bahrain.

One of the flights was intercepted at 10:30 a.m., and the second at 11:05 a.m. at between 9,000 and 10,000 feet. The report did not say when the incidents occurred.   

The UAE described the event as a serious and renewed breach of international conventions and the safety of civil aircraft traffic.
Qatar's foreign ministry claims that UAE fighter jets violated its airspace on Dec. 21 and Jan. 3. UAE has denied the claim. 3527362]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKAMCIDAJPRIAKHLNLWTKLYGSJS5FKSKFJWZURGK5CRKVAEKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BA4/7F5/BA47F5F9BB6E4647BDD5C2CE24DDD813.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United Arab Emirates]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Qatar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Qatari fighter jets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UAE military aircraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Emirates plane]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/photographer-s-terrible-editing-job-on-family-portraits-goes-viral-3527351</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Photographer's terrible editing job on family portraits goes viral 3527351]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KANSAS CITY, MISSOURI — A series of family photos caught the internet's attention, thanks to the photographer's amazing photo editing skills.

When Facebook user Pam Dave Zaring paid $250 to a professional photographer for a family photo shoot, they didn't expect the end product would turn out to be worse than what they actually look like.

After delivering the jaw-dropping photos, the photographer claimed the images were so terrible because the shadows were really bad on the beautiful, clear, and sunny day and her professor never taught her to retouch photos. 

Pam Dave Zaring later uploaded the photos to Facebook with the opening line okay, this is not a joke. The post then quickly went viral and has been shared over 380,000 times since it was first posted on January 12. 

Some commenters felt this was a marketing stunt to promote the photographer's business. 

The Kansas City Star journalist Max Londberg did some research and found a LinkedIn account associated with the photography business under the name Lesa Hall, and according to the account, Lesa Hall of St.Louis, studied photography in college.  

The photography business also has a Facebook page filled with photos done with the same editing approach. Even photos of the Donald didn't escape the Lesa Hall treatment. 3527351]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JFECTVARERPAIULBJFXLDRGIABKRZIAIDW5FAHK6IR7VTYAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/942/A8C/942A8CADB4214F74954163A5FE2F291B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ family photography failed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ family photography disaster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ terrible family photo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ funny family photo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photoshop failed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photographer failed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ terrible photographer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kansas City]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Missouri]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/israel-destroys-hamas-tunnel-under-gaza-crossing-3527292</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Israel destroys Hamas tunnel under Gaza crossing 3527292]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GAZA — Israel announced on Sunday that it destroyed 'terror infrastructure' that infiltrated Israeli territory.

According to the Israel Defense Forces, authorities detected a tunnel running from the Gaza strip into Israel and Egypt, reportedly built by militant group Hamas.

Israel has claimed to have an advanced system for detecting tunnels underground, but did not provide details.

The concrete tunnel passed under the Kerem Shalom crossing, the main passageway for goods entering Gaza, and was positioned near oil and gas pipelines.

Authorities determined it was an attack tunnel, and could be used by militants to go to Egypt from Gaza, in order to attack Israel from the Sinai Peninsula.

On Saturday, Israeli fighter jets launched an airstrike from the Gaza side that destroyed the tunnel.

Three others have been destroyed in the last two months, with the military vowing to eliminate all Hamas attack tunnels by the end of 2018. 3527292]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMBRMC3SKWPRMCZYLWPFZLSFGWIE7FILKMAFPFIKKADWEVAJKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AE9/E62/AE9E6269A2014CA19D0C73379FC4649A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hamas tunnel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tunnel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gaza tunnel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hamas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gaza]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ attack tunnel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ israel palestine conflict]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kerem Shalom border]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border crossing]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/couple-caught-with-pet-cat-inside-checked-luggage-3527228</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Couple caught with pet cat inside checked luggage 3527228]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ERIE, PENNSYLVANIA — Florida couple Olivia Sari and Nicholas Larrison last week got busted by the TSA for allegedly putting a cat in their checked luggage.

They were travelling home from Erie International in Pennsylvania when baggage detectors picked up something weird, according to a report on GoErie.com.

To their surprise, TSA agents reportedly discovered the 6-month-old female cat inside their luggage when they took a closer look. Airport police said Slim was placed inside the luggage without food, water or air.

Sari and Larrison were cited for the incident and are yet to enter pleas over the incident, reports GoErie.com.

As for Slim, she's reportedly fine and being looked after by Humane Society of Northwestern Pennsylvania. 3527228]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIWVCKSA5ARIAIXBJIAX74RGVCBVSILKBKWZGTWBSIAACRCLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F01/625/F0162594E2AC40B0819840D11B934BE9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat in luggage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tsa find cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tsa animal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal in luggage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ transporting animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luggage pet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gm-wants-to-test-self-driving-cars-with-no-steering-wheels-by-2019-3527213</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[GM wants to test self-driving cars with no steering wheels by 2019 3527213]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT — GM is asking the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration for permission to test self-driving vehicles without steering wheels by 2019. 

The carmaker has already been testing the autonomous Chevy Bolt in San Francisco and Phoenix, according to the Daily Dot. 

The fourth-generation Cruise AV has no steering wheel, no pedals, no manual controls and no driver. 
The self-driving vehicle will be using for ride-hailing, not personal use, the Daily Dot reported. 
If granted approval, GM could deploy more test vehicles in cities across the U.S. Currently, only seven states allow testing for vehicles with no steering wheels or pedals: Michigan, North Carolina, Tennessee, Georgia, Texas, Colorado and Nevada. 3527213]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDWAYIBKEFWADTHL6PA59JCMEBVZURQKRDAXTZDKNIR7ARIKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E4D/63C/E4D63C7B7FB74967B4423B4EEB145BC8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  GM Cruise AG]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GM self-driving vehicle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GM autonomous vehicle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GM no steering wheel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GM no pedals]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/swarm-of-drones-attacked-two-russian-military-bases-in-syria-3527199</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Swarm of drones attacked two Russian military bases in Syria 3527199]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TARTUS, SYRIA — Russia claims to have identified the source of a drone attack that targeted two military bases in Syria.

CNBC reports that the drones were launched from a village in southern Idlib province, by forces aiming to destroy Russian relations with Iran and Turkey, according to RT.

On January 6, Russian defense forces detected 10 drones approaching Khmeimim Air base, and another three targeting a naval base in Tartus, Syria.

The drones were assembled using a simple engine and cheap materials. Each carried eight to ten bombs stuffed with PETN explosives and strings of ball bearings.

At least one drone was equipped with a camera and had the ability to adjust the track of the others, which were all guided by GPS and a pre-programmed flight path.

Seven drones were shot down by Russian anti-aircraft missiles, while electronic warfare units took control of the rest. Three exploded upon landing, while three others survived.

The Russian bases did not suffer damages or casualties. 3527199]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLAIDKXABQRAYZRBAAFR7BHMABS5FC2AIBRVHRGASJWMBZKBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/773/CD4/773CD4AD1F4B400985258C046117185C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armed drones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drone swarm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drone attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russian drone attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russian military base]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bomblets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anti aircraft missiles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EW units]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electronic warfare]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/campaigns-look-to-end-plastic-straw-use-%E2%80%94-good-luck-3528413</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Campaigns look to end plastic straw use — good luck 3528413]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — Plastic straws are increasingly drawing attention from conservation movements around the world. 

In the U.S. alone, Americans discard around 500 million plastic straws a day, enough to circle the globe twice, or fill 125 school buses, according to CNN. 

Straws normally are not recycled because they are often made from several different types of plastics, and they're small in size. 
Straw pollution contributes to the eight million tons of plastic dumped into the oceans each year, CNN reported. 

At the current rate, there will be more plastic than fish in the water by 2050. 

Campaigns in the U.S. and the U.K. have looked to reduce plastic straw use. 
Reusable glass straws, stainless steel, copper and bamboo all more sustainable alternatives than single-use plastic. 3528413]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIWCDRCAIAAKARUBNKFR94XNADE5FC5AABRZT3RANJRZB3TAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2C0/E77/2C0E77F2BC27431B93207BF28C752AB4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic straw]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic straw dumping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic straw campaigns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic straw alternatives]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/measles-warning-issued-for-travellers-at-chicago-airport-3528301</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Measles warning issued for travellers at Chicago airport 3528301]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — A health warning was issued for anyone who was at Chicago O'Hare International Airport last Wednesday after someone tested positive for measles.

Measles is contagious and usually transmitted via the air or contact with an infected infected individual. According to the World Health Organization, it attacks the respiratory tract and then spreads across the body.

U.S. government information says symptoms can include fever, cough, runny nose, aches and white spots inside the mouth.  No treatment exists for the virus, but immunization and vaccinations can help combat it.

The World Health organization says those most at risk include unvaccinated pregnant women and unvaccinated young children. Complications from the disease can lead to more serious health problems. 3528301]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NFCAIEBEAAVBRVLWLF79D3M2IBXUT2KSJR3UAEKBLFXCRBKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E96/ABF/E96ABFC3C0F74673A35E4802EAE43FC8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ measles alert chicago]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chicago airport measles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is measles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ measles explainer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ measles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chicago o hare measles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-barred-from-flying-by-ba-for-excessive-layers-of-clothing-3528285</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man barred from flying by BA for excessive layers of clothing 3528285]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KEFLAVIK, ICELAND — A British man trying to get from Iceland back to England was arrested for trying to board a British Airways plane while wearing a ton of clothing.

Ryan Hawaii Williams was at the BA counter trying to get out of paying an additional bag fee, so he did what anyone would do when confronted by a douchey airline — he put everything on. 

By everything, we mean all the clothes that wouldn't fit in his checked luggage. That's 10 shirts and eight pairs of pants.  

And how was Hawaii rewarded for his ingenuity and out-of-the-luggage thinking? BA denied him a seat and called the cops on him.  

Then things really got hopping after po po maced Ryan and introduced him to the ground after he refused to leave.   

Hawaii tried the next day with EasyJet, which turned out to be not that easy. Ryan finally made it back on a Norwegian airline. BA and EasyJet have reportedly refunded Hawaii. 3528285]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIDWVAIAKRFRVVCFBIDR5943MFJVTFC2KSPA3GALAZARZVZPAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0A3/366/0A3366049792495C96A9565C501AC7B2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ryan Hawaii]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ryan Hawaii Iceland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ryan Hawaii British Airways]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ryan Hawaii barred excessive clothing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline baggage fees]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-grocery-accidentally-sells-poisonous-blowfish-meat-3528276</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese grocery accidentally sells poisonous blowfish meat 3528276]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GAMAGORI, JAPAN — An emergency warning was sent out in a coastal city in Japan on Monday after packages of fugu were mistakenly sold to customers.

The Japan Times reports that a grocery store in Gamagori accidentally sold five packages of assorted fugu or blowfish meat with its poisonous parts still intact.

Three of the packages have been recovered, but two have yet to be found.

The liver and internal organs of blowfish are known to contain tetrodotoxin, a lethal neurotoxin 1,200 times more potent than cyanide. One fish has enough poison to kill 30 adult humans, according to National Geographic.

Tetrodotoxin targets motor neurons, causing numbness in the lips, loss of muscle control, and organ paralysis. A fatal dose could lead to respiratory arrest and death. There is no known antidote.

Despite the danger, blowfish meat is a delicacy in Japan. But because of the high risk, only rigorously trained and licensed chefs are allowed to prepare the deadly dish.

There are still those who die from blowfish poisoning, though these are mostly amateur cooks or sport fishermen who try to cut the fish up themselves. 3528276]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLWIYKUARCWMVIYLADR3KJHGECVZSC7KWIFVTCRKZFAVCZDAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/859/511/85951102A4D446EABF35C6327F561A24.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fugu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blowfish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ puffer fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fugu poisoning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blowfish poisoning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tetrodotoxin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deadly food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neurotoxin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poison]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poisonous fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poisonous food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japanese delicacy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/teens-are-eating-tide-detergent-pods-in-latest-viral-challenge-3528272</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Teens are eating Tide detergent pods in latest viral challenge 3528272]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — Some of this generation's teens are now ingesting Tide detergent pods … because the internet told them to.

CBS reports that the challenge might have started as a funny meme, since the pods have an uncanny resemblance to certain sugary treats.

Many a sweet-toothed toddler have grabbed the colorful pods thinking they were candy, and instead got a nasty surprise.

The tiny packets contain concentrated detergent, which is made from chemicals like ethanol and hydrogen peroxide, and meant to wipe out dirt and grime. Doctors warn that the chemicals can cause vomiting, diarrhea, and internal chemical burns.

Thousands of young kids have been injured from ingesting the pods, and at least one has died.

And yet here we have teenagers popping the damn things despite all the warnings. They display it all over the internet and dare other kids to follow suit, so they can become social media famous.

Stupidity kills, kids, which means humanity is doomed. 3528272]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAFEC3SKMBRAVCHLJIAZ9L4GMEVZFZLAWKFMHICANLRRWZHAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/633/849/6338496E3D664AA3B58BCFCD87C3B9C5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tide pod challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tide pod]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tide pods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tide detergent pods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ detergent pods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laundry detergent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ online challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social media]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poison]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic chemicals]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-meanings-behind-the-tattoos-on-arrested-yakuza-boss-body-3528219</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The meanings behind the tattoos on arrested Yakuza boss' body 3528219]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOPBURI, THAILAND — Thai police recently arrested fugitive Japanese yakuza boss Shigeharu Shirai after pictures of his tattoos went viral on Facebook.

The 74-year-old Yakuza boss fled his country after he was allegedly involved in shooting a rival gang member in 2003. Shirai's tattoos led to his internet fame when someone uploaded a photo of him playing a checkers game. 

Other pictures showed that Shirai is missing a part of his little finger, that is the result of Yubitsume[c], a self-administered punishment when Japanese yakuza gangs make a mistake or break a gang's code.

While people are intrigued by Shirai's body art, tattoos were actually used as punishment for criminals in ancient Japan as it would make it difficult for them to re-enter society after they are released from the prison. However, the yakuzas see tattoos as a mark of pride as there are meanings behind each one.

The samurai on Shirai's back is quite common among yakuza folks, it represents the samurai code: honour, courage, loyalty, and proper action. 

The flower on his nipple could mean three different things: a peony, lotus, or chrysanthemum. A peony represents wealth, elegance and prosperity, it also can relate to masculinity or a daredevil attitude. The lotus in Buddhist culture means the struggle for something to reach its full potential. A chrysanthemum represents the Imperial family and links to longevity and joy.

According to Kotaku, the flower has yet to be coloured on Shirai's abdominal area is  called sujibori, a tattoo that has an unfinished story, while the water tattoo element on his lower back illustrates change, adaptation and life.

According to Thai authorities, Shirai will be charged with illegally entering Thailand and then deported to Japan to face murder charges. 3528219]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNFMYADBEDWPBRUB6LRV7DXGIABZRZQA2JRVUCRBRFAZVZJLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E95/0EC/E950EC7C4489476FBD73A7DC25E6C909.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>104</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yakuza boss arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yakuza boss arrested in thailand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yakuza tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yakuza tattoo meaning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tattoo meanings for gang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tattoo meanings men]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shigeharu shirai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Yakuza]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Japan]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cocoliztli-epidemic-connected-to-salmonella-subspecies-3528164</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cocoliztli epidemic connected to Salmonella subspecies 3528164]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TEPOSCOLULA-YUCUNDAA, MEXICO — Scientists have come one step closer to unlocking the secrets of an centuries-old contagion.

New research published in Nature Ecology and Evolution details a study looking at teeth from the remains of 29 skeletons at a centuries old burial site in Teposcolula-Yucundaa.
Those at the burial site are said to have died during the cocoliztli outbreak, a 1545 epidemic that killed millions.

The study linked the DNA found at Teposcolula-Yucundaa with a subspecies of Salmonella enterica connected to the deadly enteric typhoid fever. 

The cocoliztli outbreak lasted from 1545 to 1550. According to National Geographic, another study from 2017 found the same bacteria on the remains of a Norwegian woman who passed in 1200.

But whether or not the Mexican outbreak was from colonial Europeans remains unknown. 3528164]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAFXXTUKMFFCCZULNIAZKBFMAES5E37KWKWTU3WKZAWVA3UKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DAB/B06/DABB067D8F394F1E87E84F284E3CA67C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cocoliztli]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ salmonella]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cocoliztli epidemic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient pathogen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mexico epidemic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient mysteries]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/six-b-52-stratofortress-aircraft-deployed-to-guam-3529164</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Six B-52 Stratofortress aircraft deployed to Guam 3529164]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GUAM — America's Air Force is sending half-a-dozen B-52 heavy bombers to Guam.

Six B-42H Stratofortress bombers, along with 300 airmen, are being deployed from  Barksdale Air Force Base in Louisiana to Guam. Those aircraft have an operational range of 8,800 miles.

The B-52 is capable of flying at speeds at 1,037 km per hour, or Mach. 0.86, at a 
height of 50,000 feet while carrying a nuclear payload. 

According to Technical Specifications on Boeing, the aircraft's wingspan measures 56.4 meters, while it's length and height are 48,5m and 12.4m respectively. Its powered by 8 Pratt and Whitney engines that can provide up to 17,000 lbs of thrust.

Those engines can support a maximum take off weight of 480,000 lbs including a crew of five, 312,197 lbs of fuel and 70,000 lbs of armaments. 3529164]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLRMYCXASKWPVKHLNLAI9BGMACV5FK9K2LR3HTRAACWRBRPKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/60A/294/60A294236A964B3181C762E3054A32B3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ guam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ b-52 stratofortress]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ air force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ b-52 in action]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ b-52 explainer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boeing b-52]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-wants-to-blow-up-space-junk-using-giant-lasers-3529151</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China wants to blow up space junk using giant lasers 3529151]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[XI'AN, CHINA — China has come up with a new plan to rid the Earth of its space garbage, using giant lasers.

Wired reports that Earth's orbit is currently cluttered with fragments from old satellites and rocket stages, called space debris, which number at least 20,000.

Satellites and spacecrafts are frequently at risk of colliding with the fragments and being damaged by even small, pebble-sized pieces.

To address this problem, Chinese researchers from the Air Force Engineering University in Xi'an have proposed a plan to launch a satellite-mounted laser that will emit short bursts of infrared light to target small debris. 

The laser will break down the space debris into tiny, harmless particles, and hopefully rid the Earth of its space junk.

The plan sounds reasonable enough, but of course, with China, there's no telling if the space laser will actually be for cleaning, or be used as a tool for world domination. 3529151]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCAIY3VK6LWIWKHLNJFZ92AMRDSXS3RKWJFPUAAARBRVBRCAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0BF/478/0BF47800705C4E77A73CD70F94AB4847.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debris]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space junk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space garbage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space laser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china laser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china space laser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant laser]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-middle-school-student-denied-lunch-for-50-cent-debt-3529113</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Texas middle school student denied lunch for 50 cent debt 3529113]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FORT BEND COUNTY, TEXAS — A Texas mom says her 12-year-old son was denied school lunch from a cafeteria worker because of a debt less than a buck. 

Sixth-grader Matt Williams says he refused lunch at James Bowie Middle School for having a negative account balance of 50 cents.  

I was hungry, my head hurted, I felt kind of dizzy a little bit, Matt told KIAH. 
Apparently, before the Christmas break, Matt was trying to get a drink and a bag of chips. 

When it got time to pay, the lunch lady told him he didn't have anymore money left on his account and that he was out of luck. 
According the Matt and his mom, students and even faculty often carry negative balances and can still get food.  

The principal has since reached out to Matt's mom to apologize. 3529113]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IFPXTWAMCFCBAYBMBAI9BFMRDSVF39LWJRZGZGK5BWXVCVKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A87/40E/A8740E3F49D04C4CA42449093484DA0B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ school lunch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ student denied lunch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ student denied lunch debt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ student lunch account balance]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/your-car-is-spying-on-you-here-s-how-3529102</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Your car is spying on you. Here's how 3529102]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — You probably know your phone is spying on you, but what you might not realize is that your car is doing it too.

The Washington Post reports that connected cars can track and monitor location, driving habits, fuel usage, and even music preferences, and relay this information back to automakers.

The data is supposedly meant to update car features and improve safety, and in some cases help law enforcement evaluate accidents or crashes.

But it can also put consumers at risk. Location data can be used to infer sensitive information about a person's health, religion, or political affiliation, and a unique profile can be developed with enough data points.

With no car privacy rule to regulate them, automakers can partner with data firms, and generate revenue when the information is sold to third party companies.

Car companies technically inform customers about the data collection, but they're often buried in lengthy contracts.

Despite claims that driver data is not shared without consent, a lack of transparency means customers don't know what happens to their data and how exactly it is used. 3529102]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NACXREBFJFCVRTLJPFZ7LYGEDBXSK7KRCFPHICARDA7BKXAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EC4/C3E/EC4C3E4E328E4488A694DB115D6B44C9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ privacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car privacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car spying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ no privacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big brother]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big brother on wheels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data collection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data firm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ personal data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ private information]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/google-is-going-to-build-three-new-underwater-internet-cables-3529008</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Google is going to build three new underwater internet cables 3529008]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA — Google is planning on laying three new underwater cables in 2019 to help expand its cloud business. 
The company announced its new routes in a blog post on Tuesday, CNBC reported. 

The first will run from Los Angeles to Chile, the second will link the U.S. to Denmark and Ireland, and the third will connect Hong Kong and Guam. 

The cables are set to be ready by 2019. The cable from L.A. to Chile will allow Google to provide better cloud services to users across Latin America. 

The cable running from the U.S. to Denmark and Ireland will boost capacity for North Atlantic users.

The Hong Kong-Guam cable will help Google reach customers in the Pacific region and Australia. 

Google now has investments in 11 cables that are planned or under construction, CNBC reported. 3529008]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLWXCAIAREAGBZ9LVBFZ7LXMFKSXSTZLWIFZHIAA2IRVBZBLB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/601/DE9/601DE97CFC2E4C6AB876224A3BCF3160.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google undersea internet cables]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google cloud services]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google internet cables]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/seven-year-old-delivery-boy-sparks-debate-in-china-3528999</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Seven-year-old delivery boy sparks debate in China 3528999]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[QINGDAO, CHINA — A video showing a 7-year-old boy making deliveries in the eastern Chinese city of Qingdao has gone viral.

The image has added fuel to the ongoing debate about child poverty in China. Published on Chinese video site Pear Video, Li Changjiang[c], nicknamed Little Li, delivers packages to people on his little delivery cart. In an interview Pear Video, Little Li says that he delivers up to 30 packages a day. 

According to multiple reports in China, since the age of 3, Little Li was raised by his father's former colleague, Yan Shifang[d]. Little Li's father is believed to be dead due to abuse of alcohol, and his mother remarried and lost touch with him.

After picking up several odd jobs, Yan started working a delivery man and began bringing Little Li with him going around the city. Surprisingly, Little Li enjoyed the delivery job and soon wanted to have his own little delivery cart. 

Ever since the video was posted online on January 14, Little Li's story has been one of the most discussed topics on China's social media site Weibo, with most commenters expressing sympathy and hopes for a better life for Little Li.

The BBC reports Little Li is now staying with a welfare centre for children and will be enrolled in a school soon. 

Little Li is not the only child who become online famous because of his story. A picture of a 7-year-old child, nicknamed 'Ice Boy', went viral for the image of him covered in ice after walking 2.8 miles to school. 3528999]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIFKXRHAMDFCARTB5AR374RMMBBTEZKLWJR5URGBRBA5Y36BD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A4A/642/A4A642B6B4F64F31AC0E7767C26BEFE2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>103</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ young courier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ courier kid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ courier kid china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ child labor china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese courier boy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ child poverty in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ child without parents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ grow up without parents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ little li]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Qingdao]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-koreas-are-going-to-march-under-one-flag-at-winter-olympics-3530166</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The Koreas are going to march under one flag at Winter Olympics 3530166]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYEONGCHANG, SOUTH KOREA — One of the coolest things about the Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang this February is the sudden thawing of tensions between South and North Korea. 

The two countries dropped a bomb, announcing they'll march under one flag at the opening ceremony. 

The plan is to also field a joint women's hockey team. 

And as a bibim-bonus, the North is also throwing in its 230-member all-female cheerleading squad.  

Pyongyang may send up to 500 athletes, cheerleaders, musicians, officials and reporters across the demilitarized zone. 

North and South Korean skiers will train together at a resort in North Korea before the games.

It remains to be seen if the goodwill during the games will continue after the Olympics, but knowing Kim Jong Fatty — the world should be just fine. 3530166]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMBWXCABKVGAKDTALNKFZKDVMEDV7ERQKJPFVFKXKFLAPWCUKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8C0/A0A/8C0A0A771240C0A6E8CCFA2DAE7F5735.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>86</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Winter Olympics 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Winter Olympics PyeongChang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un Winter Olympics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North Korea South Korea Winter Olympics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Korea Unification]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Winter Olympics]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-koreas-are-going-to-march-under-one-flag-at-winter-olympics-3530161</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The Koreas are going to march under one flag at Winter Olympics 3530161]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYEONGCHANG, SOUTH KOREA — One of the coolest things about the Winter Olympics in Pyeongchang this February is the sudden thawing of tensions between South and North Korea. 

The two countries dropped a bomb, announcing they'll march under one flag at the opening ceremony. 

The plan is to also field a joint women's hockey team. 

And as a bibim-bonus, the North is also throwing in its 230-member all-female cheerleading squad.  

Pyongyang may send up to 500 athletes, cheerleaders, musicians, officials and reporters across the demilitarized zone. 

North and South Korean skiers will train together at a resort in North Korea before the games.

It remains to be seen if the goodwill during the games will continue after the Olympics, but knowing Kim Jong Fatty — the world should be just fine. 3530161]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIRPC3TA6IAMY3AKFLWZLDRMJIETFAKLWJWZHRBBSIRKBRCKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/56C/A10/56CA109941BABD1B5679E54B5867D08D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>86</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Winter Olympics 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Winter Olympics PyeongChang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kim Jong Un Winter Olympics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Korea South Korea Winter Olympics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Korea Unification]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Winter Olympics]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cape-town-could-run-out-of-water-in-90-days-3529909</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cape Town could run out of water in 90 days 3529909]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAPE TOWN, SOUTH AFRICA — One of the biggest cities in South Africa may soon become the first major city in the world to run out of water.

Cape Town is facing a water crisis, and has less than a hundred days before Day Zero on April 21, when the water supply is expected to run out, according to the South African.

Years of extreme drought have caused storage levels in dams to drop below 30%. Once it falls to 13.5%, taps in the city will be shut off.

Local authorities restricted water usage to 87 liters per person per day, but after only 39% of residents complied, the limit has now been lowered to 50 liters.

Its four million residents are being told to take 2-minute showers, and have been banned from filling pools, watering gardens, or washing cars.

Households that go over their water allowance will also be asked to pay higher tariffs.

After Day Zero, citizens will need to line up at one of 200 water collection points throughout the city, where each can collect a maximum of 25 liters a day.

Authorities have also been looking into alternative ways to source water, like wastewater recycling, drilling into aquifers, or seawater desalination. 3529909]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEARMDCUK6IRCYKFBSKR39UYG2KSXR3RK2KFZTZAANJRTAAIAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/071/21C/07121CCD10C94F5BB8CCECCFED6BE451.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drought]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ no water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cape town]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cape town drought]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water shortage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water supply]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south africa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water rationing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rations]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tennis-player-struggles-to-peel-banana-at-aussie-open-3529759</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tennis player struggles to peel banana at Aussie Open 3529759]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA — Bananas proved to be tennis player Denis Shapovalov[d]'s toughest obstacle at the Aussie Open.

On Monday, Shapovalov played against Greece's Stefanos Tsitsipas[e]. During the changeover in the third set, Shapovalov struggled to peel a number of bananas and looked really annoyed with the stubborn fruit, but the persistent Canadian finally managed to eat one before taking his first victory at the tournament.

This is not the only banana-related incident that happened during the tournament. On the same day, American tennis player CoCo Vandeweghe [f]got the strangest code violation for wasting time because she refused to take the court until she'd had a banana, and called the umpire rude for not letting her wait for her banana delivery. 3529759]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNFAXRCBRDWPY3ALICW7K44NBJSXFZKA2LW3HTTBSJR7ACUBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C4D/60D/C4D60D0099A843498FA23051946B3E95.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ peeling banana skin off]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to peel banana the right way]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ peel bananas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ denis shapovalov aussie open]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ denis shapovalov tennis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aussie open 2018.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/skyscraper-sized-asteroid-set-to-pass-close-to-earth-in-feb-2018-3529751</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Skyscraper-sized asteroid set to pass close to Earth in Feb 2018 3529751]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — A massive space rock will fly past Earth in February — the largest that's expected to come close to the planet this year. 

Newshub reports that asteroid 2002 AJ129 is 1.1 kilometers wide, making it slightly longer than the Burj Khalifa, the world's tallest building.

The asteroid is hurtling through space at a speed of more than 107,000 kilometers per hour, 15 times faster than the hypersonic X-15 aircraft.

It is set to pass within 4.2 million kilometers from Earth on February 4, 2018, a distance NASA considers 'potentially dangerous' despite a low chance of a direct hit.

If an asteroid this size were to collide with Earth, studies suggest debris could cloud up the atmosphere, blocking the sun and causing temperature drops that could trigger a mini ice age.

NASA is currently incapable of intercepting an asteroid beelining straight for Earth. That technology won't be ready until after 2024.

Best keep your fingers crossed that no giant space rocks decide to come knocking til then. 3529751]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLWIACXAEBR3DRXLSKF79U4GZABRSZKKBKRTTIGAAAFRBZHKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EEE/693/EEE693702FD0437680289DA193ABB5AA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid apocalypse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid approaching Earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2002 AJ129]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid hit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid collision]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space rock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mini ice age]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burj khalifa X-15]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypersonic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-iphone-workers-allegedly-exposed-to-toxic-substances-3529684</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese iPhone workers allegedly exposed to toxic substances 3529684]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SUQIAN, CHINA — Workers at an Apple iPhone suppliers' factory in Suqian, China are exposed to toxic substances, according to an investigation.

The report by New York-based China Labour Watch has criticised Chinese factory employees working at Apple supplier Catcher Technology work 10 hour days, six days per week.

The report also claims that the workers face exposure to toxic substances. It claims some workers hands aren't adequately protected by the provided gloves and that protective ear plugs and eye wear are not always available.

China Labour Watch says that some employees' eyes have experienced vision issues from cutting fluid and that noise in the factory can cause irreversible hearing damage.

The report also claims the factory's wastewater was directly dispensed into the public sewage system. Analysis of this found that it exceeded local standards for water quality.

In May last year, the report says 90 were sent to hospital following a chemical leak at the plant, and that five were in intensive care as a result. Investigation of the incident by the Administrative Committee of the Suzhou-Suqian Industrial Park said the cause was a mechanical failure, notes the report.

Apple told the Guardian it investigated these claims, interviewed 150 factory workers and found no violations of it's code of conduct. The tech giant told the paper that workers were provided with protective equipment and that wastewater was treated appropriately. 3529684]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRAFXYAGKZGFCXCFLWKRRKBBMVDBISC5AZAWVTICAMFF7AC5AA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D4E/5B9/D4E5B9E41931434CAF64A2A148FC118D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ factory worker in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese iphone workers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ catcher technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china labour watch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese iphone factory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apple]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apple code of conduct.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-working-on-underwater-water-missile-barge-3530339</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea working on underwater water missile barge 3530339]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG — North Korea is working on a barge capable of launching ballistic missiles from underwater.

The North has begun work on a second submarine-launched ballistic missile test stand barge. According to 38 North, it resembles old Russian PSD-4 test barges.

The barge reportedly measures 9 meters by 22 meters, making it around one third of the length of the Sinpo Class Submarine.

According to submarine expert HI Sutton, the old Soviet raft could be sunk to a set depth, and then the missile would be launched from a central a tube. 3530339]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVAWECRHKVAAGVATLMDF79SHG2LS7RZNKJJFTTIGK6JACBRCBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E1D/3D3/E1D3D3D5D1FCA62852C0F5CBDB38F27D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>38</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dprk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea missile barge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ slbm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sinpo class submarine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian psd4]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ submarine-launched ballistic missile test stand barge]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cashier-free-amazon-go-store-opens-to-the-public-3531773</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cashier-free Amazon Go store opens to the public 3531773]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Amazon's first cashier-free store in Seattle is now open to the public, nearly 14 months after it began a trial run for company employees.

The New York Times reports that customers enter the Amazon Go store via an app on their phones, which generates a QR code that is scanned on an electronic turnstile.

Cameras mounted on the ceiling do not have facial recognition technology, instead detecting motion and sensing depth to track shoppers through the store.

This, combined with weight sensors on the shelves, helps the system identify what items are being picked up by which shopper.

Once an item is taken off a shelf, it is added to a customer's virtual cart. If an item is picked up but later returned, the system removes it from the cart.

Once the customer finishes shopping and leaves the store, the cost of items in the cart is calculated, and the total amount charged directly to the linked Amazon account.

Despite having no checkout and no cashiers, the store has staff to check the IDs of shoppers purchasing alcohol. Employees are also on hand to restock shelves and prepare the store's ready-to-eat meals.

Amazon has said it might open more Amazon Go stores in the future, but the plans are not immediate, and the company wants to focus on its flagship store for now. 3531773]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NWKAKVB5DATWAVLNLW5K2CMZDE5EZQK6KF7FAAAEAAKDTXBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/54E/201/54E201FBFE4BAC17584AAB14783758FE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>84</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon go]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon go store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cashierless store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ automated store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weight sensors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ camera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motion detection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motion tracker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon account]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seattle]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-government-goes-into-shutdown-mode-3531614</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. Government goes into shutdown mode 3531614]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The U.S. government shutdown at the weekend after legislators failed to reach a funding agreement.

Shutdowns happen when the U.S. President and Congress fail to sign a bill authorising spending to let the government function.

There's been 19 in total. Past shutdowns have gone on for a few days to several weeks.

Essential services such as the post office, TSA and air traffic control will continue as normal. As will the military, border guard, prisons and social security.

Meanwhile non-essential staff will be furloughed and won't go to work on Monday. Services such as the ATF, Department of Education and National Parks could be affected during this time.

The 2013 government shutdown saw up to 850,000 not report to work, reports CNN. 3531614]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNWCCRDB5BAEW3ALVCR79LRM2JVXRC2AIDWVUTSKRAWKDRAAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/06E/E03/06EE036291114EB08021C25A21E52568.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ government shutdown]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ government shutdown explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us government shut down]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shut down explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ congress shutdown]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shutdown explained]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/compact-nuclear-power-system-%0Acould-sustain-life-on-mars-3531604</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Compact nuclear power system 
could sustain life on Mars 3531604]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MARS — NASA is testing a nuclear fission reactor prototype that could enable long-term stays on the surface of the red planet.

The Las Vegas Review-Journal reports that the first humans on Mars will need to be able to generate power to transform the planet's water and carbon dioxide into liquid oxygen and fuel.

To enable such a feat, NASA and the Department of Energy have come up with the Kilopower project, a nuclear power system that comes with a Uranium reactor core, which uses fission to generate electricity.

Kilopower can generate 1 kilowatt of electricity, which can power a toaster, to 10 kilowatts, which can light up 100 bulbs.

Four to five 10-kilowatt units will be needed to power the habit- charging vehicles, generating safe drinking water, and oxygen.

The months-long testing for the kilopower prototype began in November at a Department of Energy National Security Site in Nevada.

Though a flight test is at least six to eight years away, if all goes well, the technology could be ready by the mid-2020s to early 2030s. 3531604]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDFMD3XKICRPBA9KEARTKLRMEBV7UTRKFJATUACAWJFKBAFAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C2D/46C/C2D46CFE946447138D53C1054F19B719.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars habitat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life on mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kilopower]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear reactor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uranium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars electricity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ martian]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars settlement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bat-researchers-discover-how-brain-maps-where-others-are-3531532</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bat researchers discover how brain maps where others are 3531532]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[REHOVOT, ISRAEL — New research on bats published in the journal Science provides insights into how the brain maps the social geography of areas.

Researchers trained pairs of bats, with one alpha male labelled as a teacher and the other a student, to retrieve fruit from a stand inside a room. They noted how student typically tracked the teacher's path toward the fruit.

The bats were fitted with technology to record brain cell activity. Activity was normal in students bats acting on their own, but fired when tracking the position of the teacher. Researchers believe this was social place-cells in the hippocampus.

Students bats also tracked objects like balls and dice but their brain activity responded differently. Researchers suspect this could provide insights into how that the brain cognitively maps out the environment socially, and physically. 3531532]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMBWVCKSK5ERCVRULWIAVL4UMZABKEANKSKFPFIKKNKWEVIEAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A0A/B0C/A0AB0C0ED2E640D3858787E91DE994C5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how bats fly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social place cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how do bats fly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain social tracking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain social map]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/brain-wasting-zombie-deer-disease-could-strike-humans-next-3532658</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Brain-wasting zombie deer disease could strike humans next 3532658]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FORT COLLINS, COLORADO — A mysterious neurological disease is laying waste to North American deer, and scientists worry humans are next.

The Atlanta Journal-Constitution reports that since its discovery in 1967, chronic wasting disease has infected deer populations in 24 US states and Canada, and has also been found in South Korea and Norway.

Chronic wasting disease is caused by prions, deformed proteins which accumulate in certain organs. Infected deer can live two years before symptoms like weight loss, thick saliva, and behavioral changes manifest, according to the CWD Alliance.

The disease is contagious, and typically spreads via the saliva and feces of diseased deer, which can contaminate the environment and infect other animals.

Prion diseases are typically limited to certain species, but may evolve to overcome the interspecies barrier and infect new hosts.

Mad Cow Disease is one example, with humans contracting the disease from eating cows that had been infected by prions from sheep.

While no humans have been infected by CWD, monkeys in a recent study reportedly contracted the disease after ingesting infected deer meat.

Public health officials continue to monitor for any sign of brain-wasting diseases in humans. They have also warned hunters not to consume deer meat without getting it tested, regardless of how healthy the animal looks. 3532658]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIFXDTXAVHRCBCAL2PAK6JANAESKETSLSIF3UZAA6IFABZBLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/75F/D26/75FD2612D1454FCBAF47596EBA9AFFA8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chronic wasting disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CWD]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zombie deer disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zombie deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neurological disorder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infectious disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interspecies barrier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interspecies infection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mad cow]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/delta-cracking-down-on-fake-service-pets-3532486</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Delta cracking down on fake service pets 3532486]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTA, GEORGIA — Delta is tightening its regulations for passengers who travel with emotional-service pets. If an airline as crappy as Delta is doing something, it must be a problem. 

Delta says it's seen a big uptick in incidents involving poorly trained animals since 2016. More and more the airline is getting complaints of animals taking a leak, dropping deuces and even biting other passengers. 

Starting on March 1, passengers traveling with service pets need to show Delta proof of health or vaccinations for the animal 48 hours before flying.

People traveling with emotional- or psychological-support animals will need a signed note from a doctor confirming the animal won't go berserk. 

In the past, Delta said passengers who have tried to use turkeys, possums, snakes and even spiders as support pets. 

From now on, if you're looking to bring hedgehogs, ferrets, insects, rodents, snakes spiders, possums, amphibians, non-household fowl or animals with horns, tusks or hooves on a flight, you're going to have to find someone other than Delta. 3532486]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSJRPCRGA2JRKVASKAAAV9UXMSIEXFANAFPFMUZGK2KWGWZQAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D6E/7DC/D6E7DC0E99684238A01E464B593EB32B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delta air lines animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emotional support animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delta animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emotional support animals on flights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animals on flights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delta air lines]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sushi-lover-found-5-foot-long-tapeworm-in-his-body-3532417</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sushi-lover found 5-foot-long tapeworm in his body 3532417]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FRESNO, CALIFORNIA — A sushi fanatic from Fresno ended up with a 5-foot-long tapeworm, and doctors think the ridiculous amounts of raw fish may be the reason.  

The man went to the the ER and complained about bloody stool. The doctors did not think anything particular was up until the dude pulled out a tapeworm from a grocery bag. 

Turns out the tapeworm was actually 5-and-a-half feet long. The man said it felt like his guts were coming out on the can. He then tried to grab the little fellow, but it started moving.

The CDC had released reports of contaminated Alaskan salmon being infected with Japanese broad tapeworm parasites. 

The man and his doctor figured out it was his daily feast of salmon sashimi that was most likely the cause. 

The guy is now taking medication and has given up sushi — for now. 3532417]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASNFCCKXB5CRMVI7L5CR39LYMSKB5RKRK5DWTURLKAFRXAKTBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/49C/B23/49CB23F7F12542F581700EBFADF4A31A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tapeworm sushi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tapeworm found in man's body]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tapeworm man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant tapeworm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tapeworm food]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/serial-stowaway-sneaks-past-tsa-boards-plane-to-london-3532355</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Serial stowaway sneaks past TSA, boards plane to London 3532355]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — A woman with a history of sneaking onto planes without a ticket has been caught yet again — though not before flying all the way across the pond.

The Chicago Tribune reports that serial stowaway Marilyn Hartman has been arrested several times since 2014 for attempting to hitch free plane rides.

In her latest stunt, the 66-year-old hid behind her hair and snuck past two TSA agents who were checking boarding passes at Chicago's O'Hare airport.

She tried to board a plane to Connecticut, but was turned away by the gate agent.
Undeterred, Hartman took a shuttle to the international terminal, where she stayed overnight.

The next morning, she blended in with a large group of passengers and successfully got past a gate agent and a CBP officer, making it onto a flight bound for London.

The crafty criminal initially hid in the plane's bathroom, but later walked out and found an empty seat. She eventually was busted at Heathrow when she was unable to present a passport.

Hartman was put on a flight and sent straight back to Chicago. She's now being held on a $25,000 bond, and has to wear an ankle monitor to keep her away from any airports. 3532355]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKFCCTSAECRKCRSLFIAK7DVGIAVXU35KMAF5GKYKBKWAVRMKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3D5/6C7/3D56C7CC6CE847B4889346226AC5BD2E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ serial stowaway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stowaway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TSA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane ride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman gets on plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman sneaks into plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Marilyn Hartman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ London]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chicago]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport security]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-thinks-the-us-navy-breached-its-sovereignty-again--3532299</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China thinks the US Navy breached its sovereignty (again) 3532299]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SCARBOROUGH SHOAL, SOUTH CHINA SEA — The People's Republic got mad last week after one of Uncle Sam's destroyers sailed near an island China claims.

U.S. Navy officials says USS Hopper, a destroyer vessel, sailed near the Scarborough Shoal last week, reports Reuters.. The rocky outlet is claimed by Taiwan, China and the Philippines.

China says the vessel came with 12 nautical miles of the island and breached the country's sovereignty by doing so.  The Chinese Navy reportedly ordered the USS Hopper to withdraw immediately after discerning its identity, reported Reuters.

The U.S. says it was an innocent passage and followed international law. 3532299]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAWPYKTKRBWEBZRBSPRX7BFGIEB5EC6AIDATT3WK5ARGBT5LC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/458/D20/458D20A8A11A44279D4F1BA32F5AC9BD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south china sea dispute]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south china sea us navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china claims]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uss hopper south china sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  scarborough shoal]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/moscow-testing-a-100-megaton-torpedo-nuke-says-pentagon-3533516</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Moscow testing a 100-megaton torpedo nuke, says Pentagon 3533516]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — A leaked draft of a Pentagon document suggests that Russia is working on an underwater thermonuclear torpedo.

First reported by the Washington Free Beacon, the project — codenamed Kanyon by the Pentagon — was conceived to target coastal areas, naval bases and sea ports. The weapon is believed to operate autonomously, the New York Times reported, citing officials. Russia reportedly refers to the device as Ocean Multipurpose System Status-6.

According to Popular Mechanics, the weapon operates like a drone. It has a range of 6,200 miles, can dive to over 3000 feet and travel at 100 knots (around 115 mph). The warhead measures 5.5 feet wide and is 79 feet long, reported Popular Mechanics, citing submarine expert H. I. Sutton.

The device can also wield a 100 megaton nuclear payload and reportedly has the radioactive isotope Cobalt-60, meaning area struck by it would be dangerous to humans for around a century. It is being tested by the Russian Navy on a Sarov-class submarine which carries it on its pressure hull, reported Popular Mechanics. 3533516]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMDAPDAJKFKAEATDL6JW57JGMVBSZSIMKFJRTGIKA6IWPBADKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/56F/561/56F561649FC74E53A94125F8507DB9EF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian nuke torpedo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moscow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ torpedo nuke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater nuke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater atomic bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ocean Multipurpose System Status-6]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kanyon bomb]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kentucky-school-shooting-leaves-2-dead-17-wounded-3533193</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kentucky school shooting leaves 2 dead, 17 wounded 3533193]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BENTON, KENTUCKY — Two are dead and 17 others injured after a teenage boy opened fire inside a Kentucky school.

The Lexington Herald Leader reports that the incident at Marshall County High School in Benton, Kentucky began just before 8 a.m., when a shooter started firing at students in the common area.

The rampage continued as the students ran for cover. A 15-year-old girl was shot and killed on the scene, while more than a dozen others were wounded.

Five shooting victims were airlifted to a Nashville hospital, where one boy later died from head wounds. The four others are expected to survive after being shot in the head, arm, chest, and abdomen.

Police have apprehended the 15-year-old male suspect, who will be charged with murder and attempted murder.

The gunman's identity has not been disclosed since he's still a juvenile, but will likely be made public if the case is moved to adult court.

At least nine US school shootings have been reported so far in 2018, but the incident in Kentucky is the year's first fatal school shooting. 3533193]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARBWMAKXKRCR7AI9B6KWZ6L3MFIB7FALA2PRXTAKANJAMWZIAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/807/A06/807A06B0EAA94CFBBE5F1CA4CC948A9F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kentucky school shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ school shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kentucky shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kentucky high school shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ teen shooter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marshall county school]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ benton]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kentucky]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/artificially-cooling-the-planet-may-do-more-harm-than-good-3533168</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Artificially cooling the planet may do more harm than good 3533168]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COLLEGE PARK, MARYLAND — Scientists are looking to engineer the climate to fight global warming. But a new study shows it may do more harm than good.

AFP reports that stratospheric aerosol injection is a form of geoengineering that involves spraying sulfur dioxide into the upper atmosphere to form clouds that reflect solar radiation.

Using computer models, a study published in Nature Ecology and Evolution found that spraying 5 million tonnes of sulfur dioxide above the equator every year for 50 years could drop surface temperatures by one degree Celsius.

But if sulfur seeding is suddenly stopped, the planet would warm rapidly, with temperatures rising several times faster than the predicted rate.

Plant populations would die out, and wildlife, especially amphibians and land animals, wouldn't be able to migrate quickly enough. The loss of just one species could impact an entire ecosystem.

It just goes to show how tricky it is to mess with something as unpredictable as climate. So despite all the benefits we think geoengineering might bring, we're probably better off focusing on reducing greenhouse gas emissions. 3533168]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDFKDIGKEDAGBRWL5DWZ7DWMAEBTEC9AWJWXGAAKAFRVARPAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2BD/64E/2BD64E62AF2E4B1BA2ABD6605E73BB3D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geoengineering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar geoengineering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sulfur dioxide spray]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon emissions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon dioxide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ greenhouse gas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stratospheric injection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stratospheric aerosol injection]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/eagles-bro-slams-into-a-subway-pole-like-a-true-philly-fan-3533138</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Eagles bro slams into a subway pole like a true Philly fan 3533138]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA, PENNSYLVANIA — Philly fans are excited. Just ask this subway pole. An amped up Philly bro was attempting to get Eagles fans pumped before the big game.  

Eagles fanatic Jigar Desai[c] was waiting for a train to catch the NFC Championship against the Minnesota Vikings.

Desai noticed a bunch of Eagles fans in another subway train, so he decided to Philly bro them up.
  
Jigar decided to run next to the train while playing cheerleader, but unfortunately, the subway pole had other plans for Jigar-Jigar. 

Philly's finest also got some actual facetime with the train. Desai took some time, but he eventually got up. 

Luckily for Desai he was able to make it to the game to watch the Eagles destroy the Vikings. 3533138]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIAAGCIAK6IAPWTDB6LRZ74SGJIBXST6KSPF5TIDAECWKBRABH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2F8/711/2F87118BD3534F93991ADBDF9D8FCDD3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan runs into pole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan hits pole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan reaction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sports fan interactions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ philadelphia eagles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/super-blue-blood-moon-to-bring-earth-a-lunar-trifecta--nasa-3533048</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Super Blue Blood Moon to bring Earth a 'lunar trifecta': NASA 3533048]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOON — NASA says Earth is in for a lunar trifecta of a super blue blood moon on January 31, 2018.

Lunar orbit of Earth follows a 29-day cycle. The blue moon, like the one on January 31, occurs when there are two full moons in a calendar month.

The moon will also be close to Earth during this time, meaning it will be brighter than normal. This is called a supermoon. 

When the moon passes through the Earth's shadow during the Jan. 31 lunar eclipse it will appear red. This creates the blood moon.

Most of Asia, Australasia and the northwestern America will be able to see this super blue blood moon, while much of South America, Africa and West Europe will not.
The rest of the world will be able to see it partially depending on their location.

The last time a total lunar eclipse to coincided with a blue moon was in 1982, reports Time, citing NASA programmer Ernest Wright and ex-NASA astrophysicist Fred Espenak. 3533048]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFMCIIAMCRPWAVBSLAI9USNFJB3RCRKECF3TILK5DRCWAMBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5F8/7E6/5F87E621003748B3BBD724F996FB7A2D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super blue blood moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total lunar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super blue blood moon 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total lunar eclipse 2018]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-successfully-clones-first-monkeys-from-transferred-dna-3534318</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China successfully clones first monkeys from transferred DNA 3534318]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI — China has cloned monkeys using transferred DNA, possibly paving the way for human cloning.

Nature reports that biologists in Shanghai have cloned two genetically identical macaques using the same technique that produced Dolly the Sheep.

Somatic cell nuclear transfer involves taking the nucleus of a cell, which contains its genetic material, and injecting it into an egg that has had its own nucleus removed.

The egg cell is then treated with enzymes to stimulate embryo development, just like a naturally fertilized egg.

In all, the researchers created 109 embryos and implanted them into 21 surrogate monkeys, resulting in six pregnancies but only two live births.

The macaques, named Zhong Zhong and Hua Hua, aren't the first primates to be cloned though — that distinction belongs to Tetra, a rhesus monkey created using a simpler embryo-splitting method.

The Chinese team believes the monkey clones could be useful in medical research, specifically in the study of genetic diseases like Parkinson's or autism. 3534318]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNRGDZABBKAADIXBJJAX9DUGICB7R34KABWRG3TASLRPVAABG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6C7/E36/6C7E36680FA3450E82EAEFA3F3AE95E9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cloned monkey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ monkey clone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ macaque clone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cloning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal cloning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human cloning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cloning technique]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ somatic cell nuclear transfer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SCNT]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dolly the sheep]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ring-of-fire-is-active-warns-united-nations-3534255</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ring of Fire is ACTIVE, warns United Nations 3534255]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE PACIFIC — Recent volcanic and seismic activity in various Pacific Ocean nations prompted the UN to warn that the Ring of Fire is active.

The warning, posted to the official UN Office of Disaster Risk Reduction Twitter feed, comes after eruptions and earthquakes hit areas in the Philippines, Indonesia, Japan and Alaska this week.

As the naming implies, it is a ring of hundred of volcanoes spanning 25,000 miles across the Pacific Ocean. Much of it was created through the subduction of tectonic plates.

This is where oceanic crust of the earth clashes with heavier continental plates, and is forced underneath them due to the weight, reports DW. The resulting pressure is explosive and results in magma eruptions and earthquakes.

Because of these subduction zones, the Ring of Fire is home to 452 volcanoes and around 90 percent of the world's earthquakes. 3534255]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAWXAKTKIGA5YIRL5CRILDXGVABZU32KACFTTIKBRDA3WRCKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/781/0D9/7810D9FCE5A2408C955B313964D10271.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pacific ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tectonic subduction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ring of fire pacific ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ring of fire volcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ring of fire earthquake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ring of fire pacific ocean video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ring of fire pacific active]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indonesia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ philippines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-flu-can-kill-3534165</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How the flu can kill 3534165]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — The flu season in the U.S. this year has been particularly harsh, already having claimed the lives of at least 30 children, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.   

Although most people do not die from the flu, young children and people with other illnesses, such as heart disease, lung disease and diabetes are at elevated risks. 
Adults can succumb to the flu in three ways: pneumonia, sepsis and heart attack. 

Pneumonia can develop in a person who is infected with influenza.

Pneumonia causes the small air sacs of the lungs to fill with fluid or pus, sometimes leading to death. 

With sepsis, the influenza virus can trigger the body to release chemicals into the blood to fight infection that triggers inflammation throughout the body. That inflammation can then trigger multiple organ system failure. 

The third way the flu kills adults is by triggering heart attacks. A new study in the New England Journal of Medicine found that a person is six times more likely to have a heart attack during the week after being diagnosed with the flu, compared to the year before or after the infection. 

Experts are urging people to get flu shots, even though it may not always prevent an infection from the flu virus. 3534165]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDWKACUKRBA7CAVLWJWT6JAGWKVXFK4AFIW7GRKKMFWAATYAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/483/EE9/483EE9E7A87247619F39467EA6A4E0CC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu shots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu pneumonia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu sepsis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu heart attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ influenza]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/swedish-team-plan-to-build-hotel-and-spa-on-river-3534109</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Swedish team plan to build hotel and spa on river 3534109]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LULE RIVER, SWEDEN — A team of Swedish architects have unveiled plans to construct a floating luxury hotel.

Dubbed The Arctic Bath and Spa, the hotel will be placed on the Lule River in Harads village, northern Sweden, reports Fortune. It will be frozen into the river during the winter and float the rest of the year.

Inhabitat reports the hotel could potentially open this year. 3534109]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5BRAYAFKBLWGX3HLNJRIL2GMACVTRTSAFKWPT3YKBIFEAABLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9AA/347/9AA347BB2868473FA5D5F73129C667FA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>38</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ floating hotels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ buildings that float on water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lule river]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swedish river]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ floating hotel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic bath and spa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luxury hotel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unique creations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luxury escapes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luxury hotels in sweden]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-hampshire-man-bites-police-dog-dog-bites-back-3534048</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New Hampshire man bites police dog, dog bites back 3534048]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOSCAWEN, NEW HAMPSHIRE — A New Hampshire man bit a police dog while resisting arrest, and let's just say it didn't end well.

Fox News reports that state troopers responding to a shooting incident had managed to detain three people, before being told a fourth one was hiding in a trailer on the property.

The suspect ignored repeated commands to surrender, prompting the homeowner to break a glass door to gain entry.

K9 Veda entered the trailer while the suspect was trying to hide under some clothes. After kicking and punching the dog and troopers, he got Veda in a chokehold and bit her on the head.

The dog didn't like that one bit, and promptly returned the favor. Troopers tasered the suspect and finally brought him in.

Veda has been cleared medically and is back on the job. Can't say the same for the perp, who really should've known better than to out-bite a trained K9. 3534048]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LRAAAFASLR7D3HB6JA5KLVM5CE5S35ABKFXTIAKZAWKWIMLB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4B8/5B2/4B85B22C046440B797F0CBC0D9239123.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man bites dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man bites police dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog bites man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ k9]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new hampshire state trooper]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/eagles-fan-punches-police-horse-outside-eagles-stadium-3534025</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Eagles fan punches police horse outside Eagles' stadium 3534025]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA, PENNSYLVANIA — This Eagles' fan had a mix-up with a police horse. 

The incident happened prior to the Philadelphia Eagles dominating win over the Minnesota Vikings. When a mounted state police officer was attempting to clear a crowd near the stadium, 19-year-old Andrew Tornetta refused to corporate and became very aggressive at the cop.

The teen decided to show the police some brotherly love by punching the horse right below its eye, before trying to cowardly hide in the crowd.

The brainless teen was charged with aggravated assault, simple assault and recklessly endangering another person. 3534025]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAWVDKXKIGRECIUL2JWT7UUNEESKFIIA5DWZGCRA5DAZBRKKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2EC/35B/2EC35BF55D634B71A81033F4B1681E5B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan mix up with horse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mix up with horse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan losing control]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan crazy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eagles fan out of control]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Philadelphia Eagles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-bites-into-iphone-battery-it-explodes-in-his-face-3534006</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese man bites into iPhone battery, it explodes in his face 3534006]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOMEWHERE IN CHINA — A man in China who was out shopping for an iPhone battery decided to bite it to see if it was real. Thought that only worked with gold.   

Einstein was reportedly at an electronics store somewhere in China shopping for a replacement battery last Friday. 

Apparently in China, you bite into things to see if they're fake. It's even better when the thing you're biting into contains battery acid. 

The Chinese guy finds a battery and decides to go to town on it like it's chicken chow mein. The jaws of fury then cause an explosion that hilariously envelopes the man's head. 

Unfortunately, the guy made it through the accident with only his ego destroyed. 3534006]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIWCCRIAIDAKCARLWJAKKDYGEDSKUT2LSJWVTABAZDWMWAEAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3D6/EA8/3D6EA82478DE46228A7BFC7EAEC20748.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man biting iphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man bites iphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese man bites iphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biting iphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone explodes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone battery]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tesla-on-autopilot-rear-ends-fire-truck-while-driving-at-65-mph-3533962</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tesla 'on autopilot' rear ends fire truck while driving at 65 mph 3533962]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CULVER CITY, CALIFORNIA — The U.S. government is looking into an accident involving a Tesla Model S on auto and the rear end of a fire truck.

Culver City firefighters were attending the scene of an accident on Monday when a Tesla Model S, reportedly driving on autopilot, struck the rear of a parked fire truck.

Fire officials said the car was traveling at 65 miles per hour before it crashed into the truck on Interstate 405. No one was hurt in the accident, but it has prompted an investigation by the U.S. National Transportation Board.

Tesla told KTLA that autopilot function is intended for use by fully attentive drivers. The function isn't fully autonomous. 

According to the San Jose Mercury News, firefighters advised the drive to see medical staff after the crash but he refused treatment and showed no major injuries. 3533962]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKRMCADA2IRPDRVLEBAX9SBGFJBRS34AVCFXHTXA6IACCRHKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/658/8E8/6588E8D5038B52737148F498A4E280A5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tesla model s fire truck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ telsa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tesla autopilot crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tesla autopilot accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tesla autopilot fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tesla model s crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elon musk]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hackers-using-fake-cryptocurrency-apps-to-steal-money-personal-data-3535342</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hackers using fake cryptocurrency apps to steal money, personal data 3535342]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Hackers are using malicious cryptocurrency apps to steal money and personal data from Apple and Google apps stores, according to a new study. 

Researchers from internet security firm RiskIQ looked at more than 18,000 apps to find ones blacklisted by cybersecurity vendors, CNBC reported. 
They discovered 661 blacklisted cryptocurrency apps across 20 app stores including Google Play and Apple's App Store. 

Google Play offered the highest number of malicious apps with 272 available for download. 
Hackers used phrases like bitcoin exchange, bitcoin wallet and cryptocurrency to trick potential victims, the report said.  

RiskIQ recommended investors thoroughly research possible exchanges and wallet apps before use. People should check the developer's name, user reviews and number of app downloads. 3535342]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LFEDIFARAAGVKHLRDWTKD3MJLSXRAQKNLRTGCYK6IR3WKXAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D45/19D/D4519DE8D25B17F5496D92D6C1D527B5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency apps]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malicious cryptocurrency apps]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Apple App Store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google Play Store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sdv-1000w-south-korea-s-10-person-military-submersible-3535334</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[SDV 1000W: South Korea's 10-person military submersible 3535334]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL — The South Korean Navy has a submersible that also doubles as a surface vessel.

According to Korean Naval manufacturer VOGO, the vessel can be deployed via airdrop from a C-17 or C-130 aircraft. It can carry a crew of 10. 

On the surface the SDV 1000W can travel at 35 knots, or 40 mph via diesel engines and waterjet propulsors. While submerged it can travel at 6 knots or 7 mph using lithium polymer batteries and silent electric motors.

Submarine expert H I Sutton reports that the vessel functions like a wet-sub, in that the crew still wear diving gear and receive oxygen from a sizeable on-board air system. This lets passengers exit underwater, but the vessel can also be run up a beach. 3535334]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABLFVY3TAREFCAISL6LRT9DXGMABVRC4KMAAXGIBBRAACAABKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4DC/3A4/4DC3A4389C87C5C532B155844D95B460.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater boat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sdv 1000w]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south korea navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ VOGO]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UDV]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ submersible]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/earliest-human-remains-outside-africa-found-inside-israeli-cave-3535171</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Earliest human remains outside Africa found inside Israeli cave 3535171]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ISRAEL —Scientists have found what they suspect is the earliest human remains outside of Africa in a cave on Mount Carmel, Israel.

The partial upper jawbone, found in a 2002 excavation then intensively analyzed for 15 years, is said to be between 170,000 and 200,000 years old. According to the Smithsonian Magazine, many archaeologists believed humans migrated from Africa 60,000 years ago.

Details of the finding were published this month in the journal, Science. 3535171]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAFCYCXKIBWECRXL2JA5LUSMMEB3RAIA2KFZHTSKECWPAKVAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4BF/D0E/4BFD0E9F4670EC6DCF45B1AF29538667.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earliest human remains found]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient humans remains]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ most ancient civilization]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oldest human remains]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient humans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient findings unearthed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oldest ever human remains]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ m]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/50-cent-forgot-he-had-700-bitcoin-now-worth-8-million-3535091</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[50 Cent forgot he had 700 Bitcoin now worth $8 million 3535091]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — While everyone was going bananas for Bitcoin at the end of last year, 50 Cent apparently had 700 Bitcoins he totally forgot about.

Back in 2014, he released Animal Ambition and became the first artist to accept Bitcoin as payment. 

From the deal he received more than 700 Bitcoins. Those coins are now worth $7 - $8 million — for now.  

Bitcoin is currently at around $11,200, but still remains highly volatile. 

Not bad from a kid from South Side, I'm so proud of me, 50 Cent wrote on IG. At least someone is. 

Just think how proud 50 would have been of himself, if he sold when the price was at $20. Looks like 50 had 21 questions but a Bitcoin wasn't one. 3535091]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6JFCAKWAABR7BA9LJJF77L3GIESKU35KBLFTFKYKADAMARKAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2A3/2EF/2A32EF5475FE8596775D14F19774B919.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 50 Cent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 50 Cent Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 50 Cent forget 700 Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Curtis Jackson Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 50 Cent broke]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/recurring-snowfall-on-the-sahara-evidence-of-global-warming--3534890</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Recurring snowfall on the Sahara evidence of global warming? 3534890]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VLADIVOSTOK, RUSSIA — Recurring snowfalls on one of the hottest places on Earth stems from global warming, says a top Russian meteorologist.

The Russian News Agency reports that on January 7, a blanket of snow fell on the Sahara desert, near the northern Algerian town of Ain Sefra.

The Sahara has been known to get as hot as 122 degrees Fahrenheit during the day. But while temperatures drop at night, it's unusual to see snow due to the dry air.

In 1979, snow fell in the area for 30 minutes. It was 37 years before the next snowfall, but only a year passed between then and the most recent one, which saw 15 inches of snow cover.

According to Roman Vilfand, Head of Russia's Federal Service for Hydrometeorology and Environmental Monitoring, the frequency of such an unusual weather phenomenon is evidence that global warming is on the rise. He adds that the same is true the current cold spell in the eastern US, an unusually warm Russian winter, and rainfall and flooding in Western Europe

With the state of the climate as dismal as it is and with no signs of improvement, guess there'll be more extreme weather in our future. Yikes. 3534890]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNWGCKUBEARPB3ABICWX94XGSJVXS3RK6KW3UCTAEAFKYC6AC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E0D/03E/E0D03E3A96594C66BC0E37D22EF34718.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snow on the sahara]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sahara snow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sahara snowfall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ desert snow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ desert snowfall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extreme weather]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flat-earther-still-planning-to-launch-self-in-homemade-rocket-3534812</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flat-Earther still planning to launch self in homemade rocket 3534812]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLAT EARTH — Remember Mad Mike Hughes? Of course not, why would you.

A few months ago, Mike made headlines over the flat Earth when he tried to raise money to launch himself in a homemade steam powered rocket a mile across the Mojave Desert.

The plan was to shoot himself high enough to see that the Earth is just a disc. Unfortunately, paperwork and mechanical failures stopped the November launch from happening. 

Mike went back to the drawing board and redesigned his rocket and now says he's good to go on February 3. 

The plan is to fly straight up for a third of a mile and then let gravity take over. But does gravity really exist? 
Hughes eventually says he wants to shoot himself up 52 miles in the air by year's end to see for himself the shape of the Earth.  

He says it'll cost him $2 million for the hot-air balloon, rocket pack and space suit to get him to his vantage point. 
Maybe Mike should hit up Kyrie Irving or  J.J. I don't believe in dinosaurs Reddick for the cash. 3534812]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANNFVXTSBAEFICZYLJPFRLSCGFIBVERMAJKWRHKRAACRPCZHBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E0D/03E/E0D03E3A96594C66BC0E37D22EF34718.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earthers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mad Mike Hughes flat earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mad Mike Flat Earth launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mad Mike flat earth rocket launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kyrie Irving Flat Earth]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hackers-using-youtube-ads-for-cryptomining-3537041</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hackers using YouTube ads for cryptomining 3537041]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Hackers are using YouTube as a way to turn passive viewers into cryptocurrency miners, according to cybersecurity firm Trend Micro.

The issue was brought to light at the beginning of the week over social media with complaints that YouTube ads were raising red flags in anti-virus software, Mashable reported. 
A service called Coinhive was apparently taking over a viewer's CPU and using it to mine digital coins. 
According to Trend Micro, attackers used Google's DoubleClick ad software for traffic distribution.

Japan, France, Taiwan, Italy and Spain were affected by the malvertising campaign. 
Google confirmed the cryptojacking threat, and eventually blocked the ads and removed the malicious actors from their platform. 3537041]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEBRIDADKWKAZBA7KFKA77JANACBIURNKNIWRHALKBJAGV3RAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/572/FA9/572FA953CD824F7CB27A4226FAF830E6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube cryptomining]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptomining]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptojacking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Coinhive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/raw-pork-delivered-in-shopping-carts-sparks-investigation-3536963</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Raw pork delivered in shopping carts sparks investigation 3536963]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN JOSE, CALIFORNIA — Photos of raw meat being handled under iffy conditions at a California supermarket have gone viral, sparking disgust and outrage among netizens.

The San Jose Mercury News reports that Loretta Seto was about to shop at 99 Ranch Market in San Jose when she spotted two men delivering slabs of raw, unwrapped pork in shopping carts. 

Seto snapped a photo of the carts and put it up on Facebook, along with a warning that the carts came from a Costco across the street. Assuming the carts were returned uncleaned, that means countless customers have probably been contaminated with nasty meat germs and don't even know it.

Responding to the post, the market claims they've dumped the pork in the photos, but deny involvement and say they've filed a complaint with the vendor.

That vendor is Jim's Farm Meat Co. in Winton, who in turn claims the meat left their facility wrapped and in a combo bin. They're not sure if the delivery method was a request from 99 Ranch, but are looking into the matter and have since fired the two delivery men.

An investigation is also being carried out by the Santa Clara Department of Environmental Health, who caught wind of the issue from Seto's post. 3536963]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJAIX3SASKFXB3ELSLRT72BGVCS7E35A6PWVHZCANLFACRFBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BF2/B3A/BF2B3AAF57764A879ABB65337C9FCD62.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meat in shopping cart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raw meat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raw pork]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contaminated meat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contaminated pork]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ germs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shopping cart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unsanitary]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unsanitary meat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dirty meat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dirty shopping carts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shopping cart germs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 99 ranch market]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Costco]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-soldiers-are-accidentally-leaking-intel-through-fitness-apps-3536799</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. soldiers are accidentally leaking intel through fitness apps 3536799]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Information about location and staffing of U.S. military bases around the world has been revealed by a fitness-tracking company.

The data was released by Strava in a data map that indicates all the activity tracked by users of the fitness app, the Guardian reported. 

The Global Heat Map published by Strava uses satellite information to plot the location and movements of its users over a two-year period by lighting up areas of activity. 

The app can be used on smartphones or fitness trackers to see running popular routes in cities, or track people in remote areas. 
Military analysts discovered over the weekend the data also reveals sensitive information about U.S. soldiers on active service. 

Nathan Ruser, a researcher at the Institute for United Conflict Analysts, first discovered the oversight. 

If soldiers use the app like normal people do, by turning it on tracking when they go to do exercise, it could be especially dangerous, Ruser said. 

In locations like Afghanistan, Djibouti and Syria, Strava users are almost all foreign military personnel, meaning their bases stand out brightly. 

Strava apps and devices can have their location services turned off. The company issued a statement urging users to visit their website to make sure they fully understand the privacy settings. 3536799]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSNFVCAGBRFARBCELVAAXKLXMJIBRE3SAFIR3HRFKNKWGVT9BH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/68A/2AD/68A2ADC52AC84C3F98DB88F21B941F49.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Strava Global Heat Map]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Strava fitness tracking company]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fitbit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US military personnel fitness apps]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US soldier fitness apps]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/secret-service-issues-atm-jackpotting-warning-to-banks-3536765</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Secret Service issues 'ATM jackpotting' warning to banks 3536765]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The U.S. Secret Service this week issued an alert, warning banks about an ATM exploit known called jackpotting.

According to online security blogger and journalist Brian Krebs, the Secret Service has been warning banks that attacks are taking place in the USA. Krebs, citing the Secret Service alert, reports that thieves use an endoscope attached to a phone to find an internal part of the ATM that'll connect with their laptop.

After that, the cash machine appears as Out of Service and will be in control of the thieves, according to the Secret Service alert reported by Krebs. They can order the ATM to dispense currency to a collector, or money mule, at a rate of 40 bills per 23 seconds.

The Secret Service alert warms the exploit targets ATMs inside pharmacies and big box retailers as well as drive-thru ATMs, according to Krebs. 3536765]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAAIXADK2KFRBIUBABA79U3MNJS7STRK6PWMTAAAAARAVZHKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E05/E06/E05E06DEA5AF4045A2DDF9AA58B1624A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atm jackpotting hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us secret service]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atm jackpot hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atm jackpotting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atm robbery hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atm machine robbery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cash machine jackpot]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/wherever-you-look-your-eardrums-move-with-your-eyeballs-3536699</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Wherever you look, your eardrums move with your eyeballs 3536699]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA —  New research has found that eyeballs and eardrums work together to decode vision and noise.

Researchers discovered found that eardrum movement corresponds with where the eyes are looking, even when no sound is present.

The research was published in January in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences. 3536699]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIAWVDIIK5FA3ARTLSPWZL4SGJJV7S32A6IWXUCRAEDWIAAMLH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E05/0E8/E050E894FB7949CA91FE815F478711C9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>34</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ duke university]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sight and sound]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how do we see and hear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how do eardrums work]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how do the ears work]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eardums and eyes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how do we see]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how does hearing work]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how does the sound we hear reach the brain]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-jet-flies-within-5-feet-of-u-s-navy-plane-over-black-sea-3537906</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Russian jet flies within 5 feet of U.S. Navy plane over Black Sea 3537906]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BLACK SEA — A Russian jet unsafely intercepted a U.S. Navy plane, the latest in a series of close calls between the two countries over the Black Sea.

According to a press release from the U.S. Naval Forces Europe-Africa, a U.S. EP-3 plane was conducting a reconnaissance mission in international airspace over the Black Sea on Monday when it encountered a Russian aircraft.

The Russian military reportedly detected an unidentified aircraft approaching their airspace, and sent a Sukhoi SU-27 fighter jet to intercept it.

The SU-27 came within five feet of the U.S. plane, crossing directly in front and causing it to fly through a trail of turbulent air.

The intercept lasted a total of 2 hours and 40 minutes.

According to the Pentagon, the EP-3 did not do anything to provoke the Russians, and that such actions increase the risk of miscalculation and mid-air collisions.

But Russia's Defense Ministry denies any wrongdoing, claiming its jet flew in accordance with international law when it intercepted the U.S. plane, reports CNN. 3537906]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAFADKXKMCACVKCBJKR79LSMECE7F35AJJRZHZBASLWKDRAAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/978/A81/978A81DD4CDF4542A128CC58635C4BE8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian jet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US navy plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unsafe intercept]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SU-27]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EP-3]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US plane intercepted]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian jet intercepts US plane]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-team-considers-nationalizing-5g-network-3537816</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump team considers nationalizing 5G network 3537816]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — National security officials in the Trump administration are considering nationalizing a part of the country's mobile network to protect it against China, Axios reported. 

A PowerPoint and memo made by a senior National Security Council were obtained by Axios. The documents suggest the U.S. needs a centralized nationwide 5G network within three years. 
The government could pay for and build a single network or it could have wireless providers build their own 5G networks. 

The presentation talked about the need to build a network in order to compete with China's dominant position in the manufacture and operation of network infrastructure. 
The documents say that it would be faster for the government to build a network and then rent access to carriers like AT&T and Verizon.  

They also argue that a secure 5G network is vital for the development of emerging technologies like autonomous vehicles or virtual reality, as well as to counter Chinese threats to US economic and cyber security. 3537816]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZDWPCKVKRBRKVR7BWKR792GMABSKSZIKEAWVGTRAJIA7XTUKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B36/CD1/B36CD1E14B8A4CFFBE2EC01A3954F10B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[5G network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump nationalized 5G network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wireless technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[information infrastructure]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/united-bounces-lady-enroute-to-visit-dying-mother-3537570</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[United bounces lady enroute to visit dying mother 3537570]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PUEBLO, COLORADO — United demonstrated how to #flythefriendlyskies last week once again, this time by ejecting a woman enroute to see her dying mom. 

Last week Carrol Amrich was flying from Colorado to Minnesota to see her dying mom. 
According to the New York Times, she checked in, scanned her ticket at the gate and got on the plane. 

According to the New York Times, the ticket was bought by Amrich's landlord Ines Preslas via Traveller Help Desk, and then changed to an earlier flight through United Airlines when they heard Amrich's mother's condition had gotten worse.

But while she was strapped in, a gate agent came to remove her and said her ticket was refunded. Nobody flies for free, the gate said to her, Amrich told the Times.

Back in the airport, Amrich called Prelas and put her onto the gate agent. Prelas offered to pay for the ticket again via credit card, saying they could work out the details later. Sadly though the flight left, without Amrich.

Next, Amrich drove 1,000 miles without stopping in a last ditch attempt to see her moribund mother, but by the time she got there her mom was gone. 

A customer rep for Traveller Help Desk told the Times by email that they were sorry for Amrich's loss, and had they been contacted directly all of this could've been avoided.

Prelas said a United rep explained that changing the ticket through them wouldn't cause any problem, even though it had been booked through an online travel agency. 3537570]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMCACXTSK6KWMDZUBJJR7L4WNECS7ST2KIAFMGIKAADWMBZEKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7DA/009/7DA009EF0B5B4FDBBB06E0EC72E3FDE1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united airlines ejects passenger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fly the friendly skies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united airlines removes passenger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united removes passenger]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-runs-from-traffic-cop-and-ends-up-getting-tased-in-the-ass-3537533</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man runs from traffic cop and ends up getting tased in the ass 3537533]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — Police cam footage shows how one man tries to run from a traffic cop, only to get tased in the behind. 3537533]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSJFADRGAECAEDZYBSKW76DSNEESTST2K5ARTT3YAMAR5VZAAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B5C/857/B5C857275F474ED9B7D238D701AC714C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>570</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupid criminals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ running from the cops]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tased by police]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tased while running]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how tasers work]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how taser guns work]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chicago]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Illinois]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ running from police]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ traffic cops]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/frozen-meteor-collected-by-villagers-actually-airplane-feces-3537452</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Frozen meteor collected by villagers actually airplane feces 3537452]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FAZILPUR BADLI VILLAGE, INDIA — Indian villagers found what they thought was a frozen meteor, but turns out it was actually frozen feces.

The frozen meteor reportedly crashed into a farmer's field on Saturday. 

Meteors can be worth lots of money, so people flocked to the field and gathered pieces of the rock to stash them in their refrigerators. 

The yellow-brown meteor was said to be around 20 pounds and had a transparent surface that resembled ice. 

A group of scientists from India's Meteorological Department conducted research on the samples of the meteor, and surprise — the meteor was actually frozen human feces.

Folks later learned that their refrigerators were preserving airplane poop this whole time,  so they had to clean everything in their houses that had come in contact with the meteor.

Aviation experts said human waste that leaks or is discarded from the sewage system of an airplane usually turns into clumps ice in the time that it takes to reach the ground. 3537452]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBKWGCICAZDRKVRULVART944GIDVTEC5KMCF5UTTBSIRMWRGAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8B7/242/8B72425028F24CECB16CC09CEAA87ECF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-01-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frozen meteor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fallen frozen meteor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airplane feces]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ feces from airplane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frozen feces from airplane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ things fall from the sky]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meteor in india]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
