<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/rare-two-headed-copperhead-snake-found-in-virginia-3705016</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Rare two-headed copperhead snake found in Virginia 3705016]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WAYNESBORO, VIRGINIA — Scientists are ecstatic over the discovery of an exceptionally rare two-head copperhead alive in the wild.

According to the Wildlife Center of Virginia, a woman in Northern Virginia spotted a baby copperhead snake slithering in her yard, and upon closer inspection found it had two heads.

Radiographs revealed that each head has its own brain, trachea, and esophagus, but shared a heart and a set of lungs. The left trachea is more developed than the right, while the right esophagus is more developed than the left.

Scientists say it's better for the right head to eat based on the snake's anatomy, but are attempting to feed the left head due to it being more dominant and responsive.

Two-headed serpents are an extremely rare find in the wild as they often have trouble coordinating their movements when escaping from predators, which contribute to their short life spans.

The competing heads also tend to fight over food, though this particular copperhead's mutation is such that its heads don't quarrel, and seem almost oblivious to each other.

Herpetologists estimate the animal is about 3 weeks old, but have yet to figure out its gender. They will continue to monitor the snake, and likely place it in a zoo or educational facility if it survives. 3705016]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMBWVCRJKIERCACCLFPAI9JCGIDS7RC6AICAVUACAREREAREAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D6B/21B/D6B21B7AADA72204EE9AFFAB4C7459AE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ two headed snake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ two headed copperhead]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ copperhead]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby copperhead]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby snake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rare snake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ venomous snake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viper]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snake]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/pcbs-in-ocean-threaten-livelihood-of-killer-whales-3704997</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[PCBs in ocean threaten livelihood of killer whales 3704997]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DENMARK — Toxic chemical polychlorinated biphenyls, or PCBs, were found lingering in marine life such as killer whales, according to a new study published in the journal Science.

PCBs were banned in most countries decades ago, however they are still used in some parts of the world, which has allowed them to gradually seep into oceans, according to CNN.

PCBs were used in paints, coolants, carbonless copy paper and other products. 

PCBs can be consumed by plankton, which are then eaten by larger fish. As the PCBs move up the food chain, they become more concentrated. 

This puts killer whales in danger of consuming highly concentrated PCBs as they are near the top of the food chain. 

The chemical was found to disrupt the whales' reproductive system, brain function and the endocrine system.

Mother whales can also pass the deadly chemicals on to their offspring through lactation.  

Researchers warn animals living off the coasts of the UK, Brazil, Hawaii, and Japan have a high risk of population collapse because of PCBs.

ORCA, a charity group dedicated to protecting whales, described the report as an absolute tragic state of affairs and… needs immediate action. 3704997]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IAAYAFAFJWPAKALRDR374WNABBZRK3AJKR3FKXAECR3CZKAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EF0/0D0/EF00D025565153EA439DF3ACB46608B7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>81</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PCBs chemicals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic chemicals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ killer whale]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic pollutants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ killer whale threatened by toxic chemicals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ banned chemical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic chemical threatening marine life]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/limiting-kids-screen-time-could-boost-brain-power-3704931</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Limiting kids' screen time could boost brain power 3704931]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  — An observational study has found that two hours of recreational screen time a day along with more sleep is linked to improved cognition in children.

According to a study published in the Lancet Child and Adolescent Health, the Canadian 24-hour Movement Guidelines recommends 9 to 11 hours of sleep per night, less than two hours of screen time, and an hour of physical activity daily for kids aged 8 to 11.

But a study of 4,520 U.S. children found that only 5 percent met all three recommendations. Forty-one percent met at least one guideline, 25 percent met two guidelines, while 29 percent met none at all. 

On average, American children slept 9.1 hours per night, had 3.6 hours of recreational screen time per day, and 3.7 hours of physical activity per week.

According to the findings, screen time and sleep had the strongest links to improved cognition, and kids with more than two hours of screen time had poorer development.

Researchers say parents should manage screen time, and suggest encouraging more physical activity and tech-free zones. 3704931]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JFCCKVAMBAEARRBBJF76DYM6KVRSTRK2PA5GCXKNKREYAKAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CCB/7E9/CCB7E97DB8F598495ED0DFD49B5C5B55.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ screen time]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kids health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cognition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ improving cognition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ screen exposure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ health guidelines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ physical activity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ better brains]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-neuron-circuit-shows-gut-has-direct-link-to-the-brain-3704769</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New neuron circuit shows gut has direct link to the brain 3704769]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA — A new Duke University study has found a new neuron circuit that proves the gut has a more direct connection to the brain than previously thought.

Science reports that enteroendocrine cells lining the gut have protrusions similar to neurons, leading researchers to suspect they may be sending signals to the brain via the vagus nerve.

When a fluorescent green rabies virus was injected into the colons of mice, the virus labeled the vagus nerve before landing in the brain stem, proving there was a direct circuit.

Enteroendocrine cells grown in the same petri dish as vagal neurons connected together and began firing signals. The cells released the neurotransmitter glutamate, involved in conveying senses like taste or smell, which the neurons picked up on within 100 milliseconds.

The findings could have massive implications on our understanding of appetite and how to suppress it. Current suppressants target slow-acting hormones, but going after the synapses may in fact be the more effective approach. 3704769]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIRCDTXABJAKWZ7KBIRI7JAMVES3UT9AFLFVTKTKSLFAAIAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/D87/1EE/D871EEB6F2DB43EAB06395D7F7561601.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut brain connection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neuron circuit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut sense]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ enteroendocrine cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vagal nerve]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ second brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glutamate]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/creepy-skull-shaped-asteroid-to-pass-by-earth-for-sequel-flyby-3704726</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Creepy skull-shaped asteroid to pass by Earth for sequel flyby 3704726]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — Earth will be having another spooky encounter with a 'death comet' that first swung by our planet three Halloweens ago.

Spain's agencia SINC reports that asteroid 2015 TB145 is a skull-like space rock that came within 310,000 miles of Earth on October 31, 2015.

Dubbed 'The Great Pumpkin' by NASA due to its Halloween flyby, the asteroid is set to once again pass by our planet on November 11, 2018, but at a much farther distance of 24 million miles.

Observations during the first flyby indicate that the asteroid most likely completes a rotation in 2.94 hours, and reflects only 5 to 6% of sunlight, making it just slightly more reflective than charcoal.

Astronomers think the asteroid may be an extinct comet that lost its water and other volatile compounds after numerous orbits around the sun.

Though the second approach may not be as favorable as the first in terms of distance, scientists say they will still be able to observe and obtain new data on the spooky space rock. 3704726]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIRIYZHABLWIB3EBNLRTLDXGFIERUZIAWJWMGZKASIRMWRFAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6E0/9B0/6E09B081DD9C085EA479CB37E8A49E18.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skull comet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skull asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ creepy asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ death comet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid flyby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skull rock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the great pumpkin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space rocks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid 2015 tb145]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2015 tb145]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween asteroid]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fruit-heavy-diet-makes-melbourne-zoo-animals-fat-rots-their-teeth-3705539</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fruit-heavy diet makes Melbourne Zoo animals fat, rots their teeth 3705539]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA — Animals at the Melbourne Zoo are dealing with obesity and bad teeth, thanks to a fruit-heavy diet that's chock full of sugar.

Fruits may be a vital component to a healthy human diet, according to an Australian government report, but the same cannot be said for animals, who are getting serious problems after a trip on the fruit train, reports the Sydney Morning Herald.

The problem is that cultivated fruits have been genetically modified to be sweeter than their wild counterparts.

Some, like plums, have nearly double the sugar level nature intended.

Animals love the sugary treats, but end up eating only those and nothing else, which not only plumps them up, but also rots their teeth.

To save the poor buggers from their sweet tooth, keepers are swapping out the fruit for green leafy veggies. 

They're also serving up panda pellets packed with nutrients and minerals to the red pandas. The pellets are mixed in with a little bit of pear, which gets them the red panda seal of approval.

Bottom line is, whether you're human or animal, it's always best to have a balanced diet. 3705539]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KABWEDICKZBRKAIRLZAAK9UWMADB7ST7KRDFPGRLA5DAZACSAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A0E/08E/A0E08EA3F0975C2994D53AA8B73E6D67.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fruit diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ obese animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rotting teeth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ melbourne zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fat animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sugar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ increased sugar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sugar in fruits]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ healthy animal diet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-ramps-up-expansion-of-coal-power-plants-3705523</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China ramps up expansion of coal-power plants 3705523]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA —Satellite images show coal power plants across China appear to be expanding and ramping up production.  

There was an increase in new coal projects across China at the provincial level between 2014 and 2016, up to 259 gigawatts of coal-energy capacity, according to a study by Coal Swarm.

The Chinese government ordered the Huadian Nanxiong coal power plant to be suspended in January 2017, however, two new cooling towers were added in March 2018.

Other images show water vapor appearing from cooling towers at the Zhoukou Longda power station in central China, which means the plant is still in operation.

At present China has 993 gigawatts of coal power capacity but the new coal projects would lead to a 25 percent increase, according to Coal Swarm.

The satellite images show that the central government hasn't been able to control the suspension of more than 100 power plants, with the provincial governments believing the power plants will help boost local economy.

According to the lead author of the study, all coal plants would need to be phased out by 2045 to avoid effects of climate change, according to the lead author of the study. 3705523]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IRCCRFASIAEBAYBJJR76L3MSJVXRT5KZDFXGAEAIEAGATXAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/34E/1EB/34E1EB57309A0FFFED06C2F7CE6FAFE7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>80</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china coal power plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china coal plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new coal plants in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coal plants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate warning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  coal power capacity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Huadian Nanxiong coal power station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ increase of coal power plants being built in China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coal plant construction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coal plant pollution]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/artificially-conceived-lions-cubs-born-in-south-africa-for-first-time-3705348</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Artificially conceived lions cubs born in South Africa for first time 3705348]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PRETORIA, SOUTH AFRICA — Researchers at the University of Pretoria have successfully used artificial insemination to birth two lion cubs.

According to AFP, researchers collected sperm from a male lion and blood samples from a lioness to determine her hormone levels.

After the blood samples indicated it was the correct time, she was artificially inseminated.

In the past, lions would have been moved out of their habitat. Using the new method, the lioness was able to stay in her current environment.

Scientists are hoping this new method can be repeated in order to save the wild lion population in Africa which has been declining over the last two decades.

Lions in 26 African nations are extinct, while those in the wild have plummeted by 43 percent over the past 20 years, according to the International Union for Conservation Nation.

Animal welfare groups however argue that lion breeding in South Africa revolves around tourism rather than conservation. 3705348]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2KFGDIEAEBAKDRRB5DA7K2CMMAV5EC9AZDW3UZAB5CAPARFLG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DF2/641/DF2641E6DC3D1C7BE3C4C5A9A9FD18C1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ South Africa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ worldfirst lions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lion cubs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world first at south africa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial insemination]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial insemination lions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial insemination lion cubs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lions conceived artificially]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-space-rovers-send-back-footage-from-asteroid-3705311</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese space rovers send back footage from asteroid 3705311]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE —  Japan's rovers that successfully landed on an asteroid have sent back their first images.

Japan's space agency made history last week as it was the first to ever land robot rovers on an asteroid. The rovers have now sent back high resolution photos of Ryugu's surface.

Due to Ryugu's weak gravity, Rover-1A and Rover-1B move around by hopping. Each rover stays in the air for 15 minutes and moves horizontally up to 15 meters with each hop.

Rovers-1A and Rover-1B are each equipped with multiple cameras which are now taking stereo images of Ryugu's surface. They have also sent back video of the asteroid's rocky surface.

For the next part of the mission, the Hayubusa 2 spacecraft, which deployed the rovers, plans to land on Ryugu by bombing the surface with a missile to create a landing zone for the ship. It will then collect asteroid samples.

Scientists involved believe the samples will give us a glimpse into the beginning of the universe.

The spacecraft is set to return to Earth by the end of 2020. 3705311]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIRCDIHASIAKAATBSLARKJBM2KSZEANKSLFVGTRASIRIW3VAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6C1/2B4/6C12B426BA6A4C51B7DD2AFEA43FA5D2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unmanned rover]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rovers on asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan rover landing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  japan rover lands on asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan rover in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japanese asteroid mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ryugu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Rover-1A]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Rover-1B]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sample materials from asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hayabusa 2]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-shocked-by-power-of-earthquake-tsunami-in-indonesia-3706248</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists shocked by power of earthquake, tsunami in Indonesia 3706248]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SULAWESI, INDONESIA — Scientists have a theory about what might have caused the tsunami that followed the earthquake in Indonesia last week to be so destructive.

The 7.5-magnitude earthquake struck the center of the island of Sulawesi, triggering 6-meter-tall tsunami waves that crashed in Palu, reports the BBC.

The earthquake itself was a strike-slip quake, which means the ground breaks horizontally instead of vertically.

Scientists say strike-slip quakes often cause tsunamis that are less than 1 meter tall.

Scientists suspect the Indonesia earthquake may have triggered an underwater landslide that destabilized sediment underwater, causing it to break free and tumble.

Palu's bay's elongated shape also may have also worked to amplify the effect of the tsunami.

The earthquake and the tsunami have already caused substantial damage in Indonesia, with more than 1,000 people confirmed dead and many more trapped under collapsed infrastructure in Sulawesi. 3706248]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZCAIYAEL2LWMCKCL2PAK6LWNFLSTRZKAJIFPGCSKEBACWZFLG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8AD/CF2/8ADCF289B1D4E4706CDB2DA5D56DCCC9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Indonesia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sulawesi island]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indonesia tsunami 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indonesia tsunami]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tsunami in indonesia puzzles scientists]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ explaining the indonesia tsunami 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strike and slip earthquake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tsunami waves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tsunami devastation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Palu city tsunami]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ palu tsunami video]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-rams-electric-wire-up-his-junk-wire-gets-knotted-in-his-bladder-3706241</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man rams electric wire up his junk, wire gets knotted in his bladder 3706241]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UTTAR PRADESH — An 18-year-old teenager went to the doctor complaining about pain and said he was having trouble taking a leak. 
When questioned by the doctor, the teen didn't exactly come clean as to why he was in such agony, according to a report published in BMJ Case Reports. 

It appears the problem was a long piece of electric wire shoved into a hole that should only be letting stuff out. 

According to the doctors, the teen was playing his own tune by using the wire to clean out his own clarinet. 
Unfortunately the good times came to an end after the wire became tangled up in his bladder. 
Surgeons at first tried to yank the wire out, surprisingly that didn't work, so they had to go back in with a laser and blast the wire into pieces. 
The operation was a success and the teen was discharged from the hospital 24 hours later. 3706241]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LWPYZFBVCFKDI7BSKRVLDRG2IB7RIQAADRTGILASJWPBANAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8C7/7B3/8C77B3B74B27825341786EE9D0C11957.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bladder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric wire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric wire tangled]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uttar pradesh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ holmium lasers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kavanaugh-blackout-theory-explained-3706081</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kavanaugh 'blackout theory' explained 3706081]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C. — As Judge Brett Kavanaugh continues to deny allegations put forth by Christine Blasey Ford, a theory has been presented attempting to reconcile the two competing narratives.

The 'blackout theory' suggests both parties are telling the truth, meaning Kavanaugh did in fact assault Ford, but doesn't remember it due to an alcohol-induced blackout.

Here, we try to explain the science behind blackouts, and how excessive alcohol intake can affect the memory.

Blood alcohol concentration refers to the amount of alcohol present in the bloodstream, measured by the weight of ethanol, in grams, per 100 milliliters of blood.

Blackouts can occur when the alcohol level in the blood reaches 0.20, which on average is about 4 drinks for women, and 5 for men, according to a report from the National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism. But to understand how this happens, we need to first look at memory consolidation.

In the hippocampus, short-term memories are converted into long-term ones through the persistent strengthening of synapses, a process known as long-term potentiation.

These synapses pass signals through neurotransmitters like glutamate and gamma aminobutyric acid, or GABA. For a signal to fire, the receiving neuron must have a higher positive charge.

Glutamate binds to neuroreceptors and opens it for positive ions, triggering signal firing. GABA, meanwhile, allows in negative ions, which momentarily blocks this action.

Alcohol increases GABA activity, causing it to inhibit signals more often and longer than usual. This prolonged depressant effect impacts consolidation, preventing long-term storage of memories.

Alcoholic blackouts may be fragmentary, in which memory loss is partial, or en bloc, in which stretches of time are completely missing from a person's memory.

Complete blackouts occur around 0.30 BAC. By 0.35, individuals could go into a coma, and at 0.40, the concentration is lethal, typically killing half of all adults who reach it.

If anything, the Kavanaugh case at least helps highlight the dangers of too much booze and though it shouldn't be an excuse for crappy behavior, it's not something to be taken lightly, either. 3706081]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AECFKDCULZDAMAARBVDW56L4GJKS5U3SAVAWRTCTKIBWKBRKBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/635/0C9/6350C93A111EDB110A057C64FAB5D872.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>142</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kavanaugh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ judge kavanaugh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brett kavanaugh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blackouts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blackout drinking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alcohol blackout]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blackouts explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science of blackouts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blackout theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alcohol]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ memory consolidation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ memory formation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bear-shot-during-hunting-trip-falls-badly-injuring-soldier-who-shot-it-3706063</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bear shot during hunting trip falls, badly injuring soldier who shot it 3706063]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOLDOTNA, ALASKA — A soldier in the army was injured after being struck by a falling bear he shot on a hunting trip, reports KTVA.

William McCormick and Zachary Tennyson were on a hunting trip when they saw a black bear above them on a ridge.

They decided to shoot the bear, causing it to start tumbling down the slope, toward McCormick and Tennyson.

The men tried to get away but only Tennyson escaped unharmed.

McCormick was then struck by the 200-pound black bear, along with a bunch of rocks.

McCormick was airlifted by a helicopter to the Providence Alaska Medical Center after receiving serious injuries, according to KTUU. 3706063]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSNRPXAGAFKFECZYLRAFTLURGSKS7ET3KZBWPHCXARDFEWKYAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/496/5E6/4965E6F47799E9F17D949FAA35CB6E4D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Alaska]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soldier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ army soldier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hunting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soldiers shoot a bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soldiers injured]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soldiers injured after bear falls on him]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cdc-encourages-public-to-get-vaccinated-for-flu-season-3707061</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[CDC encourages public to get  vaccinated for flu season 3707061]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — The CDC is encouraging the public to get vaccinated for the flu and common cold as flu season typically starts in October.

The flu can be caused by three viruses, the influenza A(H1N1) virus, the influenza A(H3N2) virus and the influenza B virus.

Symptoms of the flu can include fever, sore throat, and coughing among others.

Flu vaccines such as the standard-dose trivalent shot and the quadrivalent shot are administered to protect against the three flu viruses with an additional B virus for the quadrivalent shot.

People are encouraged to wear a face mask, wash hands and sneeze into the elbow to prevent the spread of the flu, according to ABC News.

Last year's flu season had the highest death toll in more than 40 years, with more than 80,000 people dying from the flu, according to the CDC.

The CDC estimates the flu shot reduces the risk of catching the flu by 40 to 60 percent and is encouraging the public to get vaccinated by the end of October.

The CDC says everyone above the age of 6 months should receive a shot of the flu vaccine in order to minimize the spread of the virus. 3707061]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMBWEXAJKZDWTAKDLRARVL4UMRCSIRT9ABKWXHIAKJIR5WIBAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BC1/3BB/BC13BB31FA6396914F07BE3B0EB641A8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-05T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu shot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ best time to get flu shot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ time to get flu shot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ getting vaccinated for flu season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[influenza A virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ influenza B virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CDC]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu vaccine injection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu season october]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-mega-star-who-went-missing-is-now-fined-for-tax-fraud-3706983</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese mega star who went missing is now fined for tax fraud 3706983]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — Chinese megastar Fan Bingbing has been fined around $129 million for tax evasion and other charges. 
According to the BBC, Fan was part of a government probe into how celebrities reported earnings in their contracts. 
Apparently it's common practice in the land of corruption to use yin-yang contracts —  where one contract has the actor's real earnings, and another contract with a lower figure. The contract with the fake earnings is then sent in for taxes. 
Fan posted a long apology over China's intranet, where she also said, With the good policies of the party and the state, and without the love of the people, there would be no Fan Bingbing.
The Chinese regime has now ordered Fan and the companies she controls to pay the enormous sum in taxes, fines and penalties. 3706983]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZCFAXZEKECWVDI9BMCRK92BMWJSIR36A6PATHKYKWLAMDAKKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DF2/1F0/DF21F0714CC49C66A25FEF7773BCFBAA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-05T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fan Bingbing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fan Bingbing tax evasion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fan Bingbing tax fraud]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China ying yang contracts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China corruption]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-say-a-1-5%C2%B0c-increase-should-be-new-climate-goal-3706974</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists say a 1.5°C increase should be new climate goal 3706974]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WORLD — Climate scientists are saying that limiting a global temperature rise to a 1.5-degree Celsius increase should be a new target goal.

This comes after decades of scientists saying global temperatures must be kept below 2 degrees Celsius to avoid catastrophic impacts. 

According to the BBC, scientists from the Intergovernmental Panel of Climate Change, or IPCC, and government officials are meeting in Incheon to see what needs to be done in order to meet the new target. 
Part of the reason for the change is that small island and low-lying countries were worried that a 2-degree Celsius increase would still lead to their territories being inundated by rising sea levels. 
Leaked drafts from the IPCC meeting show that a 1.5-degree Celsius increase would have some major differences than a 2.0C increase. 
Some main points are that 10 million fewer people would lose their homes from rising sea levels. Two million square kilometers of permafrost is saved over centuries. 
There would be a 50 percent reduction in people across the world experiencing water scarcity. 
The Arctic would only experience one sea-ice free summers in a century, and there would be a 50 percent reduction in species losing half their geographic range. 
Unfortunately, according to the leaked drafts, the world has already warmed by about one degree and at the current pace, the 1.5C limit would be surpassed by 2040. 3706974]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5BWKXCWKZAFTVKHBVBAZ7JHMVAETSC3A6IFZGAHKMBWGYCXAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/549/B7F/549B7F51FD69615534A5133DC8D6C3E2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-05T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ IPCC]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ IPCC meeting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ IPCC 1.5C]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ IPCC South Korea]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gay-penguins-kidnap-chick-from-hetero-couple-at-denmark-zoo-3706787</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gay penguins kidnap chick from hetero couple at Denmark zoo 3706787]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ODENSE, DENMARK — A zoo in Denmark saw some crazy drama unfold after a gay penguin couple kidnapped a chick from its straight parents.

NBC reports that according to a zookeeper at the Odense Zoo, mama penguin had gone for her daily swim and left the baby with dad. But it wasn't long before dad too wanted a dip, and had no qualms leaving the little penguin to fend for itself.

Seeing the parents were neglectful, a pair of male penguins thought maybe they could do better and took the chick for themselves.

The trio were a family for all of one day, before the real parents came looking for their kid and confronted the pair for their baby-snatching. The loud fight was all caught on camera and posted on the zoo's Facebook page. 

The fellas were definitely not keen on giving up their new kid, so zookeepers eventually had to step in.

In the end, mom and dad got their chick back, but the same-sex couple wasn't left high and dry either. They now have an egg from a female unable to care for it, so it's a win-win.

Kidnapping may not work in the human, but apparently things pan out when you're a gay penguin couple with a lotta love to give. 3706787]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKAAC3SAFKRVAZVLECRVL4WGEABZFC5KVDWRG3RAVAWPBZIAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/91F/1EC/91F1EC4A8179F49E0AA3DC922A298275.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-05T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ penguins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gay penguins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby penguin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ penguin chick]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ penguin kidnapping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ custody battle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ parental drama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Denmark zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Odense zoo]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dunkin-donuts-fires-workers-who-doused-homeless-man-with-water-3706765</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dunkin' Donuts fires workers who doused homeless man with water 3706765]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SYRACUSE, NEW YORK — Karma has finally come to two Dunkin' Donuts employees who were caught on camera being extra cruel to a homeless man.

Syracuse.com reports that the incident happened at a Dunkin' outlet in Syracuse, New York on Sunday night.

Jeremy Dufresne had come in to charge his phone and says he put his head down for just a minute when a worker later identified as Shakeen Robbins suddenly dumped a pitcher of cold water on him.

Another employee who had been filming the whole thing can be heard laughing as Dufresne hurriedly stands up and grabs his phone.

On camera, Robbins tells the man to stop sleeping in the store and to get out, as the clip ends with more laughing from the other staff member.

Dufresne is schizophrenic and says he lives outside because he prefers it. He hadn't bothered anyone at the store, and claims the other workers there have been nice to him.

The now-viral video has earned the ire of netizens and the local community, who staged a small protest outside the store on Monday. A GoFundMe page set up to help Dufresne and his family has now raised over $21,000 — way more than its initial $150 goal.

Dunkin' Donuts has since fired the two employees involved in the incident, and say they'll be contacting Dufresne to apologize.

Robbins has also come out publicly to say he regrets his actions and wants to make amends. 3706765]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6NWEXTWBZDWXARUKEAFTLSCMVDBKUZQK6KR5GALAZCRGDRCKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/916/1D8/9161D8F9651125695E9E7719EC19D78F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-05T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dunkin donuts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral dunkin donuts video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homeless man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dunkin homeless man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dunkin donuts homeless]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dunkin video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ schizophrenic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dunkin boycott]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/europe-s-first-underwater-restaurant-is-almost-complete-3706684</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Europe's first underwater restaurant is almost complete 3706684]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORWAY — Europe's first underwater restaurant is nearly complete and is set to open by the spring of 2019.

The underwater restaurant is called Under and will be located near the southernmost tip of Norway by the village of Baly, according to CNN.

The restaurant is designed by Snøhetta and will be partly submerged into the sea.

Under will be able to accomodate about 100 guests who would be able to enjoy a panoramic view of marine life such as fish, seals and lobsters as they dine.

The menu would include local seafood as well as mushrooms, berries along with other ingredients from the surrounding landscape.

Muted interior lighting helps prevent reflections off the glass in the restaurant, which allows visitors fully enjoy the view outside.

Under will also double as a research center for marine life to inform the public about the biodiversity of the ocean, according to Snøhetta.

The restaurant has already started accepting reservations starting April of next year. 3706684]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5BWACCWKZCRTACFLZARX944NFKSKFKRKNIRZHIAAFJAKDZQAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/362/C7A/362C7AC7BDDD145ECDFB6016463E4742.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-05T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater restaurant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater dining]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ subsea diner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater diner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's largest underwater restaurant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater dining norway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ underwater dining experience]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-explosive-gender-reveal-party-ends-in-47-000-acre-wildfire-3706598</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Explosive' gender reveal party ends in 47,000-acre wildfire 3706598]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GREEN VALLEY, ARIZONA — An off-patrol border agent accidentally started a massive wildfire after his gender reveal stunt went explosively wrong.

KGUN 9 reports that last April, Dennis Dickey and his pregnant wife decided to throw a party near Green Valley, Arizona to reveal their baby's gender.

The plan had been to shoot at a target containing the explosive substance Tannerite and a colored powder, and have it reveal either blue for a boy, or pink for a girl.

But when the shots were fired, it instead set off an explosion that ignited the massive Sawmill fire. Dickey called it in, but the wildfire had already begun spreading far and wide.

In total, the 37-year-old's little stunt ended up costing Arizona 47,000 acres of land and $8.2 million. Dickey has since been slapped with a misdemeanor and 5 years probation, and has to fork over $220,000 in restitution.

Ironically, despite the whole gender reveal part of the incident, the Dickeys never mentioned if their kid was a boy or a girl. 3706598]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LRICKVAJIRRDKFKABFZ6LUMWJBTEAQAABRXGTTKZDAMAZNBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/394/BF9/394BF9E229E048AE8C091FD52FC76413.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-05T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sawmill fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gender reveal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby gender]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gender reveal party]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arizona wildfire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tannerite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border patrol agent]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/manchester-students-union-swaps-clapping-for-jazz-hands-3707681</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Manchester Students' Union swaps clapping for jazz hands 3707681]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MANCHESTER, UNITED KINGDOM — A student union has decided to ban clapping, whooping and cheering and replaced it instead with — wait for it — jazz hands. 
According to the BBC, student reps from the University of Manchester actually voted to replace clapping with the British Sign Language equivalent — a wave of both hands, so jazz hands. 
Apparently clapping can trigger students with autism, sensory issues and deafness. Hold up — clapping bothers deaf people? 
At lively events such as debates, panels and talks, no more will students be subjected to the harsh sounds of audible clapping.
According to the student union's liberation and access officer Sara Khan, who proposed the idea, said clapping can discourage people from events. 
Khan said, I think a lot of the time, even in Parliamentary debates, I've seen that clapping, whooping and talking over each other, loud noises, encourages an atmosphere that is not as respectful as it could be.  
Khan said the union was looking to be more inclusive. 3707681]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIBWIXAIKRCWRBRWBSKFXK2BM2LSZRT5K6KF5G3XKVERIWC3KH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/473/DD9/473DD9DF86744594AECC0850E9AD3CBD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Manchester Students' Union]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Manchester jazz hands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Manchester bans clapping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clapping banned]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clapping jazz hands]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-find-key-to-slowing-aging-process-%E2%80%94-in-mice-3707671</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Researchers find key to slowing aging process — in mice 3707671]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS, MINNESOTA — Researchers have discovered a natural product that can reduce the level of damaged cells in mice caused by aging. 

Scientists have found that aged mice treated with Fisetin, found in many fruits and vegetables, has significant positive effects on health and lifespan, according to a University of Minnesota Medical School press release.  

As people get older, they accumulate damaged cells. As these cells reach a certain level of damage they go through a process known as cellular senescence, whereby they stop dividing. 

Younger people with healthier immune systems can clear out these damaged cells, but as people age, these cells aren't cleared as effectively. 
These damaged cells then begin to accumulate and cause low-level inflammation and release enzymes that degrade tissue. 

Researchers found that Fisetin reduced the level of damaged cells in older mice, and published their findings in the journal EBioMedicine. 
According to one of the study's authors Paul D. Robbins, these results suggest that we can extend the period of health, termed healthspan, even towards the end of life. 
Further research will need to be carried out to see if these results can be reproduced in humans. 3707671]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AAGCAFK6JARV3EKEAA56DVNFIB5R37LSJR5HRHB2KRIAAAAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B9/4EC/3B94EC5271F65A10894EB40F25F4AB13.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aging process]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fisetin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fisetin aging process]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cellular senescence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fountain of youth]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-defends-spanish-speaking-women-from-racist-shopper-3707660</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman defends Spanish-speaking women from racist shopper 3707660]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — A video that has gone viral since it was posted earlier this month features a shopper who was outraged by two Spanish-speaking woman. 

The footage shows her giving them a piece of her mind when another woman at the store promptly steps in to their defense.

Linda Dwire was shopping at a grocery store when she overheard the two women speaking Spanish to one another. She confronted them and told them to speak English and be an American, reports The Washington Post.

Kamira Trent immediately intervened and told Dwire to leave the women alone and not harass them. She also threatened to call the cops.

Dwire continued to argue with Trent saying you will lose your country, and accused her of not understanding as she is from another generation.

Trent eventually did call the cops and Dwire was arrested and charged with two counts of bias-motivated harassment.

A video of the incident was shot by one of the woman speaking Spanish and shared on social media where it has since received a million views.

Comments on social have been filled with praise for Trent for stepping in and standing up for the two, calling her a shero. 3707660]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEARGAADK2JAAARRLBIFXL2GG2JS3U3RKEDR3GIGARER5VRFAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/76D/3EB/76D3EB732462C91245A6815742991C2C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ USA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ white woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ racist white ppl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hispanic woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman defends hispanic women]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hispanic women called out for speaking spanish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ racist shopper]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman steps in to defend hispanic women for speaking spanish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman stands up against racist shopper]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-use-gene-editing-to-modify-rare-fruit-3707376</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists use gene editing to modify rare fruit 3707376]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA  — Scientists have come up with a way to modify a rare fruit and make it more accessible to the public.

Researchers have genetically modified ground cherries to be larger and easier to grow than those found in the wild, according to a study published in Nature Plants.

Ground cherries are usually found in South America as well as Central America, and are as small as a marble.

The researchers involved described the taste of the fruit as tropical yet sour with a slight hint of vanilla.

Ground cherries are also referred to as an orphan crop as it is grown on a small scale, but are difficult to produce enough to sell commercially as they often fall onto the ground before they are fully ripe.

Scientists used CRISPR, a gene editing tool, to target a gene known as CLAVATA 1 to increase the size of the fruit, which resulted in the fruit becoming 25 percent heavier.

Scientists also plan to edit the self-pruning gene found in the ground cherry to stop the plants shoots from continuing to grow once the fruit is ripe.

The researchers hope this will help make ground cherries more appealing to the public, as well as inspire other scientists to genetically modify other rare fruits. 3707376]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLWPAIGAADACDZWLWPWZL4TGSLVZRILKNKW5UTWKEEREVIEAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/95A/C7C/95AC7CCE9A454EF80ED5C01586FE58A9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crispr]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetic modification]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetically modified foods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetically modified fruits]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rare fruits]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetically modified fruit before and after]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ground cherry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ground cherry plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetically modified ground cherries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ground cherries]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-s-vision-turns-red-from-too-much-erectile-dysfunction-drugs-3707340</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man's vision turns red from too much erectile dysfunction drugs 3707340]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — A man learned the hard way that drugs have a recommended dosage for a reason, and that ignoring them could be a real eye-opener.

According to the case report published in Retinal Cases, the unidentified 31-year-old had gone online and purchased some liquid sildenafil citrate, which is the active ingredient in Viagra.

But instead of following the recommended dosage, he chugged the whole bottle down, because if a little bit is good, a lot is better, right? Wrong!

Viagra has been known to cause temporary vision issues, even with the typically prescribed dose. So it wasn't long before the man began seeing flashes of light and experiencing sensitivity. His vision also took on a disturbing red tint, prompting him to seek help two days later.

Doctors examined his peepers and found that the cells in his retina were permanently damaged. He was diagnosed with retinal toxicity, caused by too much trouser snake enhancing meds.

It's been more than a year since, but the unfortunate male is still seeing red despite receiving treatment.

Moral of the story, don't go buying random drugs off the internet, and definitely stick to the prescribed dose. 3707340]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWJFXDZHAVFA7VIVLZCR57BGMRESRRRILWJRZTZFARCRCWIBAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/735/673/7356736B810FBF7DF6697B0180F0FD66.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viagra]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ erectile dysfunction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ red vision]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ male enhancement drugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ male enhancement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liquid viagra]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seeing red]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ retinal toxicity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sildenafil citrate]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/manchester-students-union-swaps-clapping-for-jazz-hands-3709376</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Manchester Students' Union swaps clapping for jazz hands 3709376]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MANCHESTER, UNITED KINGDOM — A student union has decided to ban clapping, whooping and cheering and replaced it instead with — wait for it — jazz hands. 
According to the BBC, student reps from the University of Manchester actually voted to replace clapping with the British Sign Language equivalent — a wave of both hands, so jazz hands. 
Apparently clapping can trigger students with autism, sensory issues and deafness. Hold up — clapping bothers deaf people? 
At lively events such as debates, panels and talks, no more will students be subjected to the harsh sounds of audible clapping.
According to the student union's liberation and access officer Sara Khan, who proposed the idea, said clapping can discourage people from events. 
Khan said, I think a lot of the time, even in Parliamentary debates, I've seen that clapping, whooping and talking over each other, loud noises, encourages an atmosphere that is not as respectful as it could be.  
Khan said the union was looking to be more inclusive. 3709376]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAFGAACKMBA3ACCKFKW79UYMZEERFAMKRDWMGCXBZAAZVTXKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CBD/A94/CBDA946BC040C764775CC09BA451B9FA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-09T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>87</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Manchester Students' Union]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Manchester jazz hands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Manchester bans clapping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clapping banned]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clapping jazz hands]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/if-us-was-powered-only-by-wind-ground-could-get-warmer-3709352</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[If US was powered only by wind, ground could get warmer 3709352]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — A new Harvard study simulated the effects of switching the country's entire power grid to wind power to look at the effect turbines have on local temperature. 

Wind turbines can alter local temperatures by increasing the mixing of air at and above the surface, Ars Technica reports.
Researchers Lee Miller and David Keith from Harvard University used a high-resolution climate model of the United States to simulate what would happen if enough wind turbines were placed in the middle third of the country where the winds are highest to meet all current power needs. 
Their results showed the continental U.S. would get warmer by about 0.2 degrees Celsius on average, while the regions with the wind-turbines would warm by around 0.5 degrees Celsius. The study was published in the journal Joule. 

The study found that temperature fluctuations are greater at night and smaller during the day because surface warming and Sun driven convection are greater than the effect of the wind turbines. 
At night when the air is calmer, wind turbines mix warmer air down toward the cooling surface. 

An important point is that the wind turbines are not generating heat, rather they are moving existing heat around.   
Greenhouse gases from fossil fuels on the other hand continually accumulate and last for centuries. 3709352]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2IACDIEANIAAWIYLJJRVLDYGWKEXFK7KMAWVFIGKVCWXBKRAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/448/B23/448B239704BA5F2A8D8C3198800FE8B7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-09T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind farms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind turbines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind turbines local temperature]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind farm study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ renewable energy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hpv-vaccine-approved-for-adults-27-to-45-by-fda-3709347</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[HPV vaccine approved for adults 27 to 45 by FDA 3709347]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The U.S. Food and Drug Administration approved the use of a human papillomavirus vaccine for adults age 27 to 45. The vaccine was previously approved for people age 9 to 26.  

According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, around 14 million Americans become infected with HPV every year.  

According to an FDA press release, Gardasil 9 prevents certain cancers and diseases caused by nine HPV types. 

The vaccine protects against Types 6, 11, 16, 18, 31, 33, 45, 52 and 58, which are responsible for a majority of HPV-related diseases.

The FDA said it based its expansion on results from a study of 3,200 women age 27 to 45 that found Gardasil 9 was 88 percent effective in prevention of vulvar, vaginal and cervical precancerous lesions, cervical cancer and genital warts caused by the nine HPV types. 

The vaccine's effectiveness in men  was inferred from the data on women, in addition to a clinical trial of 150 men ages 27 to 45 who took a three-dose vaccination over a six-month period. 
According to the FDA, the safety of Gardasil 9 was evaluated in 13,000  men and women. Common adverse reactions included swelling, redness and pain at the injection site and headache. 3709347]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKAMXAIA6LWKVAVKBPRR7DTGFKVREAKLSPWVHKYKIAAZCZCKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E2F/5FE/E2F5FED4B65B92F9DBBDC8236092798E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-09T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ HPV vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gardasil-9]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ HPV vaccine adults]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ FDA]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-actually-has-a-game-show-on-xi-jinping-s-teachings--3709337</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China actually has a game show on Xi Jinping's 'teachings' 3709337]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HUNAN, CHINA — China just dropped the bigliest game show of all time focused on the greatest man to ever walk this earth — Xi Jinping. 
The show is called Studying Xi in the New Era and debuted on Hunan TV, China's second most-watched channel. 

The CCP has been scheming up new ways to ram propaganda down the throats of young Chinese. 
Each episode is 40 long minutes and pits three contestants against each other as they dive into the abortion of free thought to talk about Xi's theories and speeches. 

The first round forces contestants to answer five multiple-choice questions about Xi's policies. 
The two people with the highest scores proceed to the second round where they are subjected to Xi's speeches and must press a buzzer to get the opportunity to explain what they mean. 
The final round involves rambling for a minute-and-a-half about who knows what. 3709337]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JWXYKVAAFFAAITLNLA76LWNEEBKFIKKZAW3TIHKMDRCBZHAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/99C/051/99C0516379091885AB1961EDCF77B377.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-09T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Xi Jinping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Xi Jinping game show]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Xi Jinping thought]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Xi Jinping teachings]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese propaganda]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Xi Jinping Winnie the Pooh]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/drunk-birds-causing-trouble-in-minnesota-town-3709115</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Drunk birds causing trouble in Minnesota town 3709115]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GILBERT, MINNESOTA — The police are warning residents of a town in Minnesota to beware of drunk birds flying around.

The local bird population in Minnesota has been flying under the influence as they have been eating fermented berries caused by the early frost, reports The Washington Post.

The birds were seen flying recklessly and flying lower than usual through traffic.

Apparently the police department in Gilbert also received reports of the drunk birds flying directly into cars and windows. 

Sometimes the birds were found disoriented on the ground and needed some time to sober up.

The police explained most of the drunk birds are younger birds whose livers aren't able to handle the toxins of the fermented berries as efficiently as older birds. 3709115]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKFGDZJA5BAEWARBSKRILBCG2JB5RALKIARVTIBKFJRRBIAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/365/108/3651087152BCC21074D82E58E83E9C1C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-09T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Minnesota]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ town]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drunk birds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ birds flying under the influence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drunk birds minnesota]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fermented berries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drunk birds berries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drunk birds fermented berries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drunk birds video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ birds drunk on fermented berries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ birds drunk on berries]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-mushroom-extract-could-help-save-bee-population-3709088</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds mushroom extract could help save bee population 3709088]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — A vaccine made from two mushroom species, tinder fungus and Red Reishi mushrooms, could be vital in saving the bee population, according to a study published in Scientific Reports.

The researchers specifically targeted mycelia, a cobweb-like fungal membrane, found in both the mushrooms to create the vaccine.

The team conducted their study with two groups of bees exposed to varroa mites. One group was giving mycelium extract mixed with sugar syrup while the other was only given sugar syrup.

The virus levels of the bees were measured and scientists found that those who consumed mycelium extract saw a 45,000-fold reduction in a virus linked to colony collapse disorder, a phenomenon where bee colonies are wiped out.

Scientists involved in the study say they believe the vaccine would help support the immune system of the bees and to allow natural immunity to be strong enough to reduce the viruses.

The study comes amid reports of colony collapse disorder leading to the bee population decreasing by at least 30 percent to 90 percent in some areas, according to a report by the Florida Department of Agriculture. 3709088]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDAMDRBKWLRGAATBABA3LBBMRESXE35LWJF3UREASLF3VT4BA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/655/A24/655A246E1DB1AD660687D8B7380587BF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-09T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee population]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee population decline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to help the bee population]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ increasing bee population]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mushroom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mushroom extract]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mushroom extract might save the bees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mushroom vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mushroom vaccine bees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mushroom vaccine could save the bees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colony collapse disorder]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-angers-internet-after-feeding-hippo-plastic-popcorn-bag-3709894</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese man angers internet after feeding hippo plastic popcorn bag 3709894]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NANCHANG, CHINA — Chinese social media is in a tizzy after a clip surfaced of a zoo visitor being less than kind to the animals.

According to Sina News, the incident went down last Wednesday at the Nanchang Zoo in China's Jiangsu Province.

A short video shows a man sitting on the barrier of an enclosure, throwing fistfuls of popcorn at a hippo lounging just a few feet away in the water.

When its jaws opened wide, the man chucked all of his popcorn — bag and all — straight into its mouth. The animal is seen gulping down the entire thing, which prompts the visitor and the rest of the onlookers to chuckle in delight.

Zoo management found about the ghastly behavior the next day, and have filed a report with local police. A vet has since checked the hippo and determined that it's perfectly ok, which, whew.

Not sure the same can be said for the uncivilized perp, though, who is probably already being sussed out and shamed online by angry netizens. 3709894]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVCFEAIHKEERAX3DBACRX9DSGICVXE3RAAAW3GZHAABRTAAAAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1C9/C07/1C9C0771F7531409154052657F42993E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-10T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hippo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hippopotamus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zoo animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal abuse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal feeding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ don't feed the animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nanchang zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese social media]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hurricane-michael-headed-for-florida-panhandle-3709892</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hurricane Michael headed for Florida panhandle 3709892]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORIDA — Hurricane Michael is expected to intensify and is forecast to hit the Florida Panhandle as a Category 3 by midweek. 
According to CBS News, Florida and Alabama have both declared states of emergency. 

According to the National Hurricane Center, Michael could strengthen into a Category 3 and higher, meaning it will have sustained winds of over 111 miles per hour, by Tuesday night before making contact with the Panhandle on Wednesday.

According to the Weather Channel, this will be due to a combination of favorable upper-level winds and above-average sea-surface temperatures along Michael's path.  
According to the Weather Channel, storm surge, damaging winds and heavy rains are likely to affect areas along the northeastern Gulf Coast. 
Storm surge flooding of 8 to 12 feet is expected to occur along the immediate coastline near and east of where the center makes landfall. 

According to CBS News, Florida Governor Rick Scott has added 700 more Florida National Guards troops to aide in storm preparation and response, bringing the total to well over 1,000. 3709892]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KWXYAFAAAF3XRSLBLAX7SCGFIE7E33AIDF5TABAVDFVCZAAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7F6/FCD/7F6FCD6DAFEEEED6F0EF357D5F65DEEE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-10T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Michael]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Michael Florida Panhandle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Storm Surge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricanes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flooding]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/alaskan-brown-bears-supersizing-themselves-for-fat-bear-week-3709828</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Alaskan brown bears supersizing themselves for Fat Bear Week 3709828]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALASKA — It down to the final day of voting for brown bears living along the Brooks River at Katmai National Park & Reserve as they fight to be the fattest in the fourth annual Fat Bear Week.
According to ABC 13, park rangers are tracking bears often seen on the explore.org Bear Cam as they stuff their faces in preparation for hibernation in March Madness-style brackets. 
Alaskan brown bears start packing on the pounds in July. According to the National Park Service, bears enter a state known as hyperphagia where they eat non-stop and can fatten up to four pounds in a single day — so basically a normal 'Murican diet. 
Some bears can devour dozens of sockeye salmon in one day, with each salmon providing around 4,000 calories. 
Bears supersize themselves in preparation for hibernation and can lose up to a third of their body fat during the five to eight month slumber.
People can watch the big old bears on Katmai's Facebook page and get to vote until October 9, after which the winner will be crowned. 3709828]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LICAAXAIKFNWTCRRLIDA7KDVMRAV5R34ABJWXGZLABKFVAADLE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/332/9C6/3329C60287C38FD4BA54B0D6DDDBCDD5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-10T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alaskan brown bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fat Bear Week]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fat Bear Week Katmai National Park]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fat Bear Week 2018]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/climate-report-calls-for-immediate-action-against-climate-change-3709785</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Climate report calls for immediate action against climate change 3709785]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOUTH KOREA — A report from the U.N. scientific panel on climate changes urged governments around the world to take immediate action to avoid disastrous levels of temperature rise.

The authors of the report found that if greenhouse gas emissions continue at the current rate, the temperature of Earth's atmosphere would increase about 1.5 degrees Celsius by 2040, according to The New York Times.

Previously, scientists believed the damage would occur if average temperatures were to rise above 2 degrees Celsius.

However, the reports warns the increase of just 1.5 degree Celsius would flood coastlines as well as intensify droughts around the planet.

In order to prevent 1.5 degrees of warming, pollution caused by greenhouse gases would have to be slashed by 45 percent by 2030 and 100 percent by 2050.

By 2050, use of different sources of renewable energy such as wind and solar power would have to increase to 67 percent while use of coal would have to decrease by nearly 40 percent.

Drew Shindell, author of the report, said there is no way to mitigate climate change without getting rid of coal.

The report warned of irreversible damage such as coral reefs dying off if we fail to take action to prevent this catastrophe. 3709785]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJWXCRBAZAAXX3CBSKAT9JHGVESXST9KWJRXURHKICWVBAIKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/746/268/746268C4FB054B098ACEB54369C7FE70.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-10T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UN report]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change UN]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ temperature rising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ renewable energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea levels rising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea level rising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UN reports warns of climate crisis if action not taken soon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to help climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ temperature rise]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-used-tiny-microchip-to-hack-apple-amazon-servers-3710587</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China used tiny microchip to hack Apple, Amazon servers 3710587]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — Apple and Amazon have become the subject of intense speculation after a new report claims their servers were infiltrated by Chinese spy chips.

According to a Bloomberg investigative report, a Chinese military unit planted microchips the size of a pencil tip into motherboards while they were on the production line in China.

The compromised hardware was supplied to Supermicro Computer in San Jose, California, and inserted into servers that were then used by almost 30 U.S. companies, including Apple and Amazon.

With the microchips, Chinese hackers had access to the companies' data centers, allowing them to steal information, connect with other servers, and alter operations.

U.S. intelligence services allegedly found out about the chip in 2015, around the same time that Apple and Amazon discovered the breach on their servers.

However, Supermicro, Apple, and Amazon have denied the claims made in the report. The Department of Homeland Security also came out saying it has no reason to doubt the companies' statements.

A follow-up Bloomberg report points to 'new evidence' from a telecom company, where a similar microchip was found embedded in the Ethernet connector of servers sourced from Supermicro.

Experts say hardware hacks are a legitimate concern, and are far more devastating and hard to detect than software-based incidents.

Still, most seem to be divided on the validity of the Bloomberg expose and may stay that way until actual concrete evidence — like an actual microchip — somehow surfaces. 3710587]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AAGCKWKNMAAVZRB6PRX7DYG2LVTS32A6LWMHAGKJKACWT4AB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D23/B69/D23B69FE0515E5B20D6DB7E9BDE0FE47.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>90</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microchip]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spy chip]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microchip hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China chip hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyber security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyber threat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hardware security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supermicro]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ server hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon hacked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Apple hacked]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hubble-telescope-in-safe-mode-after-gyroscope-failure-3710581</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hubble telescope in safe mode after gyroscope failure 3710581]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — NASA's Hubble Space Telescope has gone into safe mode after two of its four functioning gyroscopes stopped working.

The Hubble had been operating with four of its six gyroscopes when two of them failed, according to reports from NASA.

At any given time, the Hubble needs at least three of its gyroscopes to work for optimal efficiency.

After one of the gyroscopes failed, controllers tried to switch to another newer gyroscope, however, that one failed as well, leaving the Hubble with only two fully functioning gyroscopes.

Gyroscopes are mainly used to make steer the Hubble and makes sure the telescope is steady in space.

The failure was not unexpected as two other gyros of the same model had already experienced problems, according to a NASA statement.

NASA also tweeted it was conducting tests on the newer gyroscope to determine the problems.

The operators will now try to revive the newer gyroscope and bring it online. 

If it is not successful, the Hubble will operate in a reduced-gyro mode, using only one gyro in order to let the telescope operate for a longer time.

However, this would affect the Hubble's ability to track fast moving objects as well as reduce the amount of sky it can view in any given moment, according to NASA. 3710581]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IFGYCVAMEFKCKHLADRZ7DXMAEV7SAIKWJFVGAAARDRMBK6KH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/53F/2B2/53F2B246AF8383BD703AC8338185AE83.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hubble Space Telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hubble telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hubble  gyroscope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hubble mechanical failure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hubble telescope gyroscope failure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ safe mode]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/artificial-sweeteners-may-not-be-good-for-your-gut-3710483</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Artificial sweeteners may not be good for your gut 3710483]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEERSHEBA, ISRAEL / ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA — In recent years, sugar has become public enemy number one as far as health is concerned, prompting people to turn to artificial sweeteners. But are they really any better for you?

Science Daily reports that researchers from the Ben Gurion University of the Negev in Israel and Nanyang Technological Institute in Singapore modified E. coli to light up when exposed to toxins, using it as a sensing model representative of the complex gut microbial system.

Exposure to six types of popular artificial sweeteners, which include aspartame and sucralose among others, had a toxic, stressing effect that made it difficult for the bacteria to grow and reproduce.

A separate study carried out in Australia looked at 29 healthy adults and randomly administered the capsule equivalent of drinking 1.5 liters of diet soda a day to fourteen of the participants. The other fifteen were given a placebo, according to a report in Diabetologia.

After two weeks, the amount of good bacteria in the fourteen subjects' gut had decreased, while gut pathogens had increased — potentially affecting the body's ability to regulate glucose.

But while both studies' findings are compelling, experts say they are insufficient to establish causality. It's also it's difficult to assess what exactly these gut marker changes mean to overall health, which means the verdict is still out on whether these sugar substitutes are in fact harmful. 3710483]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5BWEXTWKAEWGBTFLJKRZ7LVGVCERS35A6JRTUZGKIBAMWZAAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/22D/D34/22DD3449BB2DEAF94C0250599BD7AE50.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial sweeteners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sweeteners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sugar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aspartame]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sucralose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saccharine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut microbes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digestive bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial sweeteners health risks]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/us-china-tensions-in-the-south-china-sea-explained-3710470</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[US-China tensions in the South China Sea explained 3710470]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C. / BEIJING — A dangerously close encounter in disputed waters has become the latest flashpoint in worsening Sino-American relations.

The South China Morning Post reports that on September 30, the USS Decatur was sailing near China-claimed Gaven Reef in the South China Sea's Spratly Islands when it was approached by a Chinese ship.

The PRC destroyer Luyang reportedly came within 45 yards of the American vessel's bow, prompting it to maneuver to prevent a collision.

The South China Sea has long been a site of conflict, not just for the U.S. and China, but for many countries in the region, whose overlapping claims on disputed waters are based on their Exclusive Economic Zones. In contrast, China purports to own 90% of the South China Sea based on historic rights, using a nebulous 9-dash line to back its territorial claim.

As a way to legitimize and safeguard their alleged territory, the Chinese have built up and fortified artificial islands in the Spratlys, effectively creating a network of military bases.

Though the U.S. has no stake in the disputed waters, it has repeatedly challenged China's maritime claims through freedom of navigation operations, resulting in several altercations over the years.

American and Japanese ships held joint military exercises in the contested region as recently as September. Weeks later, U.S. bombers flew through the area twice in three days.

China typically condemns these maneuvers and often responds with air and naval drills showcasing their own military might.

Following the USS Decatur incident, a U.S. Navy proposal suggests a large military exercise in the South China Sea and Taiwan Strait as a global show of force to warn China, reports CNN.

The conflict comes amidst a brewing trade war between the two nations, with the U.S. imposing tariffs on imported Chinese goods, and China retaliating by doing the same.

Vice President Mike Pence further fanned the flames after complimenting Taiwan's democratic stance and recommending that Beijing take a page from their book.

China is especially sensitive about Taiwan, which it sees as a renegade province, and has consistently slammed any efforts to support the island's sovereignty.

Analysts say escalating tensions between the world's two largest superpowers are likely to persist, reports the Economic Times, but it's unclear whether they may get resolved somewhere down the line or lead to a global-scale conflict. 3710470]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIWCDRCAIFAPWA9LIAAZ9DYMWJSIRRKAWJF7GABKFJAPVIAKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/506/002/506002A395F64D4A49617B3842D29A45.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>139</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south china sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us china tensions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south china sea explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spratlys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial islands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south china sea tensions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trade war]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us china trade war]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chernobyl-has-started-up-again-this-time-as-a-solar-power-plant-3710368</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chernobyl has started up again, this time as a solar power plant 3710368]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHERNOBYL, UKRAINE — Ukraine has just unveiled a solar power plant just 100 meters from Chernobyl's nuclear site in which a nuclear disaster occurred 30 years ago.

The power plant will consist of photovoltaic solar panels to produce energy and will be connected to the power grid, according to a Reuters report.

Ukraine plans to diversify its energy sources by using renewable energy such as solar power.

About 3,800 panels will be installed and will produce enough energy to power 2,000 apartments.

The Chernobyl Solar Power Plant currently has a capacity of one megawatt but there are plans to eventually increase it to 100 megawatts.

Chernobyl's nuclear site exploded in 1986 and forced hundreds of thousands of people to evacuate the contaminated area which resulted in the area being abandoned due to radiation.

Humans aren't allowed to live in the area for another 24,000 years, according to AFP. 3710368]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFAXRIA5FWGATELBIAXKJHNBKB5STZKMDFRHAAAREAEBAFBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/300/AE2/300AE2E81C097E3CF4159C4897FDD2FC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chernobyl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear site]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chernobyl nuclear site]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar power plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ renewable energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  Chernobyl nuclear site converted into solar power plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chernobyl solar farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar power plant Chernobyl]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cops-called-on-black-man-babysitting-white-kids-3711185</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cops called on black man babysitting white kids 3711185]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MARIETTA, GEORGIA — It's 2018 and black people still can't seem do anything without raising some eyebrows, not even watching some friend's kids.

Corey Lewis found that out firsthand, despite being a fine, upstanding citizen and running his own after-school youth mentoring program.

CBS 46 reports that on Sunday, he and the two white kids he was babysitting were in a Walmart parking lot when some crazy lady decided to get all up in their business.

The woman had initially pulled up in a sedan asking if the kids were okay, then came back again wanting to talk to them. When Lewis refused, she flipped and threatened to take down his plate.

The lady went on to trail him for about an hour, following him to the gas station across the street, and then all the way back to his house.

As if that wasn't enough, she then called the cops and reported his behavior as 'suspicious.'

A Cobb County police officer showed up and talked to Lewis and the kids, and soon confirmed what everyone already knew — everything was okay. The cop did call the kids' parents, who were pretty dumbfounded about the whole ordeal.

Lewis, meanwhile, is trying to obtain the 911 record and find out the woman's identity and why she did what she did. Well — it doesn't take a genius to figure that out. 3711185]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFAAIIAMAAVAR9BJPA77LUMVASRSC5KWLAZGRCAVARAWZPKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CA3/ACF/CA3ACF00698B40E736B0AAB34CA4D6B4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ babysitting while black]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black babysitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ babysitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman calls cops on black man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ corey lewis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ inspired by lewis]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hurricane-michael-makes-its-way-across-the-southeast-3711135</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hurricane Michael makes its way across the southeast 3711135]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Hurricane Michael is now making its way inland across the southeast. 

Hurricane Michael made landfall near Mexico Beach, Florida early Wednesday afternoon.

Michael had winds of up to 155 mph when it hit the Florida Panhandle, according to the Weather Channel.

On Wednesday afternoon, a storm surge over 7.7 feet was also reported at Apalachicola, Florida.

The hurricane is now making its way inland and is centered approximately 20 miles southwest of Albany, Georgia and has since been reduced to a Category 1 storm.

Hurricane Michael continues to weaken as it crosses the southeastern U.S. and is expected to turn into a tropical storm by Thursday morning, according to the National Hurricane Center.

Nearly 370,000 people in Florida, Georgia and Alabama are without power, reports CBS News.

Photos and videos of widespread destruction have also been shared on social media. 3711135]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKWKYAIAICWPCIWKBLWXK2BM5AERERIA6PR5GZHKNJWECALAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/99A/C90/99AC900C199F20902C138A13F7870E71.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Michael]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane destruction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane michael update]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane michael damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane michael destruction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Georgia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Florida Panhandle]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/catch-and-release-may-be-harmful-to-fish-3711118</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Catch-and-release may be harmful to fish 3711118]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RIVERSIDE, CALIFORNIA — Hook injuries caused by the catch and release method may actually be harmful to fish, study finds. 

The catch-and-release method is common in recreational fishing, with most people opting to use barbless hooks to reduce the harm caused to the fish.

According to a UC Riverside study, fishing hooks cause injuries to the mouth of fish which in turn affects their ability to capture prey.

When the hook is removed, it leaves behind a hole in the mouth, according to the study published in the Journal of Experimental Biology.

Researchers explained the hole disrupts the suction feeding system, creating negative pressure in the mouth relative to the water as the fish open their mouths to suck in their prey.

Scientists captured ten shiner perch using a hook and line and ten others using a net.

The captured fish were observed using high-speed cameras. Those with mouth injuries were found to have difficulty sucking prey into their mouths.

However, a researcher involved with the study said that further studies are needed to determine the long term effects of hook-related injuries on fish. 3711118]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDWGCCXKABRGBR9KBJWX9UUMIBBKFALLRDRTHKXB5CARBIGLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/34D/E22/34DE22FB579353ED7405CD9CD0CCB144.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish hook injury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hook removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ catch and release fishing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ catch and release fishing harmful to fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish feeding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mouth injuries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hook injuries affects eating ability of fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish injury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish harmed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ suction feeding]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/why-the-brazilian-butt-lift-is-such-a-deadly-procedure-3712121</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Why the Brazilian butt lift is such a deadly procedure 3712121]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A UK plastic surgery organization has warned members not to perform Brazilian butt lifts, after a second British woman died from the procedure this year.

The surgery is immensely popular, despite having the highest death rate of all cosmetic procedures, according to a statement from the British Association of Aesthetic Plastic Surgeons. But what exactly makes it so dangerous?

Brazilian butt lifts or BBL involve taking excess fat from other parts of the body, such as the stomach and back, and injecting it into the glutes to enhance them.

The procedure carries a large risk of fat cells being mistakenly injected into large veins and going into the bloodstream. This can lead to a fat embolism, which can block blood vessels in the heart, lungs, or brain and cause death.

Other complications that can stem from BBL include bacterial infections, wound ruptures, and necrosis, among others.

Experts say many patients who have suffered botched surgeries had the procedure done abroad where it's cheaper. 3712121]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNWKDTUAACAIAKEKECR574UMJLS5R39AZCFMGTXKRCRMAZHAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BD4/4C2/BD44C2F67CA236E226FFACCC3CDE444B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brazilian butt lift]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bbl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ butt lift]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brazilian bum lift]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bum lift]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deadly surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deadly plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmetic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brazilian butt lift risks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ butt enhancement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bbl warning]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/virgin-galactic-could-launch-spacecraft-within-weeks--3711913</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Virgin Galactic could launch spacecraft 'within weeks' 3711913]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[US — Virgin Galactic is all set to launch its latest SpaceShipTwo, the VSS Unity. 

The ship is designed to carry two crew members as well as six passengers.

However, tickets for the spacecraft do not come cheap. People have paid upwards of $250,000 for a seat, according to Digital Trends.

The VSS Unity will first be taken into space with a carrier aircraft called the WhiteKnight Two, according to the Guardian.

Once the spacecraft reaches a certain altitude, the VSS Unity will be dropped by the carrier aircraft, which is when its rocket engines fire up.

The VSS Unity will have to reach heights of 100 km in order to reach space.

Richard Branson, founder of Virgin Galactic, told CNBC he is confident that they would be in space within weeks, not months. 3711913]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSKACAIGB6IAXVZRLZCW57DWMFKBREC2K6KAVGAAAEARECRHAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DA8/C3B/DA8C3B5463DA068D18F9C5A6F290A04F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Virgin Galactic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virgin galactic space flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virgin galactic launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virgin galactic animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virgin galactic space plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virgin galactic space tourism]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virgin galactic spaceshiptwo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ VSS Unity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-tourists-grab-swan-by-the-neck-after-missed-photo-op-3711891</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese tourists grab swan by the neck after missed photo op 3711891]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LUCERNE, SWITZERLAND — In yet another instance of Chinese tourists behaving badly, a couple of photo-obsessed aunties were caught on camera mercilessly manhandling a swan in Switzerland.

The South China Morning Post reports that the footage was shot near Swan Square in Lucerne, and begins with some Chinese tourists crowding around a large swan.

Despite a sign saying not to feed them, one lady used a paper napkin to bait a bird, presumably for a photo op.

When the swan snatched the paper from her hand, another woman grabbed the animal by the neck and tried to take back the napkin.

Someone in the group can be heard complaining about not getting the shot, prompting Chinese news reports to speculate that the attack stemmed from a missed photo op.

Video of the tourists was shared on Snapchat, before being picked up by a Swiss news outlet, and needless to say, most people were disgusted with the women's behavior. 3711891]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IAADTWBNIRIAAWBRDRT9DXMFIE5RTZKJLW3HZKKIBRGCAPAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9CD/EE8/9CDEE8A91A461EB89E28276D7AA1D65E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists behaving badly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese tourists]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swan selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists attack swan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swan lake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal cruelty]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral video]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-kicked-off-flight-after-over-emotional-support-squirrel-3711882</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman kicked off flight after over emotional support squirrel 3711882]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, FLORIDA — The police had to be called in for a woman who tried to bring a emotional support squirrel on a plane on a flight from Orlando to Cleveland. 

The woman notified Frontier Airlines that she would be bringing an emotional support animal on the flight. 

She just didn't inform them that her emotional support is a squirrel, according to USA Today.

When she tried to bring the squirrel along with her, Frontier told her rodents, including squirrels, were not permitted. 

She was then asked to get off the plane, however she refused, so Orlando airport police had to be called. All the passengers were then forced to deplane. 

After throwing a tantrum she was wheeled out of the gate in a wheelchair with her squirrel to cheers from the passengers. 3711882]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LFVYCVBVFWMVZ7BADAI7UVMRDBRRKSAAAATFKWAEARMXRQAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D87/8A2/D878A2F504DB3E27084AB7E1EC126F9E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emotional support squirrel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  emotional support squirrel florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emotional support animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Frontier Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frontier airlines squirrel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emotional support pets]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-we-know-so-far-about-jamal-khashoggi-s-disappearance-3713505</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What we know so far about Jamal Khashoggi's disappearance 3713505]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ISTANBUL — Saudi journalist and dissident Jamal Khashoggi has been missing for more than 10 days, prompting speculation that he'd been dispatched by his own government.

Khashoggi's fiancee Hatice Cengiz told the New York Times that he had tried to obtain a document on September 28 for their upcoming wedding, but was told by the consulate in Turkey that he had to come back to collect it.

On October 2, nine Saudi officials and intelligence officers arrived in Istanbul via private jet, booking three nights at two hotels near the mission. Around 12:13, vehicles allegedly carrying some of the agents arrived outside the Saudi consulate.

Jamal Khashoggi entered the consulate at 1:14 p.m. after leaving his two phones with his Cengiz, telling her to get help if he didn't come back out.

A Turkish source told the Middle East Eye that shortly after Khashoggi was led into the consul-general's room, two Saudi agents entered and dragged him out. The 59-year-old was taken into another room and later killed. His body was then dismembered with a bone saw in a third room.

Six vehicles carrying the Saudi officials reportedly left the consulate around 4 p.m., while two others drove to the consul's residence nearby, one of them believed to be carrying Khashoggi.

A second jet carrying six more officials arrived past 5, though it departed an hour later for Cairo, and then Riyadh. The first jet left later that night, stopping at Dubai before returning to the Kingdom the next day.

Cengiz waited outside the consulate until 1 a.m., but never saw Khashoggi emerge. She returned again the following day when he still hadn't reappeared.

Turkey has been quick to point the finger at the Saudis, telling the U.S. that they have audio and video recordings proving Khashoggi was killed.

Turkish newspaper Sabah claims Khashoggi's Apple Watch recorded his ordeal inside the consulate and sent it to his phone and iCloud, though many have questioned whether this is technically feasible.

Turkish officials allegedly want to use luminol to check for blood inside the mission, but the Saudis have only allowed a visual probe. The Middle East Eye reports that the prosecutor general is considering digging up the garden of the Saudi consul-general's residence to see if Khashoggi's remains are there.

Riyadh called the allegations baseless and claim the journalist left the consulate through the back, though no evidence has surfaced backing this claim.

They denied sending a team to Istanbul on October 2, even as Sabah published the images and details of the 15 Saudi operatives believed to be involved in the case. According to information corroborated by the New York Times, one of the men is an autopsy expert at the Saudi Interior Ministry, while another is an Air Force lieutenant. 3713505]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDRIYAGLSIWECZWLNPWT94SM5ESXFIQKRDF5TALAAEFEBTWAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/513/036/5130366C734CBA269110B93A096ED960.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-16T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>153</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jamal Khashoggi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jamal Khashoggi disappearance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi journalist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missing Saudi journalist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missing journalist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi dissident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi intelligence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Turkish intelligence]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/some-dietary-pills-found-to-contain-unapproved-drugs-3713482</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Some dietary pills found to contain unapproved drugs 3713482]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[U.S.— A total of 776 over-the-counter dietary supplements were found to contain potentially harmful drugs.

According to a study published in JAMA Network Open, 97.6 percent of the ingredients present in supplements were not labeled on the products.

Eighty-six percent of the contaminated drugs were mainly found in supplements labeled as drugs for weight loss and sexual enhancement, while 12 percent were found in muscle building supplements.

One in five supplements were found to contain more than one pharmaceutical drug.

Sildenafil, the active ingredient for Viagra, was the most common drug found in sexual enhancement supplements while sibutramine, a weight-loss drug banned by the FDA, was found in weight loss supplements.

Dr. Louis Aronne, a professor of metabolic research, told Reuters that dietary supplements are hard to regulate as they are often sold and marketed online.

Less than half of the contaminated supplements were ever recalled from stores, according to Scientific American.

The FDA can issue a warning and ask the company to voluntarily recall their products, however the FDA can't force the companies to do so as dietary supplements aren't regulated like other medication, according to Forbes. 3713482]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBJFKYICBEAFGARULNPWX74VMZCV7SKSLSJA3TZGKWKAXBAKKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F5D/1CC/F5D1CC66FD6B655936D81299224549BD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-16T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pills]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dietary supplements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dietary supplements ingredients]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contaminated supplements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ harmful drugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weight-loss drugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sildenafil]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pharmaceutical drug]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sibutramine]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/really-long-parasitic-worm-removed-from-man-s-eyeball-3713373</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Really long parasitic worm removed from man's eyeball 3713373]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KARNATAKA, INDIA — A 60-year-old man in India wormed his way in to see a doctor because his eye was constantly hurting and itching.

According to the Sun, when the doctor went in for a look, he found out what was causing the discomfort — a parasitic worm chilling in the man's eye.

Using forceps, the doctor carefully extracted a 15-cm long parasitic ringworm from the man's eye socket. Yummy.

Good thing it was removed too, otherwise the patient may have gone blind. 

The entire surgical process was filmed and shared on social media.

The doctor thinks that a mosquito may have passed on the worm larvae when it bit the patient. 3713373]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KECFXYADL5HFEBATKFJA7KBGMFJBRECZABIWVFKWARDFEBIBKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/6DC/D83/6DCD835B68C94D41BD89FADEB25D480C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-16T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[India]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[eye]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[eyeball]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[parasitic worm in eye]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[parasitic worm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[parasite in eye]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[worm in eyeball]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[eye socket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[worm removed from man's eye]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trending-halloween-costumes-for-2018-3714167</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trending halloween costumes for 2018 3714167]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C. — It's that time of the year again when ghouls, creepers, and furries can acceptably roam the streets.

And while not everyone has the foresight to plan a costume nine months ahead, Google at least has your back as far as what's trending this year.

According to the Frightgeist list of trending costumes, Fortnite isn't just the most popular video game on Earth, it's also numero uno on Halloween costume searches. So on all Hallow's eve, expect to see a gaggle of characters trick-or-treating round your hood.

Second on the list is Spider-man, which is a surprise to no one because everyone loves Spidey, and absolutely no one is over Infinity War.

If video games and superheroes aren't your thing, you'll be happy to know that unicorns are at number three. Whether it's in a onesie or an explosion of glitter and rainbow — you best rock that horn.

Four and five are Halloween staples: Everyone needs to cosplay as a dinosaur or a witch at least once in their lives.

T-rex and a Sanderson sister too campy? Maybe you're better off going as Harley Quinn, aka number six on the list. Sure she's a little nuts, but that's why it's fun.

Whether you're into Marvel or DC, cosplaying your favorite superhero is always fun. Black Panther is top notch, as is Wonder Woman. It'll be super cold in that costume, but at least you'll slay.

Johnny Depp may have moved on from Jack Sparrow, but pirates never go out of style — that's why they're at number eight. Bonus points if you can drink like one too.

Rabbits have taken over the ninth spot, though we're not sure who's more proud — Bugs Bunny or Regina George.

Finally, we can't have a Halloween without someone dressing up as a princess. With two royal weddings this year, you can bet all the Meghan Markles will be taking to the streets.

There are more costumes ranked on Frightgeist, as well as a costume map showing which ones are popular in which areas. 

Whatever you decide to be, just make sure you're ready by the 31st. Halloween waits for no one. 3714167]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADAPDKTKWJRGBAWLRAR794TMIASZETRABJFRHRBKMERZCCUAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6B0/C3B/6B0C3B8225B5CE40BE410D2AB088AB40.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-17T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>113</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween costumes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot halloween costumes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ popular halloween costumes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween costume ideas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trending costumes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  frightgeist]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mechanic-accidentally-destroys-f-16-fighter-jet-in-belgium-3713993</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mechanic accidentally destroys F-16 fighter jet in Belgium 3713993]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORENNES, BELGIUM — A mechanic servicing a fighter jet at a Belgian air base accidentally opened fire destroying an F-16. Talk about a bad day at work. 
According to Scramble Magazine, while the technician was working on an F-16 in the hangar at the Florennes Air Base, he accidentally activated the jet's six-barrel 20mm Vulcan cannon and popped off a few rounds last Thursday. 
Unfortunately for the technician, another F-16 was sitting outside the hangar and was fueled in preparation for an afternoon sortie.
  
The 20 millimeter shells caused the F-16 to immediately catch fire and explode, completely destroying the aircraft. Two other F-16s were also damaged. 

Luckily no one was killed, although two mechanics were treated for some hearing loss. 

According to the Telegraph, around 30 firefighters rushed to the scene along with other emergency crew. 

An investigation has been opened into the incident. 3713993]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKAACTTA6KAIATEL2JRR6L4GEBSZEAQKEDW7U3WANJAMDIPAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DCE/01A/DCE01A77235BB435622DB6701152EABE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-17T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mechanic destroys F-16]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Belgian F-16 destroyed by accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technician destroys F-16]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technician blows up F-16 by accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Belgium Air Force]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-saudi-arabia-can-retaliate-against-sanctions-over-khashoggi-3713909</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How Saudi Arabia can retaliate against sanctions over Khashoggi 3713909]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RIYADH, SAUDI ARABIA — U.S. President Donald Trump has threatened Saudi Arabia with severe punishment if it's proven that they are behind the disappearance of journalist Jamal Khashoggi.

In response, the Saudis have vowed to carry out retaliatory measures that could potentially spark a global economic disaster, according to an editorial by Al Arabiya general manager Turki Aldhakhil.

The Guardian reports that Saudi Arabia is the world's largest exporter of oil, shipping over 7 million barrels a day worldwide. If they were to halt sales, oil prices could skyrocket from $80 per barrel to over $400.

This would not only drive up the global cost of petrol, but also any goods that are transported by land, including basic commodities.

As a major importer of U.S. arms, the Kingdom benefits American companies and jobs. But a freeze in U.S.-Saudi relations could jeopardize this and see the Saudis buy from other arms exporters like Russia or China.

Saudi Arabia's Public Investment Fund is also set to invest over $20 billion in U.S. infrastructure — an agreement which could fall through in the event of a diplomatic standoff. 3713909]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWKAIXAHA6IFMBIRBBPRI944GEABZSTZLRAA3TICKZARXCRJLE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/8A7/437/8A74371981664C32A529928FDA782350.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-17T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>81</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jamal Khashoggi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi journalist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi dissident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oil prices]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi oil reserves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi investment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi Arabia sanctions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ economic sanctions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global economy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi Arabia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/jeff-bezos-blue-origin-awarded-500m-u-s-military-contract-3713899</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin awarded $500m U.S. military contract 3713899]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin space rocket (and SpaceX rival) was awarded a $500m USAF deal last week.

The funding is for development of the company's reusable New Glenn heavy rocket.

According to Reuters, the U.S. Air Force last week doled out over $2 billion in deals with aerospace manufacturers for the development of new rocket technology. 

The Air Force said in a news release that United Launch Alliance was awarded a contract to for its Vulcan-Centaur system. Northrop Grumman Innovation Systems will also receive funding to develop its OmegA rocket.

The funding comes as the U.S. seeks to transition away from foreign-built space systems, especially the Russian RD 180 engine. 3713899]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5CAICKWK6IAPWZXKFIFR6DRMVBBRU3RKRDRZGRHKRAFAAAMLE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/889/C85/889C8582E7B5E7A0ABABB2369F14C72A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-17T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue origin vs space x]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jeff bezos space rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new glenn rocket launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new glenn rocket landing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space X]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elon musk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space exploration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space launch system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocket launch system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue origin landing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue origin launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cornerstore-caroline-calls-cops-on-child-she-claims-grabbed-her-butt-3713784</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cornerstore Caroline calls cops on child she claims grabbed her butt 3713784]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY — A Brooklyn woman is getting roasted by the interwebs after she accused a black kid of touching her inappropriately.

The New York Post reports that Teresa Klein, dubbed Corner store Caroline by shookt netizens, went berserk at a deli in Flatbush, New York last Wednesday after a 9-year-old boy supposedly got handsy with her.

Video taken at the scene shows Klein calling the cops, screaming that the child grabbed her backside, and causing the boy and his sister to burst into tears.

Bystanders were quick to jump to the kid's defense, and repeatedly told the crazy white lady to go home.

Neighbors say Klein is notorious for terrorizing residents, and likes to abuse the police hotline for the littlest things.

On Friday, Corner store Caroline apologized after watching the surveillance video— which showed it was the kid's backpack and not his hand that grazed her.

Still, Klein says she still wants to pursue charges against the kid's mom for supposedly being aggressive and threatening her life.

This from a woman who self-identifies as a humanist, feminist, and Buddhist? Geez. 3713784]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DACAIFKWKR7VKFLFIW79DTGWJV7ETRKBKWZURLA5CAKDRJAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AE7/303/AE7303502DC61CFCE09DF8FD2651363F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-17T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cornerstore caroline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ corner store caroline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman calls cops on kid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ white woman calls cops on black kid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crazy white lady]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crazy white woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shopping while black]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/healthy-mice-made-from-same-sex-%0Aparents-for-the-first-time-3713767</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Healthy mice made from same-sex 
parents for the first time 3713767]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — Scientists in China have successfully used gene editing and stem cell techniques to produce mice with two mothers.

The researchers used cells called haploid embryonic stem cells which contained half of the usual number of chromosomes from one mouse and took DNA from another, according to a study published in the journal Cell Stem Cell.

The scientists then used Crispr-Cas9 to delete the imprinting from three regions of the DNA by cutting out a single letter of the genetic code which made the genetic material appear more male.

Without the correct pattern of male and female imprinting, a viable embryo cannot be produced.

The embryonic stem cells were then injected into the eggs of a different female mouse which then developed into embryos. This produced 29 live mice from 210 embryos.

The researchers also tried the same technique on two male mice. It involved cutting off seven imprintings from the DNA of the male mouse instead of three from the female mouse.

The embryo from the male mouse was successfully created, however the baby mouse  only survived for 48 hours after birth.

The scientists say the mice were healthy and went on to have mice of their own.

The author of the study said this technique would be ten times more difficult for humans and primates. 3713767]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSKFIYZGA5AFCAZ9LFJAK9LTGICEZRRNABKFPT3XAADRIWRBAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/43F/466/43F4663233673E124186F0E35E79829B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-17T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gene-editing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Crispr-Cas9]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DNA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crispr mice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetic code]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gene editing crispr]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gene editing china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gene editing in mice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gene editing technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ haploid embryonic stem cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna editing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna editing crispr]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna editing technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna editing mice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mice with same sex parents]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-fired-after-refusing-man-entry-into-his-own-building-3714613</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman fired after refusing man entry into his own building 3714613]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS — A Missouri woman's entitlement was on full display Saturday, when she tried to stop a black man from entering his own apartment complex.

Fox reports that D'Arreion Toles had been returning home to his loft in downtown St. Louis when a woman walking her dog parked herself in front of the door and wouldn't budge.

A series of videos taken at the scene shows Toles asking the woman, later identified as Hilary Brooke Mueller, repeatedly to please move, but she only asks if he's a resident.

When he confirms he lives in the building, she then demands his apartment number, refusing to let him through when he won't tell, saying she's uncomfortable.

And yet even after he moves past, she kept on following him — into the elevator and all the way to his unit. She seems to back off after he unlocks his front door, and does a weird 180 claiming to want to meet him because he's a neighbor.

The encounter should have ended with Toles shutting his door. But Mueller took it a step further by calling police, who came 30 minutes later asking about the incident.

The videos were posted to Facebook and have since gotten millions of views, and even more online hate directed at Hallway Hillary.

Her employers weren't too happy with her racially profiling her neighbor either, and have since fired her over the disturbing video.

Well, you know what they say about karma. 3714613]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AECAMYCUKWKFPWRSKFLFXK4UMAESVR34AJPW5HICASKFCVRDK5QFMVAGKA6AVAK7Q6ZDEWZWB2NA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9A2/61F/9A261FBB6664B5303F266B0459F58362.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man blocked from apartment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black neighbor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black american]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ policing blacks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ policing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missouri woman fired]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missouri apartment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ st. louis loft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luxury loft]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/youtube-shuts-down-globally-sends-world-into-chaos-3714605</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Youtube shuts down globally, sends world into chaos 3714605]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[YOUTUBE — October 16th — or 17th depending on where you live — a date which will live in infamy, because it's the day YouTube broke worldwide.  

The YouTube website and app reportedly went down for users around the globe.
A whole bunch of errors slammed the service, like 500 internal server errors to invalid response errors. 

Some users reported being hit with a redirect when they tried to access the YouTube homepage. 
YouTube quickly hopped on Twitter to let everyone know they are working on the problem.
Users meanwhile quickly jumped on social media to report the issues, while news outlets worldwide were saved from a slow news day.

The sheer amount of YouTube dollars lost by creators worldwide during the outage will most likely run into the tens of dollars internationally.
In the end … YouTube technicians were finally able to get the service back online. 3714605]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLRCCKSA2JREDTDLJLWZ9BHGEEB3SKZAVBWMHAHABJWKBAAKNBFKWCTKJVFZAAJQ64DKATMAWNB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/968/B36/968B36A4097127AAA4A9D1A804D21EB5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube down]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube broken]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube 500 internal server error]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube down worldwide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube error 503]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uae-plans-to-build-mars-training-city-here-on-earth-3714446</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UAE plans to build Mars training city here on Earth 3714446]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED ARAB EMIRATES — The United Arab Emirates is planning to build a Mars training city here on Earth.
The US$136 million dollar project will be called Mars Science City and consists of interconnected dome structures that span 1.9 million square feet, around the size of two Alcatraz Islands, according to Science Alert.
According to Popular Science, the city will be used by engineers to prototype future Mars building materials and construction techniques. It will also house labs that can simulate various parts of Mars' environment. 
Researchers will practice several methods of farming on light resources as Mars lacks water and nutritious soil. Waste and water recycling methods will also be tested. 

With Mars radiation being stronger than on Earth, the domes will be used to test material that can block solar radiation. 
The domed city will also be able to filter in more or less sunlight, possibly to better mirror Mars time. 

The UAE plans to have a team of people live in the city for a year to develop strategies for surviving long-term on the Red Planet. 
Besides laboratories, the proposed city will also contain a museum dedicated to space achievements. 3714446]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLFPC3XA5CRAD3FBBJRK9UWGIESRFCZAFJRTFALKRCRIVCWAELRPVCXAWWWAAK5QZSDMWZZKMGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CAE/5E0/CAE5E0C7635023FC7AB1716C0E66FB54.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UAE Mars Science City]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars Science City project]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars training city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars settlements]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-tourists-destroy-sea-of-rare-pink-grass-to-take-selfies-3714383</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese tourists destroy sea of rare pink grass to take selfies 3714383]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — Apparently some Chinese tourists thought it was a great idea to ignore barriers and jump into a sea of flowers to take selfies. 

Photos published by Chinese media outlets show the tourists entering the area to sit and lie down for photos, flattening the grass while doing so.

A woman surnamed Zheng, reportedly a caretaker of the park, said it broke her heart when she saw the tourists destroying the grass just for a few selfies.

Her voice turned hoarse from yelling at the ill-mannered tourists, according to the South China Morning Post.

She told local reporters she felt like her child was being bullied but she couldn't do anything to stop it.

She added that the rare pink grass was imported from Australia and took three years for them to tend it.

However it only took two weeks for the selfie-seeking tourists to destroy the pretty pink grass, which typically is able to last for at least two months.

She said even though the pictures the tourists took must be pretty, they have ugly behavior.

Zheng said they were left with no choice but to cut the grass down in order to ensure the pink grass has a chance to bloom again next year. 3714383]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JWCDTVAIBRKBRYLVDR59JGMMEEXF3ZLWPFMHKTAFKFEW34AMIWPVT6KA5RVVRNQVSGIBI2KEHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D90/1BB/D901BBE9462D0D94A24C85C069EBDEEF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese tourists]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie mania]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pink grass ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rare pink grass]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pink grass destroyed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese tourists behaving badly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie mania china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese tourists destroy grass flowers for selfies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists destroy rare pink grass for selfies]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uae-to-launch-space-probe-to-mars-in-2020-3714298</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UAE to launch space probe to Mars in 2020 3714298]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED ARAB EMIRATES — The Hope Mars Mission, also known as Emirates Mars Mission, will be the first mission to Mars by any Arab nation if it successfully launches in 2020.

The uncrewed probe has been named Hope or Al-Amal in Arabic to send out a message of optimism to Arabs around the world.

The Hope probe will be hexagonal in shape and structure with a mass of about 1,500 kilograms and 2.37 meters in width and 2.90 meters in height, according to Khaleej Times.

The spacecraft will also use three 600-watt solar panels to charge its batteries which will unfold once the probe is in orbit. 

It will also communicate with Earth via a high-gain antenna.

Hope will be launched from Japan using Mitsubishi's H-IIA launcher and will take approximately 200 days to travel to Mars at speeds of up to 40,000 km per hour.

The spacecraft will carry a digital camera, an infrared spectrometer and a ultraviolet spectrometer to gather climate and atmospheric data of Mars and send the images back to Earth.

If everything goes according to plan, the probe will arrive in Mars in 2021 and is expected study the atmosphere of Mars for about two years. 3714298]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLAIDAJA6LAPAR7L2LA57URMJIEZFC9KMDWZGZEKEERZBAAAAJWMVKXKNXFXYAPF66GPVTMABQA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FA2/D0D/FA2D0D65ADD40CC05C46A5A21876A985.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UAE]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hope mars mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uae mars mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uae mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  hope mars mission uae]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hope mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Emirates Mars Mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emirates mars mission 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emirates mars mission hope spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emirates mars mission-hope probe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emirates mission mars journey]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-weapons-are-the-u-s-selling-saudi-arabia--3715258</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What weapons are the U.S. selling Saudi Arabia? 3715258]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON D.C. / RIYADH — The disappearance of Jamal Khashoggi has prompted angry lawmakers to call for a halt to a $110 billion arms deal with Saudi Arabia.

Reuters reports that U.S. President Donald Trump is reluctant to block the package, saying it would hurt American jobs, even as critics dispute its actual worth since it's not based on actual signed contracts.

White House officials told The National Interest that the list of weapons to be sold to the Saudis are still being finalized, although agreements released by the Defense Security Cooperation Agency provide a partial list.
 
According to these agreements, Saudi Arabia is buying 48 CH-47 Chinook helicopters, 10 Persistent Threat Detection Aerostats, P-8 Poseidon aircrafts, and C-130 Hercules transport planes.

Land-based weaponry included in the deal include 133 M1A2S Abrams tanks, Bradley Infantry Fighting Vehicles, and the $13-billion THAAD anti-ballistic missile defense system.

As part of their naval modernization program, the Kingdom is getting four Multi-Mission Surface Combatant frigates and 48 Harpoon Block II missiles, among others.

The Saudis are also buying Standoff Land Attack Missiles, the medium-range Joint Standoff Weapon, and about $63 million worth of artillery shells.

Several U.S. weapons manufacturers like Lockheed Martin and Boeing have released statements announcing the deals, but are reportedly still awaiting details from the government. 3715258]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLAPDRHABJRACTABADA5KJAGICSVSC3KEDWXH3RAFJAAAACBZLFIBC6KM7WTB37QFZGAAI6KREA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DFD/A5A/DFDA5A4FF5C98B762CA8AB270F9CE461.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>87</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US Saudi arms deal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arms deal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi arms deal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US arms sales]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump arms deal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ military weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ $110 billion arms deal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missing journalist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jamal Khashoggi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Lockheed Martin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Boeing]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/elk-hunter-survives-grizzly-attack-thanks-to-some-bear-spray-3715192</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Elk hunter survives grizzly attack thanks to some bear spray 3715192]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOZEMAN, MONTANA — An elk hunter is thanking his — well, his friend's — bear spray after it saved him from a grizzly attack on Saturday in Gallatin National Forest. 
Bob Legasa and his hunting partner, Greg Gibson, were moving toward some elk when he heard a growl, according to Legasa's Facebook post. 
It was a 2-year-old cub and its mother only about 12 yards away from a tree. After the cub growled, it moved over and that's when the mother charged. 
Legasa didn't have time to reach his bear spray. The grizzly bit his hand, breaking a bone in his arm, and clawed at his face. 
That's when Gibson rushed over and discharged bear spray into the grizzly's face, which caused her to let go. 
Legasa pulled out his own spray, but ended up macing himself instead — doh. Gibson then discharged his spray again, but the wind blew it back into his eyes. 
The bears ran off as both men were temporarily blinded by their own sprays. 

Funny thing is that three weeks earlier, the duo made a bear spray safety video for Gibson's Montana Guide Service, according to Legasa in an AP phone interview.    

After the bear spray wore off a bit, the two made it way back to their truck. 3715192]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KAGYAFAJLWEYIVBWKRZKBCMJLSVR3ZKBIRXGZBARERECANAELWMBRAA2XAZYCZQIUGEVCJAAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/713/27B/71327BAE8604EE69BFD9D3A8776DB0EF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man survives grizzly attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ grizzly bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bear spray]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gallatin National Forest]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-to-launch-artificial-moon-into-space-in-two-years-3715018</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China to launch artificial moon into space in two years 3715018]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHENGDU, CHINA — Officials in China are planning to launch an illumination satellite in the southwestern city of Chengdu within the next two years.

The man-made moon will have a reflective coating on its surface to reflect light from the sun, according to Asia Times.

It also will have solar panel-like wings on its surface which can be adjusted for precise lighting.

The satellite will reportedly be eight times brighter than the real moon and could replace street lights.

The artificial moon would be able to light an area of up to 10 to 80 kilometers in diameter, giving a dusk-like hue to complement the real moon in the sky.

Officials in the city hope the artificial moon will bring in more tourists once it is in the sky.

However some members of the public are reportedly worried the man-made moon might have an adverse effect on animals and astronomical observation. 3715018]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJKFKXRAAIAWIDRRBNLR39DWMNIBKSK3LSJA5TZLBZDWCAZEBIQFMV3UAE7WAVIEQS6UIAKIAVEB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/79C/A4B/79CA4B2630FAACFC838D96491DA89F0D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial moon china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial moon lamp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial moon lamp explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man-made moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ replacing street lights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satellite]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/latin-american-coffee-supply-threatened-by-fungus-outbreak-3714817</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Latin American coffee supply threatened by fungus outbreak 3714817]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANTIGUA, GUATEMALA — A fungus outbreak is threatening to wipe out Latin American coffee crops and trigger a global coffee crisis.

According to the American Phytopathological Society, coffee rust is a disease caused by the fungus hemileia vastatrix, which is characterized by half-smooth spores.

Infections usually start on the lowermost leaves of a coffee plant, where the fungus protrude through the stomata on the undersides of leaves.

The disease causes powdery yellow-orange lesions to appear on the bright green leaves, making them turn a brownish yellow tinge. These lesions produce more spores, which spread by wind or rain to infect others.

Though the fungus doesn't kill coffee plants, it debilitates them by causing leaves to fall out. With its nutrition source gone, the plant is unable to produce coffee cherries.

Coffee rust currently has no cure, and while copper-based fungicides have proven effective in controlling infection, chemicals can accumulate and become toxic to the environment.

Scientists have also turned to genetic resistance, cross-breeding the rust-susceptible Arabica with a natural hybrid immune to the disease to create a more rust-resistant variety.

The resulting beans, though not as high quality as the Arabica, were at least good enough to be accepted by growers and buyers, according to the BBC.

However, the World Coffee Research has warned that the fungus is evolving, and may overcome once-immune genes in five to ten years. As of 2017, the Honduran Lempira was no longer resistant, and the natural Timor Hybrid's resistance is also breaking down.

Coffee rust had previously wiped out crops in present-day Sri Lanka during the late 1800s. But while that region bounced back by switching to tea production, it's unlikely Latin America will be able to do the same. 3714817]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAFMYCTKZBFEYISBAAAX7URNBIBTRK5ABPA5FILB2IAZDIGAIQAPVTVKNXWVB3ZFS6GTCKLAZHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BFA/C43/BFAC4393AB5D461A86627BE3FFC68F68.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>112</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee rust]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee leaf rust]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee fungus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fungus outbreak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plant fungus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plant disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hybrid coffee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colombian coffee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ latin america coffee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee supply]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-space-station-to-launch-by-2020-3714813</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese Space Station to launch by 2020 3714813]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — The Chinese Space Station is expected to be launched in 2020, according to Xinhua.

China plans to build the third multi-module space station in space, following the International Space Station and Mir.

The Chinese government plans to first launch Tianhe or the Core Cabin Module of the Chinese Space Station by 2020. It will provide the life support system as well as the power of the station.

The Laboratory Cabin Module, Shenzhou, and Tianzhou will be launched subsequently. 

The module of the Chinese Space Station will be fully assembled in orbit.

The station will be fully assembled between 2020 and 2022.

The entire station will weigh about 60,000 kilograms and will have a life span of about 10 years.

China has already launched Tiangong-1 in 2011 and Tiangong-2 in 2016 as test stations for the planned Chinese Space Station. 3714813]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KABWADACKVCAECIRKFJWR9BGMECVTURMA5AF7FCYBZDRZYIJKIIF5YAHAZ7WRV32FBZGCCKQA6PA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4A3/71D/4A371D41AE9F48BC9CF1A89B759D00F2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Space Station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China to launch space station in 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ multi-module space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china new space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese space station to be fully assembled in space]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kanye-west-s-idea-to-redesign-air-force-one-as-an-iplane-3715920</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kanye West's idea to redesign Air Force One as an iPlane 3715920]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Kanye West has proposed a plan to replace the Air Force One with an iPlane 1.

The original design of the iPlane 1 was created by Shabtai Hirshberg and consists of a jet with a wide, flat body and a transparent roof.

As seen on the self-promotion portfolio site Behance, where Hirshberg publicized his design, the jet would have wings that would be able to turn up and down while taking off and landing.

It would also potentially be able to take off and land using a standard runway or in water. It would also use a hybrid engine to ensure the plane flies quietly in the sky.

There would also be a docking area for the jets in the water when they are not in use.

However, the jet was not initially designed to be powered by hydrogen.

Hirshberg told The Verge he is currently working with a group to develop a smaller, jet-sized version of his original concept.

He also added he wouldn't mind collaborating with Kanye West and Apple if they actually decide to take the idea forward. 3715920]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEARMD3ULNJR7CR9LSIWXLD3GEEBRR37AFPWMUCSKVDWPDAGKNCF5VK5KI5RZYIPQW4XRVR6AEFA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AA/B25/1AAB251B2954F5648A844C974F03AE1D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iPlane 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iplane kanye]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iplane kanye west]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iplane one]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kanye ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kanye west]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shabtai Hirshberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iPlane design]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ futuristic plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hybrid engine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apple iplane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apple iplane 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kanye's plan to replace air force one with iPlane]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/google-completely-sells-out-with-china-dragonfly-search-engine-3715879</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Google completely sells out with China Dragonfly search engine 3715879]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA — Google CEO Sundar Pichai confirmed this week the company has decided to kowtow to Beijing by building and testing a censored search engine. 
First reported by The Intercept in August, Google's Project Dragonfly would block search results for queries the Chinese regime deems sensitive. 

So terms like human rights, democracy, religion, peaceful protests, and of course Taiwan would all be censored, in addition to all the other silly things the Chinese government gets their feelings hurt over.  
Pichai announced the massive sell out at Wired's 25th anniversary summit in San Francisco. 
Pichai claims a censored Google search engine could serve over 99 percent of queries in China. Unfortunately, for a country with 1.3 billion people, that remaining 1 percent could still be astronomical number.
According to CNBC, the CEO said that in any country that Google operates, it must balance its values — providing users access to information, freedom of expression and user privacy — with obeying the local laws. 
Well, since Beijing values absolutely none of those things, that's really not much of a balancing act, is it?  
What's even more interesting is that while Google decided not to renew a Pentagon AI drone deal because of staff backlash, it's more than willing to ignore staff protest this time around. 

Pichai claims it is still very early and that Google hasn't decided yet if it's going to roll out Dragonfly in China. 3715879]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEBRIDKULFIR3YKABNJRZ6LVGJIB5SILKZDA3UZBAICRICREL6BAKYAAKSUFCAIIQMTXKBTJASPB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8E3/17A/8E317A137BA043492A142A6582C91BD3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>120</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google Project Dragonfly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google censored China search engine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google CEO Sundar Pichai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google censored search]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google China]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-dies-from-rare-brain-disease-after-eating-squirrel-brains-3715798</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man dies from rare brain disease after eating squirrel brains 3715798]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROCHESTER, NEW YORK — A hunter in New York died from a rare mad cow-like disease he may have contracted from eating squirrel brains.

Miami Herald reports that the 61-year-old man was taken to a hospital in Rochester, New York after suffering from impaired walking and thinking.

An MRI revealed that the man's brain looked similar to those with variant Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease, which is caused by infectious proteins called prions and tied to the consumption of contaminated beef.

Prion build-up in the cells rapidly deteriorates the brain, causing it to shrink, and tiny holes to appear in the tissues — making it look like a sponge.

The disease is fatal, with patients typically dying within a year of showing symptoms.

The Rochester patient met a similar fate, and died five months after being diagnosed with the infection in 2015.

Doctors found out from his family that the man liked to hunt, and believe he may have contracted Creutzfeldt-Jakob from eating squirrels' brains.

Variant Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease is extremely rare. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, there are only four confirmed cases in the U.S. 3715798]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AWMYIFLMBW3XZVBJLWR6D4MEAS7FINA6KWRUCRAWJAEARKB2CRGWKSKFYFCBILPW4GRAR3KREB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F25/A26/F25A269B89694BF58FA0E61185852846.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel brains]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vcjd]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ creutzfeldt jakob disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ variant creutzfeldt jakob disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rare disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mad cow disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prions]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-rescued-two-days-after-falling-into-snake-filled-mine-shaft-3715729</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man rescued two days after falling into snake-filled mine shaft 3715729]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AGUILA. ARIZONA — An Arizona man is in good condition after being rescued from a mine shaft he was stuck in for two days.

ABC 15 reports that John Waddell had plummeted into the 100-foot deep shaft on Monday, after telling a friend he was going over there.

The 62-year-old broke both legs during the fall, and quickly realized he wasn't alone in the shaft — there were rattlesnakes slithering all around him.

He managed to kill three of the serpents during the 48 hours he was there, all while screaming for help.

Waddell had a deal with his friend Terry Schrader, to come look for him if he wasn't back by Tuesday. Schrader drove to the shaft Wednesday, and immediately heard Waddell hollering for help.

He called deputies, and a rescue team eventually managed to pull the man out to safety some six hours later. Despite broken bones and severe dehydration, Waddell's injuries weren't life-threatening. 

Still, the chap is lucky to be alive. 3715729]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMCFGXZBLZDFXCASBJPAXLUSMZESZRILKSPFZHCRKJLRZBAHL6BFGW3VK56FTYK5PRTXPVCMKSMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/225/7C5/2257C50288FB41E7B13C1B95FEF51EB1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man falls into mine shaft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trapped]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man trapped]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rattlesnakes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mine shaft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man stuck in mine shaft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ survival stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mine shaft rescue]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/outbreak-of-paralyzing-polio-like-disease-across-the-u-s--3715663</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Outbreak of paralyzing polio-like disease across the U.S. 3715663]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[U.S.A — The CDC has confirmed the rise of acute flaccid myelitis, also known as polio-like disease.

Acute flaccid myelitis is a disease that causes drooping eyelids,difficulty with eye movement, loss of muscle tone, decreased reflexes along with other symptoms, according to the CDC.

The disease mainly affects children and could potentially paralyze a child's arms and/or legs.

Doctors typically diagnose the disease by examining the patient's nervous system or by conducting an MRI and looking at the patient's brain and spinal cord.

As there is no specific treatment for acute flaccid myelitis, officials recommend physical therapy for muscle weakness, washing hands and staying up to date on vaccines.

This year alone, more than half of all the states in the U.S. have confirmed possible cases of the polio-like disease.

Officials are also unsure how the disease spreads and is encouraging parents to seek medical care immediately if their child has sudden weakness in their arms or legs. 3715663]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLRAAABBWKRADATLNJAI7L3GIBSTRZKAWKFZGCSKVCAAWZABNCWCAK5LWUF3WC4PW4GTAZVKRHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AC6/2AB/AC62AB783E5D9D6A2A3D51ABD5D1BE38.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acute flaccid myelitis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acute flaccid myelitis symptoms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acute flaccid myelitis virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polio-like disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polio-like virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polio-like outbreak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acute flaccid myelitis outbreak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ outbreak of polio-like disease]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cloudflare-providing-internet-security-to-syrian-government-3715489</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cloudflare providing internet security to Syrian government 3715489]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — U.S. internet security company Cloudflare is providing its DDoS services to the Syrian regime.

A DDoS is a distributed denial of service attack where several computers target a network, website or service and cause a disruption or end to its service for its users.

Unless exempt, U.S. persons are generally blocked under Executive Order 13582 from engaging in business with a Syrian state-owned entity. 

TomoNews reached out to Cloudflare and the U.S. treasury department for comment but neither got back to us by press time. 3715489]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZAFPYZELIBF7XAYL5AAR72GMNJSIR36A6PATHKYKWLRKWRJB6DRGAZEAWXA3WAPQNZUEVZWB5HA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C38/BA1/C38BA1959FBFB98959B1107E6BC8AE28.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>136</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cloudflare]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DDOS protection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ddos attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ denial-of-service attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ distributed denial of service]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Assad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria 2019]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/divers-swim-90-feet-into-sewage-tank-to-remove-massive-fatberg-3717349</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Divers swim 90 feet into sewage tank to remove massive fatberg 3717349]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHARLESTON, SOUTH CAROLINA — A team of lucky divers were tasked with the job of plunging 90 feet into sewage tanks to remove a big old fatberg.

According to ABC 7, the Charleston Water System dumped the news over social media last week that specialized divers at the Plum Island Wastewater Treatment Center had to be sent into a wet well to unclog a bunch of pumps backed up by a huge mass of flushed wet wipes. 

The divers had to make their way through 90 feet of raw sewage with zero visibility and find the source of the blockage with only their hands. 
And what did they find waiting for them? A massive fatberg of baby wipes, oil, fat, grease, tampons, string, hair and makeup pads. 
According to officials, the biggest culprit in the fatberg was definitely the wet wipes.  
It took the divers several fun-filled trips to extract the massive clumps of sewage-soaked wipes and clear the pumps. 
According to the utility, the operation took several days of around-the-clock work to get everything moving again. 
For a reward, the divers were treated to a proper hosing down from head to toe with bleach. 
According the Charleston Water, the only things you should be flushing are #1, #2 and toilet paper. Words of wisdom to live by. 3717349]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSKWPDZGARBA5B3EKFIWXLBAMNLSZRCRK2IW5HAGKFLRMACRBAKFPWCYKWWWZWRLFFZXCCI3KEGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1C8/253/1C825387D1D3D04A0B1E7B728F7BEA01.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wet wipes blockage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sewer blockage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Charleston Water fatberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Charleston Water baby wipes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-train-derailment-leaves-at-least-18-dead-3717341</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Taiwan train derailment leaves at least 18 dead 3717341]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[YILAN, TAIWAN — A train derailment in northeast Taiwan on Sunday afternoon killed at least 18 people and injured another 175, according to the authorities. 

According to The News Lens, the Puyuma Express was traveling from New Taipei City to Taitung City with 366 people on board when the accident occurred at 4:50 p.m. near the Xinma station near Su-ao in Yilan County. 
All eight cars derailed with five overturning, according to the Taiwan Railway Administration, or TRA.     
A majority of the casualties occurred in four carriages that flipped 90 degrees onto their sides, the News Lens reported TRA Director Lu Jieh-shen as saying at a press conference. 

Passengers said there were several instances of the emergency brakes being applied before hearing a bump immediately before the derailment, as reported by Taiwan's Apple Daily.
A total of 60 emergency response vehicles and more than 250 rescue personnel were dispatched to the crash site. 
Officials are still unclear what caused the crash. According to the TRA, an investigation is underway to determine what caused the accident. 3717341]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWJRPXZHAJJFVWTDBBJAKLDRGSKSTRK6KZDW5UZEKJLRABIHAFCFKVZAKJVWZVIPFF6XTWZ7KZAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/352/696/352696E3BFB4A7712335E9895BD8929C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan train derailment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan train accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Puyuma Express train accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan accident]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/pando-world-s-largest-organism-is-in-danger-of-collapsing-3717177</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Pando, world's largest organism, is in danger of collapsing 3717177]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UTAH — The Pando aspen clone located in Fishlake National Forest in Utah is considered to be the world's largest living organism, but a recent study has found it is dying out. 
According to a new study published on Wednesday in PLOS One by Utah State University researchers Paul Rogers, Ph.D. and Darren McAvoy, Ph.D., the Pando is in danger of collapse. 
According to Inverse, Pando is a massive grove of 47,000 genetically identical stems growing from a single underground root system of a quaking aspen tree that covers an area of 107 acres. 
According to Forbes, aspens have the ability to produce clones through offshoots from their root system and are able to colonize large areas of land through the root system. 
The new study found that the Pando has been declining in size for decades and has not been able to replace dying aspens. 
The scientists found that a combination of grazing animals, like mule deer and cattle, and human encroachment have led to the Pando collapse. 
The researchers found that protective fencing was effective at protecting the Pando. 
In order to survive long term, Rogers told the New York Times, that more thorough fencing would be required, along with culling some deer and making sure cattle don't graze in the grove. 3717177]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAWMC3XKABRVARWL2IWX7URGNLVTFAQLSIWXUTTAEBWMWAGKWBRIVTYABWARVINQJ2DMBI2AAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/84E/080/84E080F92303490FBF22E5B400BE9BAB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pando]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pando Clone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pando world's largest organism]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pando Clone decline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pando aspen clone]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-murder-of-jamal-khashoggi-what-we-know-now-3718109</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The murder of Jamal Khashoggi: what we know now 3718109]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ISTANBUL — Saudi Arabia has finally admitted that Jamal Khashoggi is dead, but have so far given conflicting accounts about what went down.

Fortunately, surveillance footage and Turkish intelligence info have helped piece together what really happened to the Saudi journalist and dissident. Here's what we know now.

The New York Times reports that on October 2, Jamal Khashoggi entered the Saudi consulate in Istanbul through the front entrance at 1:14 p.m.

According to a person close to Turkish president Erdogan, Khashoggi was attacked within two minutes of entering. He was dead within seven minutes, and dismembered within 22 minutes.

Newly leaked footage now shows that the Saudis employed a body double to put on a fake beard and wear the deceased Khashoggi's clothes as part of a cover-up. Reports suggested that the body double, identified as 57-year-old Mustafa al-Madani, is an intelligence agent, though his main qualification seems to be that he was of similar height, age, and build to Khashoggi.  

Madani was captured on camera strolling the streets of Istanbul with an accomplice, but was recognized as an imposter due to his different shoes.

Khashoggi's body, meanwhile, has yet to be found. Saudi officials claim they don't know the location of his remains, only saying it was rolled in a rug before being handed to a local accomplice.

A pro-government Turkish newspaper reported that on the day of the killing, a member of Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman's entourage made four calls to his office and one to the U.S., adding to speculation that he ordered the act.

Turkish intelligence sources also told Reuters that an influential adviser to the Crown Prince ran the slaughter via Skype, though many believe he may just be taking the fall for his boss.

The Turks supposedly have audio recordings and other evidence of Khashoggi's gruesome end at the hands of his compatriots, but have yet to disclose them. 3718109]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNNWPYZJBMBFMBCEBMBA37DWGFIBRE36LSKRVUABKEEF3AAJLJBFAVIDKBXRXWIIQWZDCVR5AZEB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/549/9FD/5499FD9FC178F71203E60AC7932EAD36.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>91</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jamal Khashoggi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi journalist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi dissident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jamal Khashoggi disappearance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ body double]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi cover up]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ decoy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mohammed bin Salman MBS]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Saudi Crown prince]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/two-u-s-navy-vessels-sail-through-taiwan-strait-3718084</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Two U.S. Navy vessels sail through Taiwan Strait 3718084]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIWAN STRAIT — The Pentagon sent two U.S. ships through the Taiwan Strait, a move that might amp up already tense U.S.-China relations.

CNN reports that on Monday, the USS Curtis Wilbur, a guided missile destroyer, and the USS Antietam, a guided missile cruiser, conducted a routine transit through the Taiwan Strait, to demonstrate 'U.S. commitment to a free and open Indo-Pacific', according to the deputy spokesman of the U.S. Pacific Fleet.

The two U.S. Navy warships reportedly sailed from south to north through the 110-mile waterway that separates Taiwan from China.

U.S. Defense officials told CNN that multiple Chinese warships followed the vessels during the transit, but kept at a safe distance.

America's show of force comes amidst an ongoing trade war with Beijing, as well as tensions between the two countries over China's militarization of the South China Sea.

Late last month, a U.S. guided missile destroyer passing near the Spratlys had to maneuver to avoid colliding with a Chinese ship that came within 45 yards of its bow.

China is unhappy with American support of Taiwan, in particular a $330 million arms sale package to the island nation.

While the U.S. officially adheres to Beijing's 'One China Policy', the Trump administration has sought to forge closer ties with Taiwan. 3718084]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KRMCIFAWJRAAZSLNKWZ6DUMAEBTST6K2IRTHAFK2KWTA34A6DW7WKRK6UARBIMFMSGRBI9AVGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/212/5C5/2125C5EDC246926BE56977F9A71B61BC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US China tensions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US China relations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US china feud]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan Strait]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trade war]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Taiwan relations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ One China Policy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ USS Decatur]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ freedom of navigation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ show of force]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tourists-graffiti-800-year-old-wall-in-thailand-face-10-years-in-prison-3717975</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tourists graffiti 800-year-old wall in Thailand, face 10 years in prison 3717975]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHIANG MAI, THAILAND — A pair of genius tourists could be looking at up to 10 years behind bars in Thailand for spray painting an 800-year-old wall. 
Lee Furlong from Britain and Brittney Schneider from Canada, both 23, were busted at a hostel in Chiang Mai last Thursday, authorities said, according to Reuters.

CCTV footage shows the dynamic duo spray-painting the wall near the main entrance to the city's old town around 4 a.m. on Thursday.  
Thailand authorities said the partners in crime appeared to be intoxicated. Wow, that's a surprise. 
Furlong tagged the wall Scouser Lee in an apparent reference to the English city of Liverpool. Schneider decided to keep it simple with just a B. 
According to Thai police, the two are now looking at up to 10 years behind bars, a fine of up to $30,000 or both, if found guilty. 3717975]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNRIX3TBNIWEBKDLWLWXLSANFJB3RT5KNLFXGRCB6JAKDIEKZJWKBABKA6RVBZPFN2UCBZ6KZAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/418/E38/418E38BD5EBB753165ABEA977F8875F0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists behaving badly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists arrested in thailand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists spray-painting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists vandalize]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chiang mai]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/immunotherapy-chemo-combo-wins-against-breast-cancer-3717805</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Immunotherapy-chemo combo wins against breast cancer 3717805]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Women with a hard-to-treat form of breast cancer were found to live longer when treated with a combination of chemotherapy and immunotherapy drugs.

CNN reports that triple negative breast cancer is an aggressive form of the disease in which cancer cells lack receptors for estrogen, progesterone, and HER2 — making it unresponsive to certain treatments.

Cancer cells can be treated with chemotherapy, but often develop resistance to it, allowing them to spread to other body parts. Patients usually survive 18 months or less.

A new study published in the New England Journal of Medicine found that treatment combining chemotherapy with the immunotherapy drug Tecentriq was more effective, improving overall survival rates by almost four months.

In the clinical trial, 902 women treated at 246 medical centers in 41 countries were randomly assigned either Tecentriq and chemo, or a placebo and chemo.

Chemotherapy was given once a week while the immunotherapy drug was administered intravenously every two weeks.

The drug deactivates a protein in the cancer cells which keeps it safe from the immune system, while chemotherapy roughens up its surface, enabling the immune system to recognize and attack the cancer.

The new treatment is currently being reviewed, and may well become the first FDA-approved immunotherapy drug to treat breast cancer, reports the New York Times. 3717805]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNJRGCZJANLAEBAVBIBAV9LSGNIETRKSLSKRVG3SKJJWGDICAJCWIVCRKWWFCWRFPVRXKAA6KWMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/958/D43/958D43F15455135F93D7B6DC80E7E546.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ breast cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer cure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cure for cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ triple negative breast cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemotherapy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immunotherapy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immunotherapy drug]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tecentriq]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atezolizumab]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/honduran-migrant-caravan-marches-north-to-u-s-border-3718855</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Honduran migrant caravan marches north to U.S. border 3718855]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN PEDRO SULA, HONDURAS — A massive caravan of migrants fleeing violence and poverty in Central America are marching north to the United States.

The New York Times reports that the migrant caravan started in San Pedro Sula, Honduras on October 12, with less than 200 people. Upon reaching Esquipulas, Guatemala, police blocked them for two hours but eventually allowed them to continue on.

The group's numbers swelled to over 7,000 as the journey from Honduras continued through Guatemala and to the Mexican border.

Mexico initially ordered migrants to submit to processing at a legal border crossing, but many have crossed illegally, storming through the border gate on October 19 and clashing with Mexican federal police.

The caravan is currently walking through Mexico, with over 1,000 miles to go before they can reach the United States border.

President Trump has been very vocal about his condemnations of the caravan, and has threatening to have the military close the border on them.

He has also threatened to cut off aid to Guatemala, Honduras, and El Salvador for not stopping their people from leaving their countries. 3718855]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLACDCUABNRCA3FLJJR37UUMFKV5FC9AVAFMTAHASKWXCRGASBWIB3YK2YW5WIPF63XRBRZKRHA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4D6/52D/4D652D49BCE3AE6ABC4BD276CCA6BAC7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ migrant caravan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ migrants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Honduran migrants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immigration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immigrants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ undocumented workers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ migrant route]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US border]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border control]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asylum]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-reason-why-trains-don-t-have-seatbelts-3718392</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The reason why trains don't have seatbelts 3718392]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIWAN — Seat belts on trains can cause more harm than good because the train's massive momentum makes it harder to decelerate, increasing the risk of impact injuries, according to experts.

Lap seat belts may cause spinal injuries as passengers' necks thrust forward during a crash, according to The New York Times.

Trains could use lap and shoulder seat belts, which offer more protection. 

However these seat belts could also injure passengers who get thrown from their seats upon impact.

Installing seat belts on all trains would also be very expensive for train authorities. 

A Puyuma express train crashed in Taiwan on October 21, with 18 people being killed and 190 people injured, to the Central New Agency reported. 3718392]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KECFVYIDKIAFAARVBJLA574RM5CVRSC4LVAWTFIHK2LRRCRIAALWEVK5KNXR3AAIQS3UKACMAAAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6F6/116/6F611628878D4379D7D6C4779E2C0D2D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train seats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wearing seat belts on train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train derailment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train derailment taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan train accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan train crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seat belts on train]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-longest-sea-bridge-connects-china-hk-and-macau-3718358</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's longest sea bridge connects China, HK and Macau 3718358]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — China has finally completed a 55 km long sea bridge which links Hong Kong's Lantau island to Zhuhai in China as well as Macau.

The structure is supported by three cable-stayed bridges, using 400,000 tons of steel. It is also designed to withstand winds of up to 340 kph, according to the Guardian.

The bridge includes a 6.7 km long submerged tunnel between two artificial islands in shallow waters.

The bridge connects the Greater Bay Area across southern China and encompasses 11 cities in the region.

The bridge was completed after nearly nine years and cost nearly $20 billion. 

The bridge was originally supposed to open in 2016, but didn't due to repeated delays. 3718358]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DWXCTWKEARPBZVLABFX92GMMBBTU36KJIF3HADA2IAXWTRAEJWKYKVA6VAVWREFSZDCVTIASMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/84A/3EB/84A3EB252C2C4A94408DF95113DAC0E6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hong Kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Macau]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea bridge hong kong macau]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea bridge construction china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china sea bridge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ longest sea bridge in the world]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ longest sea bridge in the world china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/not-exercising-is-even-worse-for-your-health-than-smoking-3718346</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Not exercising is even worse for your health than smoking 3718346]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CLEVELAND  —  Research has found that skipping leg day is quite possibly the fastest route to an early grave.

According to a study published in JAMA Network Open, not exercising is more harmful to human health than smoking, diabetes, or heart disease.

Researchers at the Cleveland Clinic studied 122,007 patients from January 1, 1991 to December 31, 2014, making them undergo treadmill testing and later recording mortality rates.

Their findings indicate that cardiorespiratory fitness is linked to a longer lifespan, and that there is no limit to the benefits of exercise. There have been concerns that those who are overactive or exercise excessively are at a higher risk of death, but the research reveals that this is not the case.

When compared to top exercise performers, the risk associated with death for those who were sedentary is 500 percent higher.

The study concludes that a sedentary lifestyle is equivalent to having a major disease. The good news is it's reversible, you just need to work that body. 3718346]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NWVCTVBVAAPWKAL5CR39D3GEDSRRC9K2IF3UCWAFJRVARGAZQAIVAELV6WTVIQFAUGPWI3KIEA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FF2/D09/FF2D09602335AFB98F7C505E483AE1FA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sedentary]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lazy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sedentary lifestyle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mortality]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smoking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ diabetes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exercise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ no exercise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ treadmill test]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/microplastics-found-in-90-of-table-salt-3718338</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Microplastics found in 90% of table salt 3718338]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INCHEON, SOUTH KOREA — Researchers from South Korea and Greenpeace East Asia have found that 90 percent of table salt sold around the world are contaminated with microplastics.

After analyzing salt from 21 countries in Europe, Asia, North and South America, and Africa, a new study found microplastics in 36 out of 39 brands, reports National Geographic.

Microplastic density was highest among Asian brands, especially those from Indonesia. The only three salts free from plastic were those from Taiwan, China, and France.

Researchers sampled three types of salts and found that sea salt had the highest microplastic levels, followed by lake salt, and then rock salt.

With particles often less than 5 millimeters in size and many the same color as salt, and they are barely noticeable.

The study estimates that the average adult consumes 2,000 microplastics a year through salt.

Scientists have yet to determine how harmful microplastics are to our bodies, but so far, experiments on mice haven't exactly brought good news. 3718338]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDFVYKXKAAFAWKHBJKRTKDSMJJVXE3ZA2JAVHAAARBRRVALBEKFEBC6AJWF7WC2QJ6GTAR9KVEA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3F0/1A6/3F01A62380483CFF1CA194282E9C81A5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[microplastics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[salt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[table salt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[microplastics in salt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[contaminated salt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[plastic salt]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/canadian-rapper-dies-while-trying-plane-wing-stunt-for-music-video-3719399</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Canadian rapper dies while trying plane wing stunt for music video 3719399]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRITISH COLUMBIA, CANADA — A Canadian rapper was attempting to perform a stunt on the wing of an airplane when things went real south. 
According to CTV News, Jon James McMurray had apparently been training intensively for months to walk on the wing of a small Cessna while rapping. 
While filming on Saturday, James made his way out onto the wing which caused the Cessna to suddenly plunge into a downward spiral that the pilot couldn't correct. 
James was wearing a parachute, but held onto the plane for too long. When he finally let go of the aircraft, it was too late to deploy his parachute. 
The 34-year-old landed in a hay field and instantly went to meet his maker. The plane was eventually able to land safely.   
The ex-professional skier was a fan of extreme sports like skydiving, base-jumping and BMX. 3719399]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKFMACSAAAACAIRL2PWR94UMWJV5FILKWJW7FKXAZCFRVAJLRKWEB3YAV5WVYIKPS6UKWA3AIHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E62/9AF/E629AF1316E45C448754416220B8385D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Canadian rapper]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jon James McMurray plane stunt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jon James plane stunt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jon James wing walking]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/australian-cruise-ship-dumps-food-waste-onto-the-great-barrier-reef-3719245</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Australian cruise ship dumps food waste onto the Great Barrier Reef 3719245]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GREAT BARRIER REEF, AUSTRALIA — The Australian Maritime Safety Authority has found that a cruise ship dumped 27,000 liters of food waste and gray water into the Great Barrier Reef in August.

The cruise spilled the polluted water into the reef on August 26, but authorities weren't notified until two days later when the cruise reported the incident themselves.

The cruise was detained by Australian authorities once it returned to Sydney. 
The ship had to pay a fine of US$1.5 million, CNN reported.

The cruise says the spill was unintentional and claim they only dumped 7,000 liters instead of the 27,000 liters.

However an Australian Senator cited an Australian Maritime Safety Authority report that says otherwise.

Discharging waste into the Barrier Reef is a serious offense as the coral reefs in the region are already being damaged due to climate change and environmental damage. 3719245]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AACFECTTKACAXCATL5BAVLURM2JSZEC4KWJFVGICAIAATVICASBAAWKSAI5W3VK7Q6ZGTAKJAREB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F59/A78/F59A78CE8DA70B02DDBE3391E9E86208.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ great barrier reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ barrier reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral reefs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cruise ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ waste spilt into great barrier reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ food waste]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ waste]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cruise ship spills waste in great barrier reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ food waste dumped in barrier reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Great Barrier Reef Marine Park]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-spots-perfectly-rectangular-iceberg-in-antarctica-3719065</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA spots perfectly rectangular iceberg in Antarctica 3719065]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA — A ridiculously rectangular iceberg was spotted last October 16, and there's only one question on everyone's minds: is it real?

NASA's Operation IceBridge photographed a tabular iceberg during a flyover over Antarctica. It's believed to have fractured from the Larsen C ice shelf in May, reports the Washington Post.

Unlike an angular iceberg which usually has just the tip sticking out, tabular icebergs have a flat surface and steep, vertical sides.

NASA and University of Maryland scientist Kelly Brunt explained to LiveScience that tabular icebergs form when an ice shelf grows out like a fingernail and calves off, often resulting in straight, geometric lines

The iceberg's sharp corners are an indication that its new, since wind and waves usually round it out.

The iceberg hasn't been measured, but is likely to be more than a mile across. It's definitely not the biggest one ever recorded, however, that distinction belongs to Iceberg B-15, which was 183 miles long and 23 miles wide. 3719065]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRBRMAIGK6IAAC3HL6KAR6DUGSLV5RIMKZAF7GRFA6JWZB3UKMIWMWAEKWUAZBT4QBZGRAAWB5AA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CCE/3DC/CCE3DC3CF949BA95A66E51BBFD8DB5A3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rectangular iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tabular iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Larsen Ca]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Larsen C ice shelf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice shelf calving]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ berg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA IceBridge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Operation IceBridge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Antarctica]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nypd-recalls-almost-3-000-body-cams-after-one-explodes-3719029</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NYPD recalls almost 3,000 body cams after one explodes 3719029]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — The New York Police Department has recalled nearly 3,000 body cameras after one of them exploded, according to a statement from the department. 

According to NBC News, a Staten Island NYPD officer was wearing the Vievu LE-5 body camera on Saturday night when he noticed the device started smoking.
The cop then took off the body cam, which then blew up. Luckily, no one was hurt. Unfortunately, there was no video of the incident. 
According to the NYPD statement, the incident revealed a potential for the battery inside the camera to ignite. The cause and scope of the defect are currently being investigated.
According to the NYPD, 2,990 of the 15,500 body cams in use by New York's Finest were LE-5 models. 
All officers wearing the Vievu LE-5 models were told to immediately remove them and return them back to their commands, according to police.
For now, those 2,990 officers will be without body cams. Hopefully they'll be able to stay out of trouble. 3719029]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEBRGCRDK6KRXDZRLACRILDXMBKV7S34A6IFVHIFAIDW7AKSBNCAKVKYKR7W3V34QZUXGWCIKIHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/64C/542/64C542E0D51639CB382FFD829D590841.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NYPD]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NYPD recalls body cams]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NYPD body cams]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Vievu LE-5]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Vievu LE-5 body cam]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ten-devices-sent-to-leading-democrats-and-trump-critics-3720054</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ten devices sent to leading Democrats and Trump critics 3720054]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — Suspicious packages containing pipe bombs were sent to 10 prominent Democrats and critics of U.S. President Donald Trump this week. 
According to the Washington Post, all the packages were discovered before reaching their intended targets and none of them detonated. 
On Monday, Oct. 22, the first device was sent to billionaire George Soros in New York. 

Then on Tuesday, Oct. 23, the Secret Service discovered a pipe bomb addressed to Trump punching bag, Not-So-Straight Hillary and former president Bill Clinton. 
On Wednesday, Oct. 24, Secret Service intercepted a bomb addressed to Obama in Northwest Washington. 
Another device was discovered in the CNN mailroom at the Time Warner Center in the Big Apple, addressed to former CIA director John Brennan. 
A suspect package was also addressed to former attorney general Eric H. Holder, but was sent to Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz. 
Two other packages addressed to Maxine Waters were found by authorities in L.A. and Washington. 
On Thursday, Oct. 25, Robert De Niro got into the mix as well with a pipe bomb. 
And not to be left out, were two bombs sent to former vice president Joe Biden. 
According to the New York Times, all of the packages had the same return address — Rep. Debbie Wasserman Schultz in Florida. 
Authorities are now focusing on Florida after postal service information indicated many of the packages were mailed and processed from the state. 3720054]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSJRIDZGAWLA7B3AL2IR5KDSGEEETEZLLSIAVURCASIRRWRNAWCWIYCRAE6AZWKZQJ4XCBZ7A5FB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/838/E87/838E87707EA3031E466D3724EAFA6EB0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MAGA bomber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MAGA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pipe bombs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Barack Obama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hillary Clinton]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ George Soros]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Robert De Niro]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-slaps-airport-worker-with-iphone-over-cancelled-flight-3719855</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese man slaps airport worker with iPhone over cancelled flight 3719855]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[QINGDAO, CHINA — A Chinese man's social credit is taking a hit after his outburst on an airline employee was caught on camera.

CCTV footage uploaded on Chinese site Pear media shows the man, surnamed Wu, at the Qingdao airport. He's seen arguing with the male worker behind the counter before suddenly reaching over and slapping the poor guy in the face with his iPhone 6.

Wu had reportedly been raging over his flight being cancelled the day before due to bad weather.

The the airline had already given him free accommodation and compensation, but clearly the man was itching to take it out on someone.

The worker didn't retaliate.

Police later arrived and detained Wu for 10 days, and have reportedly put him on China's travel blacklist. 3719855]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMDWXD3SKEER7BKHLBJW7K4VGJKV5ST7AJLR5TKWABIAZC3XAIIWEBAHKV6AZAC4QB6XEWZZKFNA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F0/4D3/1F04D360363BF292CD2632181F8A9C1C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese social credit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social credit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man slaps airport worker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese traveler]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancelled flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travel blacklist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ violent outburst]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-to-hold-live-fire-drills-in-spratly-islands-next-month-3719837</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Taiwan to hold live-fire drills in Spratly Islands next month 3719837]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIWAN —  Taiwan is planning to stage a three-day live fire drill on Taiping Island in the South China Sea, reports The South China Morning Post.

Taiwan reportedly plans to hold the drills between 8 a.m. and 9 p.m. from November 21 to November 23.

The exercise would be held within 5 nautical miles of Taiping island, which is part of the highly disputed Spratly Islands in the South China Sea.

The drills will involve firing into the sea and the air with 40 millimeter grenade machine guns along with other weapons in the area surrounding Taiping Island.

Fishing vessels, aircrafts and other vessels are advised to not be in the area during those three days.

The Spratly Islands are a group of disputed islands in the South China Sea and are currently being claimed by China, the Philippines, Malaysia, Vietnam, Brunei, Indonesia as well as Taiwan. 3719837]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRCFIYIGKIDF3AATB6PFZLBCGVABRRALKICFTGIEAJIARAKTKEJAPWZALSVFVVZMQF2GTBTJAZGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/513/D7B/513D7BBA1A4F4E54B45B306DD3C83F97.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spratly Islands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ live-fire drill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiping Island]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ South China Sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ South China Sea dispute]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south china sea taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan to hold live fire drills in Spratly islands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan taiping island]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/david-schwimmer-look-alike-wanted-for-stealing-beer-3719822</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[David Schwimmer look-alike wanted for stealing beer 3719822]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY — Cops in the UK are on the hunt for a thief that's the spitting image of David Schwimmer, aka Ross from Friends.

The BBC reports that Blackpool Police were trying to identify a man suspected of stealing at a restaurant and put out a CCTV still of him clutching a crate of beer on Facebook to ask for help.

Amused netizens immediately pointed out the man's uncanny resemblance to Ross Geller, and soon turned the post into a 'Friends' fanfest.

As the Ross quotes and theories piled in, even the Scottish guys in blue chimed in with a warning to stay away from the dude, who's believed to have mastered the art of Unagi, the state of total awareness.

Blackpool Police also responded by saying they confirmed David Schwimmer was in America on the day of the theft.

Still, the actor himself took to social media on Wednesday to prove his innocence, hilariously posting a video alibi showing him with a crate of beer in New York. 3719822]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLFKDIDAADR3A3HLJLAZLUSGEEBVFIMAFKF7HRLK2IATCKUK5IRIWTUKBXAXARFPVUUIBZ3AMFB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/259/E0E/259E0EF90546788F820007A9ECE8667A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ david schwimmer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ross]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ross beer thief]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ross from friends]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ friends]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uk beer thief]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ross look alike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blackpool police]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/escalator-in-rome-metro-malfunctions--injuring-dozens-3719754</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Escalator in Rome metro malfunctions , injuring dozens 3719754]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROME — Twenty-four people were injured after an escalator in a Rome metro station suddenly malfunctioned, reports The BBC.

Video recordings from bystanders show the escalator suddenly speeding downward while the people on it crashed into the bottom.

Passengers on the parallel escalator are shown trying to pull them to safety while others are seen jumping onto the central reservation between the two escalators to escape.

Many of those injured were fans of the Russian football team CSKA Moscow and were in the city to attend the football match of their favorite team.

Witnesses present say the fans were singing and jumping on the escalator before it suddenly collapsed.

Three people suffered serious injuries with one fan's foot reportedly being partially severed, while some others were trapped between the metal plates of the escalator.

The regional ambulance service was quick to respond with the injured being sent to five different hospitals across the city.

Pictures of the aftermath show the escalator in a tangle of twisted and broken metal.

Investigations are underway to find out what caused the elevator to collapse so dramatically. 3719754]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDAMDCUKBKAZDA9BBJR79BHGWLSRRC7KWPRVGKWK2KAAWRBKBCFIVT5AWXFRARIFF3XPVZWARGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/690/BEF/690BEF10AE4767779210D0CBB93ACE00.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Rome]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Italy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ metro]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Rome metro]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ escalator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rome escalator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rome escalator accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rome escalator malfunction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rome metro escalator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rome metro accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rome metro station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ escalator collapses in rome metro]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-deploys-facial-recognition-tech-on-world-s-longest-sea-bridge-3719722</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China deploys facial recognition tech on world's longest sea bridge 3719722]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[#China #HongKong #HZMB #facialrecognition #artificialintellgence
HONG KONG/BEIJING — Facial recognition and fingerprint technology have been deployed on recently opened the Hong Kong-Zhuhai-Macau bridge. 

Some drivers on the bridge will undergo facial recognition, fingerprint analysis and temperature-taking thermal scans as Beijing tries to quicken border crossings. This will only be used at one immigration lane initially. Intellifusion, the company behind it, says it is 99.5 percent accurate.

The bridge is the longest of its kind in the world, measuring 39 kilometers. It includes the bridge itself, an underwater tunnel and two artificial islands. 

According to the South China Morning Post, the technology will match the driver and car with pre-registered immigration data. Once cleared, the driver can move on.

Citing Chinese media, Reuters reports facial recognition technology will also be used to warn yawning drivers for safety. If they are found yawning three times an alarm will go off.

The South China Morning Post reports that cross-border bus and truck drivers will soon be subject to the checks as their information is already held by Chinese authorities. 3719722]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNNFXDAJBRERZAKELWPA7L4RMSKBRR34KNPFXGCRAZCFZWAEAEKAAYKYAFVFZARFQW6GCCA7KIHA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E54/3B2/E543B2DFA55DA3569CF4EA0C6198FA33.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>171</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hongkong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial recognition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial intelligence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hong kong zhuhai bridge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hong kong bridge to china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hong kong sea bridge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shocking facts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facts about china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ documentary]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china documentary]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese communist party]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china police state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beijing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xi jinping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 1984]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surveillance state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social credit system china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police state]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/one-year-anniversary-of-murder-of-journalist-daphne-caruana-galizia-3719676</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[One year anniversary of murder of journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia 3719676]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MALTA — It has been just a little over one year since the assassination of journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia.

Galizia kept a day job as a the editor of Taste & Flair magazine in Malta, but she was also known as one of the most famous investigative journalists in the country who exposed alleged money laundering by officials, government corruption, and other crimes.

She wrote about her investigations and political opinions on her blog, Running Commentary, which was established in 2008.

Her blog often attracted higher viewership than all of Malta's national press combined, according to the Guardian.

She was appreciated by her readers for being outspoken. However, there were also many critics of her work, and she acquired enemies in Malta as a result of being vocal about her opinions.

Among her work, Galizia's used the Panama Papers to publish sensitive information about Maltese politicians.

The Panama Papers were over 11 million documents leaked in 2015 that exposed the identities of prominent entities across the globe who held offshore bank accounts.

Before her murder, Galizia reportedly received death threats in the form of phone calls, letters, and notes on a daily basis.

The front door to Galizia's home was reportedly set on fire in 1996, and pet dogs she had kept throughout the years were also poisoned and murdered.

On October 17, 2017, Galizia was reportedly driving her Peugeot 108 to a meeting with a bank official. Her son heard her drive away before hearing an explosion.

He said he immediately ran out and was met by the smell of burning fuel. He saw his mother's car ablaze, then saw pieces of her body scattered on the ground. 

A witness present at the time of the explosion said the car had been flung over a small wall into a field, and its gasoline tank ignited, reported Reuters.

Police say they discovered a sim card active in the area that may have been used to send a text message to trigger the bomb, which was reportedly placed under Galizia's seat.

Three men have been charged with Galizia's murder. However, Galizia's family believes the men may have been acting upon orders from others.

The accused men were allegedly tipped off before their arrest and threw their phones into the water before the police came to arrest them, according to detectives involved in the case.

The Maltese government has offered one million euros reward for anyone who has information on the case. However, Galizia's family has dismissed it as a publicity stunt.

Her family believes Galizia was murdered as a way to silence her and to stop her from exposing more sensitive information about high-ranking officials in the country. 3719676]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJRMX3SAWKFXBATLZDWT7UXM5CE5EC7LSIFXU3SBZCW7BZFKSCWCYKRKR6FAAAJF64XIBAZBZFA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7AA/F30/7AAF30F9EE179464F4C2844B3DA3DA11.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>152</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ daphne caruana galizia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ investigative journalist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panama papers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ daphne caruana galizia death]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ daphne caruana galizia bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ daphne caruana galizia murder]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-confirms-withdrawal-from-inf-treaty-with-russia-3719658</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. confirms withdrawal from INF Treaty with Russia 3719658]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOSCOW — The U.S. national security adviser, John Bolton, has confirmed the U.S. will withdraw from the intermediate-range nuclear forces treaty, or INF Treaty, after meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin in Moscow on Tuesday. 

According to NPR, Bolton cited Russian violations as the reason to terminate the 1987 INF Treaty signed by President Ronald Reagan and Soviet leader Mikhail Gorbachev. 
According to CBS News, the U.S. claims Russia's 9M729 missile system violates the INF treaty. The system can operate at lower altitudes and reach targets across Europe and the U.S. west coast if launched from Siberia. 
The original treaty prohibited the U.S. and Russia from fielding ground-launched cruise missiles with ranges between 500 and 5,500 kilometers, their launchers and associated support structures. 
According to Bolton, it is necessary for the U.S. to withdraw in order to adapt to a post-Cold War environment with several competing global powers. He cited efforts to develop weapons by China, Iran and other countries not bound by the INF Treaty. 
Bolton also said the U.S. has not yet taken any formal steps, but that America would exit the treaty in due course. 3719658]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JAAYKVASJF3AKEBADWXKLYMADB5UT2AVDWPHAEKICRRBZMLJAFKBCVK2VF3WZMPSZUEACIKVEA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/91E/22A/91E22A402A30AE691E5FFAAC469275C2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US withdrawal INF Treaty]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US confirms withdrawal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russia INF Treaty violations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russia violations]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/da-vinci-may-have-had-eye-disorder-that-helped-him-paint-3719650</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Da Vinci may have had eye disorder that helped him paint 3719650]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A new study suggests Leonardo da Vinci may have had an eye disorder that helped him paint. 

According to Science News, visual neuroscientist Christopher Tyler of the City University of London looked at six pieces of art thought to be modeled after da Vinci, and published the results on October 18 in Jama Ophthalmology.  
According to the Washington Post, Tyler looked at two sculptures, two oil paintings and two drawings and conducted mathematical analyses to conclude that da Vinci had an exotropic tendency of approximately -10.3 degrees when relaxed.
Five of the works show an eye misalignment consistent with the eye disorder exotropia that can affect three-dimensional vision. This led Tyler to believe that da Vinci may have had intermittent exotropia. 
Exotropia is a type of strabismus where one eye turns slightly outward and can be treated with special glasses, eye patches or surgery.   
If da Vinci was able to control his exotropia, Tyler believes it may have given the painter an artistic advantage by allowing him to switch back and forth from seeing in three dimensions and two dimensions. 3719650]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNRMDIABWKA3BRTBMARXL4TGMBVZRZKKBPWVFABAABR3WZCKMLWKVIGLV7WXBZJQMRXEWCJAZAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F06/62E/F0662EB77CBC7AF0371F1DC0657412D0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  Da Vinci eye disorder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Da Vinci exotropia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Da Vinci strabismus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exotropia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strabismus]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-and-russia-spies-have-to-listen-to-trump-s-iphone-calls-3721429</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China and Russia spies have to listen to Trump's iPhone calls 3721429]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA —  It appears that President Donald Trump continues to use unsecured iPhones to talk to his pals instead of using a secure White House line, according to the New York Times. 
Apparently, Trump has a penchant for using three different iPhones. Two of them have been altered by the NSA to be a bit more secure, while the third is a personal phone. 
As none of the three phones are totally secure, Chinese and Russian spies have allegedly been listening in, according to anonymous current and former officials. 
It looks as if the Chinese believe that by gathering a list of Trump's personal friends, they'll somehow be able to influence the reality president's stance on things like the on going trade war. Good luck with that. 
Of course, the Russians didn't want to let the Chinese have all the fun, so they do have been dropping in for a listen. 
Fortunately for the U.S., most of Trump's conversations are relatively surfacy and his lack of interest in classified briefings probably means no secrets are getting spilled.  
Naturally, Trump fired back at the New York Times over Twitter, calling the report fake and saying he preferred using government authorized hard lines. 3721429]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LWCCAFAEDRPD3FBRAA76DXGWJBVST4AZDWPURDKMBATBKUBZQAEBAGLWYFAW34F64GMAI9AZEA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FDE/2F2/FDE2F2E936E432BCDD0D6592EA1C2326.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ President Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump iPhone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump iPhones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump unsecured iPhones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China eavesdropping Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russia eavesdropping Trump]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/pittsburgh-synagogue-shooting-leaves-11-dead-6-injured-3721420</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Pittsburgh synagogue shooting leaves 11 dead, 6 injured 3721420]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PITTSBURGH — A man armed with an AR-15 rifle and at least three handguns, shouting anti-Semitic slurs, opened fire inside a Pittsburgh synagogue Saturday morning killing 11 people and wounding six others, including four police officers during a firefight. 
Suspect Robert Bowers allegedly entered an unlocked door at Tree of Life synagogue at around 9:45 a.m., armed with a Colt AR-15 rifle and three Glock .357 handguns, the Washington Post reports.

According to authorities, Bowers roamed the building and fired indiscriminately at groups of worshippers he came across for several minutes.

As he was leaving the synagogue, Bowers was met by two officers dressed in tactical gear and exchanged fire with them. Bowers shot one of the officers in the hand, while the other was injured by shrapnel.
Bowers retreated back inside and barricaded himself inside a room on the third floor. 

Bowers then shot two more officers during a brief standoff with a SWAT team. He was allegedly yelling anti-Semitic remarks throughout. 
The suspect was shot several times before he surrendered to police. 
He has been charged with 29 federal counts plus 36 state counts in connection with Saturday's shooting. 

Bowers reportedly had a social media account on Gab.com where he made anti-Semitic and anti-refugee posts prior to the shooting. 3721420]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KRAYCVANLFGBRSBBIAZ9U3NACV5U3SKSLFMGACA5BRMVRBAIQFEVKVA2VR7BRFQF2XIAZ5A6NA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE3/DD4/EE3DD4421C2BDD17EF4B04713000B49F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pittsburgh shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pittsburgh synagogue shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Robert Bowers shooter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shooter Robert Bowers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/why-baby-bumps-seem-bigger-at-night-than-during-the-day-3721159</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Why baby bumps seem bigger at night than during the day 3721159]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SUVA, FIJI — With a royal baby on the way, everyone's eyes are on Meghan Markle's bump.

Eagle-eyed fans noticed, though, that the Duchess of Sussex's pregnant belly seemed much more pronounced during a dinner in Fiji than just days before in Australia, reports MSN.

It could be the clothes, but is much more likely to be due to the freaky yet very real phenomenon of pregnancy bumps appearing larger at night.

Birth doula Susannah Birch told Trimester Talk that abdominal muscles holding the baby bump become tired as the day goes on, causing them to loosen up. This allows the bump to expand and sit out further, thus appearing bigger.

The muscles recuperate during sleep, and become refreshed and better able to maintain the bump's position in the morning.

Levels of the hormone relaxin, which causes abdominal muscle stretching during pregnancy, was also found to be highest at night, according to a study published in the Handbook of Biologically Active Peptides.

Women's Health reports that pregnant bellies have also been known to 'pop' seemingly overnight, which is caused by the uterus expanding due to the growing fetus, and rising above the pubic bone. For most women, this tends to happen at around 10 to 12 weeks.

Bottom line, Markle's changing baby bump is totally normal and is just like any other pregnant lady's- not that that's going to stop anyone from continuing to observe it in minute detail. 3721159]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIAICZJA2JAIVIUL2KWTK4YGMCEXSC4LVCFMURCKFLARBCVBJDRPVADKM6R7VT5FZRXIVZWKIAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C30/71B/C3071BD1F28CFA4590AE8ADD63452003.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby bump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Meghan Markle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ royal baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ royal pregnancy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ royal baby bump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnancy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant belly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby belly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Prince Harry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby bump bigger at night]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby bump size]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-military-to-send-5-200-troops-to-beef-up-border-security-3722029</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. military to send 5,200 troops to beef up border security 3722029]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  — With the midterm elections fast approaching, Trump has begun militarizing the southern border to block caravan of approaching migrants.

Reuters reports that the U.S. Military is deploying 5,200 active duty troops to the Mexican border in response to a massive migrant caravan pushing north from Central America.

According to the head of the U.S. northern command, the first wave of the operation has reportedly begun, with 800 soldiers from Fort Knox and Fort Campbell in Kentucky already on their way to Texas.

Operation Faithful Patriot will also send medical units, C-130 and C-17 transport aircrafts, and helicopter units equipped with night vision to allow border agents to spot illegal crossers.

Twenty-two miles of barbed wire have already been sent to fortify the southern border, with more available to string an additional 150 miles, according to the Washington Post.

U.S. Customs and Border Protection is tracking the caravan of 3,500 migrants, and say they are currently moving through southern Mexico. A second group of 3,000 that recently forced their way through the Mexico-Guatemala border is lagging behind.

The nearest border entry at McAllen, Texas is still over 900 miles away, so the carvan's arrival isn't imminent. Still, that hasn't stopped Trump from using what he calls their invasion to drive his conservative base to the polls for the midterms. 3722029]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AACAPACTKBIARCZSBAARR9USG2IB5SIKLRDFTGAKB5BRMWABLAKFGVKXKSWWVWRJQ63DGWKPB5HB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/399/BBA/399BBAA2B3902848F97E236FCFBF59D6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ migrant caravan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ migrants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immigrants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ illegal migrants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Donald Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US border]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border patrol]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ night vision]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ helicopter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CBP]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ customs and border patrol]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ midterm elections]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tropical-trump-elected-as-brazil-s-next-president-3722008</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tropical Trump elected as Brazil's next president 3722008]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRAZIL — Far-right lawmaker Jair Bolsonaro won Brazil's presidential election on Sunday, promising to clean up corruption, shrink the state and crack down on crime. 

According to the Guardian, the 63-year-old Bolsonaro secured 55.1 percent of the votes after 99.9 percent were counted, defeating leftist candidate Fernando Haddad, who secured 44.8 percent of votes. 
According to Reuters, the former army captain, with close ties to the military, has alarmed skeptics with comments seen as denigrating women, gays and racial minorities. 
Some in Brazil are also concerned Bolsonaro, an admirer of Brazil's 1964-1985 military dictatorship and a proponent of using torture on leftist opponents, will curtail human rights, infringe upon civil liberties and clamp down on freedom of speech. 
In his acceptance speech, Bolsonaro promised to lead the country according to the Bible and the country's constitution. 3722008]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACAICZCKBJRGCR9BNKF56DVGJIE5ET4AEARVHIEKEAFAWAIBZLRAYCYLSXWZWC4QMRUIBI5KVEB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/383/D4F/383D4F5F65F9A9AC4990B79667201FC2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Brazil elections]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Brazil Jair Bolsonaro]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Brazil President Bolsonaro]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Brazil presidential elections]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jair Bolsonaro]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/titanic-ii-to-sail-from-dubai-in-2022-3721845</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Titanic II to sail from Dubai in 2022 3721845]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — A replica of the Titanic is being built in China and is set to sail by 2022.

The Titanic II will have 835 cabins and will be able to accomodate 2,435 passengers along with 900 crew members, according to CNN.

To make things safer this time, more lifeboats are being added onto the $500 million ship along with a welded hull.

The ship will take passengers from Dubai to New York, with passengers being able to purchase first, second, and third-class tickets, similar to the original Titanic.

Titanic II was originally expected to sail in 2016, however the development of the ship was stopped in 2015 following Clive Palmer's financial dispute with the Chinese government.

Palmer was the Australian billionaire who came up with the idea of building a replica of the ship. 3721845]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KADFGAACKICARXCHL6IAI9DSGEDVXUT6KBIFMHALB6LAMXRHAEKFMYKUKBWFXWAFF63DEVZZKJNA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/317/867/317867FAC05D3DEB8445A7A603D3A86F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Titanic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Titanic II]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Titanic 2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Dubai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china titanic replica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china titanic 2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china titanic 2 update]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china titanic ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new titanic ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new titanic ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ replica of the titanic]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-plastic-particles-present-in-poop-3721831</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds plastic particles present in poop 3721831]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Plastic has been found in participants' bodies after they consumed food and beverages stored in plastic wrapping, bottles and containers, according to a study presented at the United European Gastroenterology.

Scientists conducted stool testings and found up to nine different particles of plastic present in the stool samples.

The most common plastic particles found were polypropylene and polyethylene terephthalate.

Marine biologists have also found plastic particles present in the bodies of animals in the ocean, according to an article published in the journal Science.

Six of the eight participants had eaten fish from the sea and may have received the plastic from the fish they ate.

The study only included a small number of people and would need further studies to confirm the results. 3721831]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DWKACWKMBARYZTKBKRX7U4M5CE7UT4KFIATGRHAIDACDALASCRKWTVA57FXVT9QMRGPWA9AIGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/167/6C5/1676C5D7DD06F43B4319ECDE3776AED8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study finds humans are pooping out plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pooping plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic particles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polypropylene]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polyethylene terephthalate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic in humans]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-northwest-passage-could-be-the-newest-shipping-route-3721718</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The Northwest Passage could be the newest shipping route 3721718]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE ARCTIC — As climate change continues to impact the Arctic, countries are planning to use the Northwest Passage as a shortcut shipping route, reports online magazine Grist.

Currently, the Suez Canal and Panama Canal are used as major shipping routes in the world.

However in the future, ships traveling from Japan to western Europe could be able to travel north through the Bering Strait to Europe. 

This would slash the travel route from 13,000 miles to about 7000 miles and could potentially cut shipping prices in half.

Ships traveling from Yokohama Port could also make the journey through the Northwest Passage to New York City in about 21 days instead of the standard 25 days, traveling 7,480 nautical miles instead of 9,720 nautical miles through the Panama Canal.

As the ships travel through the Arctic, some are worried that fossil fuels used by the vessels may harm the already fragile Arctic ecosystem.

Scientists estimate that by 2050 there will be no more ice in the Arctic. 3721718]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NRCCAFB6LAADZ9BSLRKLU3GEAVRFC2LRDA5TIDBZFWKBIFAFBAGWRGAZ7R7BT9FZRDEBRWK2NB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AB2/194/AB2194AD444F2F78EC42CC7FEB77C383.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-10-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Arctic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Northwest Passage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic ice melting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic ice melting news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ northwest passage business]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic sea route]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ northern sea route]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ northern sea route opens for business]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ northwest passage explainer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic could transform into a maritime highway]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
