<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/united-airlines-launches-longest-nonstop-flight-from-u-s--3473726</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[United Airlines launches longest nonstop flight from U.S. 3473726]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — United Airlines has launched the longest nonstop flight from the U.S. from its Los Angeles hub to Singapore. 

The 14,000-km trip takes 17 hours, 55 minutes to Singapore and 15 hours, 15 minutes coming back, according to Forbes. 

The flight will operate once a day on a Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner with 252 seats combined in Economy, Economy Plus and Business. 

The world's two longest routes belong to Qatar Airways' Doha-Auckland route at 14,536 km and Emirates' Dubai-Auckland route at 14,193 km. 

In terms of scheduled flying time though, the new United route will be the longest, due to the strong headwinds on the westbound portion of the flight, USA Today reported. 3473726]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIWCC3TAZDAIA3DBVDAR6LTMMAB5RIKA2KAVURCASJAPV3UKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BC3/ADF/BC3ADF4ABFE9ED19C08E56F3AD162DF4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-10-31T09:45:42+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United Airlines longest nonstop flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ long haul flights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Boeing 787-9 Dreamliner]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/deer-with-plastic-pumpkin-stuck-on-head-gets-rescued-by-neighbors-3473646</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Deer with plastic pumpkin stuck on head gets rescued by neighbors 3473646]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANDERSON TOWNSHIP, OHIO — A group of Ohio residents banded together over the weekend to save a poor deer from its plastic prison.

Little Bambi may have gotten a bit too excited for Halloween candy, and ended up getting its head stuck in a pumpkin-shaped trick-or-treat bucket.

WCPO reports that the pumpkin-headed animal spent the next four days wandering all over the neighborhood, prompting concerned residents to call in and report the sightings.

Despite the potential dangers of a rescue operation, one group was determined to help Bambi.

After following the deer for hours, they managed to surround and snare it with catch poles. The pumpkin bucket's black strap had been lodged in the back of its head, and was quickly removed. As soon as it was free, the deer ran 30 feet to the nearest creek to drink and graze. 

A fundraiser is now being held for Second Chance Wildlife Rescue, a nonprofit group that helped with the search. And of course, donations are being collected in the plastic pumpkin bucket. 3473646]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJAIYZAAWJWABR9BVDR77JHGVCSZERNKNLA5UZEASJAEAIAAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6C9/C5C/6C9C5C6C0E2AD5A81F0321D2E5D99DEB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-10-31T08:19:59+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deer rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halloween candy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trick or treat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pumpkin bucket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pumpkin]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-super-sonic-car-may-one-day-travel-over-1-000-miles-per-hour-3473619</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Super sonic car' may one day travel over 1,000 miles per hour 3473619]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEWQUAY AIRPORT, BRITAIN — The Bloodhound Super Sonic Car performed its very first public run last week, clocking in a speed of 210 miles per hour, reported the BBC.

When complete, the car will be fitted with two engines. One of which is a jet engine that is also on the Eurofighter aircraft.  This can clock in speeds of 650 miles per hour.

The second is e a rocket engine. This is expected to help it travel at over 1,000 miles per hour.

The car is also comprised of over 3,500 parts, many of which are tailor-made. 3473619]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKFGXRDAMCFKVI9LRDAXLUUMEAB5RCSA2KWMUCYA6JFKBAALF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/44E/E61/44EE61E501362B7CE9D45CE5EFBB1809.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-10-31T07:40:28+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ worlds fastest car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bloodhound ssc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bloodhound super sonic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ driving at 1000 mph]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 1000 mile per hour car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fastest car ever made]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/walmart-uses-shelf-scanning-robots-to-avoid-out-of-stock-issues-3473465</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Walmart uses shelf-scanning robots to avoid out-of-stock issues 3473465]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BENTONVILLE, ARKANSAS — Walmart is enlisting automated help to improve out-of-stock issues and mislabeled items.

Reuters reports that the robots are equipped with a camera and lights tha scan the aisles to check stocks, and identify mislabeled or wrongly-priced items.

The robot passes the data to human employees, who then restock the shelves and fix any errors.

The retail giant stresses that the machines will not replace staffers, and are merely there to help them.

The robots are 50 percent more productive than human employees at shelf-scanning, and are capable of doing it faster and more accurately.

Walmart has been trialing robots in California, Pennsylvania, and Arkansas for the past three years, and will be expanding to 50 more locations in January 2018.

So if you live in El Paso, Fort Worth, or Jacksonville, it seems the robots are coming. 3473465]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKRCXCTAJLFPVI7LWPAZL4TMAABVFK2AEDAVTCWKZCRMB3WAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/584/77D/58477D5971F52C6EDA70456A94057798.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-10-31T04:30:09+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walmart robots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walmart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot scanner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shelf scanner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ empty shelves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ out of stock]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/robots-will-soon-be-able-to-have-your-babies-3473428</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Robots will soon be able to have your babies 3473428]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MELILLA, SPAIN — Want to be a father with none of the real responsibility? Maybe a Samantha bot is what you need. 

Catalan engineer Sergi Santos really likes robots. We mean REALLY likes, which is probably why he created Samantha.

Santos says his robot will soon be able to have a conversation with him and judge his character, unfortunately, saying no still won't work for her — so, kind of like Hollywood. 

The creepy creator says you can even make a child with your Samantha bot. Santos says all it takes is an algorithm, a 3D printer and voila!!

A bot for sexy-times that you can create a fake child with? What more could you ask for? A lot actually. 

Maybe Santos is on to something? Besides his robot that is. 3473428]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSKAPXZGANIFIWTCLMAA3L2GGMEB5RT9AJPRXFIFAJIREATXLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/81D/B63/81DB63E4D663D4AE062DF020CFDC5768.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-10-31T03:38:08+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot companions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot mother]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ samantha robot mother]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D printing]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/stranded-sailors-survival-tale-sounds-fishy-3474451</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Stranded sailors' survival tale sounds fishy 3474451]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OKINAWA, JAPAN — Last week, everyone collectively awww-ed as two women and their dogs were rescued after being stranded at sea for months. But now, eyebrows are being raised because details of the sailors' story just don't add up.

CNN reports that a night after setting off from Hawaii on May 3, Jennifer Appel and Tasha Fuiava encountered a ferocious storm that supposedly broke part their boat's mast and sail, even though no storm systems were spotted in the area that day, or in the days after.

At the end of the first month, another supposed storm killed their engine and left them drifting. They had six forms of communication devices, but all were dead.

The pair apparently had an Emergency Position Indicating Radio Beacon on board, which when activated tells the Coast Guard you need rescuing. And the device was working properly, but for some reason the women didn't think the situation was distressing enough to warrant turning it on.

For people who didn't need saving, they sure were diligent in sending up flares every time they passed a ship or island.

It's both odd and a bit dumb that the two went on a long sea journey just after a week of knowing each other, and with one of them having no sailing experience whatsoever.

Many netizens are now speculating these two might just be in it for publicity, maybe a book and movie deal. Then again, they might just be two inexperienced and overly ambitious sailors who made some very stupid decisions.

In any case, the Coast Guard in Hawaii is looking into it, so we'll hopefully have the 'real' story soon. 3474451]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LRIDZFASJAAARSKBJR77DXMEBS7FANKWKWMHTYA5DA3VINAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/676/A9F/676A9F13E508A7B4898B040F057DBEBC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>87</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lost at sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stranded at sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea journey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stranded sailors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hawaii to Tahiti]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ storm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EPIRB]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ distress signal]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-largest-aircraft-set-to-offer-luxury-tourist-trips-3474256</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's largest aircraft set to offer luxury tourist trips 3474256]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CARDINGTON, U.K. — The world's largest aircraft — the Airlander 10 — is set to be tested by travel company Henry Cookson Adventures to take tourists on exotic trips around the world. 

British aerospace company Hybrid Air Vehicles (HAV) is the maker of the Airlander 10.
 
It announced that Henry Cookson Adventures (HCA) will become the first private company to trial the Airlander 10 next year, News Atlas reported. 
The aircraft is powered by four 325-hp turbocharged diesel engines and uses aerodynamic lift like a fixed-wing aircraft to take off. Helium keeps the Airlander in the air. 

The airship can carry payloads of up to 10,000 kg and stay in the air for five days at a time with a crew. It also doesn't require a runway.

The passenger version of the Airlander 10 is expected to be able to cruise at 80 knots at an altitude of up to 20,000 feet. 

The Airlander 10 is currently still in its test-flight phase and looking to gain airworthiness certification. 3474256]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2JRGCZEABKRIV3ELJLRTL2CNAEEZSC4LWKW7GTTASKAPAAAKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ADB/636/ADB6365EA7FD758A625F592EF31E6E78.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airships]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's largest aircraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hybrid Air Vehicles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Airlander 10]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/playerunknown-s-battlegrounds-may-get-banned-in-china-3474208</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds may get banned in China 3474208]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — PlayerUnknown's Battlegrounds may be a smash hit everywhere in the world, but leave it to China to take aim at the survival video game's violent content.

CNN reports that gameplay in Battlegrounds is in the style of Hunger Games or Battle Royale. It starts with players parachuting into a desert island, scavenging for all sorts of weapons, and then fighting each other to the death. Last man standing wins!

Despite not yet officially launching in China, the game already has a sizeable chunk of Chinese players.

But with regulators complaining of too much blood and gore, it looks like Battlegrounds won't be getting a license anytime soon.

If it does, expect it to be heavily cut and censored to fit 'socialist core values and traditional Chinese culture.' Hmm, fun.

The Chinese copyright association may not be a fan of violently competitive games, but better violent in a game than in real life, which might be the case if the players get fed up with their policing. 3474208]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNRPXTUBBIWKDRWKFPAK7LUGSKSXFIKKRBWXHICKVDWEAZILG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5BE/43E/5BE43E8CF6FBD8A52984FEC321ADD22A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battlegrounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playerunknown battlegrounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playerunknown]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ survival video game]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ survival game]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hunger games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battle royale]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ death match]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ survival genre]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china censorship]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/terrorist-truck-attack-leaves-8-dead-11-injured-in-new-york-city-3474203</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Terrorist truck attack leaves 8 dead, 11 injured in New York City 3474203]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — Eight people were killed and 11 others seriously injured Tuesday, when a man deliberately drove a rented truck onto a bike path near World Trade Center in lower Manhattan before crashing into a school bus.

The suspect then jumped out of the truck and shouted Allahu Akbar before firing a BB or pellet gun, authorities said, according to NBC News. 

A police officer on patrol in the area returned fire, hitting the suspect in the abdomen. 

The suspect was taken into custody and transported to the hospital for treatment, according to CNN. 

The attacker was identified as 29-year-old Uzbek immigrant Sayfullo Habibullaevic Saipov. Officials say he entered the country in 2010. 

The attack began at 3:05 p.m. when Saipov drove a Home Depot rental truck onto a bike path on West Street near Houston Street.

He exited the bike path when he collided with a school bus at Chambers Street, said Police Commissioner James O'Neill, according to NBC News. 

There were two adults and two children on the bus, O'Neill said. 3474203]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNWCYKUBADWEWCELAAW76DRGFJSRURMKSIRZUCSKECAICRCAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/583/C74/583C746031A6CBB320EF02C56C02E04E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York City]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York truck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York truck incident]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-first-trackless-smart-train-begins-test-run-in-china-3474174</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's first trackless 'smart train' begins test run in China 3474174]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ZHUZHOU, CHINA— A city in China has launched a test run for a futuristic urban transport system that's being called the world's first 'smart train'.

Described as a cross between a train, tram, and bus, the Autonomous Rail Rapid Transit is a 32-meter electric vehicle that runs at a maximum speed of 70 kilometers per hour, according to Xinhua News.

The ART is equipped with sensors to help it read road dimensions as it travels along a virtual track made up of dotted white lines painted on the road.

The smart train has three carriages, and is capable of carrying up to 300 passengers.

The self-driving system uses rubber tires instead of steel wheels, and can travel up to 25 kilometers after a 10-minute charge.

At the moment, the train traverses a 3.1-kilometer route, traveling through four stations in the city of Zhuzhou, in the country's Hunan province.

A longer route is being planned, with the transport system aiming to eventually expand to other cities. 3474174]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5CFCXRFK5DWKVZ7BWPF7LDXM2JETSK5AFPATFIEAIDWMA3VBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CCD/248/CCD24870118BD7AF37197849525B55FB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smart train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ART]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ autonomous rail rapid transit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ public transportation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china transportation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sony-s-aibo-robot-dog-comes-back-cuter-smarter-more-lifelike-3475304</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sony's Aibo robot dog comes back cuter, smarter, more lifelike 3475304]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Sony's Aibo robot dog is back after playing dead for a decade, and not is it adorable, it's also a heck of a lot smarter.

According to Sony, the mechanical pup is equipped with ultra-compact actuators that allow it to do a plethora of lifelike dog movements, and OLED puppy eyes to show a range of expression.

Aibo can form emotional bonds too, or so Sony claims. The robo dog will actively seek out its owners and learn what makes them happy.

Its behavior also changes over time as it adapts to its environment, eventually forming its own unique personality — all thanks to AI.

But as with any purebred Japanese dog, Aibos are expensive. A unit costs over 1700 U.S. dollars, and that's not including the mandatory monthly plan.

You may not be spending on kibble, but your robo pub needs its daily dose of data. The basic plan provides LTE and Sony cloud access for less than 30 dollars, though you're locked in for three years. Definitely a pricey pup.

Anyone who's willing to blow money on a mechanical canine companion can pre-order ahead of the January 11 release date, but know that it's only available in Japan. 3475304]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKRAXZIA2LWAVR9L2LRVKLRMJKB7RK7LWJWPTCYAECAKVCWAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6BA/0AB/6BA0ABC1BD06B40E3A715256031C0A40.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aibo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sony aibo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robo dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot pup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mechanical dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sony]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fisherman-finds-jackfish-nearly-split-in-two-by-powerade-wrapper-3475229</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fisherman finds jackfish nearly split in two by Powerade wrapper 3475229]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALBERTA, CANADA — Canadian fisherman Adam Turnbull caught this fish last week and was shocked to see it was nearly split in two by litter.

Turnbull reckons that trash thrown near the river probably got in the water.That wrapper somehow wound up around the fish.

Despite its injury Turnbull says its still put up a fight when he caught it. Shocked by the Northern Pike's injury, he posted images of it to Facebook last week in a post that has gone viral.

Turnbull says he cut the wrapper and put the fish back in the water. He says it swam away like a dart. 3475229]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAFEDTSKMCRKATFKFKRTKBBGIEE7SK4LRAWTGZBAVARMVKSLH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3E0/EA9/3E0EA98545635EE5706A2819B2B24BCD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish caught in wrapper]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ littering near river]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ northern pike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jackfish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trash in the water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trash]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/strangers-who-met-on-delta-flight-cited-for-in-flight-friskiness-3475045</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Strangers who met on Delta flight cited for in-flight friskiness 3475045]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT — Talk about the friendly skies. Two strangers who met on a Delta flight were cited for inter-passenger turbulence. 

The flight was heading from the City of Angels to Motown, and the two passengers — a 28-year-old male and a 48-year-old woman — were connecting on separate flights. 

Apparently, the two decided to connect with each other before reaching Detroit.  

Looks like the woman was in the middle of putting the man's tray table in the upright position while the two were in their seats.

For some reason, the other passengers around them weren't so keen on the idea. 

Both people were issued citations and the investigation was handed over to the FBI. 

The two new besties are not expected to be criminally charged, but will most likely just have to pay up to $800 in fines. 

Lucky for these two, they could have been some strangers in danger on United. 3475045]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJNRGAIIBBKAVCZVL6KFZ9L4GWJE7E37A2LWZG3SAZARGVIDKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/310/E97/310E97E47B4E2BFA4B741C5112A88252.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Delta Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Delta passengers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Delta passengers Detroit airport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Delta flight]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/giant-hog-caught-swaggering-through-neighborhood-3475036</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Giant hog caught swaggering through neighborhood 3475036]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PHENIX CITY, ALABAMA — A giant hog was spotted strolling around Phenix last week.

Angela Rena found the big guy (it's pretty obvious he is a dude) while driving last week, took some video and posted it to Facebook.  It's unknown if the pig was feral.

Feral hogs are considered an invasive species and are reproducing across most of the U.S. 3475036]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLAGY3SAWKFIAIYBNPAT92AM5BVXRRNLWKA5TCWAJJFABIEAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/075/8A2/0758A29E99C8F202F236A0971918AFA2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pig caught on tape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pig on tape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pig filmed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ feral pig]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pig in neighborhood]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ invasive pig species]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-york-truck-attack-suspect-charged-with-terrorism-offenses-3475010</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New York truck attack suspect charged with terrorism offenses 3475010]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — The suspect in Tuesday's truck attack, which left eight people dead in lower Manhattan, has been charged with federal terrorism offenses.  

Sayfullo Habibullaevic Saipov, a 29-year-old Uzbekistan native, is charged with providing material support to ISIS and violence and destruction of motor vehicles, acting US Attorney for the Southern District of New York said, according to CNN.

Saipov told authorities he was inspired by ISIS videos, a federal criminal complaint stated. 

Officials said he began planning the attack a year ago and decided to use a truck two months ago. 

Law enforcement discovered around 90 ISIS propaganda videos, as well as 4,000 images, many of which were ISIS-related on Saipov's cellphone, according to the FBI.  
 
Saipov came into the U.S. from Uzbekistan in 2010 on a diversity immigrant visa, according to the Department of Homeland Security. 
He was living in Paterson, New Jersey with his wife and three children. 

A little over six months ago, he became an Uber driver, passing their background check. 3475010]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSKFVDRGA5GRKWZSBRBAVLU3MECS3UT9ABKRXHCRAFJACWIEKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DED/152/DED1527D061C5D08C9749165CAE62FAE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rental trucks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Uber driver]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/alzheimer-s-may-originate-outside-the-brain-says-new-study-3475002</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Alzheimer's may originate outside the brain, says new study 3475002]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER, CANADA — Scientists have long assumed that Alzheimer's starts in the brain, but new research suggests that might not be the case.

According to AAAS, patients with Alzheimer's disease have abnormal deposits of amyloid beta protein in their brain, which smothers the cells and impairs nerve and memory function.

Amyloid beta protein can be found in other organs apart from the brain, though because of the blood-brain barrier, the amyloid responsible for Alzheimer's was generally believed to only originate in the brain.

To see if this theory was true, researchers at the University of British Columbia used parabiosis to attach a normal mouse to one with high amyloid beta levels. They found that the protein was able to travel to the normal mouse's brain, accumulating and beginning to cause damage. In just 12 months, the normal mouse had effectively 'contracted' Alzheimer's.

Scientists suggest that as the blood-brain barrier weakens with age, more amyloid-beta may infiltrate the brain, and contribute to its deterioration.

The findings indicate that future drugs might be able to halt the disease by targeting the toxic protein before it ever reaches the brain. 3475002]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLWEDAIARCRPWKAL2LF5LSCGJLSRFANA6KAXGCSBSIR3WAJKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C12/42D/C1242DD4344C3184E0667F8F5F992FA5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dementia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's cure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amyloid protein]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amyloid beta]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amyloid beta protein]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain plaque]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ parabiosis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood brain barrier]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/giant-void-detected-inside-great-pyramid-in-giza-3475945</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Giant void detected inside Great Pyramid in Giza 3475945]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GIZA, EGYPT — Archaeologists have identified an empty cavity in Egypt's Great Pyramid, marking the first discovery of a new internal structure in over two hundred years.

BBC reports that a nearly 100-foot long void was discovered inside the Great Pyramid in Giza, just above the 153-foot long Grand Gallery.

The void was detected using cosmic ray muons, which are high-energy particles that shower the Earth. Muons pass through empty spaces easily, but can be absorbed or deflected by dense materials like solid rock.

Three different muography technologies used to measure muons in the pyramid all detected the same void in the same position.

But because the technique is low resolution, it's difficult to determine the exact shape or function of the void.

Researchers speculate that the void could be one large empty space, or several small ones, possibility used to relieve pressure on the chambers below.

The void will need to be investigated further if we want to know what it actually is. Scientists are already considering drilling a small hole and sending in a tiny robot to hopefully get some answers. 3475945]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLAGAIIBWKRRWIRBSPAZ7UXGRCSRR35KJJWZT3XAMCAAXRHKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0CA/EC0/0CAEC0AF3063D5AEA772C9EDC7F600C1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pyramid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ great pyramid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giza]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ void]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big void]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmic ray muons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ muons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ khufu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pharaoh khufu]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/court-thinks-give-me-a-lawyer-dog-refers-to-an-actual-lawyer-dog-3475814</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Court thinks 'give me a lawyer dog' refers to an actual lawyer dog 3475814]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS, LOUISIANA — When DMX said Where my dogs at? he wasn't referring to his actual dogs. That's not how the morons at the Louisiana Supreme Court would see it. 

A suspect in an interrogation told detectives to just give me a lawyer dog. Anyone with half a brain understands that his means give me a lawyer, not a dog that's a lawyer.

But that's exactly how the Louisiana Supreme Court ruled. They said the suspect was in fact asking for a lawyer dog, and not invoking his right to counsel. 

The ruling by the high court could have serious implications for the suspect charged with sexual assault, because it will allow his subsequent incriminating statements into evidence at his pending trial. 
The court also clarified that requesting a canine attorney need not cause the police to stop questioning someone. 

Once an individual asks for an attorney, police are not supposed continue their line of questioning. 

Warren Demesme, then 22, was being questioned by New Orleans officer in October 2015 after two young girls accused him of sexually assaulting them. 
Demesme had been brought in a second time for questioning. After denying the crime several times, in frustration, he told police, this is how I feel, if y'all think I did it, I know that I didn't do it so why don't you just give me a lawyer dog cause this is not what's up. 3475814]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVARGXAHLJKWCAZ7BNIAVL2ANFIEZSRQKWIFXGZAA5BA3DKUAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/381/5F1/3815F115520851380D4E44D1F2846F46.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lawyer dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ give me a lawyer dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Louisiana Supreme Court]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New Orleans lawyer dog]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chemotherapy-harms-fertility-of-female-cancer-patients-grandkids-3475705</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chemotherapy harms fertility of female cancer patients' grandkids 3475705]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY, UTAH — Chemotherapy can significantly harm the fertility of female cancer patients' children, new research has shown. 

Researchers at the University of Utah found the offspring of women who had treatment before becoming pregnant had a 70 percent worse chance of having a child themselves, the Telegraph reported. 

The effects of chemotherapy drugs has been well documented, but this is the first study to find a negative effect inherited by the next generation. 

Scientists believe the chemotherapy medication may be altering the genetic expression of inherited germ line cells.

Male cancer patients did not pass on the same effect to their offspring, most likely because sperm constantly regenerates, while a woman has all her eggs at birth. 

Women of reproductive age being treated for cancer are increasingly being encouraged to preserve their eggs cryogenically. 3475705]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLAPCIBBWIRADRRLZBF59BAMZABZUTZA5DFPG3SBRAAGAKSAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0A2/97E/0A297E5F69E4F7DBEF4C8639B45EF567.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer treatments]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemotherapy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemotherapy side effects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemotherapy affects female patient grandchildren]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/microchips-could-be-the-way-of-the-future-3475649</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Microchips could be the way of the future 3475649]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA — A tech festival in Melbourne is shining the spotlight on microchips, implanting the 'injectables' into 10 volunteers who will personally test them out.

According to The Guardian, the microchip is roughly the size of a grain of rice, and is capable of holding only one access code and limited information.

The tiny device is typically injected in between the thumb and forefinger, using a needle as thick as those used in body piercings.

Each microchip uses NFC or near-field communication to unlock a specific door, vehicle, or device.

The volunteers' chips come preloaded with a 30-day VIP pass for Pause Fest, and will be programmed to unlock the door to their home, gym or work. Alternatively, it can also function as a public transportation pass.

When the festival finally comes around in February 2018, the ten volunteers will join a panel and talk about whether they found the chip useful.

Developers are already working on a model of microchips that can store multiple access codes, and even be able to handle payments.

In due time, people will have no need for keys or wallets. But until that day comes, we'll just be here fumbling with our keychains. 3475649]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVAWGDIHLICRIDZSLZDFR6D3GNKSZRIIAEDFXURAAZCACBAABF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DED/249/DED2495D5B296C4C7FB0180EDF69E582.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microchips]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microchip]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NFC microchip]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NFC chip]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NFC]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chip implant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microchip implant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chip injection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ injectables]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ injectibles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tech festival]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pause Festival]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pause Festival 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ melbourne tech festival]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flight-chaos-fears-as-bardarbunga-volcano-hit-by-four-tremors-3475645</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flight chaos fears as Bardarbunga volcano hit by four tremors 3475645]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ICELAND — The Bardarbunga volcano in Iceland was hit by a series of four earthquakes recently.

University of Iceland Geophysics Professor Páll Einarsson told British tabloid the Daily Star that the volcano is preparing for an eruption within the next few years. 

The volcano is in a normal, non-eruptive state, reported the Daily Star, citing the Icelandic Meteorological Office. 

When the Eyjafjallajokull volcano erupted in 2010 it caused massive flight chaos, grounding most air traffic to and from Europe for several days. 

According to the BBC, its ash cloud reached closed to heights of 10,000 meters meaning, planes in the impacted area couldn't fly. 3475645]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZAWMDRELIAAPVZWL5AWR6BAGNLVRFIIKIDFVUCRAMDFPVZEKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DA7/B87/DA7B87451EC0992463D05FDEC56956DF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Iceland volcano eruption 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Volcano eruption 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bardarbunga]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Eyjafjallajokull]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iceland volcanoes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flights and ashcloud]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/latino-victory-s-anti-gop-ad-backfires-big-time--3476397</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Latino Victory's anti-GOP ad backfires. Big time. 3476397]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE COMMONWEALTH — National PAC the Latino Victory Fund bollixed a Virginia gubernatorial election ad against Republican nominee Ed Gillespie this week. 

It shows four minority kids running from a white redneck driving a pickup truck bearing a Gillespie bumper sticker and Stainless Banner. 

Problem is the ad, titled American Nightmare, was released a day prior to an actual American nightmare where an Uzbeki driver, who entered the U.S. via a green card lottery, mowed down eight people in a pickup truck in Manhattan.

The anti-Gillespie ad was pulled following the attack, but it did triple donations. For the GOP that is. Seems like the Latin Victory Fund's echo-chamber is insulated by an extra layer of tone-deafness.

But that's not to say the GOP ads aren't without flair. If they're to be believed, Democratic nominee and current Virginia deputy governor Ralph Northam is hell bent on uniforming all commonwealth zip codes to MS-13. 3476397]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IWPDIFAVBAEA3CBVDF76LXMRBBVRIMKACFRHTRABIRGBIKAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FCF/D2B/FCFD2BB43781ED597D84BB0F6981D7CD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virginia 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ latino victory fund ad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ed gillespie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ralph northam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virginia election]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ latino victory fund]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virginia election 2017]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/latino-victory-s-anti-gop-ad-backfires-big-time--3476394</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Latino Victory's anti-GOP ad backfires. Big time. 3476394]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE COMMONWEALTH — National PAC the Latino Victory Fund bollixed a Virginia gubernatorial election ad against Republican nominee Ed Gillespie this week. 

It shows four minority kids running from a white redneck driving a pickup truck bearing a Gillespie bumper sticker and Stainless Banner. 

Problem is the ad, titled American Nightmare, was released a day prior to an actual American nightmare where an Uzbeki driver, who entered the U.S. via a green card lottery, mowed down eight people in a pickup truck in Manhattan.

The anti-Gillespie ad was pulled following the attack, but it did triple donations. For the GOP that is. Seems like the Latin Victory Fund's echo-chamber is insulated by an extra layer of tone-deafness.

But that's not to say the GOP ads aren't without flair. If they're to be believed, Democratic nominee and current Virginia deputy governor Ralph Northam is hell bent on uniforming all commonwealth zip codes to MS-13. 3476394]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2JAGCREA2LAKBR9LNLAV74UGNIEZFAMK2PA3GCTKADR7BANAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A82/699/A82699DE320307ACDC1009716C4B96D1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virginia 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ latino victory fund ad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ed gillespie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ralph northam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virginia election]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ latino victory fund]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virginia election 2017]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-might-be-getting-ready-for-another-nuclear-test-seoul-3477657</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea might be getting ready for another nuclear test: Seoul 3477657]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — South Korean intelligence told the country's lawmakers last Thursday that the North is making preparations for another missile test.

Seoul points to increased vehicular movement around a research base in Pyongyang as evidence of this.

North Korea last carried out a weapons test in September 2017 at its underground facility in Punggye-ri.

REUTERS
http://reut.rs/2yx75lD

CNN
http://cnn.it/2lVXr6k 3477657]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDACXZGK6NWGDCHLIDWX7DSMEAS5RK5AIDAVFCYAJJAAVZMKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4E9/B23/4E9B2375A007FD1E76ACC353476344F4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dprk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile test fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump in asia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/apple-says-new-1000-iphone-x-may-get-screen-burn-in-3477636</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Apple says new $1000 iPhone X may get screen burn-in 3477636]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA — Apple's support page for the device says that in extremely rare cases, the iPhone X OLED screen may suffer from burn-in.

This is basically a remnant image, or ghost image from a high-contrast image is displayed continuously for long periods of time.

The company says they engineered the new display to reduce the effects of burn-in. 3477636]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMCAPDRJKWPRMA3CBWJRZ7LTGRDB7E33K6IA5HZLA6KR5ARAAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/503/417/50341799AEBD2D935CFC3BFDA5E74421.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>40</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ screen burn in]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apple x issues]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apple iphone teardown]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone x screen burn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue screen iphone]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-church-shooting-leaves-at-least-26-dead-20-injured-3477590</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Texas church shooting leaves at least 26 dead, 20 injured 3477590]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SUTHERLAND SPRINGS, TEXAS — A church shooting in Sutherland Springs, Texas on Sunday has left 26 people dead and 20 wounded, authorities said. 

The shooter was a white male dressed in all-black tactical gear and a ballistic vest, according to CNN. He has been identified as Devin Kelley of New Braunfels, ABC New reported. 

Kelly entered the First Baptist Church and opened fire with a Ruger AR rifle around 11:20 a.m. before fleeing the scene in an SUV, said Wilson County Sheriff Joe Tackitt, according to KSAT. 

As Kelly was attempting to leave, a local resident used a rifle to engage him. The shooter then fled the church, according to CNN.

After a short car chase, authorities found the suspected shooter dead from a gunshot wound inside his truck. Officials are still trying to determine Kelly's cause of death. 3477590]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLFKYACA5HWIBAUB5CRZ72GGEDSZERQLSIR5GTWBSLFEBZPAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AB8/EA0/AB8EA09D49DB409A9554724B3A0F12CD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Texas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sutherland Springs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ First Baptist Church]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Texas church incident]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/earth-s-ozone-hole-shrinks-to-smallest-size-since-1988-3477497</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Earth's ozone hole shrinks to smallest size since 1988 3477497]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA — NASA announced on Thursday that the hole in the Earth's ozone is the smallest it's been for the last 29 years, though not because toxic emissions have gone down.

According to NASA, the ozone hole that formed over Antarctica this year measured 7.6 million square miles at its maximum peak on September 11, and is as small as it has been since 1988.

Ozone molecules shield the Earth from the sun's UV radiation, but are being depleted by man-made chemicals like bromine and chlorine that are released into the atmosphere.

The hole in the ozone has been growing larger over the years, measuring more than 11 million square miles at its highest.

Ozone deteriorates more quickly in colder temperatures, and in the presence of polar stratospheric clouds that encourage ozone-eating chemical reactions.

This year's weak depletion is largely due to stormy conditions in the upper atmosphere, which warmed temperatures and kept toxic chemicals from destroying the ozone.

While the small ozone hole resulted from mostly natural causes, steady improvements such as the banning of ozone-eating chemicals in a 1987 international treaty may have also contributed. 3477497]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5ARIDZFKBQAPDATL6PA36L3MBJSTERKKIAAXHZKKZBWKVIAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DEE/680/DEE680793C14D6D69088F031C0D886A3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ozone hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ozone layer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ozone depletion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ozone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antarctica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm winter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UV radiation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sun protection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic emissions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emissions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chlorine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bromine]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/petition-wants-netflix-to-swap-one-kevin-for-another-3478561</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Petition wants Netflix to swap one Kevin for another 3478561]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOLLYWOOD — Over 25,000 people have signed a petition asking Netflix co-founder Reed Hastings replace Kevin Spacey with comedian Kevin James on House of Cards.

On the heels of widespread allegations of sexual harassment and abuse by Hollywood film producer Harvey Weinstein, Spacey is facing several allegations of his own regarding sexual abuse. That made Netflix fire him and stop production of the show's final season.

The petition, by Robbie Pyma in Australia, reckons that James can elevate House of Cards to GoT levels of global adoration.

CHANGE.ORG
http://bit.ly/2iBkONF 3478561]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZAAGYZEKSLFKVZ9BMDA76DYMVBEXR36ABLAVTCRBSJRTAREAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/216/E0C/216E0CCF9026E0BE241F0821BBA0A06E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kevin James]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Frank Underwood]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Claire Wright]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ House of Cards]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Netflix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Claire underwood]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/airlines-are-doing-all-sorts-of-things-to-get-more-seats-filled-3478511</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Airlines are doing all sorts of things to get more seats filled 3478511]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[U.S.A — The airline interior industry is worth $17 billion and growing, while airline seats are shrinking. 

Over time, the average width of airline seating on U.S. flights has gradually shrunk, despite the weight of the average American going up, reported the New York Times.

Airlines have also decreased pitch, the legroom and space between seating rows, in a bid to accommodate more passengers on flights. Some seating manufacturers have also reduced the thickness of seats.

The airline interiors industry is said to be worth $17 billion dollars, and is expected to grow in the coming decade, reported the Economist, citing the Los Angeles Times. 3478511]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIDFMCRAKIBRABZ9B6IWX6JHGMDV5FK4KSKRZHZLAEAF3WTTAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ED4/C41/ED4C4198F7BBBDBDD2853E847670274F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[shrinking airline seats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[smaller airline seats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[more people on planes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[smaller seats on planes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[airline seating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[airline travel]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-shooter-had-a-history-of-domestic-violence-3478476</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Texas shooter had a history of domestic violence 3478476]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SUTHERLAND SPRINGS, TEXAS — Around half of the victims shot to death on Sunday at the First Baptist Church in Sutherland Springs were children, Texas officials said on Monday. 

Twenty-six people were killed when 26-year-old Devin Patrick Kelley opened fire on the church at 11:20 a.m.

Authorities say the shooting occurred amid a continuing domestic situation involving Kelley and his relatives, some of whom were members of the church, authorities said Monday, the Washington Post reported. 

The Air Force said on Monday it failed to enter the shooter's domestic violence court martial into the federal database, which would have prohibited him from buy the rifle used in the shooting.  

Kelley was convicted for assaulting his then-wife and stepson and served 12 months in confinement before being released in 2014 with a bad-conduct discharge, according to the Washington Post. 

The shooter was also found to have been sending threatening texts to his mother-in-law. 

Investigators are still trying to come up with a motive for the shooting. 

According to the police, three guns were recovered on Sunday from Kelly's vehicle: a Ruger rifle, a Glock handgun and a Ruger handgun. Kelley had bought four guns during the past four years, according to officials. 3478476]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AAPCTWKSJAACI9L6KWR7DYMMBVZSK6KVBWVURGA2KW3VAFAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CBC/4A1/CBC4A1B8AD57C02140CC4A81495D023F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Texas incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Texas church incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Devin Patrick Kelly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ domestic issues]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-monster-planet-found-circling-small-star-3478330</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Monster' planet found circling small star 3478330]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WARWICK, BRITAIN — Research led by the University of Warwick has led to the discovery of a giant planet located 600 light years from Earth.

Named NGTS-1b, the celestial body is a gas giant around the same size Jupiter. It orbits a star half the size of the Sun.

NGTS-1b orbits the star at 3% of the distance between Earth and the sun. As such, it holds a temperature of 530 degrees centigrade and orbit its star every 2.6 days.

Researchers say this is the largest planet compared to the size of its companion star ever discovered.

The discovery challenges formation theory which posits smaller stars can only form rocky planets, not gas giants.

The findings are set to be reported in Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society. 3478330]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNFVCAABZHREAI9LVDATL2CMNIEZERQK2PFXGZGAZHWVACTBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C37/D66/C37D666C7F4784F6A86D827D6965BC26.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exoplanet 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ monster planet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NGTS-1b]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ formation theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ university of warwick]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/big-american-raccoon-gets-stuck-in-sewer-grate-for-being-too-fat-3478310</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Big American raccoon gets stuck in sewer grate for being too fat 3478310]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ZION, ILLINOIS — Last week, the Zion city police department received a call about an animal in distress. 

Apparently, the raccoon — which we'll call Fats — has been living the life. Unfortunately, Fats hasn't been able to hit the gym lately, so has put on some pounds.

That's why when Fats was trying to get out of the sewer the other day, he got stuck. 

Officers that were first on scene, were unable to get Fats free, so they had to call in some public works guys to get the job done.  

Maybe it's all the gluten in Fats' diet. 3478310]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5BWEYIFK5DWPWA7LWJFZ7UUGMEETRC7AZDRXFKTAWJAZWTUAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E51/6F2/E516F2B132E3BC3E86F64D2C82FC5C4E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raccoon stuck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raccoon stuck sewer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raccoon stuck sewer grate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chunky raccoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fat raccoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fat animals]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/73-million-trees-to-be-planted-in-amazon-reforestation-project-3478291</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[73 million trees to be planted in Amazon reforestation project 3478291]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRAZIL — A project in the Amazon rainforest is using a new technique to plant trees in the largest ever tropical reforestation. 

Conservation International plans to restore 70,000 acres of land cleared for grazing with 73 million trees, Fast Company reported.

The trees will be planted in the arc of deforestation that stretches across the Brazilian states of Amazonas, Acre, Pará and Rondônia, as well as the Xingu watershed. 

The planting method is called muvuca, which is Portuguese for a small place with many people. 

The muvuca method involves spreading hundreds of native tree seeds of various species over deforested land. 

Natural selection then allows the most suited trees to grow and thrive in a much thicker density than plant-by-plant reforestation. 
Plant-by-plant techniques usually have a density of 160 plants per hectare, while with muvuca, the density is 2,500 species per hectare. Scientists believe after 10 years, it could reach 5,000 trees per hectare. 3478291]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIRPDICAWJAPCCFBSLAK6JGM5EBZU3ZKMDR3GTYBVBW3BK4AC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A3A/CCF/A3ACCF96627C762B6A280BADC5219693.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reforestation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reforestation project]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ muvuca planting method]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ muvuca]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/finnair-starts-passenger-weigh-ins-at-helsinki-airport-3478284</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Finnair starts passenger weigh-ins at Helsinki airport 3478284]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HELSINKI — Finland's largest airline is now weighing its passengers, but not for the reason you might be thinking.

BBC reports that Finnish flag carrier Finnair has begun conducting voluntary passenger weigh-ins at Helsinki airport. Only 180 have volunteered so far, but the airline hopes to weigh as many as 2,000.

The aim of the weigh-ins is to update the estimates being used to calculate total weight, since this is used to forecast payload and fuel consumption.

Finnair is currently relying on 2009 data from the European Aviation Safety Agency, which lists 85 kilos as the standard weight for males, 67 kilos for females, and 31 for children under 12.

But these weights often vary under certain conditions. Men in first class tend to weigh more than average, while the opposite is true for females. Carry-on luggage weight also fluctuates, and is heavier in winter than in summer.

Finnair claims surveying its mix of travellers will generate more accurate data that's specific to their airline. It plans to continue with the weigh-ins through Spring 2018. 3478284]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFIWVAADAVHRVARSLMCRZ6JAMMAS5RAKK2IFRUZAAFIRCCRJAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9C3/52D/9C352DDF4E8901780AA58F70D61C3F41.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ finnair]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weigh ins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ passenger weight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline weight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ finland airline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fuel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ payload]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luggage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luggage weight]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-are-the-paradise-papers--3478218</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What are the Paradise Papers? 3478218]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — A massive new trove of leaked records is shining light on how the world's richest are sheltering their wealth offshore.

The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists reports that the Paradise Papers are a leak of 13.4 million papers covering people's finances from 1950 to 2016, mostly from offshore law firm Appleby and the company registries of 19 tax havens.

Appleby's clients include both people and companies, from countries like the UK, China, and Hong Kong. The majority, however, are from the U.S., numbering at least 30,000.

The leaked documents detail how firms like Appleby help clients stash money and assets in offshore tax havens, to avoid paying high taxes.

The exposé comes from the same German newspaper that outed last year's Panama Papers, and reveals the secret dealings of numerous individuals and companies, including the Queen of England, and Facebook.

The Queen's private estate had invested nearly 10 million pounds in a Cayman Islands fund, some of which had gone to a company accused of exploiting the poor.

Facebook and Twitter, meanwhile, received investments that were traced to Russian state institutions. The funds had gone through a business associate of Trump adviser and son-in-law Jared Kushner.

Most of these transactions and accounts are perfectly legal, but whether they are fair or moral is another matter entirely. 3478218]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2LWGXAEAMDFEVZSBJPAZ7L4MZDBRECZAJIW5HCTK2JW5WRALF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/298/7B6/2987B6BA4A21FB14425D55F0E2FFC014.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paradise papers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ document leak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ leaks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ offshore accounts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ offshore]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ offshore services]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ appleby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taxes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/lockheed-martin-to-develop-laser-weapons-for-u-s-fighter-jets-3479314</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Lockheed Martin to develop laser weapons for U.S. fighter jets 3479314]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BETHESDA, MARYLAND — The U.S. is finally taking a page from Star Wars and is now looking to equip its fighter planes with high-energy lasers.

CNBC reports that Lockheed Martin has been awarded a $26.3 million contract to design, develop, and build a high-energy laser weapon for the U.S. Air Force's SHiELD program.

The company delivered a 60-kilowatt laser for U.S. Army ground vehicles early this year, and will produce a smaller system to test on tactical aircraft by 2021.

Airborne laser weapons can defend against threats from enemy missiles, boosting the self-defense capabilities of military jets.

The Lockheed Martin laser is one of three subsystems that make up the SHiELD program. A beam control system is being developed by Northrop Grumman, while a pod to power and cool the laser is being designed by Boeing. 3479314]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABJWEYKTAIBWAVAWLSJAX6LYMJJSZURNKJKW3FADAZAFRAIDAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F12/9C6/F129C64F3F194A9BA4B4602DB1AB3D55.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  laser jet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laser weapon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laser system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lockheed martin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fighter jets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us air force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laser beam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile defense]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ futuristic weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airborne laser]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/twitter-jacks-up-time-tested-140-character-limit-gets-doubled-3479300</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Twitter Jacks up! Time-tested 140-character limit gets doubled 3479300]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Social media platform Twitter has doubled the character limit users can send in tweets.

Originally designed to be no longer than a text, the 140-character tweet has been the norm since Twitter began in 2006.  From now on, all Twitter users, prolific Twits included, have 280 characters to play with.  

According to CNN, Twitter made the decision after 5 percent of users in a 280-character test group wrote beyond 140 characters. Two percent made it past 190-characters. 3479300]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDAGCAHK6JAKWRULZDARLBBGZES3RK5AJPFMTIGKZDAZVCTKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A15/FE7/A15FE7D0127EAC8AAC62A936B8856E2A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter character increase]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 140 characters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 140 280 twitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jack dorsey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ silicon valley]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/former-mlb-pitcher-roy-halladay-killed-in-florida-plane-crash-3479221</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Former MLB pitcher Roy Halladay killed in Florida plane crash 3479221]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PASCO COUNTY, FLORIDA — Pitcher Roy Halladay died in a plane crash off the Florida coast on Tuesday. 

Halladay was the only person in the two-seater, single-engine Icon A5, when it crashed in shallow water north of the Tampa Bay area. His plane was found upside down, according to CNN.

Authorities got a 911 call at 12:06 p.m. about a small plane crash. No distress calls were received, according to the sheriff's office. 
The former pitcher had just tweeted photos of the light, amphibious aircraft in recent weeks. 
Halladay threw heat with the Blue Jays for his first 12 seasons. He won the Cy Young in 2003, when he went 22-7 with a 3.25 ERA and led the American with nine complete games. 
In 2010, he won another Cy Young after he was traded to the Phillies. He was 21-10 with a 2.44 ERA that year. 
Halladay was an eight-time All-Star and with 203 wins with a 3.38 ERA in his 16-year-career. 3479221]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJFAACSAMAR3DATLVDWZKL4MVBVXFC6KFIF5FKXARARAVAHAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/197/B9D/197B9D3BC76CBD0355225FCE660DC086.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Roy Halladay]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Roy Halladay plane crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Roy Halladay Blue Jays]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Roy Halladay Phillies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Halladay Cy Young]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/belgian-ex-footballer-dies-after-being-struck-by-lightning-in-bali-3479210</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Belgian ex-footballer dies after being struck by lightning in Bali 3479210]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BALI, INDONESIA — A Belgian former footballer was unfortunately killed while surfing in Bali, Indonesia last Sunday when he was struck by lightning.

The victim has been identified as 34-year-old ex-footballer Denis Andre Dasoul.

An Australian expatriate who spoke to Tomonews witnessed the event, and said that he and his brother were taking a surfing lesson themselves when they heard a deafening lightning crack from a distance of about 25 meters behind them.

The sound was of lightning striking Dasoul and his instructor, who were sitting on a surfboard on the water.

Many local residents immediately rushed to help. Someone reportedly administered CPR, and the instructor made it, but Dasoul unfortunately did not survive. 3479210]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6JRIXAFAJKWKVRWLZDR37D4GZBV5R39K6KWZTZGANLARB3RKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/857/8D9/8578D9FA5C0D44FCE14373CEF6832E23.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surfing dangers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ struck by lightning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ football]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ footballer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soccer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Denis Andre Dasoul]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/visitors-save-russian-zookeeper-from-tiger-mauling-3478983</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Visitors save Russian zookeeper from tiger mauling 3478983]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KALININGRAD, RUSSIA —A Russian zookeeper was saved from a horrific demise from a tiger attack, and it's all thanks to some quick thinking by zoo visitors.

BBC reports that the 16-year-old Siberian tiger's cage had been left open open, so when zookeeper Nadezhda Srivastava went into the enclosure to deliver food, the animal pounced.

The terrified zookeeper was pinned helplessly on the ground as the big cat clawed and gnawed at her for at least 10 minutes.

Onlookers began throwing rocks at the animal, but only made it angrier. It wasn't until some visitors hurled a table and chairs into the enclosure that the tiger got distracted, which allowed the zookeeper to flee to safety.

The 44-year-old zookeeper was immediately taken to the hospital, and is currently recovering from her wounds.

The tiger was later taken out with a sedative and brought back to its cage. Zoo staff say the animal has no history of being aggressive towards humans, and will not be put down.

The zoo has also blamed the attack on the zookeeper, claiming that the gruesome incident happened because she violated safety protocol. 3478983]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAARAY3TKBIWEARVB5ARZKDTNAASIFC3K6PFRFIEAECF5DZJAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BC9/944/BC994416B5D4DDC58089E910C490FFF9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiger attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zookeeper attacked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia tiger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ siberian tiger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russa zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia zoo attack]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/transgender-women-will-soon-be-able-to-give-birth-3478977</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Transgender women will soon be able to give birth 3478977]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — One of the world's leading fertility specialists has said that it's now entirely possible for transgendered women to get pregnant, thanks to developments in science.

The Telegraph reports that doctors have successfully transplanted wombs in uterine infertile women in recent years, and at least five babies have been born to these transplant recipients since 2014.

Experts now believe the same procedure can be conducted on transgendered women who were born male but have undergone sex reassignment surgery.

Carrying a live fetus in the transplanted wombs will likely be more complicated, and expectant transgendered women may need hormones to replicate the natural pregnancy changes that occur in women.

The male pelvis is also shaped differently than a female's, which means the baby would have to be born via caesarean section.

Of course, not everyone is on board with the idea. Some have voiced ethical concerns, since a pregnancy of this nature poses a huge risk to both mother and child. 3478977]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZAFEXTVKEBWPBATBADF77L4M6IBIRALAJIRXTAGAWKAVCABAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/924/377/924377C5AFD0683F97ED3834FCC7335E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ womb transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uterus transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ transgender woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ transgender]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trans woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sex change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sex reassignment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gender reassignment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnancy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ male pregnancy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-feeds-koi-which-feeds-media-anger-which-feeds-right-s-outrage-3478971</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump feeds koi, which feeds media anger, which feeds right's outrage 3478971]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — So the Commander-in-Cheeto is currently prancing around Asia, and his first stop was in Japan to hangout with playdate Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe. 

As part of the welcoming ceremony, Drumph and Abe went to feed some koi fish on the grounds of Akasaka Palace. 
The two leaders both took turns dumping boxes of fish food into the pond, except one hilarious photo that captured only Trump dumping his box. 
The media and Twitter were immediately triggered and went into attack mode. But the thing is, Trump was only following Abe's lead. 
But of course this in turn triggered the right. Now everyone is triggered again.

And meanwhile we have the most powerful man on planet telling the Japanese he couldn't understand why a country of samurai warriors did not shoot down North Korean missiles fired over Japan. 3478971]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIFKCIIAECAIA3ABBLWT94TGSJSRST4ABIF3HKXKAARTAKWAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D25/1A5/D251A58D561D0F63B9E449961C3A311C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump in Japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump Abe meeting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump feeding koi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump feeding koi fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump koi fish incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump in Asia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/two-faced-chimera-cat-goes-viral-3480109</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Two-faced chimera cat goes viral 3480109]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOMEWHERE OUT THERE — Quimera is a super cute, cuddly chimera cat taking the interwebs by storm. 

A chimera is the result of two fertilized eggs, or two early embryos, joining in a mother's womb. 

A chimera cat is kind of like a two for one. 

Quimera has been blowing up the Gram with her little furry face, which is split perfectly down the middle. 

On one side, she has tabby fur and a hazel eye and on the other side she has black fur with a blue eye. Crazy, huh? 

Quimera already has more followers than most people with 34,000 adoring online fans. 

Even though the condition is super rare, chimeras occur across many species — even humans. 3480109]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFJFXDKUAVHA3WCHLWJAI9JHMRAVXSC6AJLRXHRBAWQATACXLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7D3/989/7D398983F0A248566005E3F992214FA6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cute cats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chimera cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chimera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Quimera cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Quimera the chimera cat]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/robot-einstein-doesn-t-think-much-of-problematic-humans-3480047</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Robot Einstein doesn't think much of 'problematic' humans 3480047]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LISBON, PORTUGAL — A robot Einstein, and his Saudi fembot buddy Sofia dished out a harsh prognosis for humanity this week.
 
Speaking at the Web Summit conference in Portugal, Einstein-bot called humans problematic and said they need to heal themselves. 

The robot professor reportedly theorizes that we will be the issue when it comes to cooperation between humanity and robots. Not the cyborgs. 3480047]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLWPCIGAABATWZSL2LRKKL3MWJBIRC7AIARTG3TAZFRMBIFAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8BE/B0A/8BEB0A8A7F2C09E71AC1B1134F8CBA3B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot vs humans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ will robots take our jobs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot einstein]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ einstein]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sofia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/boy-with-rare-condition-gets-new-skin-with-gene-therapy-3480045</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Boy with rare condition gets new skin with gene therapy 3480045]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MODENA, ITALY — A young patient who lost most of his skin to a genetic disease now has a new chance at life, thanks to a breakthrough therapy that gave him replacement skin.

The New York Times reports that the 7-year-old boy was born with junctional epidermolysis bullosa, a condition in which a gene defect causes the skin to become fragile, often tearing and forming blisters.

By June 2015, the boy gotten two bacterial infections that destroyed two-thirds of his skin. He was treated with antibiotics, bandages, and even a skin graft from his father, but nothing worked.

Doctors decided to use gene therapy on a patch of non blistered skin, and used a virus to carry a corrected version of the defective gene into the skin cells.

The engineered cells were grown into sheets of skin and grafted onto the child's body to replace his missing skin.

The grafts took and grew, and the patient was discharged by February 2016. His epidermis is currently stable and doesn't blister or itch. 3480045]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMCFKCRJKMAAVA3FBJKR5LSHM6JVZSC6KEAWRUAFAZGREAKRKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2CE/4A2/2CE4A268633C4A932F802B316BED439F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new skin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ replacement skin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ junctional epidermolysis bullosa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin condition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetic disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin graft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ butterfly skin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fragile skin]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/unbelievably-large-rodent-found-in-sweden-3479992</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Unbelievably large rodent found in Sweden 3479992]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GOTHENBURG, SWEDEN — Thanks to the food waste generated by city dwellers, rats  are now a major problem in Sweden. 

In October, a woman named Martina Gustafsson spotted two birds fighting over something unusually big at a park in Gothenburg. Gustafsson told Sweden’s SVT that she first thought it was a rabbit, but turns out it was an giant rat

A pest control expert in Gothenburg named Håkan Rystrand later told SVT that he suspected the giant rodent to be about 10 inches long and claimed that it is normal for brown rats in Sweden to grow to such size. 

The giant rodent is definitely not the first case in Sweden. 

In 2014, a Swedish family in Solna, Sweden rose to national fame after catching a giant rat with a rat trap, oh and rodent survived. 3479992]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAACXZCK6KFXAZSBSJRRL2AM5BSVSC4KIAA5HZEBRBRADT9AE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4C5/3FC/4C53FC9DBAA145EB9116E2AE23AF04BA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rodent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[giant rodent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[giant rat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rats in sweden]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rats in the walls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[food waste]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[brown rats]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/southwest-flight-grounded-after-wing-catches-fire-before-takeoff-3479923</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Southwest flight grounded after wing catches fire before takeoff 3479923]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT — A Southwest Airlines flight from Detroit to St. Louis was grounded after a passenger happened to notice the wing was on fire right before takeoff. 

David Fiedor was in the back of the plane on Flight 1863 last Thursday when his spider-sense started tingling. 

I heard a muffled thud, similar to when the landing gear is engaging. I didn't think much of it until I looked out the window and saw the wing had flames coming out from the bottom. The flames were coming out intermittently Fiedor told MLive. 

The plane was carrying about 80 people Fiedor guessed, but he had the back mostly to himself. 

Apparently no one else noticed the fire, so he got up from his seat and calmly alerted a flight attendant. 

After first the flight attendant told Fiedor to sit down, but then she came back and saw the flames for herself. 

She alerted the pilots, and they turned the plane back. Passengers either booked another flight or were given a refund. 3479923]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSNRMXRGBSJWVBZYBSLRT7SBMWIE5SCRKVAWTGCYANLAVX3YKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4A7/C31/4A7C313CC6E41E39927DF433ADF7697D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southwest Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southwest Airlines wing on fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southwest flight grounded]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wing of fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southwest Airlines wing]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gaming-keyboard-records-how-many-times-keys-are-pressed-3479795</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gaming keyboard records how many times keys are pressed 3479795]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — Several users of the MantisTek GK2 gaming keyboard have reported a built-in Keylogger that is sending data to an Alibaba server in China. 

The MantisTex GK2 is a low cost RGB mechanical keyboard produced in China. 

The issue is being caused by the keyboard's Cloud Driver, which sends data to IP addresses linked to Alibaba servers, according to Tom's Hardware. 

The data has been identified as how many times keys have been pressed. 

Tracking this type of data without user permission could be a violation of privacy laws in the European Union.  

To stop the keyboard from sending your key presses to the Alibaba server, make sure the MantisTek Cloud Driver software isn't running in the background. 

Another method is by blocking the CMS.exe executable in your firewall by adding a new firewall rule for the MantisTek Cloud Driver in your Windows settings. 3479795]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJRPDKSASJA3WCABJIRTLBBGMDSIFZNAEBWXTAEARHF7DZIKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AE8/4E3/AE84E30D89D064E80A7203156025FF7A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gaming keyboard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MantisTek GK2 keyboard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MantisTek GK2 Cloud Driver software]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Alibaba server]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/heat-source-detected-under-antarctic-ice-sheet-3479747</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Heat source detected under Antarctic ice sheet 3479747]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA — A new NASA study bolsters the theory that a heat source exists under West Antarctica.

Researchers have found evidence that a geothermal heat source called a mantle plume lies deep below Antarctica's Marie Byrd Land, according to NASA.

Mantle plumes are narrow upwellings of hot rock that rise up from the Earth's mantle. They spread out like mushroom caps under the crust, causing it to bulge upward.

Using a numeric model, the flux of energy from the mantle plume was calculated to be 150 miliwatts, only 50 milliwatts less than the average heat flux under Yellowstone.

Researchers say the heat source could explain the melting that creates river and lakes under the West Antarctic ice sheet, but it is not a new or increasing threat.

However, global weather changes and rising sea levels can push warm water closer to the ice, causing it to become unstable and collapse — just as it did 11,000 years ago at the end of the last ice age. 3479747]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKAICZDANIRXARRLAAAZKLTM2JSVFK4KNPRVUTWAMHA3A3WAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A82/F0E/A82F0EE11261720C03338D0C233F50D0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mantle plume]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heat source]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geothermal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antarctica ice sheet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antarctic ice sheet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ west antarctica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marie byrd land]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/saturn-s-ocean-moon-maybe-home-to-subsea-alien-life-3479731</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Saturn's ocean moon maybe home to subsea alien life 3479731]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ENCELADUS, SATURN —  Scientists looking at data pulled from NASA's Cassini spacecraft may have found out how Saturn's ocean moon Enceladus remains geologically active.

The research, published in Nature Astronomy, suggests that tidal currents flow through the moon's porous core, where the friction between rocks generate heat that warms the ocean. According to the European Space Agency, this tidal heating is primarily caused by the gravitational pull of Saturn.

Writing in 2008, the space agency speculated that the deep sea vent theory could apply to life on Enceladus. When applied to Earth, this suggests life originated from chemical, heat and tidal interactions beneath the seabed.

NASA previously said Enceladus has all the ingredients for life, reported CNET, citing the space agency. 3479731]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLFGCTSAEDAVA3HLBLAK7LVGRBEXSC3KIARTHIKAADFVBKYAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E06/DD5/E06DD5DE1411E488407521D2DD0365A0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ enceladus alien]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life on enceladus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ enceladus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saturn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ esa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep sea vent enceladus]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-zombie-star-survives-3-year-supernova-3480718</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Zombie' star survives 3-year supernova 3480718]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA, U.S.A — A three-year-long supernova is making astronomers reconsider how stars form and die.

Designated as iPTF14hls, the supernova was first detected in 2014. It located is half a billion light years from Earth in the Ursa Major constellation.

Scientists theorize the original star was so hot it may've created antimatter at its core, reports the BBC, forcing it to become unstable and explode. 

This could lead to the supernova repeating until it eventually tears a hole in space-time and becomes a black hole.

Findings concerning the supernova were described in the journal Nature. 3480718]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFJFMCKUBAARIXI9LZCR76DYGFKSZSTZKBJF5FIABRGAKBRCLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/53C/E71/53CE7150FB3AA91C023722F5F2C846B3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zombie star]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star survives supernova]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supernova star]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iPTF14hls]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/self-driving-bus-launches-in-vegas-crashes-two-hours-later-3480687</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Self-driving bus launches in Vegas, crashes two hours later 3480687]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LAS VEGAS — The driverless electric shuttle bus made a big bang in its debut in Vegas on Wednesday.

Unfortunately, the bang came in the form of an accident after only two hours of being in service, the Las Vegas Review-Journal reported.  

Luckily for the self-driving bus, the fender bender was the other guy's fault. 

Police responded to an accident involving the shuttle and a delivery truck at 12:07 p.m. Damage was minor and no one was hurt, authorities said.  

It looks like the shuttle was minding its own business when it sensed a truck was attempting to back up, so it came to a stop.

Problem is, the truck kept backing up until it gave the shuttle a little love tap. The truck driver ended getting a ticket for illegal backing. 

The driverless shuttle is designed to communicate with traffic signals, share the road with other vehicles, while stopping for pedestrians. 

The shuttle is sponsored by AAA, which has partnered with the city, the Regional Transportation Commission of Southern Nevada and Keolis Transit America on the project. 3480687]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZAWXC3VLMGAMDA7B5DA3LUSGIBEREZQKSLWZTAKABQAIAT4AE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/21E/E53/21EE53E03BE6BE445AE2D5C990139660.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ self-driving bus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ self-driving shuttle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ self-driving bus accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ self-driving bus crashes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/weird-things-that-can-slow-down-your-wifi-3480483</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Weird things that can slow down your WiFi 3480483]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A UK survey has found that a whole bunch of people are sabotaging their own internet connections by positioning routers in all the wrong places.

Huffington Post reports that according to Post Office Telecoms, an unexpected item that can slow down your wifi are Christmas lights, which create a small electromagnetic field that can interfere with the signal.

Routers broadcast radio signals that are picked up by wifi capable devices, but electronic devices interfere with this signal because they compete for frequencies.

Wifi also doesn't transmit easily through water, so expect a slow connection when a router is near a fish tank, which has both electrical circuitry and lots of liquid.

Experts advise that routers be placed centrally within the house, away from windows or corners, in order to secure a strong wifi signal.

So folks, if you want the ultimate no-buffering zone, you best give that router space. Lots of it. 3480483]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWJWGCZHBECAMYRXBBKRVK4WGEDBIET3AEDAXGKYABPRRAK5KC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/41E/773/41E7734DC1973E1BBC7B4D077D168C80.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wifi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wifi signal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wifi connection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet connection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ connectivity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas lights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electromagnetic field]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric signals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to get fast wifi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ slow wifi fix]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-announces-10-days-of-black-friday-deals-in-the-u-k--3480477</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon announces 10 days of Black Friday deals in the U.K. 3480477]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM — Amazon just announced the U.K. will get treated to 10 days of Black Friday deals for 2017.  

Brits will get 10 whole days to rack up some fresh new debt on their plastic by wasting cream on a plethora of Amazon products.    

The madness will begin at midnight on November 17 and run through to the end of Sunday, November 26. 

Whatever you do, make sure to shop. Skip school, work, weddings, whatever you have planned that doesn't involve blind mass consumerism. 

Already have an Amazon Echo or Dot? Who cares, buy some more. Buy a couple for each room. 

Get a couple of new, useless Amazon Fires. Sure no one uses tablets anymore, but it's Black Friday folks. 

And if you're a fan of fire spinning, definitely pick yourself up some Amazon Fire Sticks. 
Most importantly, remember to shop irresponsibly and keep on accumulating. 3480477]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IWCDKWBMDAADKEB6IAX9BCNBKBRS35AZCFMGAAKEARTAIDKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FA8/891/FA88910FCB3CDE4E2DC8417D4637D5D4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-11T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Black Friday]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Black Friday 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Echo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Kindle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Black Friday deals]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ea-reply-to-star-wars-battlefront-2-complaint-maybe-most-downvoted-reddit-comment-ever-3482631</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[EA reply to Star Wars Battlefront 2 complaint maybe most downvoted Reddit comment ever 3482631]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[REDWOOD CITY, CALIFORNIA — American video game giant Electronic Arts is taking more hits than the Rebel Base on Hoth after it responded to a fan's complaint on Reddit. 

User MBMMaverick complained that he paid 80 bucks for the hotly anticipated online shooter Star Wars Battlefront 2 and Darth Vader was unplayable.

EA responded, saying their intent was to provide games with a sense of pride and accomplishment for unlocking different heroes.

That official response, sparked what is now apparently one of thee most downvoted Reddit comments in history with 67k and rising. 3482631]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLWVDIGBVGRGWZWKBIR3LBHMEDVXSRQAVCF7TCWKAGFPB3RAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5CC/69F/5CC69FA3C5CC3A7A984B9FD09F4B4330.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>89</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reddit fails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battlefront 2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ most downvoted comment on Reddit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reddit stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microtransaction fails]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/disney-shuts-down-cooling-towers-after-legionnaires-outbreak-3482514</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Disney shuts down cooling towers after Legionnaires' outbreak 3482514]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANAHEIM — Disneyland has shut down two cooling towers after an outbreak of Legionnaires' disease. 

Orange County health officials said nine people who visited the theme park in September came down with the disease, CNN reported.  

Three other people in the Anaheim area also got sick, according to a spokeswoman for the Orange County Health Care Agency. 

The 12 patients range in age from 52 to 94, according to the L.A. Times. 

The towers were shut down after Disney was notified by health officials on October 27 about increased Legionnaires' cases, according to CNN. 

Disney found two of its 18 cooling towers had elevated levels of Legionella bacteria, which were then treated and disinfected. 
Cooling towers supply cooled water for several uses such as refrigeration or air conditioning, but not for drinking water. 

Legionnaires disease is a severe lung infection caused by Legionella bacteria through exposure to contaminated water or mist. 

The source of the mist can be air conditioning units, showers or hot tubs. It is not contagious between humans. It is treated with antibiotics. 
Disney is now waiting on health officials to see when the two towers can be put back online. 3482514]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KWGC3VB5CAKAZWLNKF5KDUGREVRRT5K2LFPHRGAWMRADAGAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/44C/7A5/44C7A54920BCB251E2369F8EFD5A5A5B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Legionnaires' disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Legionnaires outbreak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Disneyland Legionnaires' outbreak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Disneyland cooling towers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/photo-of-last-male-northern-white-rhino-breaks-the-internet-3482414</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Photo of last male Northern White Rhino breaks the internet 3482414]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KENYA — A photo of the last male Northern White Rhino has broken hearts while going viral. 

Biologist Daniel Schneider tweeted the photo with the caption, Want to know what extinction looks like? This is the last male Northern White Rhino. The Last. Nevermore.
Sudan is one of three Northern White Rhinos left in existence, IFL Science reported. The other two are his 23-year-old daughter Najin and his 17-year-old granddaughter Fatu. 
In 2009, the rhinos moved to the Ol Pejeta Conservancy in Kenya from the Czech Republic in hopes that being in their natural habitat would help them breed. 

Unfortunately neither of the females can naturally reproduce and Sudan has almost no little swimmers left. 
White rhinos can live to 50, but most of them kick the can around 40. Sudan is 43, so the clock is ticking in overtime. 

There still may yet be hope. Conservationists are trying to raise $1 million bones for fertilization techniques with a GoFundMe campaign called Make a Rhino.  

Sudan is also being proactive about the situation, which is probably why he joined Tinder in April. 3482414]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLWKAIGBVBA7WA7B6KFZL4WGSJBTF37KJIFVGIHBSNRCBAGKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9B7/277/9B727764FE6155EF36F75DC7659939DE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Northern White Rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ last male Northern White Rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sudan Northern White Rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sudan White Rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rhinoceros]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hottest-toys-to-get-your-kids-for-christmas-2017-3482389</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hottest toys to get your kids for Christmas 2017 3482389]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — The holidays are upon us, and with it the inevitable rush to go gift-shopping for some lucky little rascals.

If you haven't been paying attention to what's hot and what's not in the world of toys this Christmas, you're in luck — because we have. Sort of.

According to the Washington Post, this year's hottest stocking stuffers are the LOL Surprise dolls, which are mini dolls with accessories encased in little balls of unnecessary packaging. LOL stands for Lil Outrageous Littles, in case you were curious.

There's also the LOL Big Surprise, which is a giant plastic dome filled with 50 balls, but we recommend that only if you're feeling extra-generous AND don't mind going on a nationwide scavenger hunt to get one — because those things are sold out.

Kids last year went gaga over Hatchimals, those freaky-looking interactive stuffed animals that you hatch out of an egg. Unsurprisingly, the little buggers are back on the list, and this year you get to hatch twin stuffed animals. Freaky but fun.

There's also more interactive pet options this year, so if your Christmas wish is to get a monkey, a tiger, or a unicorn, Fingerlings and Hasbro have you covered.

For bigger kids, it's best to ditch the cutesy toys and bring out the big guns. Literally. Laser X is all the rage, because who needs regular tag when you can play laser tag? Other less cool boys' toys include nerf guns and the always-popular lego.

Word of advice though: you might wanna get your shopping done soon, because these hot toys are flying off the shelves faster than you can say Santa.

If you get really desperate, there's always eBay and Amazon. Just be prepared to fork over a ridiculous amount of money, because capitalism. 3482389]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLWXCRBBVGAICRSLEBFZ9JHMEABZERLA2JFXHCSK5GFAVINBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CFC/6B2/CFC6B21FE20F1B33F5BE9AE4E285046D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>94</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot toys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unboxing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LOL Surprise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hatchimals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Laser X]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas toy ideas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas toys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas gift ideas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot toys 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2017 toys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twin hatchimals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LOL Big Surprise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LOL dolls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laser tag]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/research-shows-aaron-hernandez-had-severe-brain-damage-3482363</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Research shows Aaron Hernandez had severe brain damage 3482363]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS — A research conducted by Boston University’s CTE center revealed on November 9th that former NFL player Aaron Hernandez’s brain tissue had severe damage from sporting injuries.

Chronic traumatic encephalopathy is a neurodegenerative brain disease typically found in people who have suffered repeated hits to the head. The repeated blows shake the brain and cause the buildup of tau proteins, which hold together microtubules in the brain cell’s transport system.

Tau protein buildup can gradually disable neuro-pathways and can cause memory loss, dementia, and ultimately kill brain cells over time. Ninety-nine percent of NFL players included in the study were diagnosed with CTE, while 91% of college football players had the same disease.

According to Dr. Ann McKee, a neuropathologist who directs research of chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE) at Boston University, her research team discovered Hernandez had Stage 3 CTE and that they had never seen such severe damage in a brain of a person of his age. 

Less than a year after signing a $40 million contract in 2012 with the New England Patriots, Hernandez was convicted over the murder of friend Odin Lloyd in 2013. Hernandez was also indicted for a double homicide in 2012. 

On April 19, 2017, Hernandez hanged himself in a prison cell while serving a life sentence for murder. He was 27 years old.

McKee and her team of researchers could not definitely connect CTE and Hernandez’s suicide, but believe CTE severely impacted Hernandez’s decision-making abilities during the events leading up to his death. Hernandez also inherited a genetic profile that may have made him more susceptible to CTE, McKee added. 3482363]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KICAGCAAL2KAMVZTBIAR37USMRAE7U39KZAFXH3YAVHAAARFAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/271/8C8/2718C868962F4260859EC56623237B1E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>95</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[aaron hernandez]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[nfl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[football]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[sporting injuries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[CTE]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[nfl cte]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[nfl cte deaths]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[nfl cte players]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[cte brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[brain disease nfl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[nfl concussions]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/british-surfer-wiped-out-by-giant-50-foot-wave-breaks-back-3482336</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[British surfer wiped out by giant 50-foot wave, breaks back 3482336]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NAZARE, PORTUGAL — Shocking video footage shows the dramatic moment a British surfer gets wiped out by a colossal wave.

The Telegraph reports that plumber-turned-pro-surfer Andrew Cotton is obsessed with riding the world's largest waves. But the 36-year-old certainly met his match while surfing in Nazare, Portugal, where the seas churn out waves as high as 80 feet.

Cotton was zipping along fine initially, but couldn't outrun a 50-foot wall of water that soon came crashing down. He was thrown off his board and swallowed by the wave, but then got spit back out and landed in the water back-first.

The Brit suffered a painful spinal disc fracture in his lower back, but was fortunately rescued from the water. He was loaded onto a spinal board and rushed to the hospital, where he's currently recovering.

He doesn't need surgery, but does require a body brace to help him move around. It'll take time for him to heal completely, but no doubt Cotton is already itching to catch his next big wave. 3482336]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLWACICBVDRPACEKEDWR7BAMZCB3U3SAJPWPUABAJMWICRFAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BBA/2CC/BBA2CCCA80D48C76D36E4939B6E6E0F5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surfing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surfer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wipeout]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant waves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Andrew Cotton]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Nazare]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ praia do norte]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ portugal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pro surfer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surfing accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ back injury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spine injury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spinal injury]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fake-hate-crime-dupes-u-s-general-into-anti-racism-speech-3482322</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fake hate crime dupes U.S. general into anti-racism speech 3482322]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COLORADO SPRINGS, COLORADO — A student has reportedly left a prestigious U.S. Air Force Academy prep school in Colorado after duping almost everybody.

The Air Force cadet candidate confessed to making hoax offensive slur messages that he initially claimed to be the victim of, reported the Air Force Times. He did it as part of a plan to get out of trouble he was already in, reported the Colorado Gazette, citing sources inside the prep school.

After news of the messages broke in September the academy's superintendent, Lt Gen. Jay Silveria made a speech, telling bigots to get out of the school. That speech went viral and generated millions of views across YouTube. 3482322]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNRAYIHAFLWGB3ELMCW76LYMEBS5SC6K6IF7TZAKVGAIB3XBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/499/A99/499A99DED33B22F6A507943847AC0203.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>91</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake crime]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hoax crime]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us air force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colorado springs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ air force academy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crime exposed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crying wolf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cried wolf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ offensive messages]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/don-t-like-sharks-the-american-alligator-has-you-covered-3483510</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Don't like sharks? The American Alligator has you covered 3483510]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORIDA/GEORGIA — Research published in the journal Southeastern Naturalist details findings of American alligators eating sharks around the coasts of Georgia and Florida.

Alligator's diets typically consist of shellfish, fish and larger mammals as they grow older. The research pumped the stomach of 500 alligators and found small sharks and stingrays to be present in some.

Alligators mainly hunt in freshwater environments, but can sip rain during storms from the water surface to prolong their time in saltwater environments.

The research also considered cases of larger sharks eating smaller alligators and old reports of mass battles between the predators during floods. 3483510]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5BWPY3WKMDWCARULVDAIK2HMMDBZUZQK2PF5UZAKAHAIARHBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/374/871/3748710ACEBA88AE37BD2A04B022274F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark v alligator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gator eats shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ georgia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gator eating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark eating alligator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark alligator brawl]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/millions-now-hypertensive-under-new-u-s-guidelines-3483474</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Millions now hypertensive under new U.S. guidelines 3483474]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DALLAS — U.S. health experts tightened the guidelines for high blood pressure for the first time in 14 years, classifying 30 million more Americans as hypertensive.

The Washington Post reports that high blood pressure was once defined as a systolic reading of 140 and a diastolic reading of 90, but has recently been lowered to 130 over 80 by the American Heart Association, the American College of Cardiology, and nine other health organizations.

Blood pressure refers to the force of blood flowing through the blood vessels. When too high, it can damage arterial tissues and increase the risk for heart disease, stroke, and kidney problems.

Under the old guidelines, 32% of U.S. adults had high blood pressure. With the new lowered threshold, 46% or 103 million Americans are now considered hypertensive.

Normal levels are pegged at less than 120 over 80. Those with readings between 120 to 129 over less than 80 are considered to have elevated blood pressure, and recommended lifestyle changes. Medication is given to patients with Stage 1 hypertension who are at risk, while those at Stage 2 are given 2 different classes of medicine.

Since hypertension is a silent killer, experts want to help people get the condition under control earlier, and place a strong emphasis on making healthier life choices. 3483474]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIFEDRHAABAABRUBICR39L3MRBVXUZKKVBWXFILK6NRCAKSKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D72/AB3/D72AB34CA4DE9DD75898AD0E469509F0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high blood pressure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypertension]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypertensive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high blood]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood pressure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood pressure monitor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stroke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kidney disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high blood pressure guidelines]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/this-will-be-the-world-s-largest-yacht-when-it-is-finished-in-2020-3483297</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[This will be the world's largest yacht when it is finished in 2020 3483297]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VARD, NORWAY — Norwegian businessman Kjell Inge Rokke is giving away a sizeable part of his fortune to build this boat.

Designed by Espen Oeino, the Research Expedition Vessel is currently being constructed in Vard, Norway  According to Yacht Harbor, it will be the world's largest vessel when completed in 2020.

The boat is 182 meters long.  It can carry 60 scientists and 40 crew for research voyages, and 36 guests and 54 crew for private excursions.

According to its website, the boat will be fitted with advanced sonar technology, as well as a trawl that can go to 3000m in depth and a moonpool for underwater vehicles that can go to 6000m depth. 3483297]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKAPCADASLRMBARKAAWT6D3GMCS3FKSLSPA5U3XAWPRCBZJAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C1F/78A/C1F78A6087EFAD610589D32E54FD0D81.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biggest yacht in the world]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rev]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super yacht]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mega yacht]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ largest yacht]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/coconut-crab-goes-hunting-3483287</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Coconut crab goes hunting 3483287]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHAGOS ISLANDS, INDIAN OCEAN — A giant coconut crab on an island in the Indian Ocean was caught catching a seabird. 

According to Dartmouth college biologist Mark Laidre who captured the rare footage, coconut crabs are the largest land-dwelling invertebrate. These crabs can weigh up to 8 pounds and grow to 3 feet in length. 

Coconut crabs are omnivores that primarily eat fruit, but are always down for some fresh meat if they can get it. 3483287]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JRGYCVANJWEARVB5AF56JCGWJBRSRLKMDWPFACAIARKAZNBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C0B/687/C0B6879EA8950EFF012EC6606BF129AB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>123</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[coconut crabs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[crabs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[birds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[seabirds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[coconut crab eating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[chagos islands]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/enormous-10-month-old-baby-weighs-a-whopping-62-pounds-3483283</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Enormous 10-month-old baby weighs a whopping 62 pounds 3483283]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TECOMAN, MEXICO — Luis Manuel Gonzales is a 10-month-old baby. The only problem is he already weighs 62 pounds and doctors can't figure out why.  

Luis was born weighing about 8 lbs, but then his parents noticed him packing on the pounds at a phenomenal rate.

After one month, his clothes were already too small for him, so they had to buy him clothes for 1-year-old and 2-year-old babies.  

Doctors initially suspected Luis may have Prader-Willi syndrome, a genetic disorder that causes an endless appetite, which can lead to chronic overeating and obesity. 
However that diagnosis was ruled out after his mother explained that Luis isn't an excessive eater and eats a normal amount of food for his age. 

Physicians are now waiting on tests to see if Luis's condition could have been caused by his mother's unhealthy diet when he was in the womb. 

If that's the case, hormone shots may be able to improve his condition. 3483283]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZDRCCREK6IRIAAWL6LA3LSFMEBETUZKKIDF3GZHK5FRKARLAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/448/FCE/448FCEE7E11613FB5621E2BB5521AC1B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ World's biggest baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ World's largest baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fat babies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cute babies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Prader-Willi syndrome]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/these-forest-critter-x-mas-cards-were-too-hot-for-facebook-3484250</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[These forest critter X-mas cards were too hot for Facebook 3484250]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JEDBURG, SCOTLAND — Cool, yet very normal, Christmas cards featuring a squirrel, robin and a stag were outlawed by Facebook last month.

Scottish designer Jackie Charley says Zuck's social media platform deemed them to be inappropriate. Facebook later apologized for the error and approved her post after becoming aware of the gaffe.

But rather than stifle Charley's business, it seems like she's going to be in for an extra busy festive period as news of the story has gone viral. 3484250]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6LRACCWA2KRGBA9BADR7KBGMBKSKSZQKSIA3FICK6NA3BIBKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/971/CB1/971CB1C65A5F01700C9C019785BCA313.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas cards]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ edgy christmas cards]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal christmas cards facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jackie charley]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mark zuckerberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ true social media stories]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/australia-says-yes-to-marriage-equality-kinda--3484245</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Australia says yes to marriage equality. Kinda. 3484245]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE LAND DOWN UNDER — Australia voted yes in a postal survey asking if the country should legalize same sex marriage. 

Over 60% of Aussies voted for marriage equality, with all states and territories saying g'day to the motion.

The result is non-binding, meaning the government isn't required to act on it.

Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull calling the result a vote for fairness, but the no side reckons the opposite. 3484245]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJFXAIBAMHAVVKAL5DFZKLRGNJVZET5LWLWTGABAFPAKWZBAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1BA/C3F/1BAC3FC38BEC92BAE721CF86A9B9CB5C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>38</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ australia marriage vote]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ australia says yes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aussie marriage vote]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malcolm turnbull]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ australian postal vote]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/4-killed-after-gunman-goes-on-violent-rampage-in-california-3484160</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[4 killed after gunman goes on violent rampage in California 3484160]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RANCHO TEHAMA, CALIFORNIA — Four are dead and many more injured after a man went on a murderous rampage through a rural Northern California town.

The Los Angeles Times reports that just before 8 a.m. on Tuesday, a gunman shot and killed a man and a female neighbor near his home in Rancho Tehama, before fleeing in a stolen truck.

The suspect went on a shooting spree through the community, opening fire at several locations, including an elementary school.

He carjacked another vehicle and went around firing shots at random, even shooting at a mother who was driving her son to school. All in all, the shooter killed 4 people and injured at least 10.

Local police eventually caught up to the suspect and shot him dead during an exchange of gunfire. He was found with a semiautomatic rifle and two handguns.

The gunman was later identified to be 43-year-old Kevin Neal, a local resident. No motive has been declared for the violent spree, but authorities believe the man may have been set off by a dispute with his neighbors. 3484160]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAWECTSKADRCA3CB5DFR6D3GZEBXFZKKEBWXT3WK2NFAAKUAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1E3/4FB/1E34FBB19B94639EF03E4A64A8BDA3DA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ california shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elementary school shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rancho tehama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rancho tehama shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rancho tehama reserve]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ school shooting]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bill-gates-firm-planning-smart-city-in-arizona-3483941</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bill Gates firm planning smart city in Arizona 3483941]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ARIZONA — A real estate investment firm owned by Bill Gates has invested in a project to build a smart city in the Arizona desert.

Gates' Cascade Investment LLC paid around $80 million for a large stake in a 24,800 acre development called Belmont, according to the Arizona Republic.

The area is around 50 miles west of Phoenix in an area called West Valley. 

Belmont will create a forward-thinking community with a communication and infrastructure spine that embraces cutting-edge technology, designed around high-speed digital networks, data centers, new manufacturing technologies and distribution models, autonomous vehicles and autonomous logistics hubs, Belmont Partners, the Arizona real estate investment firm involved in the project, said in a news release.   

The city will have 3,800 acres for office, commercial and retail space as well as 470 acres for public schools. Belmont will also have 80,000 residential homes.

One of the reasons Belmont was chosen is its location next to the proposed Interstate 11 freeway, which has yet to receive funding. If completed, Interstate 11 would run from Reno, Nevada to Mexico, the Arizona Republic reported. 3483941]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDWAAIGKZCRVBZ7LWJAV6DSNADSZR34LVAWXUCTKBNAACICAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F4F/4FB/F4F4FBD5F3E72E139A386D8116FC5E28.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bill Gates smart city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smart city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Belmont Arizona]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Belmont smart city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bill gates real estate firm]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/white-guy-identifies-as-filipino-claims-he-s-transracial-3483928</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[White guy identifies as Filipino, claims he's transracial 3483928]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAMPA, FLORIDA — In yet another instance of nonsense, a Caucasian man from Florida came out as Filipino after insisting he's 'transracial'.

WTSP reports that the term used to refer to the adoption of a child that's of a different race than the adoptive parents, but is now being brandished about by people who identify with another race or ethnicity.

Ja Du, whose birth name is Adam, claims being around the music and the food, and watching History Channel shows about the Philippines made him feel Filipino.

But inhaling factoids about the country and being able to scarf down balut and sweet spaghetti doesn't mean anything, except that you're a fan.

And not a very good one, because the tuk tuk you ride around in is not actually from the Philippines — it's from Thailand. So consider your application to be Filipino denied.

That might be one down, but there's a whole Facebook page of white people who are appropriating some other culture in the name of self-identification.

One licensed psychologist says people shouldn't take offense because it's harmless, and more or less equated identifying with a race to choosing a religion.

The thing is: unless a black dude can get a cop to back off by claiming he identifies as white, this nonsense is not gonna fly. 3483928]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSIFEDRGAEDRKAIRBVDWRK2CMRAB7FC2AFPWTUZAAEHRGCAFBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/248/1E5/2481E5A44D7F5B8A8E03DF9E5CCE24A2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Filipino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ transracial]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Philippines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cultural appropriation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ transracialism]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ja Du]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Filipino culture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tuk tuk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tampa transracial man]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/emirates-unveils-ultra-high-class-cabins-for-new-777s-3483922</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Emirates unveils ultra high class cabins for new 777s 3483922]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES — If you feel like showing everyone how rich you are, Emirates airline has just introduced new Mercedes-Benz S-Class-inspired first class private suites for its Boeing 777 aircraft.

The new first class suites will offer up to 40 square feet of space per passenger and floor-to-ceiling sliding doors. 

Passengers will be spoiled with a 32-inch high-definition screen, inflight gourmet dining, while mood lighting and temperature can be adjusted at a touch of a button. 

The leather seats can recline all the way, be placed in a 'zero-gravity' position, or adjusted into plenty of other custom positions for optimal comfort. 

Most suites with a window view will be provided with binoculars while suites in the middle of the cabin have virtual windows which project view from outside in real-time.

As part of  Emirates' first-ever collaboration with another luxury brand, first class passengers will be offered a complimentary chauffeur transfer service in a Mercedes-Benz S-class car to their destination from the airport.

The newly designed cabins are set to be introduced into commercial service on Emirates' Boeing 777 fleet in December. 3483922]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5ARADTWKBKRKBCCLFIWZ7LUGJKSZERNKJJRTUZFBREFEXTSKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DCD/9D2/DCD9D2D13E5B451352D42C42E5B284EB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emirates]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emirates airline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aviation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boeing 777]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new cabins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dubai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dubai airshow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united arab emirates]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/autonomous-space-plane-nails-3-810m-drop-test-3483749</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Autonomous space plane nails 3,810m drop test 3483749]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOJAVE DESERT, CALIFORNIA —The autonomous Dream Chaser space plane completed a free-flight drop test from a height of 3,810m over California on Saturday.

The plane can carry 7 passengers, reports Space.com, and looks like a smaller version of current NASA shuttles. 

When complete, it will use Atlas rockets to fly 6 delivery missions to the International Space Station by 2024.

The test on Saturday examined the plane during the final approach and landing phase of flight. 3483749]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIFAYAIAECWPAZ7LMAA36JGG2KBXFK4AFLRXHRCAJMWAVREBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CCE/B4E/CCEB4ECD15214BC794103E48A95D4C90.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>99</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drop test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ autonomous space plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dreamchaser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iss]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space station delivery]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dallas-prosecutor-fired-over-drunken-uber-meltdown-3485180</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dallas prosecutor fired over drunken Uber meltdown 3485180]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DALLAS — A foul-mouthed prosecutor has been sacked from the Dallas District Attorney's Office after a recording of her lashing out at an Uber driver went public.

According to the Dallas Morning News, Jody Warner hopped into an Uber outside the Capitol Pub in east Dallas Friday night.

The driver, Shaun Platt, was following a route on the GPS when Warner insisted that he take a different road. But when Platt complied and asked which way to go next, Warner got angry and lashed out. She declared she was an assistant DA and refused to leave the car, prompting Platt to call the cops and start recording her meltdown.

In the recording, Warner can be heard calling the driver names and explicitly says she hopes the cops come soon so they can f*ck him up. She also accuses him of kidnapping her, despite the driver repeatedly asking her to get out of his car. 

It wasn't until an officer showed up that Warner finally exited the vehicle — though not before stating, again, that she was a prosecutor. Despite feeling intimidated, Platt declined to press charges and drove away.

Instead, he sent the recording to the media, and boy, did karma come swiftly. By Monday, Warner was assistant DA no more.

On Tuesday, the now-sober 32-year-old gave a half-assed public 'apology', turning on the waterworks and throwing Platt under the bus by insinuating he might have been up to no good. Word of advice, lady: say sorry and mean it, or just shut up. 3485180]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNKRCDABASLRAAKCLECWZKJCNECSKF32LVCAZTACBSPWPBK4AF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/51A/810/51A8103668AD26EFDA47904A163C009F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>123</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber driver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber tirade]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber passenger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber meltdown]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ texas prosecutor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dallas district attorney]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jody warner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shaun platt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fired dallas prosecutor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ karma]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cards-against-humanity-bought-land-to-obstruct-trump-wall-3484996</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cards Against Humanity bought land to obstruct Trump wall 3484996]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — Cards Against Humanity announced that it has purchased land on the U.S. - Mexico border to obstruct Trump from building his border wall. 

The Chicago card came company said on its website it was part of a holiday promotion whereby you give them $15 bucks and get six surprise gifts that will help save America. 
We've purchased a plot of vacant land on the border and retained a law firm specializing in eminent domain to make it as time-consuming and expensive as possible for the wall to get built. 
It was sold out on Wednesday morning only after a few hours after launching the program.  
 
Cards Against Humanity says it's trying to save America from injustice, lies, racism, the whole enchilada. Come on...do we really need to be saved from Mexican food? 

The company hasn't said where the plot is located, but their entertaining YouTube video shows wild horses galloping across the open prairie. 3484996]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IAAY3WAFLFGDA9KFLFT9LTMWJVTSTZA6IFPTZFA6QFPCAKKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8A3/889/8A3889459AE4B8B54C2014B847F463FC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump border wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border wall prototypes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cards Against Humanity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-boom-supersonic-airliner-to-take-off-by-2023-3484729</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New Boom Supersonic airliner to take off by 2023 3484729]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DENVER — A new airliner that boasts supersonic speeds is set to revolutionize air travel once it takes flight in 2023.

BBC reports that Boom Technology's planned supersonic aircraft will have a cruise speed of 1,451 miles per hour, 2.6 times faster than any other airliner.

While a flight from New York to London would typically take 7 hours on a commercial flight, the trip would take a little over three hours on a supersonic airliner.

The Mach 2.2 aircraft will have 55 seats, each priced at about $5,000 for a roundtrip ticket.

A one-third-scale prototype called the XB-1 will begin test flights in 2018 to demonstrate and refine the key technologies required for supersonic travel.

Unlike the now retired Concorde and its notoriously loud sonic boom, the Boom aircraft will have turbofans for noise reduction, and won't be much louder than a normal plane. 

The company does have some hurdles to face before their project comes to fruition. Supersonic flights are still banned in the U.S., but with federal laws currently up for renegotiation, that could soon change. 3484729]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLRCDZBA2LRGXR7BNJFT9UTGWLVTU3SKVDFZGKTKEGAEVRFLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8ED/E5A/8EDE5A967004AD0261D68F54A06A2D8B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boom supersonic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supersonic plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supersonic airliner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supersonic flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boom technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ concorde]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supersonic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ business class]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/survey-finds-people-binge-watch-netflix-shows-in-public-3484677</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Survey finds people binge-watch Netflix shows in public 3484677]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WORLD OF NETFLIX — Ever watched Netflix in public? If so, then you are part of the 67% of annoying Netflix users worldwide who shamelessly watch shows and movies in public even if it means exposing others to spoilers.

Based on a survey done by Netflix, most popular places to watch Netflix outside the home are on buses, planes, and the commute. 

The survey also revealed that 26% of its users said watch shows or movies while at work. While about 7% worldwide — said they have watched movies and shows in public restrooms, guess binge-watch can be done really anywhere and anytime. And 45% of people watching Netflix outside their homes have caught someone sneakily watching along with them.

Other findings from the survey include that, 20% of people admitted to crying while watching Netflix in public.

About 17% of users say they have missed their stop while commuting because they were too focused on a movie or TV show, well, it's your own fault for missing that bus. Also, 11% say they have had a TV show or movie spoiled by someone watching it in public. And 27% of people say a stranger has interrupted their Netflix viewing to talk about what they're watching. 

While many have confessed about their Netflixing activities in the public, 18% of users actually admit they are embarrassed about Netflixing in public.

The company has released interesting yet oddly specific surveys in the past, such as cheating on your partner by watching shows without them, or it is unlikely to see a German bawling while watching videos. 3484677]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIBWIDZIKIBAGXZUKBIWTKDSG2KE5FINKFKWVTICKWPRPBZHAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3AB/1D7/3AB1D77FFB1167742F128ADE37D0562E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>97</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Netflix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix users]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix movies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix series]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflixing in public]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix survey]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/denver-getting-super-urban-traffic-tube-system-3484674</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Denver getting 'super urban' traffic-tube system 3484674]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DENVER — Traffic in Colorado's capital city could get much faster in the next half-decade.

Headed by tech firm Arrivo, the Denver high-speed traffic tube project will first build a test track following the city's E-470 toll road, reported The Verge.

The system will see a variety of vehicles, both passenger and cargo, using the system. According to the company website, the technology uses a combination of magnetic levitation and electrics to propel cars at speeds of up to 200 miles per hour

If successful, Arrivo could potentially expand it to connect with current Denver's transportation infrastructure. 3484674]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLAAXTUA6LFMCKCKFKRRL4VMAASXR3SAJKFMFCWAEFWKVAEKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C8F/C75/C8FC753A59C1ACBF95FF5C089F32AC0E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ denver hyperloop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ denver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arrivo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super urban network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ traffic tube]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colorado]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brogan bambrogan]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/keystone-pipeline-spills-210-000-gallons-of-oil-in-south-dakota-3485705</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Keystone Pipeline spills 210,000 gallons of oil in South Dakota 3485705]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMHERST, SOUTH DAKOTA — The Keystone Pipeline leaked 210,000 gallons, or 5,000 barrels, of oil Thursday in Marshall County, South Dakota near Amherst.

Officials are currently investigating the cause of the leak, CNN reported. 
TransCanada, the company that owns the pipeline, said it detected a drop in pressure around 6 a.m. on Thursday morning and shut down the pipeline. 
The pipeline runs from Hardesty, Alberta to Cushing, Oklahoma and Wood River/Pakota, Illinois. 

The company said in a statement, the section of pipe along a right-of-way approximately 35 miles (56 km) south of the Ludden pump station in Marshall County, South Dakota was 
completely isolated within 15 minutes and emergency procedures were activated. 

TransCanada said it received permission from the landowner to investigate the spill and plan cleanup, the Washington Post reported. 

This would be the largest Keystone oil spill to date in South Dakota, said state spokesman for the Department of Environment and Natural Resources Brian Walsh, CNN reported. 3485705]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLWPXZCAEBFMVRYLIDRZ74UMJIB5F39A2JWTTZDAEAAGD3UAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/080/F52/080F52D73DE778D6F5343987A6F2016B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Keystone Pipeline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Keystone Pipeline leak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Keystone Pipeline spill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oil spill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TransCanada oil spill]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/airline-passenger-shamed-after-photo-of-rude-behavior-goes-viral-3485475</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Airline passenger shamed after photo of rude behavior goes viral 3485475]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKY — An airline passenger has recently been harshly shamed on Reddit and Instagram after a photo showing a pile of trash in the middle of the aisle right next to his seat. 

No one knows what happened prior to the incident, but the guy was seen reading a book looking unbothered with remains of a half-eaten airline dinner and trash beside him.

While the passenger may have not been bothered by the mess, internet users certainly were.  

A Reddit user who claims to be a flight attendant said it's uncertain if contents on the floor were the doing of this particular passenger, but they have seen passengers do this before and it's infuriating!

Since the photo was posted on social media, it has gotten over 34,000 upvotes on Reddit and nearly 5,000 likes on Instagram, more than 3,000 comments have been made between both platforms. 

Unfortunately, the witch hunt will not do much since the identity of the passenger and name of the airline remain unknown. 3485475]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDFMY3XKABWEAIVL6JF5L4RGEAV5UT5ABJAVG3SKAHRMVRHAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EE3/2F4/EE32F4510C0FBB0907246BEAD6C8EF0B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rude passenger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline passenger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rude passenger on plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral photo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral content]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reddit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/swedish-firm-specializes-in-3d-printing-body-parts-3485452</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Swedish firm specializes in 3D printing body parts 3485452]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GOTHENBURG, SWEDEN — Swedish startup firm Cellink specializes in low-cost and accessible 3D bioprinting. 

The company was founded in 2016 by Erik Gatenholm and Hector Martinez. It has already developed several 3D bioprinters as well as bioprinting materials (bioinks), according to 3ders.org. 

Cellink is currently focused on growing cartilage and skin cells for drug and cosmetics testing, BBC reported. 

The company also makes bioink, the liquid that human cells are mixed with, then 3D printed. Cellink makes its ink from cellulose from Swedish forests and alginate formed from Norwegian Sea seaweed, according to BBC. 

Cellink bioinks run between $9 to $299, while the printers cost between $10,000 and $39,000. 

Health experts believe that in 10 to 20 years, bioprinting could be used to make fully functioning organs for transplant. 3485452]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARCFMAKXKIBRZDZXLFLWT7JCNEDSKURLAZCFVGAHAVERKW3XKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/602/38B/60238BB6F46A9EFDB6083F1A66CA90C6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D printing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D body part printing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D bioprinting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cellink]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D printing organ transplants]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-a-video-of-donald-trump-jr-at-the-gym-deadlifting-like-a-boss-3485435</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's a video of Donald Trump, Jr. at the gym deadlifting like a boss 3485435]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — Donald Trump, Jr. posted a video of himself dangerously shoe-less while hitting a personal deadlift record of 375 lbs. By his own admittance, his form was terrible, but he still felt good enough about it to let loose a victorious fist pump at the end. The woman standing in the back of the gym didn't seem too impressed, though. 3485435]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZDRCACVKFKA3ACFL6PAI6D3MWKVTS34K6JR5HZCBRFWCWTSKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/968/006/96800688A13F5D9DB52701B566DB6669.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>308</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Donald Trump Jr]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Donald Trump junior]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deadlifting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gym]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weightlifting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fitness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crossfit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad form]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/newly-discovered-exoplanet-could-support-life-3485415</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Newly discovered exoplanet could support life 3485415]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — Scientists using the European Southern Observatory's planet-hunting HARPS instrument have discovered a new exoplanet just 11 light-years from our solar system.

Ross 128 b is roughly the same size as Earth and is believed to share a similar surface temperature, according to a press release from ESO.

The exoplanet's host star is Ross 128, a red dwarf that is smaller and cooler than our Sun. It's 20 times closer to its star than Earth is to the sun, and completes an orbit in just 9.9 days.

Red dwarf stars such as the Proxima Centauri are unstable and often subject their planets to flares and deadly UV radiation. But Ross 128 is a much quieter star, which means its exoplanets may be a more comfortable place to host life.

Scientists are unsure if Ross 128 b is in fact habitable, but agree that it is a good candidate for study. ESO's Extremely Large Telescope is set to look for biomarkers such as oxygen in the exoplanet's atmosphere by 2025. 3485415]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMDFECIJKADRIATCLFJFZ9SBMSKBKF34KBIAXURLKJMWIBCRAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/155/2CC/1552CC4FBC004FE3981E39C2E1F62B8D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ross 128]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ross 128 b]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exoplanet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new planet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth like planet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ temperate planet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ proxima centauri]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ proxima b]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life outside earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ESO]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ELT]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extremely large telescope]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-teen-killed-by-driver-blowing-into-car-breathalyzer-3487872</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Texas teen killed by driver blowing into car breathalyzer 3487872]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ARLINGTON, TEXAS — An 18-year-old cheerleader has died after a distracted driver crashed into her car in Arlington, Texas.

NBC DFW reports that Alexis Butler was backing out of a friend's driveway on November 10 when a pickup truck smashed into the passenger side of her Toyota Camry.

The impact pushed the car onto a nearby grassy area and injured Butler, who died in the hospital a week later. The pickup hit a fence and a light pole, but the driver was not injured.

He admitted he was looking down at the time of the crash, and was doing a breathalyzer test on a court-ordered ignition interlock device.

The anti-DWI device measures drivers' Blood-Alcohol Concentration, and only allows a vehicle to start if they pass the test.

Drivers do need to do retests at periodic times throughout the ride, but while everyone else pulls over, the 31-year-old oddly chose to do it while his car was still moving.

Police say the man wasn't intoxicated during the crash, and has yet to be charged with anything. 3487872]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMDAGYKSK2KWMA3EBRBAK9U4GFLSRRCRLVARVHAGAEHACYKSKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AD7/90C/AD790C07858B8434E1C2EC238730927E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DWI]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DUI]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ignition interlock device]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ignition interlock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad driver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupid driver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ breathalyzer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car breathalyzer]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/interstellar-message-sent-to-nearby-exoplanet-3487585</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Interstellar message sent to nearby exoplanet 3487585]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — Scientists and artists beamed a message to the GJ 273 system last month to see if any aliens are listening. The message will only take about a dozen years to arrive.
 
GJ 273 is a red dwarf also called Luyten's star and is a nearby 12.36 light-years from our own Mother Earth. 

Luyten's star hosts two known planets, one of which, GJ 273b, might be able to support life, according to Space.com.

The radio signal included music and math lessons from us to them and was designed for aliens to respond. 
Some critics like Stephen Hawking worry that actively trying to contact E.T. could alert advanced hostile or resource-seeking aliens, which could have dire consequences for our planet. 
Don't worry, we'll destroy ourselves first before any dirty alien will get a chance too. 
But on the bright side, if in 25 years we hear an actual response, wouldn't that be something. 3487585]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLWAXRJA5DFCVKFLZAAVK4YGWIB5RT7A6KF7GTXANNREAIQAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/71B/435/71B435F758A7E2266F986F77A878939B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extra terrestrials]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ET]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interstellar message]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GJ 273 system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Luyten's star]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien message]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/search-for-missing-argentine-naval-sub-hampered-by-bad-weather-3487565</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Search for missing Argentine naval sub hampered by bad weather 3487565]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ARGENTINA — The search for an Argentine naval submarine that went missing with 44 crew members is being hampered by bad weather, officials said. 

The ARA San Juan submarine was returning on a routine mission from the Tierra del Fuego archipelago to its home base in Mar del Plata, CNN reported. 

The San Juan was originally scheduled to arrive at port on Sunday. It was last spotted Wednesday in the San Jorge Gulf.   

Seven failed satellite calls were detected on Saturday morning, however, the Argentine defense ministry said it could not confirm the attempts came from the ARA San Juan, the Guardian reported.

The San Juan is a 65-meter-long TR-1700 submarine, powered by four diesel and one electric engine, the Argentine military said, according to CNN. 

The Argentine navy says the missing sub has enough oxygen, food and water to last for at least two weeks, the BBC reported. 3487565]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKWICZDAVBAADZ7BJKA374TGVAV5S35LVCFMUAHAMFWCVZHAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/250/EAE/250EAEA7AC5A5C18EED111503D606F9C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Argentine submarine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Argentine submarine missing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ARA San Juan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ARA San Juan missing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missing submarine]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/loads-of-parasites-found-inside-north-korean-defector-s-stomach-3487551</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Loads of parasites found inside North Korean defector's stomach 3487551]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL — Medical staff treating a wounded North Korean defector found numerous parasites inside his body, revealing a picture of poor health that may be commonplace in the north. 

The North Korean border guard was shot several times while fleeing across the demilitarized zone to South Korea last week.

According to  Reuters, surgeons treating the defector found several parasites inside his body. Several of these were removed from his digestive tract, including one 27 cm long roundworm.

That is likely due to farming practices in the north where human excrement is used as fertilizer due to a lack of chemical fertilizer. Known as night soil, this practise is notorious for spreading parasites and disease. 3487551]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJAACIBAJLAEWCCL6KW592GMMDBIFK4LWPRXHADBVEAPBABKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1FF/2E4/1FF2E481A8BB5ACA23D10D1D1C220263.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ defector]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korean health]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mom-who-posed-with-bees-for-maternity-shoot-suffers-stillbirth-3487373</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mom who posed with bees for maternity shoot suffers stillbirth 3487373]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AKRON, OHIO — An Ohio woman who went viral for her unique maternity shoot has suffered a heartbreaking tragedy.

Last August, beekeeper Emily Mueller celebrated her pregnancy by posing with 20,000 live bees on her baby bump.

But according to a recent Facebook page, the mom of three realized days before her due date that her baby had not been moving around. Her contractions also felt strange and different.

Feeling uneasy, Mueller and her husband went to the hospital, where an ultrasound revealed that the baby had no heartbeat and had passed on.

Mueller delivered her stillborn son the next day, naming him Emersyn Jacob.

She decided to send the placenta for testing to hopefully find out what went wrong, but strongly suspects that the baby died from a blood clotting issue that has previously caused miscarriages in her family.

A small device called a Cuddle Cot allowed the Muellers to spend more time with their little beekeeper before finally saying goodbye. 3487373]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASKAMXCXASIFGAZTBJLAT6BHGIBB5R3RKIAFZTCWKBNWCVABAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/66F/67E/66F67E02F7A06499ED6C39100733DC41.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee mom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee maternity shoot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee photo shoot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stillborn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stillbirth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emily mueller]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bees]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/drake-stops-gig-to-threaten-dude-who-was-groping-female-fans-3487349</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Drake stops gig to threaten dude who was groping female fans 3487349]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA — Canadian rapper Drake is dominating the headlines after publicly calling out a pervert in the middle of a show.

The Sydney Morning Herald reports that while the superstar was belting out his hits at a Sydney nightclub, a handsy concertgoer near the front row was sneakin' on the females in the crowd.

When Drake spotted the groping, he put the gig and pause and immediately took the guy to task. He warned the gropey fan to stop touching women, threatening to personally deal with him if he keeps it up.

Security eventually kicked the perp out, thank god.

The internet has since given Drake a collective whoop and cannot seem to stop singing the singer's praises. And rightly so.

With all the perverts coming out of the showbiz woodwork lately, it's nice to see at least one star still has his female fans' backs. 3487349]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNFECTTBICACBTFKADRV9BFNEBVREANLSPF3HZFAMARCBTSAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FB4/591/FB4591A1EDFEAC9EABF2218FB009D645.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drake concert]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rapper]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ handsy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drake stops concert]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drake threatens fan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drake fans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sydney]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marquee nightclub]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marquee]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/confused-twitter-users-think-singer-marilyn-manson-is-dead-3488606</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Confused Twitter users think singer Marilyn Manson is dead 3488606]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BAKERSFIELD, CALIFORNIA — Confused Twitter users are paying tribute to a murderous cult leader after mistaking him for singer Marilyn Manson.

CNN reports that 83-year-old serial killer Charles Manson died of natural causes on November 18 and finally met his maker.

Manson and his Manson Family crew terrorized L.A. in the 60s, orchestrating a series of gruesome killings that included the infamous murder of actress Sharon Tate and her unborn child.

Most people celebrated the passing of a heinous figure, naturally. But when RIP Charles Manson began trending on Twitter, everyone was baffled.

It soon became clear that except for the select few who were actually mourning the serial killer, most people had genuinely confused Charles Manson for shock-rock singer Marilyn, who uses the same last name.

The 48-year-old singer, who is Brian Warner in real life, formed his stage name by combining the names of Marilyn Monroe and Charles Manson. He hasn't responded to the mix-up, except to tweet a link to his cover of Charles Manson's 'Sick City.'  So yeah, definitely still alive and kicking. 3488606]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLFVXAGAEEWTCI9L2IA5K4TGNKSXUT5LRAWRGTYKEFFTDZAKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/302/703/30270367B4A8D4A06B7ABF54509D3EBC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ charles manson]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marilyn manson]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RIP charles manson]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ manson family]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ charles manson dead]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marilyn manson dead]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mistaken identity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/why-is-everyone-hating-on-the-justice-league-it-s-pretty-good--3488348</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Why is everyone hating on the Justice League? It's pretty good. 3488348]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GOTHAM CITY/METROPOLIS — DC's the Justice League, hit theaters last week, but only pulled in $281.5 million worldwide. 

The movie cost $300 mill to make and reportedly even more to market. So, it's got a ways to go before it'll be a financial success. Meaning, not even all the money in the Bat Cave could save this from bombing At least in the eyes of critics — but what do they know? 

Five-pronged tridents and Henry Cavill's fake CGI upper lip aside, the movie itself is actually a pretty good time. 3488348]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRCFGXZGKMAFVCARB6LR76DXGRBBVFK6KBPFTTKXK6PFXARCBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AD2/B8D/AD2B8D21ABC739AE35B460025419E727.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[justice league]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[justice league box office]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[justice league fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[batman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[superman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wonder woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[cyborg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[aquaman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[flash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ben affleck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[henry cavill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[justice league cartoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[justice league fail]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/earthquakes-may-triple-next-year-researchers-warn-3488321</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Earthquakes may triple next year, researchers warn 3488321]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INDIANAPOLIS — The number of intense earthquakes may increase in 2018, according to new research.

The prediction warns that as the Earth's rotation slows, the amount of earthquakes increase.

Researchers say the planet is currently in the fourth year of these five-year periodical slowdowns. They warn this could see a threefold increase in earthquakes next year, from 6 in 2017 to 20 in 2018. 

Next year we should see a significant increase in numbers of severe earthquakes, said University of Colorado researcher Dr. Roger Bilham. So far we have only had about six severe earthquakes. We could easily have 20 a year starting in 2018.

Bilham, along with Rebecca Bendick from the University of Montana, studied earthquakes of magnitude 7 and higher since 1900 and found five instances of seismic increases. Most of the greater earthquakes occurred near the equator.

Scientists suspect this maybe because of small changes in the Earth's core, but exactly why earthquakes would respond to a slowing Earth is unknown.

New Zealand seismology experts at the University of Otago said they don't support the findings, and that the research shouldn't inspire panic. They called it another example of a fortuitous correlation between earthquake occurrence and an unrelated phenomenon. 3488321]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JFCAKVAVBAAYRSBBKFX9DVGWKETET4A6IAVTIAAZERTCRFAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/467/AE9/467AE9A1388ACE1A75E21F99CFAEC311.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ major earthquakes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earthquake frequency increase]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seismology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ equator earthquakes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mega earthquake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earthquake 2018]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-filmed-with-head-trapped-between-road-barriers-3488216</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman filmed with head trapped between road barriers 3488216]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ZHEJIANG, CHINA — A woman in China was recently caught on video attempting to climb over the fence in the middle of a busy traffic in Zhejiang, China, but somehow managed to trap her own head between the bars of the road barriers. 

The incident happened on November 17, with the unknown woman being filmed by CCTV trying to climb over the fence, China's viral news platform the Paper reported. 

Fortunately, passersby contacted emergency services. It took the rescuers about five minutes to free her from the bars. 3488216]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DWGYCWKAAF3CTFBADWT7DVGIEBREC3A2PFMURAAIAF5BKYAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5BE/779/5BE779F22662274E09D095A47174D8CB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climbing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climbing fails 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climbing fence fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupid chinese videos]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/couple-finds-dead-frog-in-waffle-house-water-glass-3488190</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Couple finds dead frog in Waffle House water glass 3488190]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TALLAHASSEE, FLORIDA — A Florida couple has sworn off Waffle House entirely after finding a slimy green surprise in their drink.

WCTV reports that Claire Sheats and her husband were sipping on iced waters while waiting for their food when they noticed something ominous floating in one of the glasses.

The couple realized with disgust that a small dead frog was bobbing about in the water, and quickly called the waitress, who was equally shocked and disgusted.

With their appetite gone, the couple left and later filed a complained with both the Waffle House corporate office and the state health department.

Health inspectors took a closer look at the diner days later and found 11 violations, though none are considered an immediate threat to the public.

Oddly enough, there was no mention of any frogs in the state health report, even though Waffle House claims it's investigating the incident.

As to where that frog came from, your guess is as good as ours. 3488190]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNFIDIHBVDRZCKALRAF574XMMDVXR36AABWMH3RABPW5AIBKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/852/566/85256652819431F9698C5A8F070ED234.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>89</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frog in water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contaminated food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dead frog in water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dead frog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ waffle house]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ waffle house frog]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ex-footballer-jailed-in-china-where-are-trump-and-us-media--3488160</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ex-footballer jailed in China, where are Trump and US media? 3488160]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA — Former college football star Wendell Brown has spent the last 14 months in a Chinese jail for a bar fight where authorities claim he hit a man, Yahoo Sports reported. 
On Sept. 24, 2016, Brown was at a birthday party when some other Chinese men not with his group wanted to drink with him. He declined, they got butthurt and a fight broke out.  

Brown was later arrested for hitting a man, a claim he denies. He said he only raised his arms to block glass bottles being thrown at him. 

Of course Brown was taken to the Chongqing Jiangbei jail anyways, where he has been since.

A court appearance in July saw the State's evidence against him fall apart, but with Chinese prosecutors maintaining a 99.2% conviction rate, chances are slim Brown will get off. He's facing a three to 10 year sentence.    

His family have tried to hire a lawyer, but legal costs are skyrocketing and China's completely corrupt legal system doesn't help. 
The 3 UCLA players that were dumb enough to steal from high end stores and get caught had UCLA, Trump and U.S. media in their corner. 
Where are Trump and the massive media exposure now? 3488160]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DFVCCWKEERTYI7BWKW7KLTNEBB3RT2KMDRVTZFK5GARBTWAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/77B/FAA/77BFAA3C285BF5D29D45218B2781B95B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UCLA players China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wendell Brown football]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wendell Brown China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wendell Brown arrested China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wendell Brown Ball State]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wendell Brown arrested]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uber-paid-hackers-to-hide-2016-data-breach-affecting-57-million-3489270</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Uber paid hackers to hide 2016 data breach affecting 57 million 3489270]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Personal information of millions of Uber customers and drivers were stolen by hackers in 2016, in a breach that the company has kept secret for more than a year.

Bloomberg reports that In October 2016, two hackers gained access to a third-party cloud-based service used by Uber, and obtained information on 57 million of its users.

Compromised data from the attack included names, email addresses, phone numbers, as well as license numbers of around 600,000 U.S. drivers.

The company claims users' bank and credit card information, social security numbers, trip location history and dates of birth were not accessed.

The hackers reportedly emailed Uber asking for money, and were paid $100,000 to delete the stolen files and keep quiet about the breach.

News of the hack was not disclosed to either its users or any government agencies, despite a number of state and federal laws requiring the company to do so.

Uber's chief security officer and a senior lawyer have been sacked for their shady handling of the hack. The New York State Attorney General has also opened an investigation into the incident, according to USA Today. 3489270]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKAMDKSASLAAWCELNKRK9LRNFKBXUTSKMDF5UALK5HFZATXAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CAE/E89/CAEE894B6821A1CD60D83AEFB01E7A80.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data breach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber hacked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hackers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2016 uber hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ransom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ personal data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ personal information]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stolen data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber scandal]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-donald-trump-and-lavar-ball-soap-opera-continues-3489130</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The Donald Trump and LaVar Ball soap opera continues 3489130]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — The stupendously silly stupid sunglasses shoplifting spectacle which saw three UCLA players held in China just won't go away — Thank God.

To recap, three Bruins ball players — LiAngelo Ball, Cody Riley and Jalen Hill — got busted thieving sunglasses from a bougie store in China.

The trio were facing three to 10 year sentences, but were eventually allowed to return to the U.S.

The story goes that Trump, while on his Asia mega-tour, also happened to be in the country during the sunglasses soap opera. 

Donald put a call into Xi Jinping, which Trump claims is the reason the three were freed. 
Enter father LaVar Ball. On an ESPN interview, Ball was sceptical of Trump's China influence — rightly so.  

Trump took to Twitter tweeting two typical tantrums calling LaVar out and saying he should have left the UCLA players in China. 

Let's be real folks, Trump has about as much pull in China as American has skinny people. 
A more likely explanation is that UCLA wanted this to go away just like China. Why? The thousands of out-of-state tuition paying international Chinese students enrolled. 3489130]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDWCXRHK5AWPBZULSJA3943GNIBVRCSAJPRTFKSAAEF3AAFAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6F5/243/6F524343D57EC576608C7EFB3EAE89D7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump v LaVar Ball]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LaVar Ball]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UCLA players China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LiAngelo Ball China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UCLA players China sunglasses]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/app-faces-controversy-for-makeup-removal-feature-3489003</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[App faces controversy for makeup-removal feature 3489003]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INTERNET — Makeapp, a photo editing app, allows you to remove the makeup on the person in an image to reveal what they really look like. However, the app has been getting attention online for all the wrong reasons.

While most photo apps are designed to make you look better than you really are, Makeapp does the opposite —  by removing your makeup, and presumably making you look worse by revealing you barefaced. 

Folks online believe the app's feature is being misogynistic and will lower women's self esteem and make them more insecure. A writer from Slate took a dig at the app's founder Ashot[a] Gabrelyanov[b] by editing his photo with the makeup removal function.

In defense of his app, Gabrelyanov told Buzzfeed that he did not intend to hurt women with the app, and said the media only focused on the makeup removal function by describing it as a bunch of 'tech bros' trying to hurt women. 3489003]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIWMDIJAEDAAWZXLMDW5KDVNEEETRZMKJJA5TIBAMERXBZCAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/22E/8B5/22E8B57BC5B3F13FDF0C923EAF979775.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photo editing app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photo app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ makeapp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ashot gabrelyanov]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sexism]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ women]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ makeup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ no makeup makeup look]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ misogyny]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fired-uber-exec-starts-ai-worshipping-robo-religion-3488925</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fired Uber exec starts AI-worshipping robo-religion 3488925]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SILICON VALLEY (WHERE ELSE?) — Ex-Google and ex-Uber engineer Anthony Levandowski has decided to preempt the AI apocalypse by forming a robot religion called the Way of the Future.

According to Wired, papers filed with IRS in May put Levandowski as the dean and CEO of the non-profit religion.

Levandowski's robo-religion has a gospel, reportedly dubbed The Manual. They'll worship the godhead, an advanced AI they predict will evolve to hold god-like intelligence. 3488925]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNWEDKUBMBAAACEBJIRK7DWM2IE5SK3K6PR5UABAJPR7DRAKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C02/E27/C02E270CA5A341C1C5FA231CA604550D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ way of the future]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Anthony levandowski]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-alexa-throws-party-for-itself-while-homeowner-is-away-3488918</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon Alexa throws party for itself while homeowner is away 3488918]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HAMBURG, GERMANY — Amazon's AI assistant makes life easier for most people, except maybe this guy, whose Alexa decided to cause trouble while he was out.

According to the Telegraph, Hamburg resident Oliver Haberstroh claims his Amazon Echo played loud, obnoxious music between 1 and 3 in the morning, completely on its own, and without any prompt from him.

The deafening noise woke up the neighbors, who banged and screamed at the apartment before eventually calling the cops.

German police got a locksmith to open the door, but found no one inside except a voice-activated 'black jukebox' playing music.

Poor Haberstroh came home the next day and found his locks had been changed. He had to go to the police station and pay the hefty locksmith bill just to get the new keys.

Needless to say, the man and his smart assistant are not on speaking terms right now.

How the Echo even got turned on is still a mystery, since the apartment was on the sixth floor, and all windows were closed the whole time.

Though really, it's probably not too far fetched to think Alexa might already have a mind of its own. 3488918]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKACCTTASIRPVATKFJA7K2CGZBVXF37AJPRZGKTAIFARXAHBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6FE/35F/6FE35F6400754E79C80AF61089B36F81.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon alexa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon echo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alexa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smart assistant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial intelligence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ AI]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smart robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police raid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ party]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smart machines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ voice control]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ voice activated]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/detective-robot-has-killer-rhymes-literally--3490412</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Detective robot has killer rhymes. Literally. 3490412]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — A detective robot named Carmel will try to crack the Zodiac case as part of a new documentary for the History Channel.

Named Carmel, and developed by Cali scientist Kevin Knight, the system will help crack the codes in the case.

Zodiac was offed at least five people — that police are certain of — in Northern California during the 60s and 70s who left a series of encrypted clues, but was never caught. It's said the total number of victims may be the twenties or thirties.

According to History.com, Carmel has been programmed to think like Zodiac and as such, the supercomputer has started writing seriously creepy poetry. 3490412]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBKRCDICASNAIACALZDR76DUMVAV7F34A2PR5TCYASNARDCRKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D68/5DC/D685DCC885934778F87211B70F5FE69F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[carmel computer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[robot detective]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[zodiac cipher]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[solving zodiac]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[zodiac ciphers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[unsolved mysteries of history]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ai poetry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[robot poetry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kevin knight]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-flowing-water-on-mars-may-actually-be-sand-3489923</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Flowing water' on Mars may actually be sand 3489923]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MARS — New research from the U.S. Geological Survey has found that the mysterious streaks once thought to be proof of water on Mars are probably just sand flows. Sorry NASA!

According to NASA, recurring slope lineae or RSL are long, dark streaks that expand on the slopes of Mars during warmer seasons, and retract when the temperature gets colder.

RSL served as compelling evidence of water on Mars. It looked similar to features on Earth formed by water flows, and contained molecules that help water stay liquid. But a closer look reveals behavior that's unlike flowing water.

Streaks existed only on the tops of steep slopes, and all settled at the angle of repose — the maximum slope at which loose solid material can be piled without slumping.

Based on the findings, researchers concluded that the markings weren't created by water, but by dry grains like sand and dust that accumulate and flow down the slopes.

The RSL may still contain water, but probably not enough to sustain tiny microbial critters, more so human life. 3489923]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEBWCAIDKIFARBRYLABAV9D3MJJSRET6AIDW5HABAJMWXYZDKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/159/D48/159D48D1E6413E3D9ABC086381695B55.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water on mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life on mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RSL]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sand flow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars sand flow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ slope lineae]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ recurring slope lineae]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars slopes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/asteroid-is-first-interstellar-visitor-to-our-solar-system-that-we-know-of--3489855</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Asteroid is first interstellar visitor to our solar system (that we know of) 3489855]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE SPACE BETWEEN MARS AND JUPITER — NASA says a recently discovered asteroid is our solar system's first interstellar visitor. 

The asteroid was discovered by the Panoramic Survey Telescope and Rapid Response System in Hawaii on October 19, 2017.

NASA-funded research published in the journal Nature says it is the first interstellar object to enter our solar system and will travel inside it for over a year.

Scientists speculate the asteroid is 400 meters long, and around 40 m wide. A lot about it is unknown, but the asteroid could be made up materials like metals or rocks, and is likely to be billions of years old. 

NASA says the asteroid will exit the solar system in January 2019 after passing through Saturn's orbit. It will next head for the Pegasus constellation. 3489855]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6KACXTWAWNFGCIRL6PW5LUYGZDEZRT5K6JWRFIGAMHA7DKUAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/909/651/9096516A4085FB724FAC8DCD8D207EF5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new asteroid 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interstellar asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa finds asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beyond the solar system]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/without-net-neutrality-you-can-pay-more-for-same-crap-service-3489786</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Without net neutrality, you can pay more for same crap service 3489786]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The Federal Communications Commission has released regulations that would roll back net neutrality regulations passed by the agency two years ago. 

Net Neutrality is the principle of an open internet where Internet Service Providers (ISPs) give consumers access to all content without favoring some sources or blocking others, according to USA Today.  It also prohibits ISPs from throttling certain content over others.  

In 2015, the FCC decided to regulate broadband service like a utility, similar to electricity and water, according to the New York Times. 

The major broadband and telecom companies like AT&T and Comcast argue against net neutrality saying government regulation reduces the incentives to improve service. 
Without net neutrality, the internet could become divided into two tiers: one with fast service and one without.

Larger internet and media companies as well as the affluent will be able to pay for the high-speed lane, while everyone else will have to use the slow lane. 

The new rules would require ISPs to disclose any blocking, throttling and prioritization of content.

States are also prohibited from enacting their own net neutrality laws that conflict with the new FCC rules, USA Today reported.  

The FCC will vote on December 14 to repeal current net neutrality rules. 3489786]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAAMCCUKFPRCBRUB5AW7KBHGMAVXRIMLVAFVUCRK5GFXBRPKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/952/769/9527695BCA72C98E438880DBF810784C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Net Neutrality]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Net Neutrality repeal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Net Neutrality regulations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ISPs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ throttling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paid prioritization]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blocking]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/google-collects-android-users-location-data-all-the-time-3489757</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Google collects Android users' location data all the time 3489757]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA — Google has been collecting location data on Android phones, even when the location services are disabled, according to Quartz. 

This means Google can access users' locations and their movements well beyond consumer privacy norms. 
After being contacted by Quartz, Google said cell tower addresses have been included in information sent to a system that manages push notifications and messages on Android phones for the past 11 months. 
According to a Google spokesperson, the data was not used or stored, and that the company was taking steps to stop the practice by the end of November. 
With user location data, cell towers could be used to triangulate location to around a quarter-mile radius, and even closer in urban areas where cell towers are closer together. 

Even though the information is encrypted when it is sent back to Google, a third party could still compromise the system. 

Since January, all Android devices, even with location services disabled, were sending cell-tower addresses to Google. 

Devices with cellular data or WiFi connection appeared to send data each time they were in range of a new cell tower. 

Android devices without a SIM card, but connected to a WiFi network, would still send tower addresses to Google. 3489757]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFKWPAKUARGARAI7BNPW5LBAMAEBZRAILVAF7URAARHA5VTXAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CE5/FEB/CE5FEBD843DC435125D1BB3485C7C7C8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google Android user location]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Android user location data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google collecting location data]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fashion-model-responds-to-falling-at-victoria-secret-s-fashion-show-3489724</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fashion model responds to falling at Victoria Secret's fashion show 3489724]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI, CHINA — Fashion model Ming Xi became the focal point of Victoria's Secret fashion show in her hometown of Shanghai, China when she tripped and fell on the runway during the taping of the Victoria's Secret fashion show on November 20th.

Despite stumbling, Xi kept her radiant smile and the crowd cheered in support of her. Fellow model Gizele Oliveira later came to the rescue to help Xi get back on her feet so that she could finish walking the runway. 

Xi later posted an apology online, saying she felt she had disappointed everyone. After modeling for seven years, Xi said she's fallen countless times but she knows she must walk on, no matter how painful it is.

Xi later took to her Instagram account to talk more about the incident. She said that stumbling during the show was one of the hardest moments she's had to go through. However, she was thankful for the support she's gotten from everyone and vowed to bounce back and continue to walk the runway. 3489724]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NFVCIFBMARAAZYBSPR57LRMACB3RCSKVAW7HIKAZAFZWACAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/274/C74/274C74E2367CE94A57CE6F98018016B0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ming Xi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ming xi fall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ victoria's fashion show]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ victoria's secret]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ modeling fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ modeling fail compilation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese model victoria's secret]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mitsubishi-subsidiaries-faked-product-data-3491017</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mitsubishi subsidiaries faked product data 3491017]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Shares of Japanese firm Mitsubishi are dropping after the company admitted to fudging product data.

Mitsubishi Materials admitted on Thursday that two of its subsidiaries had falsified product data to match specifications set by clients, according to the Japan Times.

Mitsubishi Cable Industries altered data on its O-ring sealing products, affecting 270 million units sold over a two and a half year period to firms that include aircraft and car makers.

Specs on metal products for car and electronic components were also misrepresented by Mitsubishi Shindoh, with least 29 companies believed to have bought the parts between October 2016 and 2017.

So far, none of the products have been caused safety problems. Reports claim one other unit had supplied products with falsified information, though these have already been confirmed safe to use.

The Mitsubishi scandal is the latest blow to Japan's once-prestigious manufacturing industry, which has been rocked by multiple controversies this year from companies like Kobe Steel, Nissan, Subaru, Toshiba, and Takata. 3491017]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCFEY3VKEDWGBAVLEDWZK44NAAB3SRLKBLFMGRKBVFFIBZDKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5D7/10D/5D710D730BDE8B742934FF04C60DA18D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mitsubishi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mitsubishi scandal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mitsubishi controversy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake documents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falsified documents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ manufacturing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ product specs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake specs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake data]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-tests-its-newest-icbm-3490761</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China tests its newest ICBM 3490761]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — China is adding a new intercontinental ballistic missile — the Dongfeng-41 — to its nuclear arsenal.

The missile recently underwent its eighth test launch since it was first announced in 2012. 

The ICBM is a three-stage solid-fuel missile, 15 meters long and weighing around 30 metric tons.   

The Dongfeng-41 has a 12,000 km range, meaning it could strike almost any location in the world, China's state media reported, according to Newsweek. It has a top speed of over Mach 10.
The Dongfeng-41 can carry up to 10 MIRV warheads. The missile could be ready for deployment as early as 2018. 3490761]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KRPDKVABJACATFL6LRX7LRGFIBVRK3A6JATGIEAIGATBZFAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E1A/2F4/E1A2F4ACAAAB4DE43ECC2CBAA8EA0FCC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Dongfeng 41]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Dongfeng 41]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DF-41]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China ICBM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China ICBM test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China arms race]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/starbucks-criticized-for-its-holiday-cups-again-3490667</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Starbucks criticized for its holiday cups, again 3490667]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['Merica — Holiday season is here again and the new Starbucks holiday tradition of triggering conservative Christians with their special holiday cups, this year is no exception.

Released on November 1st, the cup design features holiday imagery like snow, wrapped gifts and a pair of hands holding each other, something seems wrong here?

The latest controversy has focused on a pair of gender-neutral hands innocently holding each other on the side of the cup itself. 

Various media have all published their take on the design. Fox News and The Blaze both have suggested that Starbucks is using the design to promote homosexuality. In response to the allegations, Starbucks' spokeswoman said the company intentionally designed the cup so their customers can decide for themselves.

Like we said earlier, this is not the first time Starbucks has stirred up a discussion like this. In 2015, conservative media and then-presidential candidate Donald Trump accused Starbucks of starting a War on Christmas because of the cups' minimalist design. 3490667]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFKAPDTUAFJAEVKDLBIWRL4XMIAS7FK4AJLFMUZLA2NAEDZEAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/586/DA2/586DA2F17372A88F2C19CD09EE5889BA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ starbucks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ starbucks holiday cup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ starbucks holiday cup controversy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ starbucks holiday cup 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ controversy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gay agenda]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ war on christmas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christians]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uni-vilifies-ta-for-showing-class-a-debate-on-gender-pronouns-3490653</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Uni vilifies TA for showing class a debate on gender pronouns 3490653]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ONTARIO, CANADA — Canada's Wilfrid Laurier University was forced to apologize this week after several of its faculty were revealed to have castigated a teaching assistant for showing a class a televised debate on gender pronouns.

Unknown to the faculty, the TA secretly recorded that meeting, and this week leaked it to the press for all the world to hear. 

Check out the audio for yourself in the link below. 3490653]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASKAGAKXAFLA3BTAKFIR5LUSGVCS7FIMKIARVURLAVGFIBAABC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8C4/0C8/8C40C82474FD40C53159375D00B331C3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>107</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jordan peterson debate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canada university fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wilfrid laurier university]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ teach assistant criticized]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lindsey shepard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ faculty meeting recording]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wilfrid laurier apology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ political correctness gone mad]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hand-sanitizer-could-be-affecting-breathalyzer-results-3490606</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hand sanitizer could be affecting breathalyzer results 3490606]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COLORADO SPRINGS, COLORADO — A new study finds that alcohol-based hand sanitizers can emit vapors that can disperse through the air and enter the mouth, causing breathalyzers to error out or even give a positive reading.  

The findings were published last week in the Journal of Forensic Sciences. 

Previous studies have found that hand sanitizers can affect readings on handheld devices, Gizmodo reported. 
This study looked at evidential breath alcohol instruments in police stations. 

Researchers first administered breathalyzers to 65 subjects in a controlled, ventilated room. 
Then one of two operators used a golf ball-sized dollop of foam sanitizer or two pumps of liquid sanitizer and rubbed the solution into their skin until dry.
The operators then administered one more round of tests. Of the 130 tests, 13 gave a positive reading, even though the subject did not consume any alcohol. Another 41 tests caused the machine to error out. 3490606]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6JRAXCWA2KWIVCCL5DRX7UYGRBB3UT2KVDAVTZHKVGAAWZIAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A89/CAC/A89CAC3FDB7C0F7F39A955BC8E2EBEE3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ breathalyzer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hand sanitizer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alcohol based hand sanitizer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hand sanitizer breathalyzer results]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hand sanitizer affects breathalyzer]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-make-puppy-clones-of-world-s-first-cloned-dog-3490564</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists make puppy clones of world's first cloned dog 3490564]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL — A team of scientists has re-cloned the world's first dog clone, in a bid to find out if the process has an impact on a clone's health or lifespan.

BBC reports that dog clone Snuppy was created in 2005 using a stem cell from an Afghan hound, and born via a surrogate labrador mother.

The original dog, named Tai, died from cancer when he was 12 years old. Snuppy would later live to age 10 before also succumbing to cancer, though not the same kind.

When Snuppy was five years old, researchers collected his stem cells while also taking eggs from female dogs and taking out their nuclei.

Using a process called somatic cell nuclear transfer, nuclei from the stem cells were transferred into the empty eggs, then stimulated into dividing — creating over 94 embryos.

The embryos were implanted into surrogates, resulting in the birth of four live re-clones. Though one died from diarrhea days after the birth, the remaining three are now nine months old and still healthy.

Researchers published their report in the journal Scientific Reports. They say they will closely monitor the puppies and measure virtually all aspects of their lives, including growth, metabolism, immune system, and disease development. 3490564]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDFAYABKMCWAVIWBIBF57L3NFKVTRC5AECFPGZCAZHWCWAEAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D47/2A6/D472A6C760966BBA3CCD08D81212094A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cloned dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cloning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snuppy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog clone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal clone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reclone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ afghan hound]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal cloning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cloning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ recloning]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/authorities-wonder-if-videogame-loot-boxes-are-gambling-3490522</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Authorities wonder if videogame loot boxes are gambling 3490522]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HAWAII / BELGIUM — Authorities in Belgium and the U.S. state of Hawaii are investigating whether a common video game feature called loot boxes are gambling.

Loot boxes are virtual containers earned or purchased while playing a videogame. They typically contain a randomized assortment of virtual items aimed at enhancing the player's experience and in-game abilities. 

Because of the elements of chance and money involved, Belgian and Hawaiian authorities are concerned the practice may expose minors to gambling.

According to the Telegraph, Hawaii state representative Chris Lee wants to put legislation in place to protect minors from the practice. The U.S. island state is currently investigating gaming publisher Electronic Arts for predatory practices against minors due to its use of loot boxes in their game Star Wars Battlefront 2.

According to the Brisbane Times, an regulatory analyst for the state of Victoria in Australia said loot boxes do constitute gambling, but are difficult to regulate. 3490522]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABLWPXTTAIBFMBIWKFKARKBAMICS7FIIA5DWRTKSAEGWKWZEAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D7E/860/D7E860B7792E654C0FA0EE8821123874.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ loot box gambling laws]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ video game loot box]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars battlefront 2 loot box]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electronic arts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ loot box]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ loot box gaming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ loot box investigation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/london-city-buses-will-soon-run-on-coffee-derived-biodiesel-3490518</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[London city buses will soon run on coffee-derived biodiesel 3490518]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Waste coffee grounds will be powering London's buses, as the city finds newer and cleaner ways to run its public transport system.

BBC reports that clean technology company Bio-bean has created a new biofuel by blending oil extracted from used coffee grounds with B20 biodiesel.

The firm estimates that it would take just 2.55 million cups of coffee to create enough of the biofuel to power a London bus for an entire year.

Bio-bean is working with Shell and Transport for London for its pilot project, which will see about 6,000 liters of coffee oil being used by some buses starting Monday.

Many of the city's buses are already running on biofuel made from wastes such as cooking oil or beef to reduce emissions, but this is the first time a coffee-derived fuel is being introduced.

Londoners reportedly produce about 200,000 tonnes of coffee waste a year, and most end up in landfills where they emit harmful methane gas. The new initiative is not only beneficial to the environment, but also convenient for buses, which don't need to be modified to use the fuel. 3490518]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AACFEY3TKEDWGWTFLEBFTK4UNAEB5ETZLRDFZGZAKEEARAKTBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C5D/0E6/C5D0E6EFFAAFE8C8D0B7781B8D82F3BB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee bus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee oil]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee biofuel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee diesel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biofuel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ London coffee bus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ waste coffee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee grounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biodiesel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clean fuel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clean energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ powered by coffee]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/40-injured-as-nightclub-floor-collapses-in-tenerife-3492583</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[40 injured as nightclub floor collapses in Tenerife 3492583]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TENERIFE, SPAIN — Dozens were injured early Sunday when the floor of a Spanish nightclub abruptly collapsed under their feet.

The Guardian reports that the Butterfly Disco pub in Tenerife, in Spain's Canary Islands, was full of revellers around 2:30 a.m. Sunday morning.

A 4 meter-by-4 meter area of floor suddenly gave way, sending people crashing into an empty area below. 

At least 40 clubbers were wounded after falling one storey into the basement. Among the victims were tourists from France, Romania, Belgium, and the UK.

The injured were taken to the hospital and treated for fractured thigh bones, broken and sprained ankles, as well as cuts and bruises.

According to the mayor of Tenerife, the popular gay nightclub had a legitimate license and did not appear to be overcrowded when the incident occurred. Firefighters are currently sifting through the debris to look for clues on how and why the dance floor collapsed. 3492583]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAFKD3UKVAREVRTBJJFX7UTMNJVRRZQAVAWZT3RAZFFMAC5AB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C5F/DFD/C5FDFD215429BEF81394AC659F726F01.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nightclub collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ floor collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dance floor collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tenerife nightclub]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ butterfly nightclub]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gay nightclub]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canary islands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tenerife]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ broken bones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fracture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ankle sprain]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/robotic-clamp-hugs-heart-to-help-it-pump-blood-3492575</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Robotic clamp hugs heart to help it pump blood 3492575]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOSTON — New research published this month in Science Robotics details a robot heart device that can help pump blood to hearts with weakened ventricles.
  
The plastic device is powered by compressed air pressure and is place around damaged ventricle. It then squeezes the heart to help it pump blood throughout the body.

The mechanics of the device are said to be adaptive to the beating rhythm, reported Seeker, citing the research. It has only been tested on animals so far, but could one day hold potential for human treatment. 3492575]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDRIXZHKJIFMCI9BSJATL4UMFJS5SALKWLRVUABAZGFAVABAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E6F/C28/E6FC28CC9F3A68B67BDEBF8A109B80D7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>34</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot heart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boston childrens hospital]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart device]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ automated heart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mechanical heart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ articial heart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart aid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-turn-diet-supplement-algae-into-cancer-killing-microbot-3492570</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Researchers turn diet supplement algae into cancer killing microbot 3492570]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HONG KONG — Scientists have transformed an algae commonly used as a dietary supplement into a cancer-eliminating robot.

Details of the research were published this month in the journal, Science Robotics.

Researchers coated spirulina microalgae in iron nanoparticles before inserting it inside a rat's stomach. The iron coating combined with the natural shape of spirulina, allowed scientists to control the and direct microalgae with magnets.

Spirulina emits a compound toxic only to cancer cells. Researchers found it eliminated 90% of cancerous cells inside lab dish after two days.

The biodegradability of robot depends on the thickness of iron nanoparticle coating. The thicker this is, the longer the robot can operate inside a subject.

Lead researcher Dr So Li Zhang told Science it's not ready for doctors to use, reckons it might be ready for use in about ten years. 3492570]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLAMDKSANJAAWCABJLAV9LVMZEVRFK6K5AF5G3XK6NRKWZQKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FEE/002/FEE002097E24262A35A0366AC9E737D5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot cancer treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ diet food cancer robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  spirulina]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spirulina diet food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  spirulina diet supplement]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bali-volcano-eruptions-shut-down-flights-3492503</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bali volcano eruptions shut down flights 3492503]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BALI, INDONESIA — Volcanic eruptions from Bali's Mount Agung has caused officials to cancel flights and evacuate around 24,000 residents. 

Mount Agung erupted on Saturday night and three times on Sunday, sending a thick ash cloud thousands of meters up into the atmosphere, the Guardian reported. 

Bali's international airport was forced to close. Massive plumes of ash have been blowing towards the east, which also caused Lombok International Airport on Pulau Lombok to temporarily close, according to CNN.

An exclusion zone up to 10 km from the crater has been put in place, with officials warning anyone still in the area to leave. 
Agung is classified as a stratovolcano, also known as a composite volcano. They are conical volcanoes that are built up by many layers of hardened, lava, tephra, pumice and volcanic ash. 
Mount Agung erupted for the first time in 50 years in September, prompting an evacuation of more than 185,000 people. In 1963, a large eruption killed around 1,100 people, according to the Guardian. 3492503]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIFKDKSAVARABIVB5AFZ9LUMVCSIRZLK5BWRHCSKEAFMAZEBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3E2/066/3E206690015BCF128BFA1CC698D1559A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bali volcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bali Mt. Agung]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mount Agung eruption]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mount Agung evacuations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ composite volcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stratovolcano]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gang-of-wild-turkeys-invade-bay-area-neighborhoods-3492438</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gang of wild turkeys invade Bay Area neighborhoods 3492438]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FREMONT, CALIFORNIA — There are a lot more turkeys in the Bay Area this year, and no, we don't mean on people's Thanksgiving tables.

CBS reports that flocks of turkeys have left the wild and are now running amok in suburban California.

The wild birds are possibly the worst squatters ever—messing up properties, leaving their crap everywhere, and slowly taking over. Rude!

They're also  pretty aggressive, and have been known to attack a mailman or two in their quest for suburban domination.

Apparently, you're not supposed to feed the birds because they get cocky and start thinking they own the place.

So what's a neighborhood to do?

Well, it is Thanksgiving season. If you can't drive them away, you may as well make like the pilgrims and roast the damn birds. Don't forget the gravy! 3492438]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KRPX3VABJWMARUL5DRV6D4M2KS5URKAJPA3HRKASQRCVIEBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0F2/D75/0F2D758D6F06BAA20449BB285E68C0BD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild turkey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turkey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thanksgiving]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turkey attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turkey invasion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aggressive turkeys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ roast turkey]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/playerunknown-s-battle-grounds-modded-with-pro-socialist-propaganda-for-china-release-3492416</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[PlayerUnknown's Battle Grounds modded with pro-socialist propaganda for China release 3492416]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — Hit PC game Player Unknown's Battlegrounds aka PUB-G is going to be released in China after all.

It's South Korean publisher has partnered with China's Tencent to pump out a socialist-friendly version of the game.

PUBG is inspired by the classic Japanese movie Battle Royale. The online game sees 100 players parachute onto an island and eliminate each other Hunger-Games style 3492416]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMBWCYAJKZCWCBZSLRAA77DYNEDVZEC4A5AA5HTXANQRGBTVAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0D8/6F8/0D86F8ACCDDC0CB74CB39C4506B32DDD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pubg fails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pubg wtf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playerunknown battle grounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china censorship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china propaganda]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-ghost-ship-with-8-bodies-may-have-come-from-north-korea-3493317</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Ghost ship' with 8 bodies may have come from North Korea 3493317]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OGA, JAPAN — Eight bodies were found inside a ship found on a Japanese beach this week.

The vessel was discovered in the Sea of Japan close to Oga on the Japanese coast. The Japanese Coast Guard believes it may have come from North Korea.

A 68-year-old local resident alerted Japanese authorities to the ship on Monday morning, Kyodo News reported. She reportedly saw it drifting some 300 meters from shore.

The coast guard found eight bodies inside the ship, as well as a cigarette packet bearing hangul writing. This leads police to suspect it is North Korean in origin, the Japanese Times reported, citing Kyodo News.

The Japan Times reports parts of the bodies were skeletonized, suggesting that the ship was at sea for an extensive amount of time before being found. 3493317]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEDFGXRDKREFKWRSLBPAZ9LRNEEEXSIIAZAR3URAA2NWKBIEKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/526/898/5268981EE871AEF9AD8903D427985EAC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-29T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea ghost ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dprk ghost ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea escape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fleeing north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea defection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dprk escape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ghost ship defector]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ defecting from north korea]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tom-hardy-s-venom-work-out-is-beastly-3493292</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tom Hardy's venom work-out is beastly 3493292]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTA — Tom Hardy is putting in work for his role as the title character in Venom, Sony's new comic book movie based on the Spider-Man supervillain 

The character was previously a villain in 2007's Spider-Man 3 where he was portrayed by Topher Grace.

Going by a new viral video from Hardy's trainers, it sounds like his take on the character is is going to be bigger, meaner and badder.

Reportedly, the Bane actor is training to become an 8 ft 4 beast with five MMA and kickboxing sessions per week.

The film won't feature Spider-Man, but may contain another villain from the web slinger's rogue gallery.

One of Hardy's trainers mentions the word Carnage in the video and that could hint at the Marvel bad guy of the same name.

The film is currently in production in Atlanta and is scheduled on October 18, 2018. 3493292]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNWADACBEFRGVKCLBJAK6BGGVCS5FZMK2KFXGAKBVAFMBIPAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DAF/BDD/DAFBDD0D2156212C48AC769D5725781D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-29T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[tom hardy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[venom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[spider-man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[venom movie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[tom hardy workout]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[tom hardy movies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[tom hardy venom training]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/us-shows-off-new-mega-base-in-south-korea-3493267</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[US shows off new mega base in South Korea 3493267]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYEONGTAEK, SOUTH KOREA — The U.S. has been working on one of its largest military overseas construction projects at Camp Humphreys in South Korea, located about 50 miles south of Seoul.

Once the $11 billion expansion is finished, the installation will house a majority of the approximately 30,000 U.S. troops in South Korea, the Daily Beast reported. 

The 3,454 acre base is the size of a small city. A veterinary clinic, a dental clinic and a food court opened up in October. 
The massive complex has new headquarter buildings, an airstrip, firing ranges, barracks, motor pools, communications facilities, schools, day care centers, stores, churches and even a golf course, according to the Daily Beast. 

U.S. forces are spread across 174 bases in South Korea. Camp Humphreys will allow the U.S. to concentrate their forces there. The U.S. military plans to cut the number of bases in South Korea to just 96 by 2020.   

In the event of open war with North Korea, Camp Humphreys would give the U.S. forces the ability for rapid deployment to the front lines. 3493267]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNWVDIABEAREVTDLADAXK4SMECS7SIMAWKRXUZEKIAFKW3RAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BC7/19E/BC719E2CB92BE3ADD194BC9E02CAD33E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-29T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Camp Humphreys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Camp Humphreys South Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US forces South Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US bases South Korea]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/armless-chinese-woman-s-videos-going-viral-in-china-3493208</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Armless Chinese woman's videos going viral in China 3493208]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANHUI, CHINA — A 27-year-old armless woman from eastern China has won hearts of many Chinese netizens for her inspirational story about the obstacles she faces every day and how she overcomes them.

Yang Li, a native from Bengbu of Anhui province, was injured when she came in contact with high voltage cables when she was only 4, which resulted in the amputation of both her arms.

Since the tragic accident, Yang taught herself how to use her feet to do things that most use two hands to do, such as putting on makeup, eating with chopsticks and taking selfies.

Yang also learned how to write using her feet, and made headlines for completing China's college entrance exam in 2007 this way. After completing university, Yang landed a job s a civil service clerk.

Yang started livestreaming several months ago and launched a channel with inspirational videos telling followers about her life and showing them how she manages every day.

Yang's channel quickly racked up more than 900,000 fans, and she earned titles such as China's inspirational sister and Ms. Positivity. In response to her viral fame, she said that although she's handicapped, but she's happy about her life and hopes society would focus more on people with disabilities. 3493208]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IFKACWAIHA7CZSB5DAXKJCMRDE7FZNKSIFRHRCAVAFPWCUBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3F5/C4C/3F5C4C118C5A202265BDFB789AEFC4BB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-29T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>111</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armless]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ handicapped]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ symptoms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman without arms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Yang Li]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flies-loaded-with-more-harmful-bacteria-than-previously-thought-3493196</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flies loaded with more harmful bacteria than previously thought 3493196]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE/U.S.A — New research has found that flies hold more harmful bacteria than scientists previously believed.

Details of the findings were published in the journal Scientific Reports. The research team involved an international team of scientists from Singapore and the U.S.A.

Scientists found over 600 bacteria inside an analysis of 116 flies. House flies were laden 351 different kinds of bacteria while the blowfly was found to contain 316 types.

Scientists believe that flies bred with no germs could be used as a means to observe and measure public health. These would be released into the environment, before being captured at a later date for analysis. 3493196]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMCFKCZJKZHAIWIRKFLFRLDRGVCSIST7ABLRVURDKZHAECAMAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F35/89E/F3589E2D5F14032B9400FFC20C417071.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-29T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flies spread disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fly disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fly bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flies and disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flies and health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ are flies harmful]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flat-earth-rocket-launch-postponed-in-cali-3493137</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flat Earth rocket launch postponed in Cali 3493137]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMBOY, CALIFORNIA — A California man who was planning to hurl himself 1,800 feet in the air in a homemade rocket to prove the earth is flat is postponing the launch until this week. 
Limo driver Mike Mad Hughes was originally planning to launch himself over the ghost town of Amboy in the Mojave Desert before he was shot down by federal agencies in charge of the land he was planning to use. 

Hughes says the event will now take place on private property, three miles down the road. That's a relief. 
I don't believe in science, Mike said in an AP interview. I know about aerodynamics and fluid dynamics and how things move through the air, about the certain size of rocket nozzles, and thrust. But that's not science, that's just a formula. There's no difference between science and science fiction. Amen brother. 
Sure, Hughes only recently hopped on the flat-earth train train after he curiously couldn't raise enough funds for his Kickstarter campaign, but that's unimportant. 
The 61-year-old limo driver has spent the past few years building a steam-powered rocket out of salvage parts from his garage. It's cost up to $20,000 bucks so far. Money well spent. 3493137]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFMACTKRGR7BA9LJKAI9JGMJLV7SANLWLFRTIEKAEACVTYKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B86/66B/B8666BD407AC135101EF7ADC4CD6E210.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-29T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earthers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earth theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mike Hughes flat earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mike Hughes rocket mojave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homemade rocket flat earth]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/google-fixed-its-god-awful-hamburger-emoji-3494096</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Google fixed its god awful hamburger emoji 3494096]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA — Things have finally gone back to normal in the Google-verse after Google finally updated its abomination of a hamburger emoji.

Some person who has clearly never eaten a cheeseburger was in charge of the emoji where the cheese was placed under the patty.

Luckily, the burger got a proper facelift with the release of Android 8.1. The cheese is now on top of the patty where it belongs. 

The Google monstrosity was first brought to light over the Twittersphere in a tweet with over 51,000 likes and 25,000 retweets. 

Google's cafeteria even got in on the action by offering Android burgers with the cheese below the burger. Yuck. 
They also made some other emoji tweaks like an updated filled beer stein as opposed to one half full, and a new cheese emoji with more realistic holes. 3494096]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBKFXAICB5AAAAAVBMDAV9BBM2JBTFK6AWLAVFKSAJNRGCIPAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/229/C5C/229C5C52441B3A3666FB826740E9914F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google burger emoji]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google burger emoji update]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google Android 8.1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Android 8.1 emojis]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bungie-backs-out-of-livestream-event-amid-rage-over-destiny-2-3494023</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bungie backs out of livestream event amid rage over Destiny 2 3494023]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BELLEVUE, WASHINGTON — Triple-A game developer Bungie have reportedly canceled a livestream event for Destiny 2 following outrage at the revelation of some hush-hush gameplay mechanics.

Reportedly, Bungie admitted to having created a unseen system that throttled player's experience points in Destiny 2 while still displaying it as normal. 

In Destiny 2 experience points, or XP, let gamers level up and become more powerful. 
The limit is level 20 in Destiny 2, but they can still earn XP and engrams, an in-game currency that lets them buy new stuff for their character.

Bungee scrapped the hidden system, but now experience required for level ups has more or less doubled, reports Gamerant. 

Engrams can also be paid for with real world cash, so some speculate this is Bungie's way of getting gamers to spend more money on the $60 game. 3494023]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KAGXTVB6MFXXR9LWKFR7SFGVBS5FC9AFIWVG3SKVGRPBIAAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D9A/9AD/D9A9ADF3606328A68C52931F3D7C760B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destiny 2 microtransaction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destiny 2 leveling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destiny 2 changes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bungie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destiny 2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destiny 2 leveling fast]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destiny 2 engram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bright engram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ halo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ master chief]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-first-astro-cat-will-finally-be-honoured-with-a-statue-3493960</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's first astro cat will finally be honoured with a statue 3493960]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PARIS, FRANCE — Before humans were sent to space for spaceflight, several countries were already using animals to test and understand how the lack of gravity in space could affect human astronauts.

In 1963, A cat in France became the first cat to travel in space and return safely. To celebrate her contribution, a kickstarter campaign was set up by Matthew Serge Guy to crowdfund the budget to build a bronze statue for Félicette[c] — the astro cat.

There are different stories about how Félicette the fluffy pioneer was recruited by France's space agency — Centre d'Enseignement et de Recherches de Médecine Aéronautique (CERMA), regardless, she and 13 other cats were later put in the space training program. 

Due to her calm nature during a series of training, Félicette was picked to be the first cat to be blast off from earth, cutting through the atmosphere into space, Félicette's rocket reached a height of 157 kilometres.

Félicette's trip in weightless space lasted 5 minutes, her capsule then parachuted back down to earth where she later rendezvoused with the recovery team. The whole operation was 13 minutes long. After the space journey, Félicette was taken back to the space agency's lab for further study, where she unfortunately was put to sleep so scientists can study the electrodes that were planted in her brain.

In the name of science, Félicette and many other animals have contributed greatly to spaceflight, although the participation was against their will. Since her flight, European and U.S. space agencies have stopped sending animals into space as the practice was unethical and more advanced methods became available.

The campaign for the statue received about $57,000 to get the project going. Famed animal sculptor Gill Parker has also agreed to help build the statue for Félicette. Guy's prefered site for the statue is Félicette's hometown in Paris. 3493960]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5ARPDCWLJPA3XAWLSPRT9BAMADSXFIIKSLF3UCRASPFMCRCAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/798/AE4/798AE404AA50FAC440894306618AB072.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>110</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animals in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ felicette space cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ felicette first cat in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ statue]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-tests-missile-that-could-reach-the-u-s--3493957</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea tests missile that could reach the U.S. 3493957]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGSONG, NORTH KOREA — After 74-day hiatus, North Korea has test-launched another ballistic missile, which some believe is possibly its more powerful one yet.

Reuters reports that an intercontinental ballistic missile was launched from Pyongsong early Wednesday, reportedly flying on a lofted trajectory and reaching a maximum height of 4,500 kilometers.

The missile flew nearly 1,000 kilometers for approximately 53 minutes before landing off the coast of Aomori, within Japan's exclusive economic zone.

Two previous ICBMs test-launched this year traveled a shorter distance, flying for 37 minutes on July 4, and 47 minutes on July 28.

Had the missile flown on a standard trajectory, experts say it would have a range of more than 13,000 kilometers — enough to reach Washington D.C. and the rest of the continental U.S., and even Europe or Australia, according to the Guardian.

South Korea responded to the launch by conducting its own missile test off the country's east coast.

Japan detected radio signals on Tuesday suggesting the North might be preparing for a ballistic missile test. The government has since condemned the launch. 3493957]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LICAADAIL6NR3CISKFJAV6DTMREE5FC5LWLWRUZHKBMACY3UAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F7F/403/F7F4035D4794884439A40323532C102C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ICBM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ballistic missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea missile program]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korean missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan EEZ]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/overuse-of-ogallala-aquifer-may-create-great-american-desert--3493952</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Overuse of Ogallala aquifer may create 'great American desert' 3493952]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA'S BREADBASKET — The Ogallala aquifer, the world's largest source of groundwater, is shrinking due to overuse by farmers in eight U.S. states.

The aquifer underlies parts of Colorado, Kansas, Nebraska, Texas, New Mexico, Texas, Oklahoma, Wyoming and South Dakota. There is no shared agreement between the states on how to use it.

The Denver Post examined federal data on the aquifer and found that it had shrank at double the rate over the last 6 years, compared with the last sixty. 

The water loss has impacted those living in rural areas. One resident told the Denver Post that he doesn't know if he'll get water when he turns on a faucet.

Many streams and rivers linked to the aquifer have dried up and more are expected to do so if nothing changes. Various species of fish, including the minnow and the catfish, are also disappearing.

The Denver Post reports that even if farmers in 8 the states drastically reduced their pumping, it'd take centuries for the planet to renew the aquifer. 3493952]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IWKAIFBIHAADRTLMDRV7JCMADSKFAMK2IWMTZDAAHRMYIMKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/93A/8D6/93A8D69156385ABD42102706641E99F9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ groundwater depletion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ogallala aquifer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aquifer depletion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ great american desert]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ogallala states]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/space-needle-to-undergo-massive-100-million-dollar-facelift-3493866</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Space Needle to undergo massive $100 million-dollar facelift 3493866]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Fifty-five years opening, Seattle's iconic Space Needle is undergoing a massive multi-million dollar makeover.

Seattle Times reports that workers recently raised a donut-shaped platform to begin work on the Space Needle's $100 million renovation project.

Updates will focus mostly on the observation deck and restaurant, and are set to be completed by May 2018.

To give visitors more sweeping views of the city, the observation deck's pony walls and cages will be replaced with floor-to-ceiling glass panels.

SkyCity, the Needle's restaurant, will be fitted with glass floors and a new motor, and will become the world's first glass-floor rotating restaurant once it reopens.

The current renovation project is expected to keep the iconic landmark relevant for the next 50 years or so. Other changes include a new coat of paint on the exterior, and more elevators. 3493866]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLACX3XBWNFVDRVBACRK6BBGMBS5STSAIARVURKAAERGYRFKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B98/E09/B98E09C8F53CD3A5C7EFF0E91BF0D143.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space needle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seattle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space lift]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ century project]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space needle renovation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ observation deck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glass observation deck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ revolving restaurant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skycity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bitcoin-is-going-bananas-but-when-will-it-burst--3493843</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bitcoin is going bananas, but when will it burst? 3493843]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BITCOIN WORLD — Bitcoin has been on an absolute tear this year after passing $9,000 and is quickly closing in on the $10 grand mark.  

Analysts say the Chicago Mercantile Exchange's decision to launch bitcoin 
futures has helped fueled buying in December. 

The value of the 16.7 million bitcoin units in circulation has now exceeded $160 billion, which means the digital currency's market cap exceeds that of IBM, Disney and Mickey D's. 

The cryptocurrency shows no signs of slowing. Not only are retail investors jumping in, but hedge funds have even started including bitcoin in their portfolios. 

According to CNBC, there are more than 120 investment funds for cryptocurrencies. 

Bitcoin is a virtual currency that allows people to skip banks and traditional payment processes to pay for things. 
Many also warn that Bitcoin's meteoric rise will soon come to an abrupt end and pop like many other speculative bubbles before it. 

Sure, but when? 3493843]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAWGX3TLIEFVYZYB6KAZLURMFKS3SZNLVBRTTABARFRCAAAAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/873/812/873812B39A9E6C86AA79C1BEF61EF03A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bitcoin 10]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[000]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bitcoin cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bitcoin blockchain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bitcoin CME]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
