<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/saudi-doles-out-construction-contracts-for-neom-palaces-3557655</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Saudi doles out construction contracts for Neom palaces 3557655]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JEDDAH, SAUDI ARABIA —Saudi Arabia's awarded the first construction contracts for its Neom mega city project in mid-February.

According to Reuters, Saudi Arabia asked companies to develop five palaces in the massive business zone. NEOM is part of Saudi's aim to diversify its economy away from oil and will reportedly be powered by renewable energy.

According to British newspaper the Independent, the area NEOM is to be built upon is 33 times larger than New York City. The city will also reportedly have its own judicial system, separate from the rest of Saudi Arabia. 3557655]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLWXYZIBRHWADTEKFIRZLDTGRAVRFINKSLA3FCSAFIWEVZEKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0DB/BA3/0DBBA3EEA2BD4352A14B834A78DE21DF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-02-28T09:29:09+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>38</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saudi mega city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saudi arabia mega city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saudi arabia new city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saudi arabia vision 2030]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saudi arabia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NEOM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neom mega city]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/prototype-hyperloop-commuter-pod-unveiled-in-dubai-3557647</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Prototype Hyperloop commuter pod unveiled in Dubai 3557647]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES — A full-scale hyperloop pod model was unveiled on Thursday, giving locals a glimpse into the future of Dubai transport.

The Khaleej Times reports that the Virgin Hyperloop One and Dubai's Road Transport Authority developed a prototype commuter pod for the hyperloop system, which can travel up to 1,200 kilometers per hour.

Pods are divided into two classes, the gold class which can seat five passengers, and the silver, which can accommodate fourteen.

Travel time from Dubai to Abu Dhabi is currently an hour and a half by car, but will take only twelve minutes via hyperloop.

Initial tests estimate the pod can transport 10,000 people to and from Dubai every hour.

Passengers won't not be able to see through any windows to avoid discomfort from the speed, but will be able access entertainment and information systems on the armrests.

Though the project is still under testing, the high-speed transportation system could launch as early as 2020. 3557647]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZBRCXZELBKWIYKFLVBF56LRGEAVRRKSKSJFMUAKKZCWCD3WKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BE7/142/BE714237EC066607F03FC923AEFEA750.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-02-28T09:22:53+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hyperloop one]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hyperloop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hyperloop dubai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hyperloop commuter pod]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hyperloop pod]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virgin hyperloop one]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ commuter pod]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ passenger pod]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dubai rta]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/southwest-flight-forced-to-turn-back-after-engine-fire-3557519</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Southwest flight forced to turn back after engine fire 3557519]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY, UTAH — A Southwest flight was forced to make an emergency landing in Salt Lake City on Monday morning after its engine burst into flames. 

Southwest Flight 604 took off from Salt Lake on its way to LAX, right after takeoff, witnesses on the ground said they heard an explosion and saw the engine spitting flames. Always a good sign. 

Luckily, the pilots were alerted about the flaming wing. After alerting Air Traffic Control, the pilot decided it would be in their best interests to hang a u-ey back to the airport. 

Passengers were switched to a different aircraft and eventually made it to LAX in one piece. 3557519]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AWKDAFLIARGYCDLSJAV9BAMRAV5SK3ABLAXGKRAZCFGDABAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4FE/89C/4FE89C845C9F478440DB1781FCF4A36A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-02-28T07:25:47+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southwest plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southwest Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ engine fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ engine catches fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airplane engine fire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fifa-likely-to-use-video-assistant-referees-in-2018-world-cup-3557502</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[FIFA likely to use Video Assistant Referees in 2018 World Cup 3557502]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RUSSIA — FIFA are likely to use video assistant referees (VAR) during this summer's World Cup, according to Reuters.

The technology allows soccer referees and their assistants to review game footage while a match is being played. According to Reuters, it has gained notoriety in Italy's Serie A league where it has caused in-games delays over decisions involving disallowed goals and revoked penalties.

The facts are that from almost 1,000 matches which were tested, the accuracy rate of the referees went up from 93 percent to 99 percent, FIFA President Gianni Infantino told Reuters earlier this week. If we, or I, can do something to make sure that the World Cup is not decided by a referee's mistakes, then I think it's our duty to do it.

UEFA boss Aleksander Ceferin said VAR wouldn't feature in the Champions League next season, explaining the technology needed more time to be learned by fans and referees. 3557502]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNWCYADAACWGYA9LRARV6DRGZDSXEC6K2IRTHRGAEDRGVKXKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4FE/89C/4FE89C845C9F478440DB1781FCF4A36A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-02-28T06:54:49+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ VAR football technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ FIFA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Video Assistant Referees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ What is VAR]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ VAR explained]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/judge-says-pharma-bro-shkreli-liable-for-10-4-million-in-losses-3557455</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Judge says pharma bro Shkreli liable for $10.4 million in losses 3557455]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — Pharma Bro Martin Shkreli's hopes to stay out of prison were dealt a big blow Monday after a judge ruled he was liable for $10.4 million in loses.  

Shkreli and his douchey lawyers had been hoping the bro would receive either no time in prison or maybe 16 months or less for his securities fraud conviction. 

Judge Kiyo Matsumoto's ruling could mean that Shkreli might be looking at a whole lot of salad tossing in the future.  
  
As a rule, the higher the loss amount of a crime, the longer the prison sentence suggested by a calculation of the federal guidelines. 
 
This means that the judge will likely be asking for a prison term of up to a decade or more for Shkreli when she sentences him on March 9. 3557455]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2LWIYIEBRAFEYZVBSJAX9JFNEEV7E34AIBWVTZBK6KAMBRFKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B34/6BC/B346BCAA8DF8CBD9600A838543C7A6A0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-02-28T05:39:53+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pharma Bro Shkreli]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Martin Shkreli]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Martin Shkreli liable]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Martin Shkreli prison]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Martin Shkreli sentencing]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/georgia-high-school-teacher-fires-gun-in-empty-classroom-3558453</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Georgia high school teacher fires gun in empty classroom 3558453]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DALTON, GEORGIA — A Georgia teacher has been arrested for firing his weapon inside a classroom.

The incident comes days after Trump and his NRA buddies proposed that arming would help prevent school tragedies.

The Atlanta Journal-Constitution reports that on Wednesday morning, Dalton High School teacher Jesse Randall Davidson locked himself in a classroom and pulled out a gun he had hidden in his computer case.

When the principal tried to unlock the door with his key, Davidson closed it on him and fired a single bullet through the window.

Students and faculty were quickly led out of the building. No one was hurt apart from a female student who injured her ankle while evacuating.

The school's resource officer talked to Davidson and eventually persuaded him to surrender after a 45-minute standoff.

No one knows why the 53-year-old did what he did, though local reports do say he once tried to confess to having someone murdered.

For now, he's facing charges of aggravated assault, carrying a weapon on school grounds, terroristic threats, reckless conduct, possession of a firearm during commission of a crime, and disrupting a public school. 3558453]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KADWGYZCKVEWMBCHL5AAR6LSGEEVTEZKKJPRZHAHA6JW3VCYAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0BD/FD0/0BDFD06831284447879F76FEEA75AD86.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armed teacher]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ teacher fires gun]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[teacher with gun]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dalton school incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dalton high school]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/crazy-weather-makes-north-pole-warmer-than-the-rest-of-europe-3558445</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Crazy weather makes North Pole warmer than the rest of Europe 3558445]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH POLE — It may still be the middle of winter, but the weather in the North Pole has gotten so warm it may as well be summer.

The Atlantic reports that Arctic sea ice typically develops a thick layer from late September to early March, with temperatures in the region normally below freezing.

This year's Arctic winter, however, is unusually warm. Temperatures have risen to over 36 degrees above normal, and sea ice has started melting.

According to The Guardian, a theory known as 'warm arctic, cold continents' suggests that as the polar vortex becomes unstable, warm air is taken in and cold air expelled. The North Pole gets hotter as a result, while certain parts of Europe are subjected to unusually frigid weather.

Though the theory itself remains debatable, the fact remains that whatever changes happen in the Arctic has a huge impact on the rest of the world. 3558445]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDFMCZBKRGAEBZSLRCR7KLYMVBE5E36A2PWPUZGAJKARAKRAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/05B/BD8/05BBD8B3A8B745628242390E5FD32686.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Arctic warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warming Arctic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Pole warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Arctic heatwave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Arctic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Pole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm Arctic cold continents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ europe cold front]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snow in Rome]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-research-reckons-earth-birthed-the-moon-3558401</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New research reckons Earth birthed the moon 3558401]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE— Researchers theorize that the moon was created inside Earth in a new study published this week.

The most prominent lunar formation theory holds that the moon was formed when a Mars-sized object named Theia hit Earth 4.6 billion years ago. A cocktail of rock and metal erupted from both celestial bodies, mixing together to birth the moon.

New research posits that a collision with something did occur but instead created a 
giant donut-like spinning mass of vaporized rock called a synestia. Researchers believe the moon was fashioned inside this — potentially over hundreds of years — by atmospheric pressure, extreme heat and rock.

Details of the findings were published in the Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets. 3558401]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NFKXREBAHWGVKFLIDA3L4SGEEBIRRQA2LAZTZFA5CR7WKXKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A08/FCF/A08FCF0E2C4346EEB932DD464D62D58A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how was the moon created]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how did the moon get created]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ synestia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what made the moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ synesita animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lunar research]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ origin of the moon]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-kid-pees-on-elevator-controls-gets-stuck-inside-3558282</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese kid pees on elevator controls, gets stuck inside 3558282]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA — When this kid from Chongqing, China used an elevator, he just had to be a little different. 

He jumped on the elevator on Feb 23 and then decided he would release some soy sauce from his little dragon. 

He one ups himself, setting his sights high — on the elevator control panels.  

After he was ready to get off, karma kicked in and the door malfunctioned, scaring the piss out of the kid. 

Tinkle-toes later had to be rescued by maintenance crews. 

The yellow rainer told the rescuers that he did not do it, and his dad believes him.

Unfortunately, the video exposes some leaks in the kid's story. 3558282]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCFXDCVKZARKAKFKFJAILDYMZBBRE35AZAW5HRGKNLRAA32KD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/31F/72E/31F72E2BFD9E4D2982F2D3564B4F0E00.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elevator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese boy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese boy in elevator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy stuck in elevator]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/meet-josef-pwag-%E2%80%94-kim-jong-un-s-1990s-alter-ego-3558241</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Meet Josef Pwag — Kim Jong Un's 1990s alter ego 3558241]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — North Korean mega belly Kim Jong Un and his dictator daddio Kim Jong Il reportedly traveled on Brazilian passports during the 1990s.

Fats traversed the globe as one Josef Pwag, while Il meandered the world as Ichong Tchoi. According to Reuters, the Brazilian passports were authentic, but the IDs: not so much.

Apparently Josef and Ichong traveled all over in the 1990s, from Hong Kong to Brazil. 
Word is they both took some time for R&R in Tokyo too. 3558241]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LWPCCVAVGRCAASBWKAX9DWM2JBKRK2AEDFVUREASLF5AREKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9C7/F4E/9C7F4EE785464EEDBA3AD16991061361.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un fake passport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un brazil passport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ josef pwag]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ichung tchoi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea brazil passport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un holiday]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong il fake passport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dprk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brazil]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korean passports]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-cities-exploding-with-solid-bed-bug-numbers-3558212</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. cities exploding with solid bed bug numbers 3558212]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — Baltimore ranked number one for the second straight year on Orkin's annual Top 50 Bed Bug Cities list.
The Atlanta-based pest control company published the list on Monday and it's based on the most home and commercial treatments for bed bugs from December 2016 to November 2017, Bloomberg reported.
Baltimore came in first, Washington second, Chicago third, Los Angeles fourth and Columbus in fifth.

Bed bug numbers were reduced after WWII, but have since made a comeback due to increased traveling, regulatory restrictions on insecticides such as DDT and tolerance to organic pesticides.

One research firm found that the bed bug control industry was worth around US$611.2 million in 2016, with some analysts estimating industry revenue could hit US$1 billion in five years, according to Bloomberg.

According to one report, hotels spend on average of US$6,383 per bed bug incident, which includes the replacement cost for soft-goods, treatment and lost business. 3558212]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLWPCTSAVGRGCTFBADRT6DUGEDVRF3ZAEAWZHTTK5BA7VZGKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/165/92C/16592C302B4CACD1789FEFE1232E32B9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bed bugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bed bug infestation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bed bug treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pest control]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pest control treatments]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Orkin]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/doctors-figure-out-what-s-causing-mysterious-polio-like-illness-in-kids-3559509</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Doctors figure out what's causing mysterious polio-like illness in kids 3559509]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AURORA, COLORADO — Doctors have long been stumped by polio-like illness that's been causing paralysis in kids, but now that mystery may have finally been solved.

According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, acute flaccid myelitis or AFM is a rare condition that causes inflammation in the spinal cord. Symptoms include facial and eyelid drooping, difficulty swallowing, muscle weakness, and paralysis.

The U.S. had an outbreak of the disease in 2014, with 120 confirmed cases, and then again in 2016, with 149 people infected.

Though tests of their spinal fluid yielded nothing, patients with AFM tested positive for a respiratory virus known as enterovirus D68, reports KUNC.

Repeated experiments on infected mice showed that EV-D68 killed nerve cells in the spinal cord, which resulted in partial paralysis.

While the findings are significant and could help doctors figure out how to control the disease, many unanswered questions remain.

Direct evidence from infected human tissue is needed to officially confirm the link between the disease and the virus. Until such time, health officials are hoping there won't be another resurgence of the crippling illness. 3559509]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASNWIYCXB5HFIACHL6IRZK2AMVDSTU33KSIWRHZFKZAFZVIBBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C79/3E3/C793E379BEA5C148E2E89EDD2966B15A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  paralysis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acute flaccid myelitis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ AFM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polio]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polio like illness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spine paralysis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mystery illness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ev-d68]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ enterovirus d68]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ enterovirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kids disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ respiratory disease]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/canadian-man-sorry-for-eating-his-pet-pig-molly-3559371</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Canadian man sorry for eating his pet pig Molly 3559371]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRITISH COLUMBIA, CANADA — A man who adopted a potbellied pig, but then ate it, is now apologizing after getting slammed online. 
Molly the pig was one of 57 oinkers rescued and nursed back to health by the BC SPCA. She was adopted in January, and dinner by February. 
In a since-deleted Facebook post, the man said Molly tried to break through a glass door and was aggressive towards a dog. 
The man and his girlfriend then did what most animal lovers would do, they made Molly into Canadian bacon. 
The bro is now apologizing after receiving some very un-Canadian-like messages online and over the phone. Ah — so you know it's sincere. 
Needless to say, the BC SPCA was less than pleased when they found out, and so was the rest of Canada, eh? 3559371]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DWPYIFKMGWKC3EB6PRZ9LYMFJE5FC9A2IFMHKSKZBF3VTWAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/18C/F28/18CF280E7BAB94B3CB7FDFD542491A91.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Canadian bacon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pet pig]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ adopted pet pig]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Molly pet pig]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ adopted pig]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rescued pig]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/toddler-allergic-to-water-including-her-own-sweat-and-tears-3559216</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Toddler allergic to water, including her own sweat and tears 3559216]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HASTINGS, MINNESOTA — An 18-month-old girl suffers from a condition where she is allergic to water, including her own sweat and tears. 

Ivy Angerman, from Hastings, Minnesota, was diagnosed with aquagenic urticaria in October, People reported.  

It's an extremely rare condition where hives form on the skin when it comes in contact with water. 

Urticaria can break out for several reasons, including food allergies, a reaction to very hot or very cold temperatures, scratching or rubbing. 

Currently, the only treatment for aquagenic urticaria is taking antihistamines before being exposed to water. 

Those who have the condition are also advised to wear moisture-wicking clothing and keep an even keel temperature to prevent sweating. 
It can also help to take quick shower and to never bath. 3559216]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKRMC3SAFPAGAI9BJPWZKDVGZBVXEZKKIDW7GCWAVCW7AKYAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D74/B5F/D74B5FDD3ED721176FA5842238B5C85D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>349</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ allergy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ allergic to water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water allergy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aquagenic urticaria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ allergies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ allergic hives]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/over-1-000-asian-ticks-infested-a-n-j-sheep-and-farm-last-summer-and-no-one-knows-how-3559209</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Over 1,000 Asian ticks INFESTED a N.J. sheep and farm last summer and no one knows how 3559209]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HUNTERDON COUNTY, NEW JERSEY — U.S. health officials last month reported an infestation of Asian ticks on a New Jersey sheep.

Samples from the 12-year-old Icelandic sheep were provided to the Hunterdon County Health Department in August, 2017. The animal's owner, reports NPR, found ticks on her arms during a shearing session.

Officials believed them to be deer ticks initially, but further analysis determined they were Asian ticks. They collected over 1,000 from the sheep's paddock and hundreds from the animal itself, according to NPR. 

The animal and property were treated with chemicals. A follow-up visit by county workers found no remaining ticks.

Details of the infestation were published in the Journal of Medical Entomology. 3559209]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6LAPCCWAJPRAXZ7BJJRXKJFMRDBVU39AFIF3TZBBRGRVAIGLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/37B/886/37B886662A3293B9248EEF6F35EF5907.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ticks on animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asian tick infestation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ticks on animal removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tick compilation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new jersey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asian tick]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is a tick]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-kid-pees-on-elevator-controls-gets-stuck-inside-3559186</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese kid pees on elevator controls, gets stuck inside 3559186]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA — When this kid from Chongqing, China used an elevator, he just had to be a little different. 

He jumped on the elevator on Feb 23 and then decided he would release some soy sauce from his little dragon. 

He one ups himself, setting his sights high — on the elevator control panels.  

After he was ready to get off, karma kicked in and the door malfunctioned, scaring the piss out of the kid. 

Tinkle-toes later had to be rescued by maintenance crews. 

The yellow rainer told the rescuers that he did not do it, and his dad believes him.

Unfortunately, the video exposes some leaks in the kid's story. 3559186]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIFPDIAARGRKAISLIART7LTGEESIR32LRAF7TAKA5AA5CK3AH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5E3/B50/5E3B50FCDE00345A7CA1801C180659E6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elevator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese boy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese boy in elevator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy stuck in elevator]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/stunning-instagram-supermodel-is-actually-generated-by-computer-3559052</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Stunning Instagram supermodel is actually generated by computer 3559052]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INSTAGRAM — Supermodel Shudu Gram has already taken social media by storm but there's one catch — she's not real.

Many fans have been convinced Shudu is a real supermodel and have posted many comments on how perfect she is and her amazing figure, and some are even asking her how tall she is and for her to share her skincare routine.

Shudu is actually a CGI model created by a fashion photographer, who said he was learning how to create 3D imagery and he had the chance to create a model however he wanted, so he created the most beautiful woman he could.

The photographer later updated Shudu's bio explaining that she's a digital model.

Meanwhile, debates over Shudu continue on the Twittersphere, while on Instagram people are just working out that the model they've been calling the most beautiful woman in the world doesn't actually exist. 3559052]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJACDTXA2NRMDRSBIBAT7SFMBIEXRRQK2PWZGZAKMDWVAANAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/847/6C1/8476C12FF1E545EA9D575D147C0AACC5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shudu gram model]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shudu gram instagram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shudu gram cgi model]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shudu gram not real]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ computer generated models]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CGI models]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cameron-James Wilson]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/11-year-old-gets-elf-ears-fixed-after-being-bullied-at-school-3558927</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[11-year-old gets 'elf ears' fixed after being bullied at school 3558927]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RICHMOND, VIRGINIA — It's a sad and twisted world we live in that children have to resort to extreme measures to protect themselves from bullying.

WRIC reports that 11-year-old Bella Harrington was teased mercilessly for her ears, which classmates said looked like an elf's. Her parents kept telling her it didn't matter what the other kids thought, but the taunts stuck with the Richmond, Virginia pre-teen.

In the end, the family turned to pediatric cosmetic surgeon, Dr. Joe Niamtu, who 'corrected' the young girl's ears in December. It was a small change, but Bella, at least, is happier now.

She's also not the only one to get this done. Apparently, doctors believe treating younger kids is better, since it spares them from the psychological trauma of bullying.

And while it's definitely heartbreaking, it's probably going to keep on until we as a species learn to be decent to each other. 3558927]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKRAY3SAFNFPCR9BNKRX7U3GFJV5URILWIW5HKSAZCACXREBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E8B/DD9/E8BDD917A88743EFB2664975641D9110.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bullying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmetic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pediatric cosmetic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ school bullying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elf ears]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bella harrington]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-yorkers-paying-a-lot-for-cheap-chinese-cough-syrup-3558852</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New Yorkers paying a lot for cheap Chinese cough syrup 3558852]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — As the flu season slams the U.S., good old Americans are looking for relief anywhere they can find it. 

In the Big Apple, it looks like people have finally discovered Nin Jiom's Pi Pa Gao, a Chinese herbal remedy made in Hong Kong. 

It helps soothe sore throats, relieve coughs and reduce phlegm with its special sauce, lettuce, cheese. 

In Asia, a bottle probably costs 5 to 6 bucks, but according to Wall Street Journal, a bottle can run as high as $70 through online third-party retailers. 

But not to fear, Amazon and Walmart have cheaper prices, but if you want it China cheap, head down to some of those old school Chinatown pharmacies. 3558852]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMCFXCAJKAARAC3HB5BAV92AMEESTRRQK6JRZUCSKACAVXIGKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E9E/115/E9E115A8633C4B329F4A9D096A5E5540.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Chinese cough syrup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Nin Jiom Pi Pa Gao]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Nin Jiom Pei Pa Koa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[New Yorkers Chinese cough syrup]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-discover-new-species-of-tardigrade-in-japan-parking-lot-3559627</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists discover new species of TARDIGRADE in Japan parking lot 3559627]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TSURUOKA, JAPAN — Researchers have found a new species of Tardigrade in a Tsuruoka City, Japan parking lot.

After the initial finding in Japan, researchers were unable to identify which type of tardigrade it was. Writing in the journal PLOS One, scientists designated the creature as Macrobiotus shonaicus.  According to Newsweek, 20 new species are found annually.

They bare resemblance to some other species of tardigrade, but the new species is noted for its unique eggs. These have lengthy tentacles and a solid exterior.

The research was carried out by scientists in Japan and Poland. 3559627]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLAICIJAWKRCB3ELBIRTK4VMNJVXU39AFLF3GTWKAGW7BAEKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E26/7CA/E267CAB2CD9BD03E94ACBD47C2C94330.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tardigrade under microscope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tardigrade]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ macrobiotus shonaicus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new species of tardigrade]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new species found]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tardigrade teeth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tardigrade egg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weird nature]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tardigrade eggs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan tardigrade]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/internet-connected-devices-could-be-hacked-to-mine-cryptocurrency-3561188</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Internet-connected devices could be hacked to mine cryptocurrency 3561188]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BARCELONA, SPAIN — Internet-connected devices could be at risk from hijacking by hackers and used to mine cryptocurrencies, according to cybersecurity firm Avast. 
Avast ran a demonstration at the Mobile World Congress in Barcelona, Spain which had several devices hijacked to run cryptocurrency mining software, CNBC reported. 

Based on their calculations, if hackers could attack 15,000 devices, they could be used to mine $1,000 worth of Monero digital cash in four days. 
A theoretical attack would start with hackers taking over a network of devices and then using that combined computing power to mine digital currency. 
Unlike Bitcoin, which requires substantial computing power to mine, Monero can be mined using a network of internet-connected devices.
Monero has grown in popularity among criminals as it advertises itself as being one of the most anonymous digital coins available. 3561188]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMCFIAAJL5DRAWZ7KBJR7L4UMVBETFKSKBKWZH3YBSIAPVZJBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DE1/1CD/DE11CD63E51C42CDB9E8E949FB2B941A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet of things]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet connected devices]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency mining]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/brain-surgeon-operates-on-wrong-patient-3561175</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Brain surgeon operates on wrong patient 3561175]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KENYA — A neurosurgeon from Kenya's biggest hospital has been suspended for operating on the wrong patient. 

The Kenyatta National Hospital said the doctor, two nurses and an anaesthetist have all been suspended pending an investigation. The CEO of the hospital was also suspended, the Guardian reported. 

Apparently, two men had been taken to the hospital last Sunday. One needed surgery to remove a blot clot in his brain, while the other needed some meds for head inflammation. 

It wasn't until hours into the surgery when doctors found no blood clot, and realized they cracked open the wrong head. 
In a statement to the public the hospital said it, deeply regrets this event and has done all it can to ensure the safety and well-being of the patient in question.
Kenyatta National Hospital is the country's largest and oldest hospital, which also serves as a teaching hospital. 3561175]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIWAXTTBIBWVBR9BJPRTL44MSLS5RKRLVBRVUCTAWJACV3VBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/672/C46/672C461C77504D1ABA54057672717476.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgery gone wrong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgery fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain surgery on wrong patient]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ doctor operates wrong patient]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/drunk-man-s-uber-ride-home-from-to-jersey-was-uber-expensive-3560940</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Drunk man's Uber ride home from to Jersey was uber expensive 3560940]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WEST VIRGINIA AND NEW JERSEY — A New Jersey man went to a party in West Virginia and got so drunk that he took a $1,600 Uber ride back home.

Kenneth Bachman of Sewell, N.J., was visiting friends last week near West Virginia University and went to a fraternity party. After a fun night with the bros, Bachman did the right thing and hired an Uber to take him home. The only problem? Home was a five-hour ride away and Bachman thought he was going back to the place he was staying during this trip.

The driver was definitely up for the job, and when Bachman got home, the fare was a whopping $1,635.93, man, that's not how you wanna end a trip. To make matters worse, he accidentally ordered an Uber XL, which is the more expensive ride. But Bachman was a good sport and paid the driver, and was gave the driver a five-star rating.

Uber said the driver did what Bachman wanted and the company has been in touch with him and he apparently agreed to pay the fare. 

Bachman said he's gonna go back to West Virginia to pick up his bags, and wanted people to say what's up if they see him. 3560940]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLFAACSBVBRABIWBICWRK4SMJLSIRAMAJLWVH3RK2JWMD3XAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BBE/52C/BBE52C56ABBF443E872448131292445A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ expensive uber ride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ $1600 uber ride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drunk man uber ride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ most expensive uber ride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber xl ride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ expensive uber xl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ west virginia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new jersey]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/oklahoma-zoo-lioness-suddenly-grows-a-mane-3560918</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Oklahoma Zoo lioness suddenly grows a mane 3560918]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OKLAHOMA CITY — Vets at the Oklahoma zoo were downright baffled after one of their female charges began to grow a very distinctly male feature.

A blog post from the Oklahoma Zoo reports that after spending 18 normal years as a fierce female, Bridget the African lioness suddenly began sprouting a manly mane, that by November had already resembled Santa's beard. 

Curiously, the luscious locks didn't seem to be contagious, and hadn't come with any behavioral changes.

Maned lionesses aren't unheard of, but usually the extra testosterone feeding the mane of glory also gives them increased aggression and male mating behaviors. In one case, a lioness named Emma's full mane growth was attributed to testosterone-producing ovaries, which when taken out caused the mane to disappear.

Bridget's zoo has taken a blood sample to figure out if it's a testosterone issue. Though it's also possible she has a benign tumor on the adrenal or pituitary gland.

In any case, her handlers aren't too worried, since the extra hair doesn't seem to be affecting their big girl's health. 3560918]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLAMCTSBWKRVVCEBNIA3L4SM6IB3SZIKBJAXUAGAZAAMAKWLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8E2/BBB/8E2BBB7E4C9E43999DAE2B116206C47D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lioness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maned lioness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lioness grows mane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Botswana maned lioness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ king of the jungle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bridget]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Oklahoma zoo]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/why-you-can-t-see-all-the-space-garbage-in-photos-of-earth-3560905</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Why you can't see all the space garbage in photos of Earth 3560905]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE JUNKYARD — There's thousands of debris floating around Earth, but none show up in images of the planet.

Writing in 2013, NASA reported there was half-a-million pieces of space debris floating near Earth. This is a mix of old satellites, rockets and spacecraft or spacecraft parts.

Whenever a spacecraft photographs the entire planet the image is typically taken from thousands of kilometers away. Space debris aren't visible at this distance.

Closer spacecraft also shoot photos of Earth. The International Space Station (ISS) is around 400 km above the planet but space debris can appear as miniscule at this range.

Much of these objects vary in size, but one of the largest spacecraft near Earth is the ISS. It measures 109 meters at its widest points, while the planet itself is over 12,000 kilometers in diameter. Meaning, even that is just 0.00085% the size of Earth. 3560905]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LICFMAIIL5CRCAIULJJAZ7URMBKE7RC6KSKFVTAKAVBWIDIGKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/16A/A60/16AA60A8762A40F3B003462348AEF624.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space junk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ why cant we see space junk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debris around Earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debri]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ old spacecraft]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/florida-python-devours-much-bigger-and-heavier-deer-3561993</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Florida python devours much bigger and heavier deer 3561993]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EVERGLADES, FLORIDA — A conservancy in Florida recently released a series of photos of a hungry Burmese python devouring a much bigger deer.

In April of 2015, wildlife biologists and land managers from Collier-Seminole State Park spotted an 11-year-old female Burmese python that had swallowed a large prey. After moving the stuffed predator to an open area, it vomited out a young white-tailed deer, yuck.

Quick fact, snakes usually vomit the prey out of their body if they feel threatened, and expelling their food gives them a better chance at fleeing.

The guys then weighed the animals and turns out the python was 31.5 pounds and the deer was 35 pounds, which means the prey was heavier than its predator.

Biologists are also questioning if the Burmese python may be harming the population of white-tailed deer by preying on young fawns before they are old enough to mate. 

The conservancy said they are learning valuable information that is helping them to push back against invasive species like the python that is significantly and negatively impacting the wildlife. 3561993]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDWMCTXKMDACBR7B6IW56LXMZCBRS3ZKEDA5HALKRAAMX35KA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/424/CB0/424CB0CE48BD6CAE466CAFFB48F7198B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ python and deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ python deer florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ python devours]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ python food chain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ python vomits entire deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ python vomits]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ python eats deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ everglades]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/untreated-depression-can-cause-brain-inflammation-3561978</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Untreated depression can cause brain inflammation 3561978]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TORONTO — A new study suggests that untreated depression could lead to brain inflammation. 
Researchers from the Centre for Addiction and Mental Health discovered people with untreated depression for more than a decade had more brain inflammation than those who had untreated depression for a shorter period, Science Alert reported. 
The study was published on Feb. 26 in The Lancet Psychiatry. 
The study looked at 80 participants: 25 people with untreated depression for more than 10 years, 25 people with untreated depression for less than 10 years, and 30 people as a control group without depression. 

Using positron emission tomography or PET brain imaging, the team looked for translocator proteins, an inflammation marker produced by the body's microglia — central nervous system immune cells.  

Scientists found people suffering from longer terms of untreated depression had 30 percent higher levels of the translocator protein. 

Long-term depression sufferers also had higher levels of inflammation compared with the control group. 

The next step will be to collect more data, but researchers hope this will lead to new approaches in how depression is treated, specifically medications that target inflammation. 3561978]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KWXYAFAEFWPBCEL6KWT7LVMJKETE39AVAFPTIDBVHRIYIEBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B31/68D/B3168DA766D1D8259A313018463775E2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Depression]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ depression treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ depression brain inflammation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ inflammation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ inflammation and depression]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/selfies-make-your-nose-look-30-wider-3561966</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Selfies make your nose look 30% wider 3561966]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEWARK, NEW JERSEY — If you think your nose looks humongous in that selfie, you're probably right. But going under the knife isn't going to fix it.

CNN reports that 55% of plastic surgeons in a 2017 poll reportedly had patients who wanted surgery to look better in selfies, which have been known to distort people's features.

Using mathematical modelling, a Rutgers University study found that selfies taken from the standard portrait distance of 5 feet produced no distortion on the subject's nose.

But those taken from just 12 inches away made the nose appear 30% wider in men, and 29% in women.

This is due to perspective. With a camera close to the subject, the nose looks larger as it's nearer to it than the rest of the face. But further away, the facial features are at a similar distance from the camera, and appear flat and proportionate.

The good news is that there's a simple fix. Just get a selfie stick that can snap your photo from five feet away, or have someone else take it.

Bottom line, there's easier and cheaper ways to look good in a selfie than getting a nose job. 3561966]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWKACXRHABIWCWR7LWKAI9USMNIBISANKNJFVFADBWIACY3WKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FAE/ABD/FAEABD59932B12F7B6BB88E4E9EDB078.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie distortion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie nose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nose distortion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bigger nose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nose surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rhinoplasty]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/apple-employees-keep-walking-into-glass-walls-and-calling-911-3561900</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Apple employees keep walking into glass walls and calling 911 3561900]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA — Apple's brand new, glass galore headquarters is turning quite a few heads. It's also cracking quite a few heads open as well. 

Bloomberg reported last month that Apple workers were accidentally running into glass panes or walls in the new complex.  

Well, it's been a month and people are still bumping their heads, so much so that there are now 911 transcripts of freaked out Apple nerds who don't walk very well, the San Francisco Chronicle reported. 

Transcripts for three calls were obtained by the paper, taken during a three-day stretch in early January. 

The transcripts look ridiculous on paper, and even sillier when read aloud. They all involve Apple workers and no doubt too much looking at your phone, and not where you're going.
Apple should really kick it up a notch and make the floors and ceilings all glass too. 3561900]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIAPXZJASLWAB3DLFKAT9BFNABE7UTRLWPRZHCTA5CFECIIAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9BF/772/9BF772E2397C82DA39A6CC8B7C3548D2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Apple headquarters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Apple employees glass]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Apple workers running into glass]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walking into glass door]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walking into glass]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-may-have-made-up-to-200-million-on-bitcoin-3561859</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea may have made up to $200 million on Bitcoin 3561859]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — The hermit kingdom has found a way to rake in the dough despite intense global pressure over its nuclear capabilities.

Reuters reports that the U.S. will be imposing sanctions on 28 ships, 27 companies, and one person believed to be helping North Korea, in a bid to pressure the regime to give up on developing weapons.

But according to former National Security Agency official Priscilla Moriuchi, the North is earning millions through cryptocurrency, and may be turning it into cash or goods to fund their nuclear and ballistic missiles program.

The North Koreans reportedly obtained 11,000 bitcoins through mining and hacking in 2017, which is valued between $120 to 210 million.

Evidence suggests they have cyber operations setup in several foreign locations, including China, India, and Southeast Asia.

The reclusive nation is believed to be behind multiple cyber attacks in recent years, like the Wanna Cry ransomware, the Bank of Bangladesh theft, and a South Korean cryptocurrency heist.

With the North Koreans capitalizing on the anonymity of cryptocurrency, experts believe more international regulation is crucial in blocking their shadowy activities. 3561859]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEDAGXADKJJWGBTFKFJAK9L4GZDVRFIKKMDWPGZCKEBAPXIHBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E06/F13/E06F138637F2506A69E8A34A827A2751.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea sanctions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear program]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea nuclear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptomining]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hackers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korean hackers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-uses-predictive-policing-to-target-ethnic-minorities-in-xinjiang-3561601</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China uses predictive policing to target ethnic minorities in Xinjiang 3561601]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA — China is using big data to target ethnic minorities in Xinjiang, detaining them on the basis that they may someday threaten the government.

Human Rights Watch reports that Beijing has been using surveillance cameras with facial recognition technology, wifi sniffers, and police checkpoints to monitor the country's Uyghur population.

Data from these sources, as well as existing health, banking and other records, feeds into the Integrated Joint Operations Platform, a system that uses predictive policing to flag down potential threats.

Authorities personally visit flagged individuals and gather more information about their families and ideological situation, but can take into custody anyone deemed suspicious, whether or not they've committed a crime.

Most detainees are sent to political education centers, where they are reportedly indoctrinated in Chinese socialist ideology.

Reports estimate that roughly 120,000 people are being held indefinitely, without charge or trial, inside the camps. 3561601]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKWAC3SAEAAAWARBVBA5LSHMIBB3F34KSIW3HZLA6JFAWIIKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CEE/C39/CEEC39BF9838A840FD80A353B0537DFD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ predictive policing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ minority report]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china surveillance state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china predictive policing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xinjiang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uighurs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uyghurs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china uighurs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ profiling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ IJOP]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ integrated joint operations platform]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china police database]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/syrian-refugees-get-3d-printed-prosthetic-limbs-3562775</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Syrian refugees get 3D printed prosthetic limbs 3562775]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMMAN, JORDAN — 
Doctors looking to 3D technology to provide prosthetic access to poor and wounded refugees in the Middle East.

Médecins Sans Frontières, or Doctors Without Borders, has been working with a hospital in Amman, Jordan to help upper-limb amputees from war-torn nations.

Before designing a prosthetic limb, the team assesses each patient and makes a scan of their stumps.

They use flexible thermoplastic polyurethane to 3D-print the socket and hand, and a firmer plastic to create the forearm. The 3D printed prosthetics take only 24 hours to design and produce and costs only a fraction of the normal price at $20.

When the parts have been assembled together, the limb can be painted to match the patient's skin tone.

Doctors make sure the lightweight prosthetic limb fits comfortably on the stump, ensuring patients will be able to use it long-term, according to their needs. 

Doctors Without Borders is still improving the process, but wants to expand to other missions in the future. 3562775]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KWPDIFBZCAAB3HLNPRK9SBMMEB7UZQAIAF5GILABJAGB3UAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B26/C5B/B26C5B7D7C4140798654EDC59B6EFCA0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthesis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthetics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthetic arm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthetic limbs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D printed prosthetics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D printing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amputees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Doctors without borders]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medecins sans frontieres]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dictator-xi-bans-fun-stuff-like-letter-n-and-animal-farm-3562627</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dictator Xi bans fun stuff like letter "N" and Animal Farm 3562627]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — China's got predictive policing, cops using facial recognition and a social credit system for everyone — and now, a ruler for life. 

And let's not forget the longest and most funnest wall in the world — the Great Firewall of China. 

To celebrate Dictator Xi Da Da's anointing, the CCP has decided to ban fun stuff like the letter 'N' and terms like 'disagree,' 'incapable ruler,' 'I oppose' and a boatload others.  

You're also not going to be able to find terms like George Orwell's 'Animal Farm' or '1984' on the Twitter knockoff Weibo. 

But don't worry China, indefinite will go by real quick. Enjoy. 3562627]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKWACAJBZBRKWKHBMDF79SFM5BV7RAQKSJFMHABKEDAMBTVAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ABC/695/ABC695405639441C8E8BED34EABCB04E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China bans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China censorship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China bans letter N]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China bans Animal Farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China bans 1984]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Emperor Xi Jinping]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/roof-collapses-at-china-airport-amid-strong-winds-3562601</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Roof collapses at China airport amid strong winds 3562601]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NANCHANG, CHINA — Passengers were caught on video screaming in panic on Sunday after series of strong winds ripped off part of the roof of an eastern China airport.

According to China's Huashang Daily, Changbei Airport in Nanchang, Jiangxi province was experiencing high winds and heavy torrential rain Sunday afternoon. The wind speeds reported up to 67 miles per hour, equivalent to a violent storm and one category below a hurricane.

At about 3:30 p.m., like a domino effect, the canopy of Terminal 2 collapsed. Vehicles at the scene drove off while a few were hit by the debris.

Fortunately, no one was hurt from the incident while flights were suspended briefly during the windy period before returning to normal operations on Monday, 3562601]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLFPYIIBVCFACA9BBPRI6BAMMCSKRK5LWIRXFCYAVCWGBRCKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ABC/695/ABC695405639441C8E8BED34EABCB04E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wind ripped off airport roof]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wind ripped off roof]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wind destroys airport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wind destroys building]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[chinese airport wind]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[chinese airport roof rip off]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/you-shouldn-t-charge-your-phone-overnight-and-here-s-why-3562567</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[You shouldn't charge your phone overnight, and here's why 3562567]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — If your phone battery is barely holding up, that might be your fault — you've probably been charging it wrong this whole time.

Time reports that modern smartphones use lithium-ion batteries that charge fast but also get used up quickly because of the sheer amount of mobile activity they power.

People tend to drain their phone batteries before plugging them in overnight. Fortunately, most are equipped with chips that protect against overcharging.

Still, it's unwise to leave a device plugged once its battery is full, since trickle charges can heat up the phone, stressing and wearing down the battery.

Experts recommend charging the phone before it empties completely, and not bringing it to a full charge. Plugging it in occasionally throughout the day ensures the battery retains its capacity longer.

Batteries also don't do well in extreme heat or extreme cold, so make sure it's not exposed to either.

Of course, they will conk out eventually, but it's always nice to prolong that lifespan and save a buck or two. 3562567]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABJWIYCTBADWCWTCLEARTLBFMZASVUT2ABPF5HKWAIBFCDIHAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/221/C97/221C97FA30CB44248BD42923EE780B13.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phone battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smartphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ charging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ overnight charging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lithium ion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lithium ion battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mobile phone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phone maintenance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battery maintenance]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-us-navy-awards-150-mil-contract-for-some-lasers-3562557</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The US Navy awards $150 mil contract for some lasers 3562557]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The U.S. Navy has awarded a $150 million contract for two high-power laser weapons systems by 2020.  
Lockheed Martin has agreed to provide the navy with a high-energy laser and integrated optical-dazzler with surveillance (HELIOS) system, Naval Technology reported. 
The HELIOS system combines a laser weapon, long-range intelligence, surveillance and reconnaissance (ISR) and counter-unmanned aerial system (counter-UAS) capabilities. 
It's designed to counter drones and small boats, as well as provide long-range ISR capabilities to decision-makers. 
The current contract represents the first phase in the navy's surface laser weapon system program, and will see Lockheed Martin supply two laser systems for testing purposes. 
The first unit will be integrated onto an Arleigh-Burke-class destroyer, while the second unit will be used for land testing at the White Sands Missile Range. 3562557]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRCFXDAGL5EACVTCKAAW77LRNFIBIRRNKADR5TCSA5BRAACSAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E5F/BA9/E5FBA9CC72364F1F828925366C0806D4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US Navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Lockheed Martin HELIOS system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high-energy laser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ HELIOS system]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/linebacker-single-handedly-wows-nfl-scouts-at-combine-3563490</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Linebacker single handedly wows NFL scouts at combine 3563490]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INDIANAPOLIS, INDIANA — Whatever you can do with two hands, this guy can do 10 times more with just one. 

Former UCF linebacker Shaquem Griffin hands down killed NFL combine this year. 

Griffin had his left hand amputated at age four because while in the womb, an amniotic band wrapped around his left wrist, preventing it from developing.  

The 6-foot-1, 227 pound 22-year-old caught the eye of scouts when he busted out 20 reps at 225 pounds with a prosthetic hand on the bench.  

Shaquem tore up the turf when he dropped the fastest 40-yard dash for a linebacker since '03 with a 4.38.  

Griffin is projected to be a fifth- or sixth-round pick with his speed and pass rush considered some of his best strengths. 3563490]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLRPCADASIAAWRWLBPF56BHGEDVXFKZAIAFRFAHKZCAGARAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5DD/2A8/5DD2A81C72A343BA95B4494C1D8E5232.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shaquem Griffin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shaquem Griffin NFL combine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shaquem Griffin one handed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Linebacker Shaquem Griffin]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-banks-to-use-ripple-for-blockchain-for-payments-3563452</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese banks to use Ripple for blockchain for payments 3563452]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Japan's financial industry is embracing innovation by looking to blockchain technology to facilitate its payments platform.

CNBC reports that the Japan Bank Consortium, comprised of 61 member banks, is set to release MoneyTap, a Ripple-powered smartphone app that will allow customers to settle transactions in real time.

The country's current system for cash transfers is limited. Transactions can only be processed on weekdays, from 8:30 a.m. to 3:30 p.m., and comes with high fees.

With MoneyTap, customers can make payments and transfers using only a bank account, phone number, or QR code.

Transactions go through the cloud-based Ripple Connect platform. Processing is instant and available 24 hours a day, seven days a week, for a fraction of the normal cost.

The app will go live in the later half of 2018, starting with three major banks, followed by a staggered rollout of the rest of the consortium. 3563452]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVARCDAHKJLAIAKHL6IWX9SCGRABTSC5KEAAXTKXAZDRGA3XAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/002/F42/002F42E33A244E64995601C92F24D987.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blockchain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ripple]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Japan bank consortium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blockchain technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Japan payment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rc cloud]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ripple connect]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cash transfer]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/shocking-brawl-breaks-out-on-a-southwest-airline-to-la-3563324</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Shocking brawl breaks out on a Southwest Airline to LA 3563324]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOUTHWEST AIRLINES — A dramatic brawl with fists flying erupted on a Southwest flight that was waiting to take off from Dallas to LA last week. 

The Southwest flight was preparing to leave Dallas for Los Angeles last Friday before the chaos took place. When things started to rumble, a dude in a grey hoodie was seen throwing punches at a man by a window seat. 

After getting punched by the grey hoodie dude, the man got back up while other passengers tried to calm things down. The grey hoodie guy decided carried on by pushing one of the peacemakers and started punching a man with glasses repeatedly before people pulled him away.

Southwest Airlines said the flight was delayed for an hour due to the fight, and the involved passengers were handed over to local law enforcement as the safety and comfort of their employees and passengers is their top priority. 3563324]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANNWADTSBADRMDRUB5DAX9LWNACVZRC9AADR3GRKKZDFAVCUBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/734/EB5/734EB562CBF04E64BDD5E464FC994EED.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest passengers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest brawl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest passengers brawl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest altercation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airlines brawl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest passengers deplaned]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest flight brawl]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/coca-cola-is-launching-an-alcoholic-drink-in-japan-3563281</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Coca Cola is launching an alcoholic drink in Japan 3563281]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — It took over a century, but Coca Cola is finally dipping its toes into the alcoholic beverages market. The catch? Only in Japan.

The Financial Times reports that with health conscious people now shunning sugar, dismal soda sales have prompted the company to branch out with more innocuous drinks.

Fortunately, they've realized that at least in Japan, the fizzy, sugary stuff sells — but only if you booze it up. Case in point: the Japanese live for Chu-His — alcoholic drinks made from shochu, sparkling water, and fruity flavorings, that's especially popular with the ladies.

Coca Cola wants a slice of that chu-hi pie, and is set to experiment on developing their own unique version.

Local beverage makers may be ahead of the game, but everyone and their obaasan is curious to see what a player like the Coca Cola company will bring to the table.

The soda giant claims it's unlikely they'll be pulling this sort of boozy stunt elsewhere in the world, even though there are plenty of fans jonesing for a stiffer drink. 3563281]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNRICRABBJREWTHLWJRZ72HGMESVS39AVAWVHIBAECRPBRKAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/27B/965/27B9651484754BCB96DD385DB975F3B5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alcoholic coke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coca cola]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chu hi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chu-hi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shochu highball]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boozy coke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japanese coke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japanese alcohol]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/teen-snaps-retainer-after-seeing-michael-b-jordan-s-sexy-bod-3564420</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Teen snaps retainer after seeing Michael B. Jordan's sexy bod 3564420]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Michael B. Jordan is God's gift to women, just ask this 18-year-old, who thirsted after him so hard she broke a mouthpiece.

Anyone who's seen Black Panther will remember the waterfall battle scene, not least because it's the first time we see Killmonger without a shirt.

SFGate reports that San Francisco teen Sophia Robb recalls this scene all too well, since the sight of that sexy sexy bod had her clenching her teeth so hard her retainer snapped. Whoops!

Robb went to see her orthodontist the next day to get it fixed, and had to tell him what happened.

The orthodontist found the story so amusing he put it up on Tumblr, and it took off from there. When Robb came across it on Twitter and realized it was about her, she fessed up online. It was the best decision ever.

Pretty soon, none other than Michael B. Jordan himself got wind of retainer girl, and offered to hook her up with a fancy new mouthpiece- hopefully made from vibranium so it won't ever break.

Guess it's safe to say retainer girl's life is made. 3564420]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NWPAKVBRBRRCTEBRDF79BGNACE7URLAECF5UZGKBLWPBAHAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/542/6DA/5426DA856FF4CEE34937FB789C71D813.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black panther]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ michael b jordan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ killmonger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ erik killmonger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ retainer girl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ girl breaks retainer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sophia robb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marvel movie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marvel universe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mcu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ celebrity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bones-discovered-on-pacific-island-in-1940-possibly-amelia-earhart-s-3564414</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bones discovered on Pacific island in 1940 possibly Amelia Earhart's 3564414]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KNOXVILLE, TENNESSEE — A new study may have the answers to what really happened to Amelia Earhart.

The Washington Post reports that Amelia Earhart vanished over the Pacific Ocean in 1937. Three years later, skeletal remains suspected to be hers were recovered on Nikumaroro Island in present-day Kiribati.

A physician in Fiji examined the bones in 1940 and determined that the remains belonged to a European male.

The bones have since been lost, but recent analysis of the skeletal measurements using modern techniques reveals the bones were in fact female.

Measurements of the arm and leg bones were determined to be a match to Earhart's estimated size and build, making it likely that the remains were hers.

The data shows the bones were more similar to the ill-fated pilot than 99% of individuals in a large sample, though without a way to examine the actual bones, it's difficult to determine an actual match with 100% certainty. 3564414]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIBRICIAKSIAAAAYBRAFR7DWGVBBVEANLSJW7GCSAFKAKWRIAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D95/598/D955989F4E49351F5D87318F9E044472.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amelia earhart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bone analysis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nikumaroro bones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skeleton]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skeletal remains]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nikumaroro island]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ forensic analysis]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-8-billion-lng-pipeline-backed-by-the-taliban-%E2%80%94-for-now-3564138</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[$8 billion LNG pipeline backed by the Taliban — for now 3564138]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AFGHANISTAN — Construction on the Afghan section of an $8 billion natural gas pipeline is being backed by the Taliban, according to Reuters.   

Construction of the pipeline, which will connect Turkmenistan through Afghanistan to Pakistan and India, began last month.

The endorsement of the Taliban is vital as the pipeline will run through many areas under its control, Bloomberg reported. 

The Taliban deems it its responsibility to revive foundational economic and reconstruction work in the country and asks international construction companies to help the Afghans in this regard, Taliban spokesman Zabihullah Mujahed said in a statement last month, according to Bloomberg. 

The TAPI pipeline is expected to carry an annual 33 billion cubic meters of gas along an 1,800 kilometer route. 

It is expected to create thousands of jobs and generate more than $400 million a year in revenue for the Afghan government. 

The Afghan section of the pipeline, with around 804 kilometers controlled by the Taliban, is expected to be completed in two years. 3564138]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KECFEXADKMDFCXZYLJJRXKJCNBLSRR3RABIW3U3RBRHFAB3TBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/32A/392/32A392978A3395249B956C579F4F4CE7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TAPI pipeline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LNG pipeline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taliban backing TAPI pipeline]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Afghanistan LNG pipeline]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/carbon-capture-and-storage-is-here-to-fight-climate-change-3564050</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Carbon capture and storage is here to fight climate change 3564050]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — Congress' recently passed budget bill has incentives to support carbon capture and storage. But what exactly is it?

The CCS Association reports that fossil fuels supply most of the world's energy needs, but harnessing them emits large quantities of carbon dioxide that can cause irreversible environmental damage.

One solution to combat this is carbon capture and storage, which works by first separating carbon dioxide from other gases at industrial facilities.

The captured CO2 is transported using underground pipelines or via ships to suitable storage sites.

It is then injected into rock formations several kilometers below the surface of the Earth, where pressure and temperature conditions keep it in a liquid state.

CCS can capture up to 90% of carbon emissions from fossil fuels, but experts believe it's most effective alongside other strategies, such as improving energy efficiency and switching to renewable energy. 3564050]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRAAMDAGK6JAKDCEBNKWR7SBGJIEZFC3KNKF5HRCAICRPAZCAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5FE/ECD/5FEECD2CB272F376667005DA90AB1029.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon capture and storage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon capture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ccs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon emissions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fossil fuel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ renewable energy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/goal-line-technology-makes-possible-return-at-world-cup-3564001</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Goal-line technology makes possible return at World Cup 3564001]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RUSSIA — Goal-line technology will be back again at the 2018 FIFA World Cup Russia. 

Here's a guide of the two goal-line systems that will be used to help referees decide whether a goal has been scored or not.

One system uses several cameras that have been installed high up within the stadium to determine whether the entire ball has crossed the goal line. The magnetic system tracks the receptors in the ball, and the magnetic fields created through underground cables calculate and determine whether a goal has been scored.

The goal-line technology automatically registers the goal and instantly alerts the referee to the fact that the football has crossed the goal line. The technology will be able to prevent shocking decisions from being made, such as the disallowed goal during a match between England and Germany in the 2010 World Cup in Germany.

According to FIFA, the following goal-line tech systems have been approved by FIFA and the International Football Association Board (IFAB) for use: GoalRef, Hawk-Eye, and GoalControl.

The technology passed its inaugural trial during the 2012 FIFA Club World Cup Japan in December 2012. It has since been used at the 2013 Confederations Cup, 2014 World Cup in Brazil, Euro 2016 in France, 2016 UEFA Champions League and Europa League finals, 2016 Copa America, the English premier league, and the German Bundesliga. 3564001]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACFIXRCKMAFGY3ALIDWRK2FGNKB5STZKMDFRHAAAZHRMAKWAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2BA/18F/2BA18F117FAD4BAAABDBB14F6AC9DB49.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ goal line technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup goal line tech]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ goal-line tech soccer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ goal-line tech football]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia world cup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup technology]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-tests-super-maglev-train-that-can-run-up-to-1-000-kph-3566302</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China tests super-maglev train that can run up to 1,000 kph 3566302]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHENGDU, CHINA — Chinese researchers have developed the world's first testing platform for a new maglev train that can run at ultra-high speeds.

China Central Television reports that China's super-maglev train uses magnetic levitation technology and vacuum tube transport to run at speeds of 1,000 kilometers per hour, faster than narrow-body Boeing 737 or Airbus A320 jets.

To test their prototype, Southwest Jiaotong University scientists led by Professor Deng Xigang constructed a test car and a 45-meter loop with a load capacity of up to one ton.

The superconducting maglev system inside the loop allows the test car to be constantly levitated 20 millimeters above the track, according to a study published in the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Transactions on Power Delivery journal.

Deng and his team are currently conducting trials and aims to complete 400 kilometer per hour runs within the year.

They will still need to conduct 1,000 kph trial runs, tackle safety standards, and deal with high construction and maintenance costs before any super-maglev trains can enter commercial service. 3566302]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRAWKAAGKVBRCBKEBAAFZLD4NFKBIF34KSLW3HRCAWJFPCTSAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E87/182/E87182C6B00B400DA4EDF1DB873AAC06.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super-maglev]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maglev]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maglev test loop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maglev train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maglev technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's first maglev test loop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's first]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first ever]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vacuum tube transport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southwest Jiaotong University]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dentists-keep-dying-from-lung-disease-cdc-doesn-t-know-why-3566096</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dentists keep dying from lung disease, CDC doesn't know why 3566096]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VIRGINIA — Officials at the U.S. Centers for Disease Control are trying to figure out why dentists in Virginia have been dying of a rare form of lung disease. 
The CDC has identified nine dentists or dental workers who were diagnosed with idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis, or IPF, all of whom were treated at the same specialty clinic in Virginia, the agency said in its Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report.

Of the nine cases, seven have died, the report said. 

Around 200,000 people in the U.S. have IPF at any one time, according to the American Thoracic Society. 
Citing a review in the journal Industrial Health, the CDC said that dental professionals were 23 times more likely to have IPF than the rest of the population. 
IPF causes scarring of the lungs and can be treated, but not cured. Over time, sufferers have difficulty getting oxygen to the body's organs. 

Doctors still don't know what causes IPF. Patients usually live three to five years after being diagnosed. 
Signs of IPF include shortness of breath, a chronic and dry cough, weight loss, fatigue, joint and muscle pains and clubbed fingers or toes. 3566096]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NRGAKVB6KRAB3DL6KF5LSFMABSTRANABKWTURKBVHAAWTZKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/453/5D8/4535D8BEF3224B81980E0078C854B4A7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[IPF]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dentists lung disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dentists IPF]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dentists diagnosed IPF]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ice-crystals-in-diamonds-reveal-water-may-exist-deep-in-mantle-3566086</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ice crystals in diamonds reveal water may exist deep in mantle 3566086]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EARTH — Scientists analyzing diamonds have found that small pockets of water may exist deep in the Earth's mantle.  

Geologists unearthed impure diamonds from mines in southern Africa, Zaire, Sierra Leone and China, according to a report published in the journal Science. 

The diamonds were then sent to the Argonne National Lab in Illinois for analysis in the Advanced Photon Source synchrotron particle accelerator. 

Mineralogist Oliver Tschauner from the University of Nevada in Las Vegas and his colleagues found more than a dozen diamonds with a distinct form of crystallized water known as ice VII. 
Ice VII has been studied in labs, but these samples are the first known natural samples. Because of the team's discovery, ice VII has been classified as a new mineral. 

The ice crystals suggest pockets of watery fluid may be present deep in the Earth's mantle, despite the high temperatures. 

The scientists estimated the diamonds were formed at depths between 610 and 800 kilometers below the Earth's surface. 
Researchers were unable to determine the exact location of the pockets or how common they could be. 3566086]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAWGX3SKVCWVARXLSJW79JHMACBVU3ZAIBRXHZKAWKFKWIAAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FC8/119/FC8119E1A8BE4CF98534F6CCA8494A1C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Earth's mantle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water pockets in Earth's mantle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water in mantle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ice 7]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ice VII]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice crystals in diamonds]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tiangong-1-space-station-set-to-fall-to-earth-3566873</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tiangong-1 space station set to fall to Earth 3566873]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — An out-of-control space station is set to fall to Earth within a few weeks, but there's really no cause for panic, and here's why.

The Guardian reports that China's Tiangong-1 space station has been orbiting uncontrolled since 2016, and has sped up its descent towards Earth in recent months.

According to the European Space Agency, reentry is estimated to occur between March 29 and April 9, with the impact point anywhere between 43 degrees north and 43 degrees south latitudes.

The 9.4 ton space station is expected to burn up as it enters the atmosphere, and may be visible from Earth as a bright streak in the sky.

Experts say a small amount of debris may survive reentry and fall to Earth, but the probability of it hitting anyone and causing harm is extremely low.

To date, only one person has ever been struck by falling space debris, and she wasn't even injured.

So this time, the odds ARE ever in your favor. 3566873]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMCFAYKSKMAWIXCCLIAAV9UWM5AE7EZKKAARVUAEAMCFAXRBAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/812/817/812817A79C2644F693A0A64494D45284.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space station falling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china space station falling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china space station crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space station crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/this-pen-can-diagnose-cancer-in-10-seconds-or-less-3566834</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[This pen can diagnose cancer in 10 seconds or less 3566834]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS — Scientists at the University of Texas have developed a handheld device that can detect cancer in 10 seconds.

The pen is aimed for use by medical professionals during surgery. 

After a tissue sample is taken, the surgeon uses a pen connected to a mass spectrometer and foot pump to begin analysis. The pump sends water through the pen the via tubing and forms a droplet.

This absorbs molecules from the tissue, and is then sent back up the tubing for analysis. The machine then investigates the molecules for signs of cancer and provides diagnosis in seconds.

The device was showcased this week at the South by Southwest festival in Austin, Texas. 3566834]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2KRADZEAJIRMYZXLVDAT7LVMZBBTSK2AECAZGRHA5HRGXZHAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/750/260/750260B386CF4638A23472102F790586.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>40</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sxsw 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ quick cancer diagnosis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ masspec pen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mass spectrometry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer research]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer story]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer story animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ university of texas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ university of texas austin]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ex-double-agent-in-u-k-poisoned-with-russian-nerve-agent-3566792</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ex-double agent in U.K. poisoned with Russian nerve agent 3566792]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Russian ex-double spy Sergei Skripal and his daughter were likely poisoned using a military-grade nerve agent, according to Reuters.  

British Prime Minister Theresa May said on Monday it was highly likely they were poisoned using a military-grade nerve agent.  

Skripal and his daughter, Yulia, were discovered slumped over on a park bench in Salisbury on March 4. They are in critical, but stable condition in the hospital, according to BBC. 
In front of parliament on Monday, May identified the chemical used in the attack as a group of nerve agents known as Novichok. 

The name means newcomer in Russian and refers to a group of advanced chemical agents secretly developed by the Soviet Union in the 1970s and 1980s, according to BBC. 

One of the chemicals — A-230 — can kill a person within minutes and is reportedly five to eight times deadlier than VX nerve gas.

Some come in liquid form, while other exist in a solid state. Some are also binary weapons, meaning they are stored separately, but when mixed produce the lethal nerve agent. 

Novichok agents were designed to evade detection by international insectors.   

The Foreign Office has called on Russia's ambassador to provide an explanation by Tuesday. 3566792]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JACX3VAWIFEAKAB6PAKLDVMSKBZFKRAFJAXTCXKZAAGVIQAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2EA/6A8/2EA6A812E8784CC1A03D95FD90EF3382.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nerve agent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Novichok]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Novichok nerve agents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sergei Skripal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russian nerve agents]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mit-says-actual-nuclear-fusion-will-be-on-the-grid-in-15-years-3566769</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[MIT says actual nuclear fusion will be on the grid in 15 years 3566769]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — Researchers from MIT say nuclear fusion is only 15 years away from becoming a reality. 
 
A team at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology working with newly formed company Commonwealth Fusion Systems says it will build a working fusion power plant in 15 years, thanks to a new superconducting material that recently became commercially available. 

The MIT Energy Initiative announced the project in a statement published March 9 on its website. 

The collaboration between MIT and Commonwealth Fusion Systems plans to use the new superconducting steel tape coated with a yttrium-barium-copper oxide to make smaller, more powerful magnets that can be used in fusion reactors. 
The new magnets will double the magnetic field of a fusion reactor, which means more power can be produced with a smaller device. 
The smaller size will reduce costs and complexity, making future fusion power plants easier to build. 

The researchers say they will be able to create the first fusion reactor that produces more energy than is required to get the fusion reaction going, the university said in a statement published on MIT News.
The planned fusion experiment, called SPARC, is set to be 1/65th the volume of the International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor project currently being built in France, according to Guardian. 

This is an important historical moment: Advances in superconducting magnets have put fusion energy potentially within reach, offering the prospect of a safe, carbon-free energy future, MIT President L. Rafael Reif said in the statement to MIT News. 3566769]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6JFIYCWAVCWKXAWLJKRZLUUGWJSZU36LSLW7HAKKAAFABKYLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A88/2DF/A882DF7F91BB4CCF9030D41A0438F9FF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Nuclear fusion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MIT nuclear fusion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ superconductor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ superconducting tape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MIT fusion device]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fusion reactor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fusion reactor magnets]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/russia-test-launches-hypersonic-kinzhal-missile-3566707</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Russia test launches hypersonic Kinzhal missile 3566707]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOSCOW — The Russians have test-launched a new hypersonic missile that's been described by President Vladimir Putin as an ideal weapon.

The Russian News Agency reports that the Kinzhal missile was launched from a MiG-31 interceptor jet that took off from an airfield in the Southern Military District.

Video footage released by the country's Defense Ministry shows the missile detaching from the jet in mid air.

The Kinzhal hypersonic missile travels at 10 times the speed of sound, with a range of over 2,000 kilometers.

The launch was reportedly successful, with the missile hitting the preset target.

The Kinzhal is part of a new line of weapons unveiled during Putin's recent state of the nation address, that can reportedly outmaneuver US defenses. 3566707]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJAPXZAAWLFEDA7KBJWZK2GM2JVXSC9ABKFZUZHKEBACVZHBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EC4/A81/EC4A81F8DFF977A7D8C6320DF6206EB8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>43</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kinzhal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kinzhal missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypersonic missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile test launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ putin]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hawk-comes-home-finds-her-man-being-unfaithful-with-another-bird-3566664</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hawk comes home finds her man being unfaithful with another bird 3566664]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY — After coming home from being hospitalised for three months, a female hawk was left heartbroken as she finds out her man shacked up with another bird.

Christo and Dora are two red-tailed hawks that have been living at Tompkins Square Park, together they had 10 kids. 

Since 2010, the population of red-tailed hawks have risen around the Big Apple, possibly due to the location of the food source, like rats, pigeons have increased around the city.

Three months ago, while Dora was away for an injury, a hawk named Nora showed up and began flapping her feathers at Christo. They even spent at the nest that was created by Christo and Dora. 

The drama hit climax when Dora came back on Monday as the three birds met beak-to-beak while screaming at each other. 

Lately, Christo was spotted visiting Dora every morning by bringing her food and helping her to build her nest, then, in the afternoon he stays with Nora to mate.

A wildlife rehabilitator who nursed Dora said red-tailed hawks normally stick together forever, but in the Big Apple hawks find a new mate within a day if one of them dies, also, a shared relationship is rare but possible. 3566664]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNFECRCBVBRGYCFLSKR3KDWGVBVTRAMAFPF3FAKKBKWPVCTAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EC4/A81/EC4A81F8DFF977A7D8C6320DF6206EB8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tompkins square park hawks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tompkins square park birds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ birds relationship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ relationship drama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cheating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cheating on wife]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/puppy-choking-on-food-rescued-by-local-police-and-firefighters-3566530</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Puppy choking on food rescued by local police and firefighters 3566530]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH READING, MASSACHUSETTS— Officers in Massachusetts are getting praise for rescuing a puppy who was choking on food.

The incident began when dog owner Megan Vitale was seen on North Reading Police Department's CCTV rushing into the station looking for help as her 9-week-old St Bernard pup Bondhi was choking on food.

Officers rushed over and noticed the puppy was not breathing, instead, it was limp and unresponsive. 

One of the officers, Jorge Hernandez wrapped his hands around the puppy and started pumping away at the pooch's chest. Firefighters also joined in to help dislodge the obstruction.

The lucky pooch was revived and later left with its owners, who made sure it got the necessary treatment at the vet. 3566530]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AFVXTWK5FWGDZXLFIARL4TGZES7RIKAWJW3GZAKSIFIAKSKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EC4/A81/EC4A81F8DFF977A7D8C6320DF6206EB8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[cops rescuing puppy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[cop rescuing animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[firefighters rescue puppy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rescue puppy videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[puppy rescue videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[puppy choking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north reading police]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/legendary-scientist-stephen-hawking-dead-at-76-3567744</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Legendary scientist Stephen Hawking dead at 76 3567744]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, UNITED KINGDOM — Scientist Stephen Hawking, one of the world's most brilliant and beloved scientific minds, died this week aged 76.

According to the BBC, Hawking passed away on Wednesday morning at his home in Cambridge. He was born at the height of World War 2, in 1942 Oxford, England. He graduated from Oxford University in 1959 and joined Cambridge University as a doctoral student. 

In 1963 doctors told him he'd be dead by 1965 after diagnosing him with Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, or ALS. Despite that, he persevered, becoming Dr Hawking and, later Professor Hawking. 

He is best known for his work on black holes, his synthesized speech, as well as popularizing science with the public through his best-selling book, A Brief History of Time. 3567744]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVAWMCIHKVGRKBIXB6KAI7D4NECSIRCZKVBRXFICKBJFKAAAAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/69F/CAA/69FCAA66D0D443F291826EA7C8B7AA3C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>108</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stephen hawking rip]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stephen hawking death]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stephen hawking tribute]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stephen hawking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stephen hawking life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stephen hawking bio]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ physics]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/united-shoves-woman-s-dog-in-overhead-bin-%E2%80%94-it-died-3567709</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[United shoves woman's dog in overhead bin — it died 3567709]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE NOT-SO-FRIENDLY SKIES — A dog passed away on a United Airlines flight from H-town to the Big Apple after a flight attendant ordered the animal be shoved into an overhead bin. 

Of course United is now in damage control. On Tuesday, the airline apologized and said it was taking responsibility for the dogocide. 

It also noted that pets should never be put in the overhead storage compartment — well, almost never. 

Witnesses said the woman's dog carrier was sticking out into the aisle, so a kind, thoughtful United flight attendant told her to stow the carrier and her pooch in the overhead bin. 
During the flight, other passengers said they heard the dog barking. Unfortunately, after arriving in New York it was no longer barking because it died. 
The dog's owner responded by collapsing to the ground in the aisle and balling her eyes out. 

United takes care of its customers, which is why its paying for the necropsy and is refunding the tickets. 3567709]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACFGCRCKAEAMAKEBRDWZ7DRMRES3UZIAADAVURBBRCA5AIHLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/69F/CAA/69FCAA66D0D443F291826EA7C8B7AA3C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[United Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[United Airlines dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[United Airlines dog overhead bin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[United dog overhead compartment]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/solar-storm-to-give-rare-northern-lights-display-in-u-s--3567699</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Solar storm to give rare Northern Lights display in U.S. 3567699]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO — Some parts of the U.S. may get a rare glimpse of the northern lights, as a solar storm fires up the planet's auroras this week.

According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, a minor geomagnetic storm will hit Earth from March 14 to 15.

Solar winds from the Sun's coronal hole are set to stream out into space and cause a slight disturbance to our planet's geomagnetic field. Charged solar particles interacting with the earth's atmosphere results in an amplified display of the Aurora Borealis, or Northern Lights.

The storm allows the lights to be visible in lower latitude areas, like Michigan and Maine in the northeastern U.S. It's also expected to have a minor impact on power grids and satellite operations.

Space reports that over the weekend, several news outlets inaccurately warned of a massive solar disturbance that can cause power outages, prompting some to panic.

In response, the NOAA's Space Prediction Center claims the storm, known as 'G1' is the lowest severity on a scale of five, and shouldn't be cause for concern. 3567699]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADAIDCTKJQRAVZSB6IA79U4GNIB3FK9AJPF7FAFAECFGBK5LD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E84/B63/E84B63AC5DF04BCE81BC292703CBB2B4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ northern lights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar storm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geomagnetic storm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aurora borealis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronal hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ G1 storm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ power grid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satellite communications]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/netflix-secret-codes-to-hidden-shows-and-movie-categories-3567550</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Netflix secret codes to hidden shows and movie categories 3567550]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NETFLIX — Hey Netflix addicts, If your Netflix algorithm is starting to show you the same predictable shows and genres, here's the hack you've been waiting for.

It sure can be annoying going through the same old suggested content. Don't worry though, Netflix actually has a set of secret codes that allow you to unlock the hidden show and movie categories.

To utilize the codes, you need to enter them into the URL manually, so for example, you want to browse B-Horror Movies, replace the INSERTNUMBER at end of the URL with the code 8195. Are you a martial arts movie junkie? Simple, just type in the code 8985, there, master Netflix sure knows de wae.

Voila, a whole new way to access new shows that you can binge watch — and always keep that algorithm guessing, oh and the codes works for all regions of Netflix, how awesome is that? 3567550]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNFGYICBZEFCAAWLBLRK6L3MBKBVFC2A5DFZHTRAZDWKDIBKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C0D/E76/C0DE7680CD1241C188DB5DA3CE500D5D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix algorithm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix hacks codes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix hacks codes 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix shows]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ netflix account]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flying-taxis-to-be-trialled-in-christchurch-new-zealand-3567498</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flying taxis to be trialled in Christchurch, New Zealand 3567498]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHRISTCHURCH, NEW ZEALAND —  An autonomous air taxi designed by Larry Page-backed Kitty Hawk has been approved for trials in Christchurch, New Zealand. 

Cora, an autonomous flying vehicle by Silicon Valley firm Kitty Hawk, has been approved for trials in Christchurch, New Zealand, reported the New Zealand Herald. 

The all-electric aircraft takes off vertically, similar to a helicopter and can carry two people. According to CNN, Cora can fly at speeds of over 150 km per hour and operates autonomously. The aircraft also has a travel range of over 100 km.

According to Stuff.co.nz, it's hoped that Cora will operate commercially in New Zealand within three to six years. 3567498]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANNWCX3SB5FFPAZYKEAFZKJGNEDB3FC2KRAWRHALBWKRGVIJBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5C4/8D9/5C48D99EA4F540EBB1C9C2004372872E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the flying car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cora]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flying car new zealand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flying taxi service]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ air taxi service]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flying car tests]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kitty hawk new zealand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cora new zealand]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/zookeeper-mauled-to-death-by-the-tiger-he-had-raised-from-a-cub-3567413</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Zookeeper mauled to death by the tiger he had raised from a cub 3567413]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FUJIAN, CHINA — A Chinese zookeeper in southern China was fatally bitten by a domesticated tiger he had raised since it was just a cub.

The zookeeper, who worked at Fuzhou zoo in Fujian province, surnamed Wu, was with the tiger inside a cage previously used for training and exercise on Sunday. 

According to the zoo, the tiger was raised by Wu since it was cub, and had been domesticated through long-term interaction with humans. Everything seemed fine until the big cat suddenly pounced on Wu and bit him in his neck and suffocated him to death.

Zoo staff eventually reached the unresponsive zookeeper, but sadly Wu was later declared dead by paramedics. 

In a interview with China's BJNews, the tiger used to perform for visitors as part of a circus event in eastern China. The show already stopped before the accident, with all of its lions shipped away, but the tigers were still awaiting relocation approval. 3567413]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KWKAKVAEHA3AATLBIWT9UXMZAS7UZNA6JFTFIFANKWGVTTKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EA0/DE1/EA0DE165F6664C15808D7A234FCAD197.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zookeeper in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zookeeper tiger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zookeeper tiger attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zookeeper mauled by tiger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiger cub in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiger in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiger in china zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiger in china park]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fuzhou zoo]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cat-uses-up-a-few-lives-after-being-impaled-on-massive-spikes-3567387</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cat uses up a few lives after being impaled on massive spikes 3567387]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A London cat is lucky to be alive after he was found stuck on an 8-foot tall fence by a good samaritan last Friday in the middle of the night.

The person immediately called the Royal Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (RSPCA), according to Metro.

RSPCA deputy chief inspector Nicole Broster showed up on the scene and called in the London Fire Brigade for a helping hand. 

The firefighters helped remove the upper part of the fence, and then transported to the cat to the nearest vet for surgery.

The two fence posts luckily missed the feline's vital organs. One pierced his back leg, and the second went through his abdomen. 
It's crazy the cat is still alive, even crazier he's up and walking around already. 3567387]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAFVAADKRARZBCDLNLW5K2FGWKV5FIQAAAF3UCXK6KWCA37KF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/698/427/69842700C48843FDBACBF30734C602BB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat stuck on fence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat impaled]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat impaled on fence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat survives impaling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat stucks]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-16-000-scholarship-awarded-to-waitress-who-cut-old-man-s-ham-3567373</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[$16,000 scholarship awarded to waitress who cut old man's ham 3567373]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LA MARQUE, TEXAS — A waitress at a Texas waffle house is getting a $16,000 scholarship after she did something awesome.

Diner Adrien Charpentier had just come out of surgery and was having a hard time cutting up his ham, according to CNN. That's when 18-year old waitress Evoni Williams went out of her way to help him. She cut up his ham and then got back to work.

But that act of kindness was snapped by another diner and shared on social media. 
Before Williams knew it, she was a social media hero. For her good deed, not only did she receive praise, but also a scholarship from Texas Southern University. 3567373]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJJWXCAIA5AAIDIUBNLAKKD3GFJETFK7K2LR5G3SAAAAPBIDAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EA9/C71/EA9C71F4EF1E4776AB85079FC1BB55E3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ humanity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acts of kindness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ random acts of kindness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ evoni williams]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ texas teen helps old man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ la marque]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ waffle house]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ random acts of kindness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ incredible acts of kindness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ helping heroes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ faith in humanity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mom-loses-most-of-her-limbs-after-hospital-ignored-signs-of-sepsis-3567369</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mom loses most of her limbs after hospital ignored signs of sepsis 3567369]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LUTON, UNITED KINGDOM — A British woman has lost nearly all of her limbs, all because of one hospital's medical blunder.

SWNS reports that on Christmas Day 2014, Magdalena Malec had to get surgery at Luton & Dunstable University Hospital after discovering she'd suffered an ectopic pregnancy.

While in recovery, the she developed a high fever and rashes on her legs - both classic signs of sepsis that doctors then misdiagnosed as an allergic reaction.

Her condition led to kidney damage and septic shock. But while the kidneys were saved with dialysis and a transplant, her gangrenous limbs were too far gone.

After waiting an agonizing six months, Malec's decaying legs, right arm, and left fingers were finally amputated. 

Sadly, her relationship with her partner broke down during the trying ordeal, and she has had to cope with the disability on her own. She currently relies on a bionic hand and prosthetic legs to help her with basic everyday tasks.

The hospital has since apologized and admitted their mistake, but Malec is hell bent on taking legal action against them, if only to prevent more negligence in the future. 3567369]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASNFAYCXBZFWAVZSBSIF76DSNEESTST2K5ARTT3YAMCA5B3YLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3C2/364/3C23644CAE93421AA5F72D5CBE522D3D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sepsis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ septic shock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amputation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gangrene]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ectopic pregnancy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ miscarriage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dialysis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kidney failure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hospital negligence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medical negligence]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/toys-r-us-going-out-of-business-3568645</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Toys 'R' Us going out of business 3568645]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WAYNE, NEW JERSEY — Toys R Us is sadly calling it quits, bringing an end to iconic toy store which dominated the industry for decades. 

The big-box retailer was unable to get its finances in order through bankruptcy and broke the news to employees in a conference call it was going to sell or close all U.S. stores, according to Wall Street Journal.   

The 70-year-old chain still has more than 700 stores across 'Murica, including Babies 'R' Us locations. It still has more than 30,000 employees.  

Saddled with debt from a 2005 buyout, a triple combo from Walmart, Target and Amazon on top of garbage holiday sales was just too much in the end. 
As consumers gravitate online, brick and mortar stores have struggled to keep up. Who will be left when the dust finally settles? 

Guess we can't all be Toys R Us kids. 3568645]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KWCCTVAACAICIVBRAFT74WMZBBVRTZKBJW7HTTASLRXATWKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C89/4AE/C894AE0D80DD4B11AE93469C801E0B8E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Toys R Us]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Toys R Us going out of business]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Toys R Us liquidation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Toys R Us liquidation sale]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Toys R Us sales]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/going-to-the-2018-world-cup-you-ll-need-a-fan-id-for-that--3568583</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Going to the 2018 World Cup? You'll need a 'Fan ID' for that. 3568583]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOSCOW — Fans attending the 2018 World Cup in Russia will need a 'Fan ID' in addition to standard match tickets.

According to information from the Fan ID and FIFA websites, the document can only be got after buying official tickets from FIFA, then by applying for the document at a seperate website or at a distribution center in Russia. Successful applicants, are notified by email or text and the ID is sent by mail, or collected from a center.

The document allows visa-free entry to Russia for 10 days prior to the document holder's first match and 10 days after their last match. Fan ID and ticket holders will also be able to travel between cities for free using trains and other public transport. 3568583]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DRGYAFKJLFECZWLBJW7L4RGSKE7EC5LWKA3TACA5CAVBZIBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6D6/0B3/6D60B38C4CBD464EB56561B2662808C1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fan id russia 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fan id]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup fan id]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup tickets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vladimir putin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fifa fan id]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia fan id]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how does fan id work]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-reporter-s-epic-eye-roll-ticks-off-the-censors-3568571</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese reporter's epic eye roll ticks off the censors 3568571]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI, CHINA — A female reporter broke the Chinese internet when she rolled her eyes during China's annual parliament session Tuesday morning. 

As China's annual session of the country's legislature marched into week two, the often scripted media Q&A session proved too much for one journalist. 

When listening to a fellow reporter speak to a Chinese official, Yicai[f] financial news reporter Liang Xiangyi[g] was so unimpressed by the long-winded question that took some 40 seconds to ask. To show her disgust, Liang rolled her eyes.

After Liang's reaction was captured by China's CCTV, the moment quickly spread across Chinese social media like wildfire. Gifs and videos inspired by Liang's epic eye-roll flooded Chinese social media, but unfortunately they were all later deleted by China's censors. 

Liang's name also ended up becoming one of the most-censored terms on Chinese social media platform Weibo, guess that's quite an accomplishment for a reporter.

The original question was basically about how China is going to supervise overseas assets, but there appeared to really long boring build-up before the reporter actually got to the question. 3568571]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAAMDZDKWJRCCASBRAFX9UTMABS7R39AEAFTUZEBSJARVCSBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/70F/515/70F515BFE3EE4990ABE6E284ED74A9AE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>85</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reporter eye roll]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reporter censorship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye roll censorship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China annual parliament session]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ epic eye roll]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet censorship china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liang xiangyi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the great wall of china censorship]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/playboy-to-introduce-digital-cryptocurrency-wallet-3568568</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Playboy to introduce digital cryptocurrency wallet 3568568]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEVERLY HILLS, CALIFORNIA — Playboy is jumping on the cryptocurrency bandwagon, and will soon be accepting virtual currency in exchange for their services.

In a press release put out by the company, they announced they were creating a digital wallet that supports the Vice Industry token and other crypto payments, for people eager to plop down a premium on adult content.

Customers can stop worrying about credit card statements revealing their illicit online activities, since anonymity is the name of the crypto game.

The Vice token even takes it a step further with a rewards program. Users get paid to access content, while advertisers find out exactly how to hit their audience's sweet spot. Win-win!

Playboy's digital wallet is set to be available before the end of the year, and might even be integrated into their gaming, AR, and VR initiatives.

Cryptocurrency and adult entertainment may seem like a match made in heaven, but the industry hasn't been all that into it. But with Playboy breaking the ice, that might change soon enough. 3568568]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NWEDKVBZDRGCI9LMAAZ6BBGICBVSKSLRAWZGAFKEDRXDIALB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1F5/912/1F59125164E64EE2AFDD5421E3938CA3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playboy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency wallet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital wallet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ online wallet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vice industry token]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vice industry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ VIT]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paid content]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-startup-can-3d-print-cheap-houses-in-less-than-24-hours-3568426</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Texas startup can 3D-print cheap houses in less than 24 hours 3568426]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS — A construction tech company is using 3D-printing to provide houses for the 1.2 billion people in the world without adequate housing.

Wired reports that Texas startup ICON unveiled a proof-of-concept model house at the annual SXSW innovation festival in Austin. The 650-square-foot structure featured a living room, bedroom, bathroom, and curved porch.

Using traditional building methods, a community of a hundred houses will take roughly eight months to complete. But with an industrial-sized Vulcan 3D printer, Icon claims it a single-storey home can be constructed using cement in only 12 to 24 hours.

Each 600 to 800 square foot home costs $10,000 to build, but the company is working to drop it to just $4,000.

ICON is working with housing charity New Story to bring the printer to El Salvador, where it plans to build a community of 3D printed houses within the year. 3568426]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJFKCCSA5AAMCRSBNLR79U3MADVXEAQKZDWVHIAABKF3VAFKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/301/1F9/3011F954DB364181BD358C543F304B15.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3d printed house]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3d printer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3d printing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cheap houses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ affordable houses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homeless]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homelessness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global housing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vulcan printer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ icon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new story]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ el salvador]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/doctors-find-large-air-pocket-in-old-dude-s-brain-3568242</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Doctors find large air pocket in old dude's brain 3568242]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTHERN IRELAND, UK — Doctors treating an elderly man who was having trouble with balance were surprised to find a 3.5-inch air pocket in the patient's brain. 

The 84-year-old man had been complaining to his primary care doctor in Northern Ireland about recurrent falls and three days of left arm and leg weakness, according to a report in the journal BMJ Case Reports.

Physicians were worried the patient may have been suffering from some form of stroke, but he was not displaying any visual or speech impairments and did not seem confused or have facial weakness, according to the report.  

A brain scan revealed a 3.5-inch long pocket of air, also known as a pneumatocele, in the man's right frontal lobe, behind the frontal sinus and above the cribriform plate. 
An MRI on the man's brain also revealed a small benign bone tumor in the man's paranasal sinuses, that was eroding through the base of the skull, causing air to leak into the cranial cavity, according to the report. 

Doctors concluded that the air pressure from the air cavity may have caused a small stroke in the patient's frontal lobe. 
Due to his old age, surgery was ruled out. He was instead given medication to prevent a secondary stroke. 

After a 12-week follow up visit, the man said he no longer had any left-side muscle weakness, the journal reported. 3568242]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLWIACXAIAR5DRVBRDAVKLXNBLS3SRIK5DWVFCTASKR5WTTKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FD6/13E/FD613E505FBE4A41A77A9747F0C861E6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ air pocket in brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain air pocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pneumocephalus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stroke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ partial stroke]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-miraculously-survives-girlfriend-s-katana-attack-3569612</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man miraculously survives girlfriend's katana attack 3569612]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMAS, WASHINGTON — Hell hath no fury like a crazy girlfriend who thinks she's being scorned, and this dude learned that the hard way, after almost being hacked to death in his own bedroom.

The Oregonian reports that gamer Alex Lovell spent hours on end playing and training for survival video game PlayerUnknown's Battleground, which didn't sit well with his girlfriend of two years Emily Javier.

Furthermore, Javier had recently spotted a Tinder app on her boyfriend's phone, scratches on his back, and red hair in the shower — which in her head meant he was cheating.

Rather than confront him, she planned his demise and bought a katana at the mall. Her rage reached its tipping point on March 2, when Lovell came home and completely ignored her.

Once he fell asleep, she pulled the sword from under the bed and aimed for the head. Luckily, Lovell got hit with the blunt end the first two times, and woke up in time to defend himself.

The 29-year-old claims years of watching martial arts movies helped him 'wing-chun his way to survival', though not without getting hacked in a few places.

Eventually, he managed to grab Javier by the arms and told her he was going to die unless she called for help. That broke her murderous spell, and she called 911.

Officers found Lovell curled up in the blood-splattered bedroom with life-threatening injuries and rushed him to the hospital.

He's since had his fingers reattached and several other body parts stitched up, and will live to game another day. Javier, meanwhile, is in jail and facing a charge for attempted murder. 

So all in all, it was a pretty happy ending. 3569612]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLAMXRDBWIFIBIRLBKAK7DXGIDBIE3SLVAWTUAKASKWXBAEAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/45C/A08/45CA085BB3234190A31F88F9B9DEBA42.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>87</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ samurai sword]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cheating boyfriend]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ angry girlfriend]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crazy girlfriend]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crazy ex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ angry ex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tinder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dating app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ katana]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/pedestrian-bridge-collapse-at-university-in-miami-3569545</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Pedestrian bridge collapse at university in Miami 3569545]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MIAMI, FLORIDA — A newly installed pedestrian bridge collapsed on Florida International University's campus Thursday afternoon.

The collapse occurred at about 1:30 p.m., and as of 5:00 p.m., at least eight vehicles were flattened and trapped under the collapsed bridge. 

According to authorities, at least nine people who had been pulled out of the rubble were immediately hospitalised, four people sadly did not make it, including a student from Florida International University.

Florida state governor Rick Scott said that the state would do its best to determine the cause of the collapse. 

FIU had claimed the $14.2 million cable-supported bridge was an innovation as the construction techniques used were intended to expedite the work and minimize disruption of traffic. 

The project was a collaboration between MCM construction and FIGG Bridge Design. 

Florida senator Marco Rubio tweeted that: The cables that suspend the Miami bridge had loosened & the engineering firm ordered that they be tightened. They were being tightened when it collapsed today.

The 950-ton bridge was supposed to open to foot traffic in 2019. It was designed to connect the school to the Sweetwater neighborhood, home to more than 4,000 FIU students. 3569545]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJAACCSBFLAMV3HKAAR76LUMEBVRE39KABR5UCSAVBRXBRCAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/224/FFA/224FFAFB592FC2AA3094B729CAA50953.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bridge collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ miami bridge collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ miami bridge collapse video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ miami bridge collapse footage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fiu bridge collapse footage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fiu bridge collapse video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida international university]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ miami]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ford-recalls-1-38-million-cars-for-detachable-steering-wheels-3569426</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ford recalls 1.38 million cars for detachable steering wheels 3569426]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT — Ford Motor Co. announced on Wednesday it is recalling 1.38 million vehicles in North America for possible loose steering wheel bolts.

The defect has connected to at least two accidents and one potential injury, according to Ford.  

The automaker said the recall includes 2014 through 2018 Ford Fusion cars and Lincoln MKZ vehicles built at plants in Michigan and Mexico, according to Reuters. 

Car dealers will replace the steering wheel bolt with a longer bolt. 
The U.S. National Highway Traffic Safety Administration began a preliminary investigation in October into 841,000 Ford cars over detachable steering wheels while vehicles were in motion. 
The latest recall affects 1.3 million cars in the U.S., around 62,000 in Canada and about 14,000 in Mexico, according to USA Today. 3569426]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJRMXRBBBIFIBKCBAAWZ9SAGICE7SC2ABJR5HALKAHFXVILKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/11F/2F5/11F2F57E81D591C01CD6AA254AA44C79.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ford recall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ford steering wheel recall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ford loose steering wheels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ford loose steering wheel bolts]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-wants-to-build-a-space-station-by-the-moon-3569323</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA wants to build a space station by the moon 3569323]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — NASA says it plans to build a station for astronauts orbiting the moon. The project is called the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway.   
The space agency's fiscal year 2019 budget request calls for launching the first element of the Gateway, the power and propulsion module, into space in 2022, according to Space.com. 
The station would be complete after two additional launches by 2025 to add habitation, logistics and airlock functions. 

The Gateway could be put in a Near Rectilinear Halo Orbit, an orbit in cislunar space that could be used as a staging area for future missions. 
The platform's position would let astronauts control telerobots on the moon's surface that could be used to explore craters as well as carry out other experiments. 3569323]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NWAYAFAADFEWCFLVCWT9BCGRBBIRALK6KWVTALKMCRZVIHAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D98/BFB/D98BFBD8EFDF82ADB1B38040D75A86CF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep-space outpost]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Lunar missions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/united-airlines-accidentally-flies-kansas-bound-dog-to-japan-3569195</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[United Airlines accidentally flies Kansas-bound dog to Japan 3569195]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WICHITA, KANSAS — United Airlines mistakenly shipped one family's dog halfway across the globe — their second pet-related mishap in just a week.

The Wichita Eagle reports that Kara Swindle and her family were moving to Wichita, and booked United tickets to fly from Oregon to Kansas City. Their German shepherd Irgo was too big to be in the cabin with them, and had to be flown in as cargo on a separate flight.

But when they got to the cargo facility in Kansas, the Swindles were shocked to find a huge great dane waiting for them, with Irgo nowhere to be found.

The airline eventually figured out that the 10-year-old dog had mistakenly been sent on a 16-hour flight to Japan instead of the great dane.

Supposedly, someone from the pet resort at Denver airport let the two canines out during a stopover, and then put them back in the wrong kennels. Idiot.

Irgo has been checked by a vet in Japan, and was put on a plane back to Kansas on Wednesday night. Here's hoping the poor dog gets home safe. 3569195]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIWCAKXBIDR7BZ7LVAWXL4XMVEBKF32AWKAZFKTBRDAZWALAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D98/BFB/D98BFBD8EFDF82ADB1B38040D75A86CF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog mix up]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[united airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[pet mishap]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[pets on planes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[pets in cargo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Kansas dog in Japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[german shepherd]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[great dane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[united airlines mistake]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/identical-twins-no-more-brother-s-dna-changes-year-in-space-3569176</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Identical twins no more! Brother's DNA changes year in space 3569176]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON, D.C. — Identical NASA twin astronauts Scott and Mark Kelly no longer share the same DNA after the former spent a year in space.

According to NASA, scientists compared the twins' DNA and RNA via whole-genome sequencing. They found that 7% of Scott's DNA had changed into so-called space-genes.
His immune system, bone formation and eyesight all went under changes, reported Live Science.

Telomeres, caps on chromosomes, typically shorten as a person ages. Kelly's lengthened, according to NASA, but returned to normal two days after he returned to Earth. 3569176]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJRPYCSBBIWEDZRBJPRZ7UXNABS3S34KNPAVURCKZBRCCIHKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CC3/BB6/CC3BB6F7E7724052AAD79C18853E16CB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ex twins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ identical twins not identical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space dna]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna and your body]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weird science twins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strange science stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weird science stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strange science facts]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/meet-the-legless-model-who-defies-general-modelling-perception-3571551</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Meet the legless model who defies general modelling perception 3571551]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA — A 23-year-old legless Californian girl has defied general preconceptions by working as an underwear model. 

According to an interview with Unilad, Kanya Sesser said she was abandoned outside a Buddhist temple in Thailand when she was only a week old. Fortunately, at age five, she was adopted by her Oregonian family.

Despite being legless and dealing with trolls and bullies throughout her life, Kanya refuses to give in. 

Kanya lives a very active lifestyle, and eschews the use of a wheelchair for skateboarding instead. She also surfs, skis, and plays basketball.

Since the age of 15, Kanya has established a successful modelling gig for herself, and says it’s a way to show she is not ashamed of her body. However, the 23-year-old says modelling is not going to be her main gig for the long run.

Her bio reads #nolegsnolimits, and Kanya’s Instagram profile has gone viral with 58,900 followers who like posts about her life, her modelling shoots and the sports she loves playing. 3571551]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIWXC3SAVERMVRVBJLAILBFMZEV7ST7KFJATFIBAWKAGAAMAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9F7/339/9F7339800FBB47048CCA4EAC02273BF3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[legless model]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kanya sesser legless]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kanya sesser legless]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[amazing real life stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[model with disabilities]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[disabled model]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[uct-wqktykk1_70u4bb4k4lq]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/death-row-prisoners-in-oklahoma-to-be-executed-with-nitrogen-gas-3571449</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Death row prisoners in Oklahoma to be executed with nitrogen gas 3571449]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OKLAHOMA CITY — Oklahoma plans to use nitrogen gas in dealing with prisoners scheduled to leave this world, though the details of the procedure have yet to be finalized.

The state plans to use the gas to induce nitrogen hypoxia, a fatal state where the brain and body are deprived of oxygen.

According to the U.S. Chemical Safety Board, 78% of the air humans breathe contain nitrogen. The lower the oxygen content, the deadlier nitrogen becomes.  As the oxygen content lowers to 16%, the brain tells the body to breathe faster and deeper. Anything below 10% oxygen content can be fatal.

Speaking to Reuters, the Death Penalty Information Center said it would take 7 minutes for a 32-kg pig to die from nitrogen hypoxia. Other countries known to use gas during executions were Nazi Germany, North Korea and the USSR. 3571449]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLWPYIBAMCWACKALEAR57LUGFJBRFIKAWIW3HRDKBKRIWIBBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/671/40B/67140BA32E1FDEE34EFA07CB49C04294.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nitrogen gas execution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oklahoma nitrogen gas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nitrogen hypoxia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ death penalty]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lethal injection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oklahoma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prisoner execution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nitrogen gas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nitrogen execution]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/united-flight-diverted-because-a-dog-got-on-the-wrong-plane-3571419</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[United flight diverted because a dog got on the wrong plane 3571419]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES — United has been on quite the tear when it comes to animal related incidents. 

Last Thursday, United Flight 3996 from Newark to St. Louis actually had to be diverted because the geniuses found a dog was accidentally aboard the plane, according to USA Today. 
The four-legged flier was supposed to be in Akron, Ohio, but was put on the wrong flight, airline spokeswoman Maggie Schmerin told CNN. 

The plane actually had to take a extra two hour detour to drop the pup off to its owners. 
United's blunder made a two-hour trip into a four-hour escapade for passengers, who were apparently compensated for the delay — hopefully not with a free United flight. 
Last week wasn't the best for United in terms of animal customer service. They suffocated a lady's French bulldog puppy and sent another dog to Japan instead of Kansas.  

United needs to seriously consider only carrying pets from now on. What could go wrong? 3571419]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFIWKY3UAVDWEBAXLEDFZLUUM5EVRRT4KSPWVGAGA5HAAVIFBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/770/2BC/7702BC72486742958CDBE0FAF5B4CCA0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United Airlines pets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United pet incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United flight diverted pet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United sends dog to wrong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United Airlines animal incidents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United pet related incidents]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/southwest-forces-dad-toddler-off-flight-to-atlanta-3571382</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Southwest forces dad, toddler off flight to Atlanta 3571382]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — United may have recently enraged passengers recently for its pet-related mishaps, but this week, it's Southwest's turn in the hot seat.

WGN 9 reports that the airline is being blasted online after video of a family getting kicked off a plane unexpectedly went viral.

The incident on the Chicago to Atlanta flight began with a toddler refusing to sit in her own seat. A flight attendant called out the dad, who then asked for a minute to calm his kid down.

The 2-year-old was already buckled in her seat when another attendant came up and told the family they had to leave. Supposedly, the dad had sniped at the female flight attendant and told her to stay out of his daughter's face.

Passenger Alexis Armstrong heard the exchange and started recording with her phone, but was rudely told to stop filming after calling BS on the female attendant's claims.

The plane ultimately went back to the gate, where the dad, his daughter, and another relative were removed. They were booked on the next flight to Atlanta.

Armstrong's video was posted on Facebook and has since gotten over a million views.

Most netizens slammed the airline for their lack of empathy in dealing with a child, while some insist the flight attendant was merely following FAA rules.

Whatever the arguments, there's really only one clear loser here, and that's Southwest. 3571382]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNACXACB2JWKVTALNJW774SMVCBZECRKSLW7HZBKACAIA33AG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E20/51E/E2051E333F8247A8AE0636D20180C3A8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest drama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ family kicked off flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dad daughter kicked off flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toddler kicked off flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline drama]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/time-crystal-research-being-bankrolled-by-dod-3571250</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Time crystal research being bankrolled by DoD 3571250]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON, D.C. — Time crystal research is to get funding from the U.S. Department of Defense.

DoD agency DARPA announced it would be funding several projects at universities in January.

Regular crystals are made up of structured atoms in a shape. If touched, a crystal won't break apart. The structure remains rigid, even when moved. It generally maintains its shape. 

Time crystals also feature an atomic structure, except these aren't solid. The structure is constantly moving, repeating it through time. Researchers say these the world's first non-equilibrium matter, reports the Daily Mail, or more simply, a matter where forces are not balanced.

According to Gizmodo, the research is classified but may have applications in atomic clocks and also, potentially, quantum computing. 3571250]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJNRMXZIB6KFMACHBJJW5KBHNFLSXSK6KNJFMGIAKMCATCTUKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/792/C31/792C319C37EE4B70AACE0679C8B46122.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ time crystals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what are time crystals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space-time crystals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strange science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DARPA projects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DARPA research]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ time crystal military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[things that shouldnt exist]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-plans-to-nuke-asteroids-to-save-earth-3572050</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA plans to nuke asteroids to save Earth 3572050]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — NASA has come up with a plan to save us all should a large space rock ever hit the planet, and it's pretty straightforward: nuke it!

According to the Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, the massive asteroid Bennu, which is taller than the Empire State building and larger than five football fields, is currently orbiting the sun 54 million miles from Earth.

It is classified as a 'potentially hazardous' object, with a 1 in 2,700 chance of crashing into the planet on September 25, 2135.

The spacecraft HAMMER, or Hypervelocity Asteroid Mitigation Mission for Emergency Response, would be able to use an impactor to change the trajectory of smaller rocks.

But for a large asteroid like Bennu, HAMMER would have to deploy a nuclear device to destroy it before it reaches Earth.

NASA has been monitoring the enormous space rock since it was discovered in 1999, and has sent out a space probe to take samples.

Bennu is one of 10,000 near-Earth objects it has detected, though only 2,500 of these are estimated to be as large. 3572050]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5BWADRFKEAAACTHB5DF5KBCMREBTECRAAAFPGCRKNKAIBRFAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AAB/B45/AABB45771A05481696D4B624545FF0A5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-21T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bennu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid collision]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ HAMMER]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nukes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear warhead]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid hitting earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid bennu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ killer asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/astronomers-record-fastest-deep-space-radio-burst-origin-unknown-3572022</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Astronomers record fastest deep space radio burst, origin unknown 3572022]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DEEP SPACE — Astronomers recorded strongest ever fast radio burst from outer space using the Parkes Observatory radio telescope in Australia earlier this month.

According to Inquisitr, signal FRB 180309 was heard by the telescope on March 9. It's signal-to-noise ratio was 4 times larger than the previous strongest signal. 

Astronomers don't know what it is, but some speculate it could be anything from stars colliding to interstellar travel, according to a report by the Search for Extraterrestrial at University of California, Berkeley.

Details of the signal were published on the website Astronomer's Telegram. 3572022]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AECFAX3UKZAFKCIWKFKFXKLYGRCERSRQLSLRZFCSAVDWCV3SAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6FC/A23/6FCA23015BE04BD9B4A3230734A0A3A2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-21T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>36</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strange space sounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space sounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ astronomy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radio burst]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fast radio burst]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radio telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extraterrestrial life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interstellar travel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neutron star collision]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-in-hot-water-over-cambridge-analytica-data-misuse-3572013</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook in hot water over Cambridge Analytica data misuse 3572013]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Facebook is facing calls for regulation after reports a political consultant gained access to 50 million users' data. 

The company disclosed the news in a blog post last Friday. American and British lawmakers are demand on Sunday Facebook explain how so many profiles were harvested without the social network notifying users, according to the New York Times. 

According the New York Times and the Observer, Cambridge Analytica used personal information taken without permission early in 2014 to build a system that could profile US voters, in order more effectively target them with personalized political ads. 
The data has not been deleted despite Facebook's demands beginning in 2015. 
Around 270,000 people allowed a researcher to use their personal data, who also scraped the data of all their friends as well, until the end of 2015. 

The researcher then sold the data to Cambridge Analytica. Cambridge Analytica worked on Trump's 2016 campaign. According to Reuters, a Trump campaign official said it used Republican data sources for voter information, not Cambridge Analytica. 

Facebook is claiming Cambridge Analytica and researchers were in breach of policy and that it was exploring legal action. 3572013]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMARMCCSKNLAMCCAKBLAVKBAGSJSKEAQKJKAXGCYKNLFAVRIKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/30C/9E5/30C9E59E045247BEB0ADB9487B3ED232.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-21T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook data misuse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook user data misuse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cambridge Analytica]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-scientists-plan-to-revive-the-northern-white-rhino-3572943</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How scientists plan to revive the northern white rhino 3572943]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NANYUKI, KENYA — The death of the last male northern white rhino may mean probable extinction for the subspecies, but scientists are working on a plan to save them.

The New York Times reports that Sudan, the world's last male northern white rhino died in Kenya on Monday, leaving the only two females, neither of which is can carry a pregnancy to term.

The best plan to carry on the species is through in-vitro fertilization, using eggs extracted from the surviving females, and stored sperm from dead males.

The fertilized egg would be implanted in a surrogate southern white rhino, the species' closest living relative, which would carry the calf to term.

If successful, scientists hope to use the procedure to create a herd of five to fifteen rhinos, that would eventually be returned to their natural habitat, according to the Chicago Tribune.

With the IVF method costing as much as $9 million, conservationists hope to raise enough money and implement it before it's too late. 3572943]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFAX3TKIAFEVZVBNKR37JHNFKSKRZKKSKF5HRKKEAWAC3XAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/836/606/836606A8612C4EC5B5767D9CC2650BE6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ northern white rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ white rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sudan the white rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ last white rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ white rhino dies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ save the rhino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sudan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ in vitro fertilization]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southern white rhino]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/unexploded-bomb-at-fedex-could-help-in-austin-serial-bomber-hunt-3572939</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Unexploded bomb at FedEx could help in Austin serial bomber hunt 3572939]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS — An unexploded package found on Tuesday could help investigators in their search for a suspected serial bomber. 

A string of explosions in Austin has left two dead and four injured.

A fifth parcel bomb detonated shortly after midnight on Tuesday at a FedEx center in Schertz, Texas, when the package went off on a conveyor belt, injuring one person. 

Later Tuesday morning, a second suspicious package was found at another FedEx facility near Austin and was disrupted by law enforcement, according to CBS News.  

FBI officials say the package contained an explosive device, while emergency dispatch audio reported there were nails and metals in the parcel.  

The FBI said in a news release on Tuesday that all six packages were connected. There have been three types of bombs used: hand delivered, tripwire and delivered.

Investigators will now study the unexploded device to look for clues and signatures that could help lead to the bomb maker. 3572939]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCAGYKVKBJWIAZULECRI94TGVDBISC6AFKWXT3TAEDFCYZEBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D6D/7CB/D6D7CB34449B4F92AF06DEFA54D7E3C5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Austin bombings]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Texas bombings]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Austin parcel bombs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Austin package bombs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Austin FedEx bombs]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/obese-pregnant-woman-shocks-doctors-with-2-inch-thick-body-fat-3572857</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Obese pregnant woman shocks doctors with 2-inch-thick body fat 3572857]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HANGZHOU, CHINA — Doctors were shocked when a woman in southern China became so obese that she had a two-inch-thick layer of fat around her abdomen.

The unnamed woman from Hangzhou was reportedly around 213 pounds overweight after giving birth to her first child. 

When the woman became pregnant again, she reportedly had such a large appetite that she basically ate whatever food was put in front of her. Her weight skyrocketed to a whopping 268 pounds, and it became difficult for her to even go out for a stroll.

Due to the woman's obesity, doctors had no other choice but to deliver her second baby via C-section. 

Doctors said the woman's body fat made it difficult for them to see the baby in her womb during the operation, as there was so much flesh in the way. Doctors measured the woman's body fat to be about 2.7 inches thick, and said the excess fat would push its way out when they were sewing up her abdomen.

Fortunately, the surgery went well and she successfully gave birth to her second child, a 7-pound baby boy.

Doctors say gaining too much weight while pregnant can raise the risks of birth complications, which could result in premature birth or require C-section deliveries. 3572857]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJNWADAIB5AAKVASL2LAXL4YMJIBXFC4A2JFVUAGBWIRAYCRBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/068/C8B/068C8B20693344289FB6AD351C7741F3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ obese chinese woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ obese pregnant women]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ obese chinese woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ obese china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ obesity in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fat body obese]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fat and obese body]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hangzhou china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-happens-if-russia-knocks-out-the-uk-s-deep-sea-data-cables--3572764</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What happens if Russia knocks out the UK's deep sea data cables? 3572764]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Late last year Britain's top military officer warned that Russia poses a threat to the country's internet and communication networks.

Trade, business, communication and nations rely largely on deep sea data cables to function. These global links connect the planet's information.

Britain's top military officer warned NATO must safeguard them as a priority due to threat presented by Russia's Navy, according to a December 2017 BBC report. In international waters, the cables are in a legally gray area, meaning an attack on them may not trigger NATO collective defence.

The cables can be easily destroyed via small explosives, according to the Center for International Maritime Security. If successful, and attack could damage a country's economy and bring their communications network to a halt. 3572764]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNWIYIAB5CFIBASKBKW7LDYMACB3SC5LWIWZGRGKMBAXWCWBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F16/8CC/F168CCC3BD574F589960B53B2E6004F6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data cables down]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Britain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russian Navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian submarines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NATO]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet down]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep sea data cable attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep sea cables]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/risks-visitors-could-while-visiting-the-2018-fifa-world-cup-in-russia-3572687</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Risks visitors could while visiting the 2018 Fifa World Cup in Russia 3572687]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RUSSIA — With the 2018 FIFA World Cup coming in Russia, security measures are going to be tightened.

Officials predict fights between rival fans and police are more likely to take place in the host cities, meaning there will be an elevated likelihood of injuries and collateral damage done to property.

Visitors of non-white racial backgrounds are likely to become targets of individual attacks by football fans or radical groups.

With limited legal assistance, minor crimes like pickpocketing, theft and robberies will likely be underreported by Russian authorities.

There is also heightened risk of cyberattacks with the intent of breaching the information security of corporate visitors.

Despite the security concerns and the recent death of a Spanish police officer when hooligans rioted before Spartak Moscow's Europa League match at Athletic Bilbao, FIFA said it has complete trust in the security arrangements for the 2018 World Cup. 3572687]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLWKDTSAMCRPWRYLSKFZKBCMRBB5FILLSLAXURKASKWGVT4BH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8C2/DF3/8C2DF3378ADA4EF7939598DFE28C51F6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup russia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup risks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup danger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup security measures]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia security measures]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2018 world cup russia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/no-flights-or-trains-for-people-with-bad-social-credit-in-china-3572675</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[No flights or trains for people with bad social credit in China 3572675]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — China is curbing the transportation rights of people with poor social credit.

Effective May 1, the country will ban citizens with low social credit scores from using flight and rail transport for one year.

According to Reuters, those banned include individuals who lied about terrorism, caused trouble on flights as well as people who used out-of-date tickets, or smoked on trains. Also affected are people who didn't pay fines and employers not paying social insurance.

China's yet-to-be finalized social credit system operates on the doctrine of once untrustworthy, always restricted, reported Reuters. 3572675]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZAWXACVKVFRTA3CLJKA59UWNAABKRK9K6KR3UTRBRDAVBCXKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6DE/6E7/6DE6E795FDB249D0A4C7A7DEFF18300B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social credit china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travel ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social credit scores]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ government surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ communist state]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uber-halts-autonomous-car-tests-after-fatal-pedestrian-crash-3572656</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Uber halts autonomous car tests after fatal pedestrian crash 3572656]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TEMPE, ARIZONA — A female pedestrian was struck and killed by an Uber autonomous vehicle in Tempe on Sunday night. 

The fatality is believed to be the first known death by an autonomous test vehicle. 

The company has halted self-driving tests in Tempe, San Francisco, Pittsburgh and Toronto.  

The crash occurred near Mill Avenue and Curry Road around 10 p.m., according to police. 

The Uber vehicle was reportedly traveling northbound at around 40 mph when a woman walking a bicycle outside of the crosswalk was struck.

The woman, 49-year-old Elaine Herzberg, was transported to the hospital where she died from her injuries, according to ABC 15.  

Tempe Police say the SUV was in autonomous mode and vehicle operator, 44-year-old Rafaela Vasquez, was behind the wheel at the time of the accident. 

The National Transportation Safety Board is opening an investigation and sending investigators to Tempe. 3572656]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVCFACIHKAAAABKABSKF59LTGVCETSZQK6LWZFCRAJJWPVTUAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5FD/BCB/5FDBCB1625CF40B1A682F2E65E03A9B2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Uber autonomous car crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Uber autonomous vehicle crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Uber autonomous crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Uber autonomous fatal crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Uber self driving fatal crash]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/protect-your-data-without-deleting-facebook-account-3573703</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Protect your data without deleting Facebook account 3573703]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FACEBOOK — Facebook has been taking criticism for its latest scandal involving the misuse of personal data with Cambridge Analytica.
According to Digital Trends, here are some ways to protect personal data on Facebook without deleting the entire account. 

The first step is to remove Facebook from connected apps, basically disabling the platform so third-party apps can not access your account or information. 
Next, users can adjust the amount of data friends and family take with them to other apps, such as birthdate, education, employment and relationships. 

The third alternative is to shut off Facebook's data collection for advertisements. This includes website and apps use and adds coupled with social actions. 3573703]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DAGD3WLSLA7DCDBIDRR7JCMVDE7RK7AFLF7UCRKRHRXBZIBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/47F/ED6/47FED6986A3946E68AF2C1E000EEDFCB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook personal data misuse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook third party apps]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ third party data]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-military-testing-unmanned-battle-tank-3573604</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese military testing unmanned battle tank 3573604]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — The Chinese have begun trialing a remotely-controlled battle tank as part of plans to upgrade its armed forces.

The Global Times reports that China's medium-sized Type 59 tank is equipped with a 100 or 105 millimeter cannon, and typically requires a crew of 4 people to operate.

The state is now testing an unmanned version of the tank, with footage from Chinese media showing a soldier remotely driving the vehicle.

Type 59 tanks were first used in the 1950s and are due to retire, but can be equipped with with artificial intelligence to turn them to autonomous vehicles.

They will be able to work with other unmanned equipment, and integrate information from satellites, aircrafts, or submarines.

For now, the unmanned Type 59 tanks still have technical issues, and will likely go through more testing and tweaking before they can be fully combat-capable. 3573604]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMDWMAKSLVBRCYKCBVBFZ7SBM5CS7SAKKFIFZUZDABKAAWZGAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E2A/86E/E2A86E4BB5C64787AF5204B228B8BB1E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unmanned tank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unmanned vehicle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial intelligence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ type 59 tank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ military tech]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ military technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china artificial intelligence]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-to-protect-your-digital-cash-from-cryptotheft-3573573</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How to protect your digital cash from cryptotheft 3573573]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE DIGITAL REALM — As cryptocurrencies have gained in popularity, so have thefts involving digital coins. 
Hackers have several methods at their disposal to steal cryptocurrencies, including brute forcing, phone-porting, phishing, ponzi schemes and mining malware, according to Visual Capitalist. 

When it comes to digital currencies, how secure your digital wallet, your private keys and any systems they use to make transactions is of utmost importance.   

Install and run antivirus software on your computers and smartphones. Be careful opening up any suspicious emails, and set up two-factor authentication whenever possible. 
Encrypt your hard drives and mobile devices, and make backups of them as well. 
Finding a trustworthy exchange is also important. 

With a centralized exchange, you allow the exchange to manage the security of your funds on your behalf. Unfortunately, this makes centralized exchanges a perfect target for hackers. 

Decentralized exchanges allow for direct peer-to-peer cryptotrading, during which the exchange is never in control of your funds. Decentralized exchanges also do not have access to your private keys. 3573573]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVCACDAHL2KAZXZ9LEDF5LDRNEDE7EAKKSKRXFCRK6KAMACUAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0AD/74A/0AD74AFFC4FA435A87E39FDB4DC120E7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptotheft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency hackers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin security]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/us-south-korea-push-forward-with-annual-war-games-3573564</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[US, South Korea push forward with annual war games 3573564]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL — Despite being delayed by the Pyeongchang Winter Olympics, the annual war games on the democratic side of the Korean Peninsula are pushing through.

According to Korea JoongAng Daily, South Korea  and the U.S. have announced that joint military drills between the two countries will begin on April 1.

The war games consist of two drills. The first, called 'Foal Eagle', is a series of field training exercises combining ground, air, naval, and special operations.

The four-week-long program involves 290,000 South Korean and 11,500 American troops.

The second drill, called 'Key Resolve', is a computer-simulated command post exercise that's set to be held for two weeks starting April 23.

This year's war games are more low-key compared to previous years, possibly to avoid provoking North Korea, who has always objected to them. 3573564]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJWMAABBEBRAYZVL6PAV9JFMVCSIE33KWLF5UABAEDAMBAFAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/50A/5C6/50A5C613177B441BA8AF8C7E951785B8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[US South Korean war games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[war games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[military drills]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[joint military exercises]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[South Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[foal eagle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[key resolve]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gulf-of-mexico-dead-zone-could-take-decades-to-recover-3574839</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gulf of Mexico dead zone could take decades to recover 3574839]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GULF OF MEXICO — The dead zone in the Gulf of Mexico isn't likely to shrink anytime soon, and could even persist for decades, according to a new study.

The Guardian reports that dead zones are low-oxygen areas in bodies of water that are harmful to marine life and can lead to massive algal blooms.

The hypoxic zones are fed by nitrogen fertilizer, which flows through waterways across America's corn belt and into the Gulf of Mexico.

The Gulf Hypoxia Action Plan currently calls for a reduction in nitrogen runoffs in order to shrink the dead zone from 5,000 to 1,950 square kilometers by 2035.

But according to a new report from the University of Waterloo, 'legacy' nitrogen that has been accumulating underground and in the groundwater also feeds into the Gulf.

It found that even if strict measures were to fully stem annual runoffs, it could take more than 30 years for the 'legacy' nitrogen to clear up, and for the Gulf to recover.

Improving water quality in the Gulf of Mexico requires certain changes in agricultural practices

More careful application of fertilizers, reduced tillage, and cultivating plants that can stop chemicals from leaching into water are just some ways to curb nitrogen pollution. 3574839]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IWXAKVBIHR3DRRLWJRXL4RMEAVTRK5A6JFVHTYAFJAAAAHLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D60/B6E/D60B6EA619FE54796E42F547F5F12969.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dead zone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gulf of mexico]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gulf of mexico dead zone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypoxic zone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nitrogen fertilizer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nitrogen runoffs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ legacy nitrogen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ low oxygen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ American corn belt]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/space-drone-that-extends-life-of-satellites-could-be-weaponized-3574409</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Space drone that extends life of satellites could be weaponized 3574409]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A UK-based space company is planning to launch satellite-servicing drones by 2020, but experts warn these could double as space weapons.

The BBC reports that the Space Drone is an 800-pound spacecraft that can dock onto ageing satellites running low on fuel, and helping to stabilize and maneuver them.

The drones remain attached for up to five years, before then moving the satellite to a graveyard orbit at the end of its life.

Experts believe the space drones can be used to clean up Earth's orbit by directing space debris to the atmosphere to burn up.

Theoretically, the drones could also be weaponized and used to hijack active satellites and push them out of orbit.

The company that makes the space drones says any technology has the potential to be abused, and claims they can prevent this by retaining control and simply offering their services. 3574409]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIFGXTXBMDWMDAVBJPFZKBGM5DV5FC2KWPFXT3SKFJR3W3UBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/68B/04C/68B04C3AB0CD348F9433A7DFABAB74AA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  space drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ old satellites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space junk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space tugboat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ outer space tugboat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ orbital tugboat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ low fuel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ graveyard orbit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weaponized satellites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ effective space]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hublot-unveils-smartwatch-designed-for-world-cup-refs-3574403</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hublot unveils smartwatch designed for World Cup refs 3574403]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RUSSIA — Swiss watchmaker Hublot has unveiled a new World Cup smartwatch called the Big Bang Referee.

It is equipped with a 35.4 mm watchface, 400-by-400 AMOLED screen, Bluetooth, Wi-Fi, and 24-hour battery.

The Google Wear OS-powered watch displays a countdown to the World Cup, and has match time alerts and stats.

Some dials are inspired by team and country flags. There are also neutral dial choices.

Referees will wear a version of the watch connected to goal-line technology at this year’s World Cup. 3574403]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5BRAXTWLBKFMAKEKFPAT9JCGMDSREAMKFIFVFAHABLFEVAIKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/922/169/92216914B28542C8BC6D6D0BD6401E06.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hublot smartwatch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hublot world cup watch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hublot world cup watch price]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[world cup smartwatch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[referee watch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[referee watch soccer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[2018 fifa world cup russia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-dies-after-getting-head-stuck-in-expensive-reclining-movie-seat-3574379</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man dies after getting head stuck in expensive reclining movie seat 3574379]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM — A UK man passed away from a heart attack after getting stuck in a movie theater seat. 

A man and his partner were watching a movie at the Vue Cinema in Birmingham, England. The two paid more to sit in ‘Gold Class’ where the seats recline. 

At some point during the flick, the man dropped his cellphone on the ground. 

When he went to go pick it up, an electronic footrest came down on his head and trapped him underneath. 

His partner and staff struggled to get him free. The leg-rest eventually broke and he was able to get out. Unfortunately the guy had a heart attack and passed away a week later.  

The movie theater said they are conducting an investigation into the freak accident. 3574379]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDAIXRGLWIFMYZYLMDRZ9LVMVDETUTRAJKWRGICAMCWAATXLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/922/169/92216914B28542C8BC6D6D0BD6401E06.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-24T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>43</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flat-earth-rocketeer-finally-blasts-off-in-homemade-rocket-3576502</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flat earth rocketeer finally blasts off in homemade rocket 3576502]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMBOY, CALIFORNIA — Flat-earther 'Mad' Mike Hughes finally blasted off in his homemade rocket.

The Los Angeles Times reports that the former limo driver spent years building the steam-powered rocket out of salvaged garage parts, and meant to launch it last November.

But the 61-year-old had to redesign his baby after Big Government stepped in. And between that and technical trouble, the launch date had to be forced back.

Saturday seemed like it would be another failure to launch, but old man Hughes was sick of hearing people say he'd chickened out. So he fired up the rocket just after 3 p.m. and blasted himself into the sky, 1,875 feet above the Mojave Desert.

Minutes later, and with two parachutes deployed, the rocket landed with a thud some 1,500 feet from the launch site.

Its front was broken in two places, but the man inside came out in one piece — dinged up with an aching back. Guess someone learned about gravity!

Mr. Flat Earth didn't go high enough to prove his theory though, but claims that's what his next project is for. So stay tuned kids, or...not. 3576502]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAWGDCSK5CAIBRSLZAW774RGIEE7EC6KADWMTIKKEBRKB3VAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/104/01E/10401E5F72DF4D6B9F720000C25DE7F2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earth rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mad mike hughes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homemade rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homemade steam rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam powered rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat earth society]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-bus-catches-fire-half-the-country-pours-out-of-it-3576481</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese bus catches fire, half the country pours out of it 3576481]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HARBIN, CHINA — A bus in northeast China caught fire last Sunday. It was carrying a couple of people.  

According to state funded site, The Paper, the incident occured in central Harbin around 1:30 pm when the bus's left rear tire blew while turning, which started a fire. 

More than 50 passengers poured out of the bus. Minutes later, the entire bus was engulfed in flames.  

Unfortunately, the fire was put out by firefighters. One passenger sustained slight burns and was transported to the hospital. 3576481]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKRGCAIANKAAV3DLJLFT9DRMAABVRT2K6LWXUZHKSJRMVRAKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CDD/43C/CDD43C15BB6F44838DA328C83DD50C51.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>88</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china buses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china bus on fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ people running out of bus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china bus incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bus on fire video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china bus video]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-refused-cheeseburgers-destroys-mickey-d-golden-arches-3576350</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man refused cheeseburgers, destroys Mickey D golden arches 3576350]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SUTHERLIN, OREGON — A man has been charged after going toe-to-toe with a McDonald's golden arches.

According to the Associated Press, Jedediah Ezekiel Fulton, 37, was visiting a McDonald's in Sutherlin, Oregon. 

There, staff refused his order for 30 double cheeseburgers. Fulton, according to the Associated Press, reacted to this refusal attacking a banner and McDonald's golden arches.

Reportedly, someone also pulled a piece on Fulton after he grabbed another person's clothing.

Fulton was hit with second-degree charges of disorderly conduct, criminal trespassing, and criminal mischief and harassment. 3576350]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFJFMCZDARARGV3CLJLA5K4SG2IETSK9KEBW3HZHA6JAPAZGKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D6B/B92/D6BB9289994047E587A75A338E7736DE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man vs mcdonalds sign]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mcdonalds vs customer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mcdonalds fights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mcdonalds stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oregon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ customer vs mcdonalds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fast food fights]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/united-passenger-gets-10-000-travel-voucher-for-giving-up-seat-3576270</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[United passenger gets $10,000 travel voucher for giving up seat 3576270]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES — United Airlines gave a passenger $10,000 worth of travel credit last week after they bumped her from a flight. 

Communications Director Allison Preiss was Texas bound for her friend's bachelorette party. Problem is one of the fully-booked planes seats was broke. Preiss live-tweeted the ordeal from the airport.

The airline asked for volunteers to give up their seat, initially offering a $1000 travel voucher. There were no takers so the airline bumped Preiss as she'd gotten the cheapest seat at $163.

According to Preiss, they offered her $2000 in travel credit, but she said she'd rather take the cash. Preiss also says United wanted her to sign a document saying she volunteered to give up her seat. 

The airline offered her $10,000 in travel credit, plus some meal vouchers, reports ABC. Preiss took the deal, and got on a later flight and still made the bachelorette party. 3576270]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NWPDIEBVAAKDRSB6LR79JHMNJVZFANLWLW5GIGAMARIWCSBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EA0/0CF/EA00CF95E88841BFB9764E115945711E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bumped from flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bumped from united flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ allison preiss]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united airlines ticket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fully booked plane]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-how-to-avoid-getting-sick-on-airplanes-3577278</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's how to avoid getting sick on airplanes 3577278]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — Where you sit on a plane apparently matters as far as germ exposure is concerned, at least according to a new study.

According to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences of the United States of America, human movement around an enclosed space such as an airline cabin can supposedly spread more viruses than recirculated air.

Since a person's seat influences their movement, those in the aisle and middle seats are more likely to get up and be exposed to germs. Passengers who pick a window seat and stay there have the least exposure.

A study found that on a flight of 150 passengers where one person is sick, only one person on average will become infected.

The odds of getting sick are highest among the 11 passengers seated closest to the sick person — three beside, four in front, and four behind.

So if you're particular about germs, maybe try booking a window seat next time.

And if you just happen to sit next to someone who looks like death warmed over, the overhead air vents might still help you ward away those pesky germs. 3577278]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAARGYCTLNIWCXZUL6IRI6LWGJKVRR3SAWJAXURKKZAAEBRFBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/347/F82/347F82EC806744C99142DC7BB2599FC3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ best seat on plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ window seat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disease transmission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virus transmission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane germs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ germs on planes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viruses on planes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kim-jong-un-may-have-paid-china-a-visit-via-armored-train-3577268</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un may have paid China a visit via armored train 3577268]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — Unusually heavy security in China's capital coupled with the arrival of a mysterious train from the North are sparking intense speculation over who came to visit.

The Los Angeles Times reports that Japanese news media first noticed the armored train crossing from North Korea into China at the border city of Dandong.

Soldiers and police were on hand when the train arrived at Beijing station on Monday, with reports indicating Kim Jong Un was onboard.

The 21-car train bears a striking resemblance to the armored train Kim's late father Kim Jong Il used to visit allies in China and Russia.

The locomotive reportedly contained a conference room, an audience chamber, and bedrooms, and was fitted with satellite phone connections and a flat screen TV.

The news has not been confirmed, but if true, this visit is the reclusive leader's first known trip outside his country since taking power in 2011.

Analysts say it's possible Kim may be in town to talk to the Chinese regarding his upcoming meeting with U.S. President Trump. 3577268]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IFVC3WBIEAMCR7B5AR79JFM2LVZF34AECF5G3WKSLAAW3UBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4BD/A59/4BDA5977AC254A85A18FC075B2D44F94.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea visit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armored train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ state visit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beijing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong il]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea armored train]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/packages-of-black-powder-sent-to-u-s-military-government-offices-3577189</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Packages of black powder sent to U.S. military, government offices 3577189]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON, D.C. — An FBI-led Investigation is underway after federal facilities, military, CIA and FBI installations all received suspicious packages on Monday.

Fort Belvoir, Fort McNair and the CIA all received packages containing black powder, reports CNN, citing officials. 

Law enforcement told CNN over 10 devices were found and explosions from the packages would not have resulted in casualties. 3577189]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFJAGAKUBBIRZAAYL2JFTL43GZBB7RIQAEDA3HRABVCAICAJBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9A4/2A4/9A42A401F41349D8B5B2F6B9118006D1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>39</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ suspicious package]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strange mail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ powder in the mail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ suspicious powder in mail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mail room inspection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ government]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mars-is-making-flat-maltesers-and-no-one-s-happy-3577001</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mars is making flat Maltesers, and no one's happy 3577001]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Fan-favorite Maltesers might be getting an unappetizing makeover, because nothing is sacred anymore.

The Sun reports that Mars apparently wants to fight falling sales by turning the malted chocolate balls into flat oval-shaped buttons. How that's going to solve things is anyone's guess.

The depressing news got leaked to the paper by someone who auditioned for a new online ad. While acting out a scene, he and some other actors were told the maltesers they'd be holding would be flat.

None of them thought flat maltesers were a good idea, probably because it isn't. You'll bet fans will riot if the change ever goes through.

So unless it's to put in more balls per bag, Mars better leave Maltesers alone. 3577001]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDAGYZGLSIWEDA9LWPRKKBFMVASVS35KSLF5UAEABKAIAZDAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/56A/BA1/56ABA108D26546C5A03CBDE17B4A019F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maltesers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flat maltesers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chocolate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malted chocolate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chocolate balls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malted chocolate balls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ minstrels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chocolate makeover]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/meet-the-interstitium-it-could-be-your-newest-and-biggest-organ-3578053</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Meet the interstitium, it could be your newest and biggest organ 3578053]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY — Scientists at New York University have discovered a previously unseen human organ, according to a new study.

Called the interstitium, the organ is a system of interconnected lymph fluid pockets that found throughout, according to the research.   

Researchers say the interstitium is a body-wide structure of lymph-fluid, collagen and proteins. The organ is also believed to comprise 20 percent of all bodily fluids, according to a CBS report.

The study also found that the interstitium had helped cancer cells move from infected areas to other areas of the body via the lymphatic system. NYU pathologist Neil Theise described this as a waterslide, according to a quote in a New Scientist report on the study. 

The findings were published in the journal Scientific Reports. 3578053]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2JFVCREAVFRCCZ7LZARXKDXMSKETET4A6IAVTIAA5DATATSKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F9A/5EB/F9A5EBA09CCD0D705F44B99C74B3FBF1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new human organ found]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new human organ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interstitium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new organ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ organ discovery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interstitium organ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is the interstitium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biggest organ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ largest organ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new organ found in human body]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ interstitium explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how does cancer spread]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lymphatic system]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-shows-off-massive-naval-fleet-in-south-china-sea-3577996</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China shows off massive naval fleet in South China Sea 3577996]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOUTH CHINA SEA — Dozens of naval vessels were spotted doing drills in disputed waters, in what experts believe is China showing off its growing military might.

Reuters reports that satellite images taken by Planet Labs Inc. on Monday revealed that the Chinese aircraft carrier Liaoning entered a vital trade waterway in the South China Sea, just off Hainan Island.

At least 40 ships and submarines were seen flanking the aircraft carrier — an unusually large show of force, according to experts.

The massive Chinese fleet was sailing in a line formation headed by the submarines, and accompanied by several aircrafts flying overhead.

It's unclear though where the fleet was headed or how long the naval exercises are set to last.

Analysts say China may be displaying inter-fleet interoperability, which the navy has been working on. It's also possible they're flexing their muscles in response to a freedom-of-navigation patrol by a U.S. warship last week. 3577996]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMBWAXABKRAWGBZVLZARTLUVM5EBVSINLSIWMGABKZAA5AIAKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ACA/5E8/ACA5E83FFFAD4678611A96141748E578.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south china sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese fleet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south sea fleet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liaoning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aircraft carrier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china military drills]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ war games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/second-wave-of-flu-virus-happening-now-warns-cdc-3577826</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Second wave of flu virus happening now, warns CDC 3577826]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTA, GEORGIA — This year's flu season has been one of the worst the U.S. has ever seen, and though it's winding down, we're not in the clear just yet.

According to the CDC, cases of the dominant and more serious influenza-A strain have been declining in recent weeks.

But another form of the virus, influenza-B, is on the rise, and now makes up for 60% of reported flu cases in the country.

Though generally milder, the B-strain virus tends to affect younger children more severely.

It's also possible for adults who have gotten sick from the A-strain to also become infected with the B virus within the same season.

Since both strains are still active, doctors recommend flu shots for those who are still unvaccinated. Standard hygiene practices should also be followed to keep the viruses at bay. 3577826]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNFAXAHBVAWGCTELEAWTK4WGIDSREC5ABIFMUAGARCACXZHAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/417/7C0/4177C08929134E15A0ADE063987816E5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ influenza]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ influenza virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ influenza A]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ influenza B]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ second wave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2018 flu season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CDC]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contagious disease]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cali-mountain-lion-captured-after-close-encounter-with-resident-3577799</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cali mountain lion captured after close encounter with resident 3577799]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AZUSA, CALIFORNIA — Residents of Azusa, California were warned to stay inside of their homes after a large mountain lion was spotted in a residential neighborhood on early Monday morning.

Before 7 a.m., Azusa police were notified a mountain lion was seen in the 600 block of West Virginia Ann Drive wandering through backyards.

While walking home, a 65-year-old woman spotted the giant feline on her front yard from across the street. According to the woman, the mountain lion was said to be about the size of a small horse or pony, Azusa authorities also added that the lion appeared to be blind in one eye.

The staring contest was interrupted when an police officer drove up and told the woman to go inside for her safety. The cat was then tracked by a police drone, it hopped a fence and moved into another backyard, then climbed a shed and hopped into the back of another home.

By 9:30 a.m., officials from the California Department of Fish and Wildlife tracked the animal down and tranquilized it. The lion was then taken away to be released into the wild, preferably further away from people. 3577799]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBJFXCRCAVFACBTCBSPRZ6DRMAABZSZIKSLWXGIBBWIWIBZMBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7CD/F8B/7CDF8BD9898340979734330B96B31E84.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain lion encounter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain lion encounter california]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain lion california]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain lion california house]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain lion california video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain lion encounter california]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain lion southern california]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ azusa california]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/offensive-language-ban-coming-to-xbox-and-other-microsoft-services-3577782</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Offensive language ban coming to Xbox and other Microsoft services 3577782]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[REDMOND, WASHINGTON — Online Xbox gamers who curse run risk of a ban, according to new rules from the Microsoft-owned service.

Discovered by blog Professional Troublemaker, new Terms of Service says use of offensive lingo could see you banned, or even the loss of your account. Publicly showing, or sharing inappropriate content or material via Xbox or another Microsoft service could have them look at your stuff.

Microsoft say they can also review your content  should you violate the terms of service. These services including everything from Outlook, Office and Word to Skype. 3577782]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMCACDIJKNIAMBZ9LWLRRL4SNEBSVSRNKSPF3TIFKFIRCBC3BD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/84D/CFF/84DCFFC2ACEB42499D9515A73E0D0925.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xbox ban for cursing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microsoft ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skype ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new xbox rules]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xbox offensive language]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xbox ban reaction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xbox]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/archaeologists-find-81-lost-settlements-in-the-amazon-3579099</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Archaeologists find 81 lost settlements in the Amazon 3579099]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ACRE, BRAZIL — Before the Europeans turned up in South America, the assumption was that the Amazon was mostly uninhabited. Well, we were wrong.

According to a new study published in Nature Communications, deforestation in the Amazon has uncovered at least 81 geoglyphs- trenches carved into the ground that were spotted on satellite images of Brazil's Upper Tapajos Basin.

The geoglyphs come in a range of different shapes and sizes, and are believed to date back centuries, from the years 1250 to 1500.

Archaeologists examined several locations and found fragments of pottery, stone axes, and fertile dark earth indicative of a long-term human settlement.

Researchers used models to estimate that between 1,000 to 1,500 wooden settlements were built in the southern rim of the Amazon alone, housing 500,000 to a million people.

This indigenous population was likely wiped out by the outbreak of diseases, and would have been worsened by the arrival of the Europeans. 3579099]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJRAYAAAJKFCVCCKFKF794VMJJSXU33AEAA5GAGKZDRVAZBLH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/296/E4F/296E4FF14FD041FF9683A12E60B5F58B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient settlement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon village]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lost settlement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lost village]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon tribe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon settlements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon rainforest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ archaeological find]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ archaeologists]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pre columbian]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/utah-cop-survives-after-car-hits-him-on-highway-3578913</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Utah cop survives after car hits him on highway 3578913]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SARDINE CANYON, UTAH — A Utah Highway Patrol trooper is lucky to be alive after being struck by a car on a highway.

According to the Utah Department of Public Safety, Sgt. Cade Brenchley was hit by a vehicle during a snowstorm on Sunday March 25. Footage of the accident shows him being thrown into the air during the accident, and bystanders later coming to his aid.

Amazingly, Brenchley survived the ordeal, but he didn't escape unscathed. The 13-year veteran officer was treated for broken ribs and a broken scapula. 3578913]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLFKXZGA5AWMAR9BWLRI74WGNJB3UTZLRAA5HIDKSLAZX3VBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4C6/9CC/4C69CC9F8806440AB3951DE4DB9F87C5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cop gets hit by car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trooper gets hit by car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazing survival story]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cop survives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trooper survives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hit on highway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ highway accident]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/costco-bandits-nabbed-mid-heist-by-seattle-cops-3578910</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Costco bandits nabbed mid-heist by Seattle cops 3578910]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Police have released footage showing the moment they busted thieves at a Costco in Seattle.

The bust went down on March 14. The clip shows cops awaiting the unsuspecting thieves outside an an entrance to the store.

Video of the incident was posted online by Seattle Police Department on March 16. 3578910]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABLWPCCTAZBRKC3ALFLRXKJGM5BB5SKZKZDW5GIKABKF5CREAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/511/A19/511A19CA7AF5420CBE8FA3092446AC6A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>40</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cops catch thieves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thieves caught red handed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shoplifters caught]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shoplifters caught red handed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shoplifters caught on camera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thieves caught on camera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police catch shoplifter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seattle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seattle police]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cops-nab-fake-u-s-marshal-who-stole-iphone-x-armed-with-bb-gun-3578907</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cops nab fake U.S. Marshal who stole iPhone X armed with BB gun 3578907]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOYNTON BEACH, FLORIDA —  Officers in Boynton Beach, Florida arrested a man on March 22 after he falsely claimed to be a U.S. Marshal.

The 61-year-old was reported for trespassing at a Best Buy on March 21, according to text accompanying video of the incident posted to the department's YouTube page.

Officers found the man to have a U.S. Marshal lapel pin, BB gun and a stolen iPhone X that was allegedly taken from the store at an earlier date. 3578907]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDFCYKUK5CWABI9L2PRR7U3MFKERUT7K6IFRTZLBWJACDTSKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CC2/A2D/CC2A2DC709B14F06BEDE83D81A4C15FC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>116</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake cop gets arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake cop gets caught]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ impersonating a police officer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cops catch fake us marshall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake federal agent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake police officer gets arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boynton beach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ best buy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ohio-officers-save-choking-baby-girl-3578904</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ohio officers save choking baby girl 3578904]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHAKER HEIGHTS, OHIO — A pair of Ohio cops were called into action earlier this month after a disabled baby girl began choking.

Two-month-old Tyra was choking and not breathing when the officers arrived to help her,
according to a post on the Shaker Heights Police Department Facebook page. 

Released police bodycam footage shows officers arriving to help the infant. 3578904]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NWGYZEBIDWEBAWKFLR57SCGNKEREZNLRCAXT3WBSLA5YIDAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E5D/545/E5D5452AFE914A95990DACAEE3B8E5D2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>85</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cops save baby girl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cops saving lives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ good cop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ohio]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shaker heights police department]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cops rescue kids]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cops rescue baby]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-firm-offers-artificial-shooting-stars-3578843</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese firm offers artificial shooting stars 3578843]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — A Japanese startup wants to offer the world on-demand fake meteor showers.

Tokyo-based Astro Live Experience will use a microsatellite to create an artificial shooting star show for the 2020 Olympics. The company now want to make it available on demand.

In December, the company plans to launch a to two satellites at an orbit of 220 miles over Earth. The International Space Station orbits at 250 miles. The heights of other the thousands of other satellites in orbit vary.

ALE told BuzzFeed they'd do a triple-check with US Strategic Command's satellite trajectory prior to any pellet launch in order to avoid collision with other spacecraft.

The problem with that, a retired U.S. Air Force Colonel pointed out, is that spy satellites' trajectories are classified and kept out of the catalog. Meaning, a pellet could theoretically hit one. 3578843]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AFGY3WKEDWEAIVL5AWX7LUMACE5RT7K2KWXHRKAAAFXYCXAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7C2/C88/7C2C889D5E1A4D1488BEDF349CAB8373.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>93</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meteor show]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Astro Live Experience]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake meteor show]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial shooting stars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man made star show]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man made meteor shower]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tokyo 2020]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ikea-experimenting-with-meatballs-made-of-mealworms-3578650</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[IKEA experimenting with meatballs made of mealworms 3578650]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK — Furniture giant IKEA has created a new version of their foods in a attempt to save the earth, except the food is all made from insects. 

To beat a looming global food crisis, Ikea's innovation research lab Space 10 in Copenhagen, Denmark has been experimenting various food alternatives.

The meatballs have been redesigned as Crispy Bug Balls, these edible balls are made from a variety of ingredients, including mealworms. 

The Bug Burger, which is made with beetroot, parsnip, potatoes and a dollop of mealworms, are topped with blackcurrant and beetroot ketchup.

And there is also the Dogless Hotdog where meat is substituted with baby carrots topped with seaweed, and a bright green bun made from algae.

Although eating insects is still quite strange to many, Ikea's food lab said the dishes should not just be healthy or sustainable, but they must be delicious, too. And to inspire people to try new ingredients, they have to titillate the taste buds. 3578650]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIFECAIAEDAKWI7LWKAR9LXM6JBIFAKLSJR3UZAAEBFVWAMKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0B7/0DD/0B70DD714EB6413AB6725BB7865F80D9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ikea meatballs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mealworm meatballs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ikea future foods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ikea food recipes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ future foods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mealworm foods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ copenhagen denmark]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-starts-testing-a-new-nuclear-reactor-3578626</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea starts testing a new nuclear reactor 3578626]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[YONGBYON, NORTH KOREA — Denuclearization is on the agenda for the Kim-Trump playdate. But meantime, the North's has a new reactor its itching to test.

A newly finished nuclear reactor in North Korea's Yongbyon complex has reportedly come online, after satellite images show its smokestack releasing emissions. 

The North claims the reactor is meant to produce electricity for civilians, since it has the potential to create enough megawatts to power a small town.

Experts point out that the nuclear reactor can also be used to create 20 kilograms of plutonium a year to power its nuclear weapons.

To achieve complete denuclearization, the U.S. will have to persuade the North Koreans to give up not just their arsenal, but also facilities that produce nuclear fuel.

Good luck and godspeed to that. 3578626]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NWKDKVBIARAVI9LWIR57UTMJKB5EC7K5AF7HRGK6LF5WILAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/60B/816/60B81682F45649D6943EA060BFF5815D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear reactor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump kim talks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yongbyon nuclear complex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ denuclearization]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/150-million-user-accounts-breached-says-under-armour-3579731</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[150 million user accounts breached, says Under Armour 3579731]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE — A wildly popular fitness app got hacked last month, exposing information on the millions of lazy people that use it.

According to Reuters, Under Armour announced on Thursday that its nutrition and exercise tracking app MyFitnessPal was breached in late February.

About 150 million accounts were compromised, with hackers getting their hands on user names, email addresses, and encrypted passwords.

Payment card data is processed separately, so it wasn't accessed.

Still, there's a chance hackers might use the info they do have to break into a user's other accounts.

So if you happen to be on MyFitnessPal, now's the time to change all your passwords.

No one knows who masterminded the hack and more importantly — why. But somewhere in the world, someone now knows for sure that America doesn't exercise. 3579731]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6NFECKWAADARAI7LSLRZ6JAMVEE7RRLKNJAZGZDASIRTVRGAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/642/511/642511EDF53624843F3A77142F924903.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ under armour]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ my fitness pal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ myfitnesspal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fitness app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exercise app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data breach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ user information]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-logged-sms-texts-and-phone-calls-without-being-clear-3579651</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook logged SMS texts and phone calls without being clear 3579651]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Facebook has been scraping call records and SMS data from Android devices for years. 

After Faceplant's Cambridge Analytica scandal, several users reported finding months or years of calls history data in their downloadable Facebook data file, according to Ars Technica. 

Facepunch needs your contacts, SMS data and call history to improve its friend recommendation algorithm and figure out who your true pals are. 

Facesuck says it has an opt-in prompt that lets the social media monster continuously upload your contact data, including call and text history. 

What could possibly go wrong by letting some brats at Facebook have access to your phone? 3579651]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMDAPDCSLSJR3VIYBMCR7KDXMSKSTR34KBIFZHRBARBAVBRFKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/978/AA9/978AA92B374B4768826D61E2F46CE613.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook SMS texts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook phone calls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook collecting SMS texts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook collecting phone data]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-s-beer-belly-turns-out-to-be-a-whopping-30-pound-tumor-3579626</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man's beer belly turns out to be a whopping 30-pound tumor 3579626]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOBOKEN, NEW JERSEY — Sometimes seeing is believing, a beach-ball size tumor that was thought to be a beer belly, was found growing inside a 63-year-old New Jersey man's belly. 

The belly trouble started out when Hoboken resident Kevin Daly was told to lose some weight after heart surgery which is quite frank but normal. 

Standing at 6'2 and fit for his age, up until a few months ago, Daly just couldn't get rid of what friends and family thought was a beer belly, however, Daly doesn't like to drink beer and has always been athletic.

Daly got CT scan from Lenox Hill Hospital in New York City which showed the beer belly was really just a massive mass occupying most of his abdominal cavity. It took the doctors six hours to get the tumor out in one piece, it turned out to be a 30-pound liposarcoma, a low grade, fatty cancer that was wrapped around a kidney.

Fast forward to two months later, Daly said he feels great and lucky as the tumor was slow growing, and now he just needs to be monitored with regular MRI check ups. 3579626]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIFKCZIBIARVAKALJKRKKLWNFJB7SCSLWPA5U3SKZHRVBCYKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0A9/6F1/0A96F1E1F02F4854B1A87367482C2278.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ belly tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beer belly tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant cell tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant cell tumor surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant tumor removed from man's belly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hoboken new jersey]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/us-in-jeopardy-from-china-and-russia-hypersonic-weapons-3579564</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[US in jeopardy from China and Russia hypersonic weapons 3579564]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — A U.S. general says the nation currently has no defense against new hypersonic weapons being developed by the Chinese and Russians.

Gen. John Hyten, the head of U.S. Strategic Command, said the weapons still need several years of development, but that without missile defense upgrades, the U.S. will be unable to detect them when they are operational, according to CNN. 

Hypersonic weapons travel at speeds over Mach 5, or 3,806 mph. Hypersonic missiles are launched into space, but then reenter the atmosphere and fly at high speeds on a flight path similar to an aircraft. 
The lower altitude trajectory make them more difficult for U.S. missile defense satellites and radars to pick them up.  

Hyten said the U.S. would need to first upgrade its sensor capabilities as well as develop more effective interceptor missiles with more lethal warheads. 3579564]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNFKAICAAARAVZYLNKAV9BHGMBVZFANAJJRZHRHK5DATBRAKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/362/6B8/3626B80516FD412FB3BC9F44E529491C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypersonic weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US hypersonic weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russia hypersonic weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China hypersonic weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypersonic]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-guy-who-made-the-awesome-ronaldo-bust-made-another-one-3579562</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The guy who made the awesome Ronaldo bust made another one 3579562]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FUNCHAL, MADEIRA — The sculptor who made the now infamous Cristiano Ronaldo bust for the airport in Madeira has taken another kick at it. 

Thanks to the help of Bleacher Report, Emanuel Santos, the 41-year-old artist behind the bronze, was given a do-over. 
In a documentary released by B/R, Santos describes how awesome it was being trolled by the whole world after the first bust was unveiled. 

Despite the harsh criticisms, Santos still stands by his original work.

But when put up to the challenge of taking another crack at it, he accepted and blasted this one in for a score. 
Although, we still think the first one had way more character and personality. More so than the real Ronaldo. 3579562]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KADRCAICLWKRAAI7B6PFZ72AMECVXE39ABIWZTZDK5HRCACVAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E28/E31/E28E318EBA67419591F10230E009FA31.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>43</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ronaldo sculptor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ronaldo bust]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ funny Ronaldo bust]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hilarious Ronaldo bust]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ronaldo airport bust]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mom-finds-epidural-needle-lodged-in-spine-14-years-after-giving-birth-3579521</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mom finds epidural needle lodged in spine 14 years after giving birth 3579521]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JACKSONVILLE, FLORIDA — A woman is suing the hospital she gave birth in more than a decade ago after discovering they'd left something in her.

News4Jax reports that Amy Bright began suffering from chronic back and leg pain after delivering son Jacob via C-section in 2003.

Doctors thought it was sciatica, until a CT scan last November revealed the real culprit: a needle lodged in her spine.

The 3-centimeter long tip had broken off during her epidural 14 years ago at the Naval Hospital in Jacksonville. There's no way the medical staff there didn't catch the gaffe, because it's SOP to check, and such a huge chunk of was missing.

It would have been easy to remedy the situation then. But now, with most of the needle buried in bone and touching the nerve that leads to Bright's left leg, doctors say removal is too risky.

Instead, the 41-year-old mother of three has to rely on pain medication and physical therapy for the rest of her life.

She's thankful her son didn't suffer any complications and is now a healthy teenager, but claims the hospital needs to pay for what they've done to her. 3579521]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIRPCTTBNJRXA3CLVDWZ7JAGWKSRS34AIBWVURBAVDRCAZDAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F7D/0EB/F7D0EB3FB0694DDAB3378EA4B9ED2609.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medical malpractice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medical boo boo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ epidural needle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ needle in spine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ needle stuck in spine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgical fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giving birth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ epidural]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ c-section]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ naval hospital]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fifa-world-cup-russia-set-to-use-artificial-turfs-3579510</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[FIFA World Cup Russia set to use artificial turfs 3579510]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RUSSIA — The 2018 Fifa World Cup tournament in Russia will be played on artificial turf for the first time in football history.

Artificial turf is made of synthetic blades in which layers of sand and performance infills are incorporated. Some systems also utilise a shock-absorbing layer underneath the turf.

Artificial turf is weather-resistant and does not need sunlight, and is therefore more cost-efficient compared to natural grass. 

FIFA requirements ensure the turf being used meet playing performance, safety, durability and quality assurance standards. 

FIFA awards the FIFA Quality mark to turf that meet the standard for amateur pitches, and awards the FIFA Quality Pro mark to turf that been shown to provide the highest playing performance for professional level football.

According to turf provider of the tournament, SIS Pitches, in total, six of the 12 stadiums in Russia to host the games at this summer's World Cup will be outfitted with artificial turf. 3579510]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5CFPYKWLZBWZVCCB5DA77DTM5EBTR39AWPF5UAEKFKAXVAJKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/856/D27/856D27A04E534FA3A91285F77EF0552E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial turfs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial turfs soccer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial turfs football]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial turfs world cup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial pitch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial football pitch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia world cup pitch]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-tiangong-1-is-plummeting-back-to-earth-3579501</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China's Tiangong-1 is plummeting back to Earth 3579501]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EARTH — China's Tiangong-1 spacecraft is predicted to fall to Earth on Saturday March 31 or Sunday, April 1.

According to Aerospace Corp, re-entry will begin when spacecraft falls to an altitude of 120 kilometers above Earth. Some of this maybe visible from Earth. After reaching an altitude of 80 kilometers, the spacecraft will likely break apart.

The UK Space Agency's chief engineer told the BBC that most of Tiangong-1 will burn up on re-entry, with surviving debris likely falling into the ocean.

Experts say the risk of it impacting a city or populated area are very low.  The chances of someone being hit by Tiangong-1 are 1 in a trillion, reported Space.com, citing Aerospace Corp. 

The spacecraft is expected to fall somewhere between 43 degrees north and 43 degrees south latitudes, reports the BBC. 3579501]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNFMDRCAABA7BKCKFJAZKBFNBKV7ST6K5AFMTICKFKRVDIEAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/562/21D/56221D343A3A4DF5B5DA7707B1B0563D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong-1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falling spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atmospheric reentry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ debri from falling spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debri lands on Earth]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-has-world-s-worst-case-of-super-gonorrhoea-3579420</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man has 'world's worst' case of super-gonorrhoea 3579420]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM — A man has been diagnosed with a severe case of super-gonorrhea that is resistant to first choice antibiotics. 
The man but picked up the sexually transmitted disease after a sexual encounter with a woman in southeast Asia, according to the BBC. 

Public Health England says it's the first time the infection was unable to be treated with a combination of azithromycin and ceftriaxone antibiotics. 

Officials from the World Health Organization and the European Centers for Disease Control say this is a first for the world. 

The infection is caused by the bacterium Neisseria gonorrhea. It's spread through unprotected sex.

Symptoms can include a thick green or yellow discharge from sexual organs, pain urinating and bleeding between periods.

If left untreated, it can cause infertility, pelvic inflammatory disease and can be spread to children during pregnancy. 

Physicians now have the man on one last antibiotic, but will have to wait till next month to see if it worked at combating the infection. 3579420]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNRGDTTAFLR7BASBSIA7L43MIABRRK9ABKFVURLAJKA5WRLKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1E8/A3A/1E8A3A350A0E4689A0F482DD8E69432D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gonorrhoea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super gonorrhoea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ azithromycin-resistant gonorrhea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infertility]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the clap]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/google-renaming-gmail-to-gpost-to-be-more-inclusive-3579391</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Google renaming 'Gmail' to 'Gpost' to be more inclusive 3579391]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA — Google announced it will be changing the name of Gmail to Gpost in an effort to fight sexism and biased language. 

Google said it was concerned with the overall environment of stereotypes and biased language within the tech community and the U.S. at large.  

In a push towards equality, Google felt the name 'Gmail' was inherently offensive to some because it's a homonym of the word 'male', according to TechCrunch.  

After an internal survey of employees, Googlers felt 'Gpost' would be less offensive, especially for women. 

The diversity and inclusion department decided to roll out the name change internally at first. 
All Gmail users will get the new Gpost update over the next few weeks. Those experiencing trouble logging in should contact Google immediately. 3579391]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMAAADZJLJKA5ATEBBKAX94YMVEVTFC2LSIW3GAKKMDA7WIJKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0FD/007/0FD00772CC1C4D41A03D99E85993C055.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-03-31T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gmail changing name]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gmail to Gpost]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google Gpost]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Google diversity and inclusion]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
