<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tesla-issues-its-largest-recall-of-123-000-model-s-vehicles-3581903</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tesla issues its largest recall of 123,000 Model S vehicles 3581903]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA — Tesla Inc voluntarily issued a recall of Model S sedans built before April 2016 in order to replace power steering bolts last Thursday. 

It informed customers over email it was a proactive move and that there were no accidents or injuries related to the issue, according to Reuters. 

Bolts, made by German supplier Bosch, in the power steering component can start to corrode after contact with certain types of road salt in colder climates. 

The carmaker said 123,000 Model S cars around the world have the bolts. 

We have observed excessive corrosion in the power steering bolts, though only in very cold climates, particularly those that frequently use calcium or magnesium road salts, rather than sodium chloride (table salt), Tesla wrote in an email to customers.

If the bolts fail, drivers would still be able to steer the vehicle, they would just have to use more force due to loss or reduction of power assist, Tesla wrote. 
According to Tesla, the retrofit takes about an hour. The company said it would inform owners once the retrofit is available in their area. 3581903]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6LWXDKWAMFRGCIWKEDR572AMICSIET6KZBWMGKTAZGRIC3XKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AE8/7B7/AE87B7906A429DDA9716357FC47231A2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tesla]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tesla Model S recall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tesla power steering bolt recall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tesla voluntary recall]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/coffee-to-come-with-cancer-warnings-in-california-3581860</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Coffee to come with cancer warnings in California 3581860]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — California coffee drinkers are in for a buzzkill after a local judge ruled that everyone must be made aware that their cup of joe could come with the big C.

The New York Times reports that a lawsuit filed by the nonprofit Council for Education and Research on Toxics claims Starbucks, Dunkin Donuts, and other coffee companies failed to warn consumers about acrylamide, a possible carcinogen produced when coffee beans are roasted.

According to CBS, previous studies have shown that animals given high levels of the chemical in drinking water developed multiple tumors, but research on the effects on humans are inconclusive.

Experts say the amount of acrylamide ingested in coffee is small compared to eating french fries and potato chips, or smoking tobacco.

Many studies have even found probable evidence that coffee consumption is associated with a decreased risk of cancer.

But because coffee companies failed to show that acrylamide posed no risk or added any health benefits, the judge ruled that coffee sold in California must carry a cancer warning label.

Medical experts say a blanket warning linking coffee to cancer could cause unnecessary panic among the general public, especially since there is not enough evidence to suggest that this is in fact the case. 3581860]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIDRAXZAKNIFKCZ9LSPRRKDUMVEBVF3SAFKF3UZLBRGWIXRHBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E93/0A6/E930A681611F1A5C157D1085DD8991AE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  coffee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer warning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carcinogenic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acrylamide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carcinogen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee roasting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee cancerous]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coffee cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ california coffee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ california]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ proposition 65]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/shark-attacks-paddle-boarder-at-hawaii-s-kukio-beach-3581737</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Shark attacks paddle boarder at Hawaii's Kukio Beach 3581737]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KUKIO BEACH, HAWAII — A 25-year-old paddle boarder was critically injured Saturday morning after he was bitten by a shark off Kukio beach in Hawaii.

Authorities said the attack happened around 9:30 a.m. when an unidentified man was stand-up paddleboarding about 100-150 yards offshore.

It was unclear how the man made it back to shore, but he was reportedly being treated by people on the beach who applied multiple tourniquets to his right arm and leg before responding paramedics arrived.

Firefighters airlifted the paddle boarder to North Hawaii Community Hospital for further treatment, his condition was not immediately known. 

The state Department of Land and Natural Resources announced that beach closure signs warning visitors will be displayed for a mile on either side of the incident for the rest of the day. 3581737]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAFECTSKRBAIX3ALNPATK4TGRASIETRLSPRVHALKEGAIBAHAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/68B/D38/68BD3868C17D2EB135928867ACE35550.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii shark attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii shark encounters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii shark swimming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii shark bite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark bite hawaii]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man bitten by shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii kukio beach]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-inks-deal-with-us-for-tank-buster-missiles-until-2024-3581710</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Taiwan inks deal with US for tank buster missiles until 2024 3581710]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIPEI — The U.S. and Taiwan have struck a deal worth $130.5 million for an annual shipment of anti-tank missiles, reports the Taipei Times.

The arrangement will see the U.S. supply Taiwan with 460 TOW-2B Aero RF (radio frequency) anti tank missiles, the Taipei Times reports, citing a Taiwan Ministry of National Defence source. This will reportedly see the U.S. supply Taiwan with the missiles on a yearly basis from 2018 until 2024.

The deal is part of a $1.83 billion arms sales package that Taiwan negotiated with the Obama administration in late 2015. 3581710]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLWED3SAMBACDRUBRAFR7SAM6JETST3KJLWTTAEBVARAWTUKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0A8/D26/0A8D26A15DA9162DC7DD069309F4CAA5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan v china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tow missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anti tank missile in action]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tank buster missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tow missile v tank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tow missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tow tank missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tank buster missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anti-tank missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tow-2b]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/crypto-payments-to-be-available-in-6-000-south-korean-stores-3581586</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Crypto payments to be available in 6,000 South Korean stores 3581586]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL — South Koreans are about to get a lot more options on where they can spend their hard-earned virtual currency.

Korea JoongAng Daily reports that South Korean cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb recently partnered with a digital payment service operator to allow the widespread adoption of crypto payments.

Barcodes built into mobile apps will allow consumers to pay for goods at physical stores using the cryptocurrencies they hold at the exchange, according to a news release from Bitcoin.

The payment system is set to be available at 6,000 retail outlets around the country within the first half of the year, and could expand to 8,000 outlets by the end of 2018.

On top of this, Bithumb also signed an agreement with a Korean travel website, allowing customers to book hotels and other accommodations via cryptocurrency.

Virtual currencies are incredible popular in South Korea. It's currently the third largest market for cryptocurrency after the U.S. and Japan. 3581586]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASKFKX3XAACWKCCDB5ARI74YMRCSVR3ZAFKR3HAAKMGRMV34KE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A49/2B2/A492B2925425F98CF841355D11479DFE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crypto payment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency payment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin payment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bithumb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exchange]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korea pays services]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-jesus-breaks-into-pizza-hut-then-confesses-all-on-911-call-3581536</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Jesus' breaks into Pizza Hut then confesses all on 911 call 3581536]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DEFINITELY NOT BETHLEHEM, NORTH CAROLINA — A dude claiming to be Jesus Christ broke into a Pizza Hut late last month, then called 911.

In audio from an emergency call, obtained by station WFMY-TV, Jesus says he broke in because he was hungry and had some pizza. The caller later turned out to be Richard Lee Quintero. 

The 48-year-old claimed to suffer from schizophrenia and later taken into custody by police 3581536]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRCAMYZGKBLFCCZTLSLR36JANABE7SRQKAAFZHIDA5ARRA3YKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A0D/BA2/A0DBA2510469199B858697CDDE4F54AF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-03T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>124</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man who thinks he is jesus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jesus pizza hut break in]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weird 911 calls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ people claiming to be jesus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pizza hut break in]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pizza]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jesus christ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north carolina]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ richard quintero]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/arrested-taiwanese-exchange-student-found-with-1-600-bullets-3582634</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Arrested Taiwanese exchange student found with 1,600 bullets 3582634]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DREXEL HILL, PENNSYLVANIA — Pennsylvania police have found more than 1,600 rounds of ammunition and a handgun allegedly belonging to a Taiwanese exchange student who reportedly made violent threats.

The 18-year-old exchange student An Tso Sun, was arrested last week after threatening to shoot up Monsignor Bonner & Archbishop Prendergast Catholic High School in Drexel Hill, Pennsylvania. 

In the latest investigation, local authorities discovered 1,600 bullets for an AR-15, AK-47 and an untraceable handgun that Sun had put together. 

According to the police, a black bag with the firearms inside was found in Sun's room by his host family, and they hid it before the police arrived for their initial search.

The student's attorney had said last week that nothing his client had was illegal, and that the student was truly making a joke about wanting to shoot up the school, calling it a misunderstanding.

Upon his arrest, Sun was expelled from the school and remains in jail at Delaware County Jail in lieu of a US$100,000 bail for one count of making terroristic threats. His first hearing will be held on April 11.

Sun's parents arrived in the US on March 31 to help their son with the legal process. 3582634]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLAMDTXABJAABKCLFIRZ9SHMVCBVEANLWJRTTCXBREFCVZCKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A17/12B/A1712BDC29ED92DB05F5F7B0FDF84499.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exchange student in usa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exchange student arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ foreign student arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bullets and gun]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwanese student handgun]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/teen-rugby-player-left-paralysed-after-swallowing-a-slug-3582581</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Teen rugby player left paralysed after swallowing a slug 3582581]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SYDNEY AUSTRALIA — A young rugby player in Australia was left paralysed after agreeing to swallow a slug on a dare at a party in 2010.

Sydney native Sam Ballard, 19 at the time, was seen on a video asking friends at a party if he should swallow a live slug on a dare. 

However, Sam fell ill and was hospitalised, later finding out he had become infected with rat lungworm, which is found in faeces of rats and can be spread by slugs and snails.

Although the parasites can rarely cause infection, in Sam's case his brain was infected. He was diagnosed with eosinophilic[c] meningo-encephalitis[d] and fell into a coma for 420 days. 

What made matters worse is that when Sam woke up, he found himself quadriplegic and needed 24-hour care. 

Sam, who's now 28, requires a motorized wheelchair to move around, his family and friends have raised enough money to ensure he gets all the help he needs.

Sam's mom told the media that the incident has changed both of their lives, and because of Sam's condition, he has seizures and cannot control his body temperature, and he has to rely on a feeding tube. 

Last year, Sam's mom was told Sam's disability insurance money was being cut to $135,000 Australian dollars, which left the family heavily in debt as they already owed nursing service $42,000. National insurance officials said they are now working closely with Sam's family to find a solution so Sam can continue to survive. 3582581]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKFXY3SAIHWCVRUBRDA3LSBGRAB7UTZKJKWPU3WABPAEWAQKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AB6/19B/AB619BF67B3FB0BB807825290DEE96D9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>86</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupid dare challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stupid challenges to do with your best friend]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swallow slug]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swallow slug australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swallow slug dare]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swallow slug paralysed]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-plans-large-rainmaking-network-on-tibetan-plateau-3582567</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China plans large rainmaking network on Tibetan plateau 3582567]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TIBETAN PLATEAU — China is embarking on its largest weather-modification project yet, as it attempts to bring more rain to the Tibetan mountains.

Climate models predict that the Tibetan plateau, which holds Asia's biggest freshwater reserve, could see severe drought due to decreased rainfall and rising temperatures, according to the South China Morning Post.

In response, the state-owned China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation is building combustion chambers to turn solid fuel into silver iodide for cloud seeding, and placing them on steep mountainsides.

Winds help produce an upward draft that sweeps the particles into the clouds, where they then induce rain or snow.

The plan is to bring precipitation over an area spanning 1.6 million square kilometers, or three times the size of Spain. Five hundred chambers have so far been deployed in Tibet and Xinjiang.

The science behind the project may not be groundbreaking, but it's the first time such a large scale use of the technology will be attempted. 3582567]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARBWGD3XKVDRCWIXBSLRK9JAMMDBTEALA2PWTHIBKSNWIWRFKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6F7/35B/6F735B051559E85C5DEB744228F91A13.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cloud seeding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tibet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tibetan plateau]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water reserve]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ make it rain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rainmaker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rain making]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drought]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rainfall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial rain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weather modification]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/is-your-cell-phone-giving-you-crazy-cancer-studies-say---3582550</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Is your cell phone giving you crazy cancer? Studies say ... 3582550]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RESEARCH TRIANGLE PARK, NORTH CAROLINA — Two new studies have found a correlation between cell phone radiation and cancer in lab rats. 
Smartphones emit non-ionizing radiation, measured in radio-frequency, RF, energy. 

It's accepted high doses of ionizing radiation, such as x-rays, CT scans and nuclear power plants cause cancer, according to Scientific American.  

However, it's still unclear if long-term exposure to non-ionizing radiation can cause cancer. 
Researchers from the U.S. National Toxicology Program tested 3,000 rats and mice of both sexes for two years, while European scientists at the Ramazzini Institute in Italy studied 2,500 rats from fetal stage to death. 

The studies found that prolonged exposure to even low levels of RF radiation cause male rats to develop rare heart tumors called schwannoma, which affects a neuron called a Schwann cell.

In the Ramazzini study, researchers also found a weaker link between RF exposure and glial cell cancer in the brain of female rats. 3582550]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMCAMYABKJJFEVZWBSPA5L4YGWIBVEAMAFKWXGILAFQAPAKUAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/752/D9F/752D9FD4CE0DE15A4E79B925DD209566.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cell phone cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cell phone cancer link]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cell phone cancer study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radio frequency energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radio frequency radiation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/there-s-a-whole-lot-of-junk-about-to-enter-earth-s-atmospheric-trunk-3582422</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[There's a whole lot of junk about to enter Earth's atmospheric trunk 3582422]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EARTH'S ATMOSPHERIC TRUNK — More space debris is expected to fall re-enter Earth's atmosphere this week following the plummet of China's Tiangong-1.

According to Space.com, the rocket body of an Indian Polar Satellite Launch Vehicle is expected to fall to Earth around April 3. Part of a European Space Agency satellite called Ariane-5 is also expected to drop to Earth on the same day.

Fortune reports that Kazakh spacecrafts Flock 2E-3 and 2E-6 are expected to plummet to Earth on Wednesday and on Friday this week.  

Popular Science reports that 200 parts of space debris fell to Earth in 2014, and 400 fell in 2016.  Most land in the Pacific Ocean.

The only person known to be hit by falling debris is Lottie Williams. According to NPR, she was walking in a park in Tulsa, Oklahoma in 1997 when a 6-inch chunk of metal travelling at a low speed struck her from behind. Scientists believe it came from a NASA second-stage Delta II rocket. 3582422]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZDAGC3VKBLRKACHLZAAT9SBMACVXRAMAWKRXHRHBRERAW3RAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FB2/6E8/FB26E850972D2676BD2CF76736E6E996.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tiangong-1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space junk falling to Earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space junk 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debris falling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hit by space junk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hit by space debris]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lottie williams]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/13-000-year-old-human-footprints-discovered-in-canada-3582405</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[13,000-year-old human footprints discovered in Canada 3582405]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CALVERT ISLAND, CANADA — Humans may have been stomping around Canada as early as 13,000 years ago — and they left footprints.

According to a study published in the journal PLOS-ONE, researchers discovered an ancient human footprint along the coast of Canada's Calvert Island in 2014, before then uncovering 28 more in subsequent excavations.

The well-preserved prints are believed to have been made by two barefoot adults and one child some 13,000 years ago.

The foot impressions were left on light brown clay, which was filled in and preserved by sand, thick gravel, and another layer of clay.

The findings lend support to the theory that ancient humans travelled from Asia to North America near the end of the last ice age by following a route along the Pacific coastline.

Fossilized tracks are themselves rare, but these particular ones have also earned the distinction of being the oldest known human footprints found in North America. 3582405]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNFGC3TBRDRKBI7BNLA7743NADE5URNK5AAXGCWA2NRXVCUAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/030/743/030743A5B50E890A2E318E1DC0275B00.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ footprints]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oldest footprints]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human footprints]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ preserved footprints]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice age]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice age migration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ migration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ calvert island]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient migration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canada]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human migration]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-developing-mosquito-radar-with-military-tech-3582376</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China developing mosquito radar with military tech 3582376]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — New radar technology can track the flight path of a mosquito from a mile away, claim Chinese scientists.

The device uses technology from China's missile defence system, reports the South China Morning Post, citing an unidentified researcher. A prototype is being tested at the Beijing Institute of Technology.

The device can reportedly identify which species a mosquito belongs to as well as its gender, flight speed and direction. 3582376]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAWGDCUK5DREBKFB6PR592FGECBRRILKBLFMTCWAMARPACUAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/12D/04D/12D04D81866EF913CE2C641E21FD6213.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquito radar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china mosquito radar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquito technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquito]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquito bites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquitoes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese mosquitoes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/are-plastic-straws-finally-on-the-way-out--3582250</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Are plastic straws finally on the way out? 3582250]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EARTH — Municipalities around the world are increasingly cracking down on plastic pollution, especially single-use straws. 

According to the National Park Services, Americans use about 500 million straws a day which works out to 1.5 straws a person every 24 hours, according to the Tampa Bay Times. 

In the U.K., 8.5 billion plastic straws are used each year, according to the Telegraph. 

Straws are difficult to recycle and usually end up in landfills or being incinerated, but they are increasingly clogging up waterways as well. 

Cities worldwide are increasingly discouraging the use of straws with some even outright banning them. Others have vowed to phase out plastics over the next decades. 
Plastic straw alternatives have also started to gain in popularity. They are made from materials like bamboo, metal, glass, paper, potato or corn paste. 3582250]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLRIDRGAFIAABI7B5BAT74UGSJEZFAQKADFXFIKARHFPACUKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E23/89B/E2389B5415BBBA61BCE14FA7366420B1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-04T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastics pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic straw pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic straw ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ single-use plastic straw]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ single-use plastic]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cop-escorts-too-pregnant-mom-and-family-from-disney-cruise-3583510</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cop escorts 'too pregnant' mom and family from Disney cruise 3583510]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MIAMI — YouTuber Emily Jackson says she had traveled with her family of 10 from St Louis to Miami to join the cruise earlier this week.

The family of 10 reportedly being parents, a husband, two kids and other relatives.

After they got there, Jackson says Disney staff deemed her 25-week pregnancy to be too far along to be cruise-worthy. Naturally, Jackson was mad.

Disney policy is that nobody over 24 weeks pregnant can join the cruise. 

The vlogger recorded some of her exchange with the very Disney-like Disney staff and posted it to YouTube. But mess with the mouse, and the mouse will send you packin' along with a heat packing cop garbed in tactical gear.

Jackson said she and her kids had to wait for 2 hours under the Miami sun while their luggage was unloaded. They offered her a refund but she told St Louis news outlet KMOV that won't cover how much they spent on the rest of their ruined vacation. 3583510]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNRGD3UBWLRPAATBWIRZ6D4GVDSVEZIKADWTG3TAFQFKBKYAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AEA/77C/AEA77CB9CA86EF373FB5CB60A7015B33.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ too pregnant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disney cruise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant woman and cop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disney removes pregnant woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walt disney]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emily jackson]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the jackson hive]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dark-patches-on-venus-could-be-signs-of-microbial-life-3583278</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dark patches on Venus could be signs of microbial life 3583278]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VENUS — A new study theorizes that the dark splotches on Venus may be a sign that there's life on the planet. Microbial life, that is.

According to a paper published in the journal Astrobiology, climate models suggest Venus had a habitable climate and liquid water for 2 billion years, before a runaway greenhouse gas effect raised surface temperatures and turned the atmosphere toxic.

The research suggests that microorganisms may be living in the planet's lower cloud layer, which has a stable temperature and more Earth-like atmospheric pressure.

Dark patches on Venus could be microbial blooms made of sulfuric acid and other light-absorbing particles, which can persist for days while changing shape and contrast.

Certain bacteria on Earth can survive in high altitudes after being swept into the atmosphere; others have also been known to thrive in extremely harsh environments.

Thus far, the probes that have explored Venus have been incapable of distinguishing between organic and inorganic particles.

So until a new contraption gets there, no one knows for sure if life does exist on the hottest planet in the solar system. 3583278]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJLRMDAAAFJAIVZVKEAARKJBGRCS3RT4K6JWVGKWKEERGBZBLB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DD4/756/DD47569D26B59040180F84DDB3A7D6D3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ venus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life on venus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark patches]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ venus dark patches]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extremophiles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microorganisms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microbes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microbial bloom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microbial life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ signs of life]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-opens-fire-at-youtube-hq-wounding-3-before-taking-own-life-3583218</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman opens fire at YouTube HQ, wounding 3 before taking own life 3583218]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA — A woman opened fire at YouTube headquarters in San Bruno on Tuesday afternoon, wounding three people before taking her own life. 

According to law enforcement sources, the shooting was a domestic dispute, with the shooter targeting someone at the campus, according to the L.A. Times. 

The shooting took place at around 12:46 p.m. in an outdoor cafe on the grounds. It's still unclear if the attacker worked at YouTube. 

San Bruno Police Chief Ed Barberini told press on Tuesday that one person, believed to be the shooter, was found dead of a self-inflicted gunshot wound, according to the L.A. Times. 

Three victims were transported to San Francisco General Hospital with gunshot wounds. A 27-year-old woman is in fair condition, a 32-year-old woman is in serious condition  and a 36-year-old man is in critical condition, hospital officials said, according to SFGate. 3583218]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARARMX3XK6JFGWRTBNJFR7LTM2IETERLKVAATUZHAVHFPVICBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9B8/0E7/9B80E70C59815FBB67960210E2F050B8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube HQ shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube headquarters shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ YouTube]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-a-cosmic-discovery-9-billion-years-in-the-making-3583161</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's a cosmic discovery 9 billion years in the making 3583161]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EDGE OF THE KNOWN UNIVERSE — Astronomers have sighted the outermost star the in known universe.

Icarus, or LS1, is 9 billion years from Earth. Hubble saw it because of gravitational lensing, where distant star light is bent and magnified via the gravity of a passing galaxy. What was sighted came from a time when the universe was at 30% of its current age. 

The star is believed to be a luminous blue supergiant, similar in size to our sun, but twice as hot. Researchers knew it wasn't a supernova because it wasn't exploding.

Astronomers also tested its cluster for a dark matter theory that posits primordial black holes constituted much of the early universe, according to NASA.  That wasn't shown however, as the Hubble telescope would have observed different light patterns from the star if black holes passed in front of Icarus. 3583161]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNWEXCTBVDFAACEL6KAKKLUGWJBVERNKNIW3GZDKMFAPBTYAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CA9/7A1/CA97A1747F26ADD825C1019E5F42FF80.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ icarus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hubble telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ls1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ls-1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ farthest star ever]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark matter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark matter theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ primordial black hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ esa]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mit-develops-depth-imaging-system-that-sees-through-fog-3583087</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[MIT develops depth-imaging system that sees through fog 3583087]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — MIT researchers have developed a new imaging system that can estimate the distance of objects obscured by fog. 

One of the main challenges to the development of self-driving navigation systems that use visible light is their inability to handle misty or foggy driving conditions. 
The system uses a time-of-flight camera, which emits short laser bursts at objects and then counts how long it takes for the light to bounce back. 

Fog normally scatters laser light, which is problematic for autonomous vehicles. But thanks to an algorithm developed by the scientists, the system can find patterns in the scattered light to calculate distance.  
Researchers tested the system in fog much denser than cars would encounter in the real world. 

The team from MIT Media Lab's Camera Culture Group found that the system performed even better than human vision.  

The goal is to integrate the system into autonomous vehicles so that even in bad weather, self-driving cars can avoid obstacles. 3583087]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIACDAIA2KRIAZUBVDAV7DWGWLS5U3RKRDR3URKAVFAVBRBKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/676/B7D/676B7D2A28F1EA9C7671BC1624DCC9CC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  MIT self driving car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MIT self driving imaging system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MIT autonomous imaging system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MIT imaging system fog]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-first-homemade-aircraft-carrier-to-go-on-maiden-sea-trial-3584131</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China's first homemade aircraft carrier to go on maiden sea trial 3584131]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DALIAN, CHINA — Beijing is prepping to get its first domestically-produced aircraft carrier started on sea trials after its unveiling a year ago.

The South China Morning Post reports that China's conventionally powered Type 001A aircraft carrier was made using a special Chinese steel, and can carry up to 48 aircraft — eight more than the Liaoning.

The ship is set to embark on its maiden sea trial in the northeastern Bohai Sea, just before the PLA Navy's 60th anniversary celebrations on April 23.

Basic functions to be tested include power, damage control, radar, and communications systems. The ship may just circle the bay for the trial, but a longer two- to three-day voyage is possible if no issues arise.

Unlike the Liaoning aircraft carrier, which is designed to operate independently, the Type 001A is meant to sail with several other vessels as part of a battle group.

Getting the ship combat ready will likely take some time, but if all goes as planned, the as yet unnamed carrier might be joining the navy as early as 2019. 3584131]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIWADRJBMAR5AZWLNLWR72FMSJEZRALAJJA3GZBKZHWPCAAKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D95/A5D/D95A5DA6BBC269FD2A8B8D407EAC7C5D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aircraft carrier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Type 001A]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese aircraft carrier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea trials]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maiden voyage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PLA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Liaoning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shenyang J-15]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fighter jets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ helicopters]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/aussie-teen-who-swallowed-slug-on-a-dare-now-disabled-for-life-3584121</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Aussie teen who swallowed slug on a dare now disabled for life 3584121]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SYDNEY — A rugby-playing Aussie teen is now confined to a wheelchair for the rest of his life after eating something he really shouldn't have.

The Queensland Times reports that back in 2010, Sam Ballard had picked up a garden slug during a drinking session, and turned to his buddies to ask, 'Should I eat it?'

When one mate dared him to, the then 19-year-old popped the poor slug into his mouth and swallowed — not knowing it had parasites that would later burst inside his body.

Within days, he developed severe leg pain and had to be taken to a doctor, who figured out he had a bad case of rat lungworms and a brain infection.

The parasite is typically found in rodents, but can get into slugs or snails via infected rat doo doo.

Ballard contracted eosinophilic meningoencephalitis, a type of meningitis. But instead of recovering like most people, he went into a coma for 420 days and came out of it paralyzed from the neck down.

At 28, he requires round-the-clock care, since he can't regulate his body temperature, is prone to seizures, and has to be tube fed.

It's pretty tragic, and shows just how much damage a split-second of silliness can actually cause. So next time you decide to eat a slug, please don't. 3584121]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNFXDKUAAFA3VRTBJIA37DVMBKETSTZAJPFPG3TAIGAGCAKBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7E3/0AF/7E30AFA4AE9BAE9D6922FB138012524D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ slug]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ teen eats slug]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ parasites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ quadriplegic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paralysis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disabled teen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rat lungworm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dare]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain infection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ slug parasites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rat parasites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eosinophilic meningoencephalitis]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hotel-forgives-man-whose-room-was-trashed-by-seagulls-3583947</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hotel forgives man whose room was trashed by seagulls 3583947]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VICTORIA, CANADA — A Canadian man who had his luxury hotel room trashed by seagulls over some pepperoni in 2001 has been pardoned.
Nick Burchill was banned from the Fairmont Empress in Victoria, British Columbia in 2001 after the feathery fiasco.  

Burchill said in a Facebook post that he was bringing some pepperoni to some Naval friends on the west coast back in April of '01, according to BBC.

He wanted to keep the meat cool, but his room had no fridge, so he plopped the some pepperoni out on his table and window sill to chill.

Then he went for a four- or five-hour walk. When he came back, he found an entire flock of hungry seagulls — around 40 he claims — going to town on his meats and his room. 

According to Burchill, the room was all feathers, seagull doo doo and chunks of pepperoni everywhere. 

In an attempt to clear the room out, he tossed a shoe at a seagull, which ended up going out the window. Only problem was that he needed the shoe for a meeting. 

Burchill eventually made it to his meeting, but then later got a letter from the hotel saying he was banned for life.
In March, after Burchill penned an apologetic letter asking for forgiveness, the hotel lifted to ban. 3583947]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIFGYIIBIBF3BRTLJKRIKJGMRES3SANAJKR5GALKZGFMXCXAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/000/38E/00038EFCFF26A1AD46B405FA9D33321B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seagulls destroy hotel room]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seagulls hotel pepperoni]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man pardoned by hotel seagulls]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/homeland-security-detects-activity-from-phone-hackers-in-dc-3583829</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Homeland Security detects activity from phone hackers in DC 3583829]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The U.S. government has detected 'anomalous' activity from telephone spying equipment in Washington.

According to the Associated Press, the Department of Homeland Security detected abnormal activity from international mobile subscriber identity-catchers (IMSI catchers). The DHS did not identify the source of or number of devices.

These devices act as a fake cellular tower and attract signals from the target's phone away from the real network. The technology is also used by U.S. intelligence and law enforcement.

They can be used to listen in on phone calls, track user location data and read messages. 
According to the Associated Press, some can infect devices with malware. 3583829]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEARMDCULNLRZWISBRAW59LSM2KS3FZNKMCFMTAGAWPRKXIFBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/83D/4DD/83D4DD3A8C47B10ACA34B44ABF856316.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ imsi catchers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phone hacking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phone hacking usa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dhs finds imsi catcher]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ foreign imsi catchers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police imsi catcher]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cia fbi imsi]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-confusing-rules-of-football-explained-3583800</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The confusing rules of football explained 3583800]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FOOTBALL — While the World Cup is approaching fast, some people still have a hard time figuring out some of the rules of this popular sport favored by much of the world.

A ball is out of play when the entire ball has crossed the touch-line, regardless of whether it is on the ground or in the air. The ball is in play when it rebounds off a match official, goal post, crossbar or corner flag post and remains in the field of play.

If a foul is committed outside the penalty area, but continues inside the penalty area, the referee shall award a penalty kick.

A player is offside when any part of the player's head, body, or feet is in the opponent's side of the field. 

A player is also offside if he or she is nearer to the opponent's goal line than the ball, and nearer to the opponent's goal line than the second to last opponent, or, if the referee determines that you have participated in area of active play.

As confusing as such rules are to many, FIFA has a handy list of these regulations available on their website for anyone who is interested in understanding how they keep this beautiful game fair. 3583800]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KFEDIFBZBR3DZSBVDWX6LTGZCV7RCRKFLRTTIBKAARKCZJAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/35D/0DC/35D0DCB251691359C900F4DD6D51F46A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is offsides in soccer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soccer rules ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soccer rules for beginners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soccer rules explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soccer rules offsides]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world cup rules]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-nightmare-bacteria-spreading-across-u-s-hospitals-3583758</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Nightmare bacteria' spreading across U.S. hospitals 3583758]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — Nightmare bacteria that are resistant to almost all antibiotics are spreading across U.S. hospitals, federal health officials said on Tuesday. 

The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention set up a countrywide lab network in 2016 to help hospitals diagnose infections quickly in order to stop them from spreading, according to Scientific American. 

The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention found 221 cases in 2017 of a rare breed of antibiotic-resistant bacteria. 

One in four germ samples analyzed by the CDC lab network found special genes that allow them to spread resistance to other bacteria. 

The CDC also said in 11 percent of people tested carried these superbugs without displaying any symptoms.

People infected with these bacteria spread the disease to other people in the hospital, such as patients, doctors and nurses. These people can then in turn act as silent carriers and infect others even if they don't become sick.   

According to the CDC, every year about two million Americans are sickened from antibiotic-resistant infections, while more than 23,000 patients are killed. 3583758]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2JRCAIEBFIACDRSLSJWRKL3MWLVRFK4AFLRVGREBREAAVZGLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A53/DFE/A53DFEBCBB2529E323732BE443D0219A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nightmare bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antibiotic-resistant bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ superbugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hospital superbugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hospital antibiotic-resistant bacteria]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/old-fogies-can-still-make-new-brain-cells-study-says-3584882</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Old fogies can still make new brain cells, study says 3584882]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — A new study claims the brain continues to produce hundreds of new neurons daily, even in older people, in a process called neurogenesis. 

Scientists from the University of Columbia published their results in the journal Cell Stem Cell on Thursday. 

Lead researcher Dr. Maura Boldrini and her team examined the brains of 28 dead people age 14 to 79 to see if aging affects neuron production, according to the L.A. Times. 

The team looked for the presence of neurons in different stages of development, including stem cells, intermediate progenitor cells, immature neurons and new neurons. 

The study only looked at the hippocampus, partly because previous studies have shown that part of the brain is one of the few areas that can make new neurons into adulthood, according to the L.A. Times. 

Boldrini and her team found similar numbers of neural progenitor cells and immature neurons, regardless of age. 

The team concluded that the human brain can produce neurons even as people grow old. 3584882]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIWCCCSAABRMVA9LFIA7944MBKB5SAQLWPWTGTXAWPRKYK3KE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BCC/643/BCC643B150823CB087DCA735E35E3AD1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neuron]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neuron production]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ adult neuron production]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neuron production older people]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/corals-spew-deadly-toxin-during-home-fish-tank-cleaning-3584718</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Corals spew deadly toxin during home fish tank cleaning 3584718]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OXFORDSHIRE, UNITED KINGDOM — An family nearly died after the world's second deadliest poison leaked into their home during a fish tank cleaning.

The Washington Post reports that many home aquariums not only hold exotic fish, but also zoanthid corals, which release a highly toxic substance called palytoxin when provoked.

Palytoxin is lethal when ingested or injected into the bloodstream, but can also be dangerous when airborne.

According to a report from the Marine Aquarium Societies of North America, scrubbing zoanthids can trigger them to spew the toxin, which spreads as an aerosol and endangers those who inhale it. Vapors released when the coral is boiled in water or broken may also cause damage.

Breathing in the toxin typically causes flu-like symptoms that may include a high fever, muscle pain, coughing, difficulty breathing, and eye irritation.

Experts recommend handling the deadly corals in a well-ventilated space while wearing gloves, eye protection, and face masks.

Pets and small children should also be kept away from any water or substance that has come in contact with zoanthids. 3584718]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJFCYKXAMBWGVCHBWIR57SAM2JE5SK9KFKF5HRLARHACVRGLG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/72F/B7F/72FB7F8CB89077EEA2F69CF0B005077D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic coral]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ palytoxin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deadly toxin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deadly coral]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poisonous coral]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic substance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zoanthid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ palythoa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish tank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ home aquarium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aquarium]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dozens-of-dino-footprints-found-on-isle-of-skye-in-scotland-3584619</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dozens of dino footprints found on Isle of Skye in Scotland 3584619]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ISLE OF SKYE, SCOTLAND — Fantastically large beasts stomped around the Scottish coast millions of years ago, and very literally made their mark on Earth.

According to a study published in the Scottish Journal of Geology, researchers uncovered around 50 dinosaur tracks in a tidal area on Scotland's Isle of Skye.

The prints were made by carnivorous two-legged theropods — primitive cousins of the T-rex that were five to six meters long and weighed about a ton.

A set of tracks unearthed earlier in 2015 had belonged to sauropods, which were long-necked plant-eating dinosaurs related to the Brontosaurus.

Both sets of footprints date back 170 million years to the Middle Jurassic period. They were likely made in muddy, shallow water and washed over by sediments, which solidified and preserved them.

The Mid-Jurassic was a critical time for dino evolution, but fossil evidence from this time period is rare, making the footprint discovery a veritable treasure trove of information for scientists studying the era. 3584619]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNFIYAHBMDFECKELNKR37DUMMEBTUZMKMAFPGREKBNRKDZGBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/600/2BD/6002BD66F81B24E118D65E62510ACD91.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dinosaur footprints]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dino footprints]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dino footprint]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dino tracks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dinosaurs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dinos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fossils]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fossilized prints]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ middle jurassic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jurassic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ theropods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sauropods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ T-rex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brontosaurus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ isle of skye]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-zombie-raccoons-terrify-ohio-town-with-odd-daytime-behavior-3584503</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Zombie' raccoons terrify Ohio town with odd daytime behavior 3584503]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[YOUNGSTOWN, OHIO — Residents of an Ohio town are seriously spooked after raccoons in the neighborhood began exhibiting some very strange behavior.

WKBN-TV reports that one man was with his dogs in broad daylight when he spotted a raccoon approaching. It stood on its hind legs and bared its teeth before collapsing into a comatose-state.

It got back up moments later, but the man didn't stick around to figure out if it was rabid, undead, or something else entirely. 

Police reported receiving 14 other complaints in Youngstown over the course of three weeks. All animals were captured and have been put down. Ohio's Department of Natural Resources says they were likely suffering from distemper, not rabies.

Distemper is a viral disease that causes coughing and seizures in raccoons, and causes them to lose their fear of humans.

Pets and other animals may be infected, so it's best to steer clear of any weird critters. Though it's at least not transmissible to humans.

Let's just hope it stays that way. No one needs the Walking Dead at their doorstep — the world is stressful enough already. 3584503]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJLFVAAAA5EA5CAWKAAWX6JHNAES3SK9AWKA5H3SASNFAAKUAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E88/63D/E8863D3B4159E3A6D3B04BB6DA80501F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zombie raccoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raccoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raccoon attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rabid raccoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rabies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ distemper]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-a-luxury-space-hotel-for-the-incredibly-rich-and-douchey-3585069</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's a 'luxury space hotel' for the incredibly rich and douchey 3585069]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN JOSE, CALIFORNIA — Startup Orion Span announced on Thursday it plans to build a space hotel to launch in late 2021 and start accepting guests by 2022. 

We are launching the first-ever affordable luxury space hotel, said Orion Span founder and CEO Frank Bunger, at the Space 2.0 Summit in San Jose, California, according to Space.com. 

A 12-day stay at Aurora Station will begin at $9.5 million. The space station will be roughly the same size as a large private jet cabin. 

It will be 43.5 feet long by 14.1 feet wide and have a pressurized volume of 5,650 cubic feet, according to an Orion Span representative. It will orbit at an altitude of 200 miles.   
For comparison, the International Space Station is 357 feet long and has an internal pressurized volume of 32,333 cubic feet. 

The Aurora Station will be able to accommodate four paying guests and two crewmembers. 

Orion Span is also planning for new modules to be added to the space hotel over time. Long-term, the company says it hopes to sell actual space in new modules for living or subleasing. 3585069]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6NFIY3WB5AF5BAXBVARZL4YNFKB7UT9AFJFMTICK5EWCBIGLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/600/759/6007590A4F93FF8DE499656016DE8CF0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  luxury space hotel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Aurora Station space hotel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space tourists]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Orion Span]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space hotels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ private space travel]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/rna-plant-vaccine-could-replace-toxic-pesticides-3586695</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[RNA plant vaccine could replace toxic pesticides 3586695]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HELSINKI — Conventional pesticides are a double-edged sword that scientists are now seeking to replace with more natural RNA-based plant vaccines.

The U.S. Department of Agriculture estimates that without pesticides, roughly 70 percent of the world's crops would be lost to pests. But such chemicals are toxic — killing insects but also affecting the rest of the environment.

New research in the Plant Biology Journal details an approach that involves directly spraying plant leaves with an RNA-based vaccine. Developed in France and Finland, this inoculates against specific pests or pathogens.

The vaccine triggers a process called RNA interference, which prevents invading RNA strands from carrying out their functions, thus causing the pest to die.

RNA molecules in the vaccine do not negatively affect the host plant. The RNA also has the added benefit of being biodegradable because it breaks down quickly.

Instead of chemical synthesis, scientists used a bacteria-eating virus called a bacteriophage to help generate the RNA. 3586695]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IWEAKWARBACWIRBBPWXK4WGMAS3FK5KICFRTZAAEEFPV36AG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/17F/783/17F7833D605343FA80D63BDDDA6C19B0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pesticides]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RNA vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RNA pesticide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bio pesticide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pests]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ farm crops]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ farming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemical pesticides]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic chemicals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic pesticides]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mozilla-releases-tool-to-help-stop-facebook-from-tracking-you-3586656</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mozilla releases tool to help stop Facebook from tracking you 3586656]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA — Mozilla has released a Firefox tool called Facebook Container to stop the social networking site from tracking online habits outside Facebook’s own site.  

The extension isolates a user’s Facebook identity into a separate browser tab making it harder for the site to track the user’s activity on other websites using third-party cookies, according to a Mozilla blog post.  

After installing the extension it will delete the user’s Facebook cookies and log the user out of Facebook. 

The next time the user logs in, Facebook will open in a new blue-colored browser tab, or container tab. 

When using Facebook through the Mozilla extension, if the user clicks on a non-Facebook link or goes to a non-Facebook website in the URL bar, these pages load outside of the container. 

Clicking Facebook Share buttons on other browser tabs will load them within the Facebook Container. 

Mozilla warns that if people used their Facebook accounts to create an account or as logins to other apps, they may not be able to log in when using the extension. 3586656]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AECFIC3UKECAXWIRBBIWXLDSMFJS7F33AWPAZHIEAEGRPDREAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5B0/B1F/5B0B1F0A10E846DC9FB60B1EC56ADDA6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Mozilla Facebook Container]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Facebook Container extension]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Facebook tracking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[third-party cookies]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ex-nasa-astronauts-pass-ufo-lie-detector-test-3586612</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ex-NASA astronauts pass UFO lie detector test 3586612]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALBANY, OHIO — Four NASA legends have passed lie detection tests examining historical accounts of their encounters with UFOs.

According to British tabloid the Daily Star, the Institute of BioAcoustic Biology examined voice recordings of the space men and their UFO encounters.   

The lie detection technology, reported the Daily Star, confirms only that those telling the stories believe what they say is true and not the accounts themselves.

O.G. moonwalker Buzz Aldrin claims to have seen something during the Apollo 11 moon mission. He described it as L-shaped and unidentified, but later explained in a Reddit AMA that he was convinced it was likely a panel from the rocket.

According to the Daily Star, Apollo 15 pilot Al Worden's belief he's seen an alien is no lie.
Last year, he told Good Morning Britain that he believes in aliens, saying he sees one every morning in the mirror. Worden believes humans are aliens from another world.

The Daily Star reports accounts from other NASA icons Edgar Mitchell and Gordon Cooper — both believers in UFOs — also passed the lie detector tests. 3586612]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDRPDCUKJLRZA3FBNLWX6JFGFKE5FK9KZCA5TIEARGAKVAHAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/438/2A3/4382A3514D90460FA3E22AED1F101752.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa ufo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moon mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apollo 11]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lie detector]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ buzz aldrin ufo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ al worden ufo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ edgar mitchell ufo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gordon cooper ufo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Institute of BioAcoustic Biology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien lie detector]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ buzz aldrin aliens]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ astronaut aliens on the moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ buzz aldrin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ edgar mitchell]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gordon cooper]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ al worden]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dozens-killed-in-suspected-syrian-gas-attack-3586526</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dozens killed in suspected Syrian gas attack 3586526]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DOUMA, SYRIA — Dozens of people were killed in suspected chemical gas attacks on the town of Douma near Damascus on Saturday.
According to the U.S.-based Syrian American Medical Society, at least 48 people have died, while the Union of Medical Care and Relief Organizations said that 70 deaths have been confirmed, the BBC reports.

The pro-opposition Ghouta Media Center said a helicopter dropped a barrel bomb containing Sarin gas. 

Rescue workers said hundreds of people were showing signs and symptoms consistent with exposure to an organophosphorus compound. 

One paramedic was quoted by the Guardian saying, the attack was near bomb shelters and so it spread quickly in them. The gas was concentrated and in a place where people thought they were safe.

The paramedic said many victims had expanded irises and loss of motor control, with a high number suffocating from the gas. 
Rescue workers said many victims' bodies remain uncollected because of further shelling, lingering toxic gas odor and lack of protective gear. 
Syrian state media has the denied chemical attacks, saying rebels in Douma were about to collapse and spreading false news. 3586526]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIFMYZIAVDF7A3DLSPAR9DXNBJERFCSA6KFMFACAFQAMW3YKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E64/297/E642973B68B94632829A2C60A0FFE5D7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria civil war]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria chemical attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria chemical gas attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Douma chemical gas attack]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-harvest-first-vegetables-grown-in-antarctic-greenhouse-3586374</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists harvest first vegetables grown in Antarctic greenhouse 3586374]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA — At a greenhouse in the least hospitable continent on Earth, scientists have successfully farmed their first batch of fresh greens.

Deutsche Welle reports that German researchers at Neumayer Station III have developed a method to grow fruits and vegetables without sunlight or soil.

A high-tech greenhouse in Antarctica was used to grow produce despite subzero temperatures outside. Optimized lighting, a closed water system, and controlled levels of carbon dioxide were used.

The first harvest yielded 3.6 kilograms of fresh greens, 18 cucumbers, and 70 radishes.

Scientists are working on several different types of plants, and hope to harvest 4 to 5 kilos of fruits and veggies a week by May of 2018.

The Antarctic project, named EDEN-ISS and run by the German Aerospace Center, aims to produce a wider range of produce that could feed future human missions to the moon or Mars. 3586374]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKAPDKTAFLR3VRTBWPR7KLXGSKBVRC4KNPA5HAKAAARAWTXKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B60/35F/B6035F14AEE9482390AA5A13F8DF4732.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ greenhouse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vegetables]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ harvest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Antarctica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space greenhouse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ greenhouse vegetables]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Antarctic vegetables]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ veggies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ produce]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/great-pacific-garbage-patch-is-three-times-the-size-of-france-3586363</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Great Pacific Garbage Patch is three times the size of France 3586363]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PACIFIC OCEAN — A new study suggests the Great Pacific Garbage Patch could be 16 times larger than previous estimates.  
The results of a three-year study beginning in 2015, commissioned by the Ocean Cleanup Foundation, were published in the journal Scientific Reports on Thursday. 

With 30 vessels and a C-130 Hercules aircraft, researchers catalogued a sample of over a million pieces of plastic, mostly comprised of microplastics less than 0.5 centimeters in diameter, according to CBC News. 

The study estimates the patch could contain more than 1.8 trillion pieces of microplastics. 

Scientists say there are more than 79,000 tonnes of plastic in a 1.6 million square kilometer area of the North Pacific Ocean. 
Researchers found plastic bottles, containers, packaging straps, lids, ropes and fishing nets among the other refuse that had been collecting for decades. 

As the plastics breakdown into smaller pieces, they threaten marine life that can eat them and die from them. 3586363]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KACC3VAFIRXARSBBLA77LXGWJV5SKRKWPR5TKWA5HRCBIHAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/934/936/93493651C7CE45D1B3AAB94F33AD977C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-10T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Great Pacific Garbage Patch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean plastics pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean microplastics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastics pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pacific plastics pollution]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/israel-accused-of-carrying-out-missile-strike-on-syrian-airbase-3587457</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Israel accused of carrying out missile strike on Syrian airbase 3587457]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOMS, SYRIA — Syria and Russia are accusing Israel of targeting a military base where Iranians were stationed.

Russia's Defense Ministry claims the T4 airbase in Syria's Homs province was attacked early Monday by two Israeli F-15 warplanes, according to NBC.

The aircraft reportedly approached from the Mediterranean Sea and fired eight missiles from Lebanese airspace.

Syrian air defense systems shot down five of the missiles. The remaining three hit the western part of the base, killing 14 people. According to the head of British-based monitoring group Syrian Observatory for Human Rights, most of those who died were Iranian or members of Iran-backed groups.

The missile raid came just hours after a deadly poison gas attack killed at least 40 people in a rebel-held stronghold near Damascus.

Syrian media initially suspected the U.S. to be behind the airstrike, following threats by U.S. President Donald Trump to make the Syrian government pay for the poisoning, but the Pentagon has since denied any involvement. 3587457]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KICFVCRAKZGRKDCCBBKRR9JGMRBEREZIKSKFPU3SAZHAMDAMBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F45/81A/F4581A757B174A13AFB22B271DA48E6C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ IDF]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Israel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Iran]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria airstrike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ air strike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Israel air strike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Israeli air strike on Syria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syrian air base]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ t4 air base]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Iran Israel conflict]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Israeli F15]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ F15 war planes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Syria air defense systems]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-put-jamming-equipment-on-its-fake-man-made-islands--3587388</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China put jamming equipment on its fake, man-made 'islands' 3587388]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOUTH CHINA SEA — China has installed military jamming equipment on two of its Spratly Islands outposts that can disrupt communications and radar systems, U.S. officials say. 

Satellite imagery taken by commercial satellite company DigitalGlobe shows a suspected jammer system with its antenna extended on Mischief Reef, one of China's seven artificial islands, the Wall Street Journal reported. 

Three of its man-made outposts — Fiery Cross, Mischief Reef and Subi Reef —  now have 10,000-foot runways, airplane hangars, ammunition depots, barracks and deep-water piers for ships.

The new jamming equipment was installed within the last 90 days on Fiery Cross and Mischief Reef, according to U.S. intelligence, the Wall Street Journal reported.  
China claims sovereignty over all of the South China Sea, however their territorial claims overlap with those of Taiwan, Brunei, Malaysia, Vietnam and the Philippines. 3587388]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KADFCXZCKRDFIDRRL2IR3L2CMIABTSINKJPAXTKWAJNFGCT5AB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4AE/963/4AE963F5AD574BB2B072C91594DB7940.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ South China Sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spratly Islands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China jamming equipment Spratly Islands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China artificial islands]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China man-made islands]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-life-saving-drug-naloxone-helps-reverse-opioid-overdoses-3587354</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How life-saving drug Naloxone helps reverse opioid overdoses 3587354]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The U.S. is in the midst of a massive opioid epidemic, with tens of thousands of overdose deaths per year, and millions more addicted to illicit drugs.

The New York Times reports that on Thursday, U.S. Surgeon General Jerome Adams issued a rare advisory urging more people to carry the overdose-reversing drug Naloxone. The last advisory had been sent out 13 years ago, when women were told not to consume alcohol while pregnant.

During an overdose, synthetic drugs like heroin or fentanyl flood the brain and lock onto the opiate receptors, causing breathing to become dangerously slow.

According to the advisory from the Surgeon General's Office, Naloxone can reverse the effects of an overdose and comes in two forms — a nasal spray, and a syringe that should be injected into the muscles of the thigh, buttocks or arms.

The emergency medication works by knocking the opioids out of the receptors in the brain — blocking and temporarily reversing their effects for 30 to 90 minutes.

Police officers and medical responders are among those who have been using Naloxone to counter overdose deaths.

The life-saving drug is also available at local pharmacies and local health departments. 3587354]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBJWVDRCAEGRCAAWBMAAT72AGRBVRFC7KIARXTALKZEWEVRFKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/437/129/4371296A1B2E4AF79CD99F146A7CC991.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ naloxone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ narcan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drug overdose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ opioid overdose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how naloxone works]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how narcan works]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ your brain on drugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to reverse an overdose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life saving drug]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-cheats-death-after-crane-collapses-at-construction-site-3587332</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man cheats death after crane collapses at construction site 3587332]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST. PETERSBURG, FLORIDA — A construction worker is lucky to be alive after a giant crane collapsed and narrowly missed landing on him at the construction site of the future police headquarters in St. Petersburg, Florida.

The dramatic event occurred last Thursday morning around 8:30 a.m. when the crane's load came crashing down, followed by the crane's arm, reports the Tampa Bay Times.

CCTV video shows workers scrambling from the falling crane, which landed just a few feet from one worker.

Fortunately no one was injured in the incident, according to the St. Petersburg Police Department's Facebook page.

The Tampa Bay Times reports that the Occupational Safety and Health Administration has opened an investigation into the incident. 3587332]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDWIXTUKVBWKY3DKBKA79JCGEBETRT5KFLFXTKXASPWIAAKKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B74/8E9/B748E953B74F437CA95C340116E2EB6F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crane collapsing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crane collapsing video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man survives crane fall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crane collapse florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crane collapse construction]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/this-broadband-blimp-can-send-as-much-data-as-30-cell-towers-3587238</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[This broadband blimp can send as much data as 30 cell towers 3587238]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOMERVILLE, MASSACHUSETTS — New technology could bring mobile broadband to millions of Americans living rural areas lacking internet connectivity.

Massachusetts firm Altaeros told IEEE Spectrum magazine their floating mobile broadband supertower platform is about 70 percent cheaper than normal broadband deployment.

Floating at 250 meters, an autonomous aerostat carrying antennas and receivers is connected to a ground station by three tethers. One of these sends power and data to it.
The supertower is able to observe weather conditions and reorient itself accordingly. Altaeros says one can provide as much coverage as 30 broadband cell towers.

Future applications of the technology could see it being deployed to disaster areas while being towed behind a truck. 

The supertowers could also help reduce carbon emissions, as developing countries often use diesel generators to power cell phone towers. According to Altaeros, a supertower powered by a generator can provide coverage to an area that would require 20 to 30 generators if covered by cell phone towers. 3587238]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LICFVCRIKZGRKCZ9B6PAV94RMZCEZSZKKRAA5T3XBRHFKCZKBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F4A/F2C/F4AF2C95677AFE8C33DE89E620A3C4E4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flying blimp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aerostat blimp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aerostat internet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ altaeros supertower]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  cell tower]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ altaeros blimp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ altaeros energies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cell tower replacement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mobile broadband]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-to-see-the-jupiter-triangle-in-night-sky-3587169</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How to see the 'Jupiter Triangle' in night sky 3587169]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — In April, Jupiter will form a special triangle with two bright stars in the night sky, and it will be visible with the naked eye if you know where to look.

Writing in Space.com, Hayden Planetarium astronomy lecturer Joe Rao calls it the Jupiter Triangle. 

Jupiter forms a triangle with two bright stars that can be seen this month in the night sky starting around 11 p.m.

Face east-southeast and you will see a roughly isosceles triangle comprised of the star Arcturus and the binary system Spica, with Jupiter forming the brightest of the three points.

The Arcturus-Jupiter and Arcturus-Spica sides of the triangle measure about 38 degrees in length, while the Jupiter-Spica side is about 30 degrees long.

The triangle will narrow in shape throughout the month, as Jupiter moves in the night sky towards Spica.

The triangle will be visible until September, when Spica disappears into the sunset. Jupiter will do the same in early November. The gas giant will not reappear in this part of the sky until 2030.

If light pollution prevents you from seeing the Jupiter Triangle, there is a long, narrow triangle currently visible high in the western sky during the evening, in the constellation of Gemini, the Twins. 3587169]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIWVCCTAMGRPCISLVCR3KDUNEAS7ET9AWLWVUZCKBPFMVZQAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ACA/C7E/ACAC7EF5C10BEFE80D824182EB6028C2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>80</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jupiter triangle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to see the jupiter triangle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jupiter triangle astronomy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ astronomy triangle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jupiter triangle april]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stargazing jupiter triangle]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dutch-company-wants-to-use-drones-as-wind-turbines-3588147</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dutch company wants to use drones as wind turbines 3588147]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE HAGUE, NETHERLANDS — A Netherlands-based company has conceptualized a wind farm where high-altitude drones gather the energy. 

Traditional wind turbines gather most wind energy at the tip of their blades. Dutch firm Ampyx Power instead use a drone tethered to an offshore platform to gather wind energy at higher altitudes.

According to reNEWS, the concept-Airborne Wind Energy (AWE) system is deployed on floating platforms. From there, the drone would fly to an altitude of 500 meters, where it creates electricity from high-altitude winds.

Ampyx Power says the Energy Center for Research of the Netherlands calculated a virtual AWE wind farm operating near the east coast of Scotland to cost 137 Euros per megawatt hour. The company says this is cost competitive against other floating applications. 3588147]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6NAMD3WB6JAPATALWKRZ7BHG2IEZS32AEBW7GTSKSPRRWKYBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A81/8F0/A818F01B489846B68E05CE2E4D15F70E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind turbine drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ renewable energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amyx power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ awe system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airborne wind energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airborne wind energy system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ AWE system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind energy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/little-girl-s-easter-bunny-reaction-goes-viral-family-not-so-pleased-3587955</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Little girl's Easter bunny reaction goes viral, family not so pleased 3587955]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KISSIMMEE, FLORIDA — A Florida family isn't quite laughing after a Snapchat video of their little girl freaking out at some guy in an Easter Bunny outfit went viral. 

It's safe to say the 2-year-old was a little shocked when the Easter Bunny came into class to say hi the other day.  

The family told ABC News that they didn't find out until after the video went viral, unfortunately they don't find it quite as amusing. 

The family also said people's comments have been rather unpleasant. Well, welcome to the internet. 

But hey, at least now she's an Easter legend. 3587955]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSNAIAAGB6IARBITKBPAV7UYM5ESXERNKJPWVGZCKFMWMDZGKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8E1/593/8E15938CF4B848F29F80994F1E0E3C34.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ easter bunny scares kids]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ easter bunny]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ easter bunny caught on tape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ easter bunny scares class]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ easter bunny scares little girl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ little girl scared of easter bunny]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ easter bunny viral]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bots-behind-majority-of-links-shared-on-twitter-3587881</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bots behind majority of links shared on Twitter 3587881]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — News of Russian-linked Twitter bots retweeting Trump during the 2016 election called into question just how much of social media is being manipulated by non-human actors.

But while a new study confirms the pervasiveness of automated accounts on the Twitterverse, it also finds there's less political bias there than most of us think.

According to CNET, bots are applications that execute automated tasks. This can refer to applications like Alexa or Siri, or programs with more malicious intentions, like viruses.

On Twitter, bots are software-controlled accounts capable of tweeting or retweeting without direct human input.

A recent Pew Research Center study that analyzed 1.2 million tweeted links found that only one third were sent by humans. The rest were posted by suspected bots.

The study found that 66% of tweeted links to sites covering news were shared by bots, compared to 90% for adult sites, 76% for sports, and 73% for commercial products.

Interestingly, the bots' link-sharing behavior wasn't slanted toward a specific political stance. The number of links to sites shared by liberals was roughly the same as to those shared by conservatives.

It's worth noting that the researchers didn't assess the accuracy of material being shared, or distinguish between good and bad bots — which means it's still unclear how useful or problematic Twitter bots actually are. 3587881]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSNFEYAGB5DFIBASLFIAX9UWGMBB5FC9LRDWPGAKA6QFKAK2AB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/494/F09/494F09337DB64D1BB08DA35337E49792.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>93</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitterbots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter bots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tweets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ link sharing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ automated accounts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pew research center]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-developing-robot-bee-swarm-to-explore-mars-3587847</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA developing robot bee swarm to explore Mars 3587847]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — NASA researchers are working on robot bees to explore Mars.

According to a new NASA proposal for Martian exploration, robot Marsbees would use a rover as a mobile base for operations and charging. They can stay airborne for 4 to 6 hours. The space agency says the Marsbee is the size of a bumble bee, with a wingspan similar to a cicada.

According to the plan, the low Martian gravity reduces the power requirements for generating lift. It's because of this researchers have incorporated a flapping wing design, with a torsional spring to absorb wasted energy.

The Marsbees will also be equipped with sensors and wireless devices. They'll use these to further map and sample the red planet, as well as search for methane gas — a key indicator of life.

The Marsbee proposal is being worked on by a team scientists from the U.S. and Japan. 3587847]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSIRMCZGASJAGVTCBBKRT7LRNEEEZFC5AWIW5G3TAZGREXKWAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/606/C77/606C777FB7694B71A7B3D0717C45C648.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot bees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars exploration rover]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marsbee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marsbee swarm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marsbee robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cicada]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bumble bee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ red planet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/esa-space-junk-removal-satellite-reaches-the-iss-3587793</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[ESA space junk removal satellite reaches the ISS 3587793]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PARIS — A spacecraft designed to collect space garbage has arrived at the International Space Station. 

The RemoveDebris satellite was launched into space on April 2 aboard a SpaceX's Falcon 9 rocket, according to Tech Times.  It was developed by several companies in conjunction with the European Space Agency.
The satellite weighs 100 kilograms and comes equipped with a 30 centimeter long 'harpoon' that can be shot towards space debris in order push it away from functioning satellites. 

It also has a net that can be launched towards objects. After wrapping around the debris, the net can be cut loose to burn while reentering the Earth's atmosphere. 

After being deployed from the ISS, the satellite will conduct preliminary tests attempting to capture cubesats acting as space junk.  
Tests will also be carried out on the spacecraft's ability to use its laser navigation technology to track space fragments that are spinning out of control. 

Researchers are expected to start testing the spacecraft within the next few weeks. 3587793]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DRMDTWKJJAMAAULFJRRLSCMWLSRSC5LRDWVHAFA6PAIAZNAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/288/E4A/288E4A17F4914C3B84B8FEDC555EA2F7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debris]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debris collector]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ESA RemoveDebris mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RemoveDebris satellite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space junk]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/airbus-to-offer-luxury-pods-in-a330-cargo-holds-by-2020-3588989</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Airbus to offer luxury pods in A330 cargo holds by 2020 3588989]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOULOUSE, FRANCE — Airbus announced it plans to offer luxury sleeping cabins in the cargo holds of their A330 wide-body planes by 2020. 


The European aircraft company is partnering with Zodiac Aerospace to develop modular compartments that are easily interchangeable with cargo containers, according to the Guardian. 

The spaces will be separate from the economy and business class seating areas in aircrafts. 

Passengers will be able to book sleeping compartments, meeting rooms, lounges and children’s play areas, according to Wired. 

Each of the areas fits inside a container that can be inserted into the cargo hold like traditional cargo. 

According to the Guardian, a Zodiac Aerospace spokesperson said that pods could be removed and changed in about a day. Depending on the model of the A330, three or four cabins could fit into each airplane. 3588989]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LFIYKVBRCWGDRSBNLA574XGWIB3EAKKADR5T3SBSMW5XZKBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9C4/BD4/9C4BD43CBA9B4A91BBC56E718DCA1774.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Airbus sleeping pods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Airbus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Zodiac Aerospace]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Airbus lounges]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Airbus meeting rooms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Airbus sleeping cabin cargo hold]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sleep-loss-could-give-you-a-brain-full-of-alzheimer-s-proteins-3588927</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sleep loss could give you a brain full of Alzheimer's proteins 3588927]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BETHESDA, MARYLAND — If you think your sleepless nights are harmless, a new study begs to disagree.

The study, published in PNAS, reports that Alzheimer's disease has been associated with a build-up of beta-amyloid proteins in the brain, which manifests as plaques.

Since sleeping is believed to flush amyloids from the brain, lack of sleep has been correlated with a higher risk of the neurodegenerative disease.

In a study conducted by the National Institutes of Health, amyloid levels in the brains of 20 healthy subjects were measured after a full night's sleep.

When the subjects were deprived of sleep for more than 24 hours, scans revealed that the levels of beta-amyloid had increased significantly.

While the immediate effects of sleep loss are clear, the study failed to look at the implications over a long period of time.

But even without establishing causation between lack of sleep and dementia, it's clear sleep is crucial to a proper functioning brain. 3588927]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLWMCAIBVDRMBCEL5BF59JHMNLVZURLK2JFZHAAKAAAZDZCAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9C4/BD4/9C4BD43CBA9B4A91BBC56E718DCA1774.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dementia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sleep loss]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sleep deprivation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain plaque]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amyloid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beta amyloid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amyloid protein]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/zuckerberg-owns-or-clones-most-apps-he-cites-as-competition-3588902</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Zuckerberg owns or clones most apps he cites as competition 3588902]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INTERNET — When asked by Senator Lindsey Graham in testimony in front of the U.S. Senate yesterday if Facebook was a monopoly, Mark Zuckerberg answered by saying the average American uses eight social apps.

What he didn't say was that Facebook owns or has cloned most of these apps.

Citing mobile app insight service App Annie, Techcrunch reports that Facebook owns three of the Top 10 iOS apps in the U.S.: Instagram, Messenger, and Facebook. Those three are the social apps most used by Americans. 

And Facebook either has or is working on a similar version of competing social apps. Stories is Facebook's latest of several attempts to copy Snapchat. Watch Video is being developed to go after YouTube.

Facebook also owns WhatsApp, the 19th most popular iOS app in America.

By selecting the Social Media category on App Annie and sorting by the most popular apps, you can clearly see that the top three are owned by Facebook. 

This is not a coincidence. Over the years, Facebook has always either bought or sought to copy any emerging social network that challenges its power, Techcrunch reports.

If you're still not sure if Facebook is a monopoly or not, ask yourself this question: If you deleted your Facebook account, could you find all of your friends and family on another social app?
 
MySpace, anyone? 3588902]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLAIDRHBSKRAA3ABBLFTKBBMFLSKUT6KJIW7TIGAWMRZDKXAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FCD/9E1/FCD9E1B6F04B434895F08000944DC060.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>107</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mark Zuckerberg congress]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mark zuckerberg congress highlights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facebook instagram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facebook owns whatsapp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facebook competitors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ top social apps]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-s-going-back-to-mars-via-california--3588884</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA's going back to Mars (via California) 3588884]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VANDENBERG AIR FORCE BASE, CALIFORNIA — California will play host to the first interplanetary launch from the U.S. west coast next month.

NASA will launch their insight mission to Mars from the Vandenberg Air Force in California on the morning of May 5, 2018. The higher it gets, the more visible it'll be to more of the state. NASA reckons 10 million Californians will be able to see it.

Protected by an aeroshell, the lander will travel for around 6 months to the red planet.
Once close to the atmosphere it'll begin a 6-minute descent around 80 miles from the Martian surface.

As it approaches the surfaces, the spacecraft will get rid of its heat shielding and deploy a parachute. Once there, the Insight lander will remain stationary and not move around. NASA will use to probe the Martian surface and analyze soil samples from deep inside the planet. 3588884]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIWVYAIBMFWED3ELACW57LTGREVTSINKJPW5TZKKZHWXDZBAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/385/8DD/3858DDA5541040F98143DA90B7C571CF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa insight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa mission on mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ insight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ red planet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa 2018]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/zucker-bot-the-internet-thinks-facebook-s-ceo-is-a-robot-3588858</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Zucker-bot: The Internet thinks Facebook's CEO is a robot 3588858]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — Facebook grandmaster Mark Zuckerberg traveled to Congress on Wednesday to do some Q&A on the Cambridge Analytica scandal and attend the elderly.  

During the hearing the tech billionaire reportedly admitted responsibility for the abuse of user data and said Facebook didn't do enough to stop it. 

The internet, being the internet, seemed more concerned with Zuck's mechanical responses and how he may have been a robot. Naturally, a slew of Zucker-bot themed memes followed suit. 3588858]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLFEDAHBRBREAZVBMCRI9U4MZEB3SIQAIDATTADAAGATAAFLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/88A/528/88A5287BD9D14A498EBAECB5E816DFCF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ is mark zuckerberg a robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mark zuckerberg robot meme]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facebook ceo robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mark zuckerberg robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zuckerbot]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scotland-sets-up-massive-8-8-mw-wind-turbine-3588811</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scotland sets up massive 8.8 MW wind turbine 3588811]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ABERDEEN, SCOTLAND — One rotation from Aberdeen's massive new 8.8 megawatt wind turbine can generate 24 hours of power for one house.

According to Inhabitat, the first of 11 massive wind turbines have been installed near Aberdeen on the Scottish coast.  When complete it's believed they will generate 70% of Aberdeen's energy needs, displacing 134,128 tonnes of CO2.

Each turbine is 191 meters tall, nearly double the size of the Statue of Liberty.
The blades measure 80 meters in length, and together with the rotor, make for a circumference larger than that of the London Eye. 3588811]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDWMDZGLVDRCVZVKEAAZ94RNABS5RZKAWIRZHKWKNNRCDRDAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/97E/15C/97E15CEAA45D4A30AFA9E388D9233232.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ largest wind turbines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind turbines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Scotland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ green energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind energy power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ most powerful wind turbine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind turbines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ renewable energy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nanoparticles-in-canned-goods-may-be-doing-your-gut-harm-3588615</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Nanoparticles in canned goods may be doing your gut harm 3588615]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BINGHAMTON, NEW YORK — In case you needed more proof that fresh is best, a new study has found that nanoparticles in your food packaging could be doing your gut harm.

According to the Binghamton University study, the inside of canned goods are typically lined with zinc oxide nanoparticles, which have antimicrobial properties.

When looking at how much nanoparticles were transferred to food, researchers found 100 times the recommended daily allowance of zinc oxide.

While in the small intestine, the nanoparticles caused the remodelling or loss of microvilli, resulting less nutrients being absorbed into the cells.

High doses of zinc oxide also triggered pro-inflammatory signaling. This can increase intestinal permeability and allow harmful compounds to pass into the bloodstream.

Since only a cell model was used to demonstrate the effects, it's difficult to determine how long-term ingestion will impact human health. For now, the researchers are looking at the nanoparticles' effect on animals. 3588615]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKAPYZDB2LFCBTEL2IAI9JAG2JVTETRAZAR3GTSK6PAZDTRAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/936/BC4/936BC467F0624177A8FF77F6627F882C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nanoparticles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zinc oxide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canned food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad for your gut]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ is canned food bad for you]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ food packaging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nutrients]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digestion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digestive problems]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gastrointestinal]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-will-kim-jong-un-travel-to-meet-with-donald-trump--3589695</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How will Kim Jong Un travel to meet with Donald Trump? 3589695]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TO BE CONFIRMED —   North Korea may not be equipped with transport capable of getting its leader Kim Jong Un to his May meeting with US President Donald Trump. 

Citing a former CIA analyst, the Washington Post reports that North Korea uses old long range Soviet aircraft. Analysts also told the paper that North Korean airline Koryo has shorter-range Tupolev jets.

Unconfirmed reports last month put Kim in China, saying he got there via an armored green train. If true, he could also travel by rail to a European venue via Moscow or to a spot in Russia itself. There are several North Korea to Russia train services in operation, according to travel website Seat61.com

Analysts say Kim could also borrow aircraft from one of its neighbors, or travel with South Korea or Sweden. However the Post reports these options could be embarrassing for the North Korean leader. 3589695]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAWGAIDKIBRAVRWLWKRR7JHGWIERU3ZA2JAXHRGKEGWRAC5AF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/04C/1DF/04C1DFA66AB1F89C5595F2B06AD53BE1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump kim meeting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump kim meet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ usa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea travel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ koryo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dprk]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-first-electrified-road-for-charging-moving-vehicles-3589682</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's first electrified road for charging moving vehicles 3589682]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[STOCKHOLM — The world's first electrified road that recharges batteries of moving vehicles driving on it has opened in Sweden. 

Around 2 kms of electric rail has been embedded in a road close to Stockholm, according to the Guardian. 

The system transfers electricity from the installed underground rail to the vehicle above through a flexible arm that connects to the charging vehicle, according to Inhabitat. 
The electrified road is split up into 50m sections. Individual sections are only powered when a car or truck is overhead. The current is disconnected if a vehicle stops. 

When the vehicle drives off the electric rails, the system calculates the energy consumption and debits the driver. 

At a cost of around €1 million per kilometer, the cost to electrify roads is 50 times lower than required to build an urban tram line, according to the Guardian.  

The Swedish government's road agency is planning for future national expansion. 3589682]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRBWCXRGKAAWXD3HLIDAT7DSGRDVTRAMKNKRXFAHK5HWXBRBKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C79/297/C792975A273E3C6547F2C513A591CA31.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electrified roads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sweden electrified road]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Stockholm electrified road]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric vehicle charging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moving electric vehicle charging]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/breast-cancer-surgery-healing-process-may-trigger-relapse-3589503</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Breast cancer surgery healing process may trigger relapse 3589503]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — New research suggests that the healing process following breast cancer surgery may be triggering cancer in other sites to spread.

According to MIT News, previous studies of breast cancer patients indicate they are prone to metastatic relapse 12 to 18 months after undergoing surgery for  growth removal.

It's been suggested that dormant cancer cells in other sites that were previously kept in check by the immune system are allowed to become active as the body focuses on healing its wound.

Experiments on mice conducted by the Whitehead Institute found that while T-cells stalled the growth of injected cancer cells,  simulated surgeries in areas far from the cancer resulted in increased tumor growth and incidence.

Fortunately, there is a solution. Mice given anti-inflammatory drugs during or after surgery developed significantly smaller tumors, which often disappeared completely.

Early research in humans shows the same strong association between anti-inflammatory drug use and a decline in metastasis, but more studies are needed to confirm the data. 3589503]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZAAMACVKNLACWCEBVDAK9JGGVBS3FIMKZDR3URDBVFRCWRIKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/07D/5DD/07D5DD8FC7184B88AFC2F131030BCDE8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ breast cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ breast cancer surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer spread]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NSAID]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anti-inflammatory drugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ growth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ relapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dormant cancer cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mastectomy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lumpectomy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cool-way-to-remove-keloid-scars-with-a-rubber-band-3589385</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cool way to remove keloid scars with a rubber band 3589385]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE INTERNET — YouTube tutorials are helpful for a lot of things. Keloid scar removal probably isn't one of them. 

Keloids are heaped up scars that are the result of an overgrowth of granulation tissue at the site of a healed skin injury which is then slowly replaced by collagen. 

According to a new and not very safe genre of tutorials on YouTube, basically all you need is a scar, a rubber band — and ideally a lower than average IQ. 

The idea is that you cut off the blood supply to the scar, which eventually turns black and falls off. 

The only drawback is that it hurts like hell and can cause further disfigurement and possible unintended necrosis. 
  
So don't do it. 3589385]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNFECIABEBARAA7BRAW59DWMEBVZST7AIAATGKTKFPR3WK7BE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4F2/E00/4F2E008DAA1346EF803344F31379ED4C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ scar removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ keloid scar removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rubber band scar removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ scars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ keloid scars]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/detroit-area-teen-asking-for-directions-shot-at-for-being-black-3591735</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Detroit-area teen asking for directions shot at for being black 3591735]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROCHESTER HILLS, MICHIGAN — A retired, white Detroit firefighters has been charged with assault with intent to murder after he tried to shoot a black teen who knocked on the man's suburban home to ask for directions. 
  
Brennan Walker, 14, of Rochester Hills woke up late for school last Thursday and missed the bus, so he decided to walk, which takes about and hour and a half, the New York Times reported. 

Brennan didn't have his phone, so was without GPS. He ended up getting lost, so he did what any normal kid would do, he asked for directions. 

The Rochester Hills freshman tried a few houses until he got the Zieglers. He reportedly chose the house because he saw that it had a neighborhood-watch sticker. He knocked and a woman answered the door.

The teen tried to explain he was a student and needed directions, but the white lady freaked and thought he was trying to rob the house — because robbers usually knock first. 

That's when her husband, 53-year-old Jeffrey Ziegler, got even more scared and petrified, so he went upstairs to get his shotgun.

According to law enforcement, Ziegler was not terribly weapons-competent and was slow to discharge the weapon, which allowed Brennan to get away safely. 

Brennan's mom had even given her son tips on not looking to black around the whites, like not wearing hoodies or walking with your hands in your pockets. 

Security footage backed up Brennan's side of the story. Ziegler was arraigned last Friday. His bond was set at $50,000. 3591735]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLRPX3XANJWVVA7BACRK9BGMNJVRSC7AJIF3TZCKMHWEAIAAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/31F/E8A/31FE8AAF2B8642D9BF1DF0CD1ED5058A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>87</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ teen asks for directions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ teen gets lost]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jeffrey Ziegler arraigned]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Brennan Walker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Rochester Hills]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/subsea-trove-of-rare-minerals-found-near-japanese-island-3591514</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Subsea trove of rare minerals found near Japanese island 3591514]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — A plethora of rare earth minerals have been discovered on a remote Japanese island, according to new research published in Scientific Reports.

Researchers says that the seafloor surrounding Nishinoshima island is laden with enough 16 million tonnes of rare-earth oxides, the South China Morning Post reported, citing the study.

On a global scale, the study estimates that the find could meet 62 years of yttrium demand, 47 years of europium, 32 years of Terbium, and 56 years of dysprosium needs. 3591514]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAAIDADKSIA3WTDL5CRZ7L3NBKSKRCRKNKWMGIGAVGFAWZABE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/52A/379/52A379CF2F6C4777B2AD9C400EB66A93.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rare earth minerals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new discovery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nishinoshima island]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth minerals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ europium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ terbium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dysprosium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yttrium]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/instagram-model-ruins-vision-after-undergoing-risky-eye-operation-3591458</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Instagram model ruins vision after undergoing risky eye operation 3591458]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MIAMI — A Miami-based Instagram model ruined her vision after trying to change her eye color by undergoing a very risky surgical procedure.

According to the New York Post, Nadinne Bruna travelled to Bogota, Colombia in October 2016. There she spent $3,000 to to have medical staff injected her eyeballs with silicone.

But the procedure went wrong and hurt Bruna's optic nerves, giving her glaucoma. 
Brunna returned to Colombia to try and repair the damage, but it was already done. 


The 32 year-old later had the implants removed back in the U.S., but her condition was irreversible. As a result, she's now got the vision of a 90-year-old.

Brunna blames herself for what happened, telling the New York Post she was stupid and didn't do the research.  

She had to quit modeling and is now living off savings plus income earned via Instagram. Bruna has close to 200,000 followers on the site.

Eye specialist Dr. Richard Rose told the New York Post that people wanting to change their eye color should use contact lenses as they're safe, removable and approved. 3591458]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AECAIDTUKBIA7WTALSJRR9BAMMESTST6LSLWTUTYKRERMAAFBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4F2/11E/4F211EC30B96488C8447964E6B086170.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nadinne bruna]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye surgery gone wrong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye color change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye op]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmetic surgery gone wrong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ operation gone wrong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ silicone implants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ silicone eyeball implants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vision ruined]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmetic surgery colombia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ironman-who-broke-neck-planning-on-running-boston-marathon-3591392</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ironman who broke neck planning on running Boston Marathon 3591392]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOSTON — The world's fastest Ironman, who experienced a hangman's fracture in his neck just six months ago, is planning to compete in the Boston Marathon.  

On October 11, 2017, triathlete and marathon runner Tim Don was involved in an accident when a vehicle turning into a gas station struck him in the side, according to the New York Times. 

Don experienced a hangman's fracture, a broken C2 vertebra. 

In order to keep competing, Don elected to have a halo put on. With a halo, titanium pins are screwed into the skull, two in front and two in back and then attached to metal bars, which are connected to a bust that must be worn for three months. 

Training in the halo has been extremely painful for Don. He's worked on strengthening his core and lower body. He was also able to train on an exercise bike as long as he did not lean forward to overload his neck.   

Don says he expects to finish the marathon in around 2 hours and 50 minutes. 3591392]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAWGYACKVDW3BTDLRARVLDTGIEBTEC4KFKFTT3RAFNREAAIAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F9B/366/F9B366A0E56C4E11BC418B40E036F2B8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tim Don]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ironman Tim Don]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tim Don broken neck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tim Don Boston Marathon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tim Don neck Boston Marathon]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gold-backed-cryptocurrency-used-to-attract-muslim-investors-3591356</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gold-backed cryptocurrency used to attract Muslim investors 3591356]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBAI — Cryptocurrency traders are now turning to gold to draw investors from Muslim nations.

Reuters reports that many Gulf states don't consider cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin or Ethereum as compliant with Sharia law, which emphasizes economic activity based on physical assets.

To address this, Dubai startup OneGram has begun issuing a gold-backed cryptocurrency. Each unit has a corresponding gram of gold stored in a vault.

The company obtained approval from an Islamic advisory firm, and has so far issued tens of millions of dollars worth of the currency. Only 60 percent of the planned amount of coins remains to be sold.

A similar gold-backed crypto from HelloGold was released in Malaysia last October, after receiving permission from Islamic scholars in Kuala Lumpur. 3591356]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LICFVAAIKAHACDAYLFLFT7BCNAAV7FC4KMBWRTAHBVHRPCRAKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/817/D95/817D9567BE494A1FAE06249DF38DCAD6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gold cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gold bar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Islamic cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Muslim cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ onegram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ middle east]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gulf states]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-accidentally-discover-plastic-eating-enzyme-3592442</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists accidentally discover plastic-eating enzyme 3592442]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GOLDEN, COLORADO — Researchers from the U.S. and Britain say they have created a plastic-eating enzyme that could be used aide in the recovery and recycling of plastics. 

The enzyme is able to digest polyethylene terephthalate, or PET, plastic. PET plastics take hundreds of years to breakdown and have become an enormous source of pollution, according to Reuters.

The findings were published on Monday in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences journal. 

Scientists from the U.S. Department of Energy's National Renewable Energy Laboratory and Britain's University of Portsmouth made the discovery while looking at the structure of a natural enzyme believed to have evolved in a recycling plant in Japan.

Researchers added some amino acids to the enzyme which ended up speeding up its plastic-eating capabilities. 

The team will now work on improving the enzyme to see if it's capable to breaking down PET plastics on an industrial scale. 3592442]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIDWVYIAKMHFZBZWBBJAV7LUGZBERU36KADW5FAAAMFFCAZAAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/817/B91/817B919F2FB644F483A799904D239686.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic-eating enzyme]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastics pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PET pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic digesting enzyme]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastics recycling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PET recycling]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-s-presidential-limo-will-be-ready-this-summer-3592210</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump's presidential limo will be ready this summer 3592210]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — A new fleet of presidential limousines is set to debut this summer, with one of the Cadillacs already in the possession of the Secret Service, Fox News reported.

Wrapped in black and white camouflage during its testing phase, the new presidential vehicle is expected to sport styling elements similar Cadillac's CT6 sedan. Known as Cadillac One or by the Secret Service as The Beast, it will use a Kodiak medium-duty truck frame with custom-made body panels.

The seven-seat interior is sealed to protect against a biological or chemical attack, with windows that can withstand armor-piercing bullets.

The current edition of the Beast has 20-cm-thick heavy armor-plated doors and a reinforced steel plate running underneath the vehicle to protect it from roadside bombs.

The presidential limousine has tear gas cannons and a night vision camera, as well as a pump-action shotgun. Extra weapons, an oxygen supply and bottles of the president's blood type are also on board. The fuel tank is armor-plated and encased in foam to prevent it from exploding. The kevlar-reinforced tires are puncture and shard-resistant, with steel rims that allow the car to continue driving if the tires are destroyed.

Unlike the CT6, the Beast probably will not use the CT6's semi-autonomous drive system. Instead, it will always be driven by a highly trained agent who's skilled in defensive and evasive driving techniques.

The vehicle bears the American flag and the Presidential Standard while traveling domestically. When abroad, the Presidential Standard is replaced by that country's flag.

Cadillac has built every presidential vehicle since 1993. Cadillac President Johann de Nysschen told Fox News that the presidential vehicles have always been part of Cadillac's heritage and tradition. One they hope to carry on in the future. 3592210]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIFMCTSARBAXDZ7BJIWTL4YGZDBRRT6K2LWZGCTKMFRXATYKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8E1/831/8E183152565D42CF8EB2F0B538138979.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>97</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Trump car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Donald Trump car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cadillac One]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US president car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the beast car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 


TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump limo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump presidential limo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump limousine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump limo the beast]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump limousine video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the beast]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gm limo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gm presidential limo]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sitting-too-much-changes-your-brain-and-affects-memory-3592180</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sitting too much changes your brain and affects memory 3592180]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — Sitting too much is linked to changes in parts of the brain important for memory, according to a preliminary study by UCLA.

Researchers wanted to look at the effects of sedentary behavior on brain health, particularly the sections of the brain critical to memory formation, UCLA reported, according to Science Daily. 

The UCLA team found 35 people ranging in age from 45 to 75 and asked their physical activity levels and the average number of hours per day spent sitting the week before. 

A high-resolution MRI scan was taken of each subject's medial temporal lobe, MTL. The MTL is the region of the brain involved when forming new memories. 

The scientists found that sedentary behavior is a significant predictor of thinning of the MTL and that physical activity is not enough to offset the harmful effects of prolonged periods of sitting. 

This is not to say that sitting too much causes thinner brain structures, but instead that extended periods seated are associated with thinner sections, the researchers said. 

According to the researchers, MTL thinning can be a precursor to cognitive decline and dementia in middle-aged and older adults. 3592180]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZDAGACVKJLRCAZRBSLRR7LSM5BSTS3SAFPFVHRGAFNFCVAAAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/470/47F/47047F0377854CA5B7F80F2D9DB73D21.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sitting too much]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sitting brain memory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sedentary behavior]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prolonged sitting]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-say-we-must-prevent-robots-from-betraying-us-3592102</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists say we must prevent robots from betraying us 3592102]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AI — British scientists published a report stating that there are increasing fears of robots betraying mankind by hurting or lying to them.

Scientists who are worried about the issue warned cyber attacks could turn robots bad. 

Especially for military robots equipped with lethal autonomous weapons. 

Professor Stephen Hawking once posited that if artificial intelligence turns against humanity, it could prove to be the worst event in our history.

Scientists also fear that robots might develop a lingo to communicate with that we humans won't understand.

A reported published by Britain's House of Lords Artificial Intelligence Committee warned the impact of robots taking over our jobs, and urged more education and training so mankind can still have a place alongside AI in society. 3592102]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWKWKYIHAEAWZBCEKBPAI7DYMMBBRFAKK2IFMHAHKMFAMARBAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/317/A4E/317A4E509BDF43C19E475598F61104B8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robots betray humans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial intelligence betray]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robots lying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robots hurting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robots hurting people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robots hurting humans]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-begins-search-for-more-earth-like-planets-3592063</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA begins search for more Earth-like planets 3592063]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA — NASA's new planet-hunting satellite will seek out Earth-like worlds over the next two years.

Called the Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite (TESS), the spacecraft searches for planets which orbit a star and cause a dip in its brightness. This pattern is akin to how Earth orbits the Sun, and repeated brightness dips may indicate planet supporting life.

Planets orbiting other stars are termed exoplanets. This covers planets of all sizes from Earth and Mars, to Jupiter. TESS will search for exoplanets outside the solar system.

NASA says TESS will cover an area 400 times greater than observed by the Kepler satellite. Over 2 years it, it will look at 26 different sectors of space. According to NASA, TESS will observe stars up to 100 times brighter than previously covered. 3592063]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIRIYCSAWIF3ARRLEDFX9BHNADSTST2KNIF5HCXBRFFMVZFKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EE1/84F/EE184FD449184E41B5D691C71853123C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-18T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth-like planets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kepler]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tess]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exoplanets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth-like planets nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa exoplanets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa tess mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ james webb telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kepler mission]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spacex-just-got-approval-to-build-big-falcon-rocket-at-the-l-a-port-3593208</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[SpaceX just got approval to build Big Falcon Rocket at the L.A. port 3593208]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti announced Monday that SpaceX will build Mars spaceships at a facility at the Port of L.A. 

Today, I am pleased to officially announce that SpaceX will start production development of the Big Falcon Rocket in the Port of Los Angeles. This vehicle that holds the promise of taking humanity even deeper into the cosmos than ever before, Garcetti said during an annual speech, according to the Los Angeles Times.  

The Big Falcon Rocket is a two-part launch vehicle designed to transport 100 people and 150 tons of cargo into space, according to Business Insider. When completed, it will be more than 348 feet tall.  

The fully reusable rocket can be quickly refuelable and is designed to burn liquid methane, which can be manufactured on other planets and moons in the solar system, including Mars. 

According to public documents, SpaceX asked for permission to lease a 19-acre site called Berth 240 at the former Southwest Marine Shipyard. 

SpaceX wants to build a 200,000 square-foot rocketship factory on a historic site, so will now need to get approval from the port's Board of Harbor Commissioners. 

The initial 10-year lease, which contains two options for 10-year extensions, has a starting annual rent of around $1.38 million with annual adjustments based on the Consumer Price Index, according to the LA Times. 3593208]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJRAYZAA2KWIAKCBJKAZ92AGIAB5RT4AVBW7UTWKAAAVWRHAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/410/95D/41095D635B1841BDB3B5A4F061C0A065.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX Big Falcon Rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX BFR Port of Los Angeles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX Port of Los Angeles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/buruli-ulcer-skin-eating-infections-on-rise-in-australia-3593199</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Buruli ulcer: Skin-eating infections on rise in Australia 3593199]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VICTORIA, AUSTRALIA — Doctors are scrambling to figure out how cases of a skin-eating disease are on the rise in the land down under. 

Citing experts, the BBC reports Australian cases of Buruli ulcer have increased 400% since 2014. The disease can cut to the bone, spreading toxins that eradicate skin, blood vessels and fat This is what causes the ulcer to form.

Mycobacterium ulcerans, the bacteria in the disease, is from the same family as leprosy and tuberculosis, according to the World Health Organization. Its origin is unknown, but doctors writing in the Medical Journal of Australia, speculate it may come from the environment, soil or could even be carried by mosquitoes.

The WHO says early detection and antibiotic treatment are key to dealing with Buruli ulcer. The disease is commonly treated with a different combination of antibiotics, surgical techniques such as skin grafting as well as physiotherapy.

The BBC reports health authorities have spent more than 750,000 USD combating the disease and raising awareness of it. However, doctors writing in the Aussie Medical journal are calling on Australia to do more, asking officials to immediately fund research into combating the disease. 3593199]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLWVDRDAIHRKAKCBVAA794XGNLSRRC6KMAFTHCTK5HREWZALD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9F5/CE3/9F5CE3983EEB41D6956DBAD05ADCF9BE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>92</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ myobacterium ulcerans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ buruli ulcer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ulcer in australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin eating ulcer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ buruli ulcer virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is the buruli ulcer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin infection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ulcer on skin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ buruli australia virus]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-breaks-into-gamestop-wearing-plastic-bag-on-his-head-3593062</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man breaks into GameStop wearing plastic bag on his head 3593062]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST.MARY'S, GEORGIA — A burglar who looks like he could win the worst costume of the year is wanted after police said he broke into a Georgia GameStop wearing a water bottle wrapper on his head.

According to St. Mary's Police Department, the break-in took place at about 1:19 a.m. April 13 at a GameStop in Georgia near Highway 40. 

The suspect thought he needed a disguise, which is true, so he covered his face in what was left of the plastic bag that goes around water bottles, genius.

Police said Mr. Plastic bag broke into the store by kicking out the bottom glass panel of the front door.

However, it is unknown if anything was taken by Mr. Plastic bag. 

St. Mary's Police uploaded the surveillance footage to their Facebook page appealing for help from whomever has information on the suspect. 3593062]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZBRGC3VK2LAACITL2KRT9URGEDB7SAIKVDRXHRAASPRXWIDAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1C7/F84/1C7F841E11814CC89E2833557FB86BFD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man wearing plastic bag]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burglar in plastic bag]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gamestop thief]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water bottle wrappers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wearing water bottle wrapper]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gamestop theft]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/plane-engine-explosion-breaks-window-kills-woman-3592989</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Plane engine explosion breaks window, kills woman 3592989]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA — A mid-flight engine explosion at 32,000 feet on Tuesday led to chaos over the skies of Philadelphia.

According to the New York Times, Southwest Airlines flight 1380 was enroute to Dallas from New York when one of its two engines exploded mid-flight.

According to NBC Philadelphia, the National Transportation and Safety Board are investigating the incident as engine failure. 

The Boeing 737 aircraft was reportedly carrying 143 passengers and five crew at the time. It later emergency landed in Philadelphia. 

Shrapnel from the explosion shattered a plane window. NBC Philadelphia reports passenger Jennifer Riordan to be partially pulled through the window.

A passenger later told the New York Times Riordan was also hit by some shrapnel from the damaged plane engine. He explained passengers and crew dragged her back in, but she was unconscious when they did. 

Riordan later died despite attempts to revive her. 3592989]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNKWIYABAAAWPDZSBRAATK4TNFJV7RZLKZDA5G3YAAFFCYAMBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EBE/9CF/EBE9CF507F0A4743AD4793F0731C422B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>112</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane window breaks mid flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plane engine explodes mid flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flight 1380]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jennifer riordan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ passenger sucked from plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gary kelly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boeing 737]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CFM56]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/late-bedders-more-likely-to-die-younger-new-research-says-3592762</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Late bedders more likely to die younger, new research says 3592762]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ZZZ — New research suggests people who go to bed late were shown to have a 10 percent higher mortality rate than early risers.

The study, published in Chronobiology International, observed 433,628 individuals for a 6-and-half-year period. Fifty-thousand late bedders of those sampled were more likely to die or suffer from diseases and mental health issues.

This, co-lead author Kristin Knutson explained, may be due to stress, lack of exercise, alcohol, drug abuse or other unhealthy behaviors. Knutson suggests night owls could try to get to bed early more regularly and be exposed to light early in the morning. 3592762]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKFKYCSAEAFPXZTBSIRIK2HM2IE5RRLAWLA3HIHA6MFPAIGAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/120/91C/12091C0BAD474E09BE861B4965DECE5F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ going to bed late]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sleep and health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ night owls health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ early risers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sleep problems]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ insomnia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ healthy sleeping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unhealthy sleeping]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-restroom-hand-dryers-circulate-poop-bacteria-3592755</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds restroom hand dryers circulate poop bacteria 3592755]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[STORRS, CONNECTICUT — Colonies of fecal bacteria have been found in air from restroom hand dryers, according to new research.

The University of Connecticut study found bacteria blasted from hand dryers in 36 bathrooms within the institution's School of Medicine building. 

The research, published in Applied and Environmental Microbiology, found traces of the harmless lab-made PS533 and Staphylococcus aureus. The latter is associated with infections. The study's lead author told Newsweek the PS533 bacteria traveled from a lab through the air.

Researchers also applied their test to restroom hand dryers with HEPA filters, but found that 25 percent of bacteria were still present. 3592755]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLWXDRCAIHAKAISB6PWZ6DSNBIBTRK6AECF7FAAA2PFADTSAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/42F/AFD/42FAFDE2D2D14EBBB8DC1406CAEFD8AA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>39</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hand dryers vs paper towels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hand dryers and germs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ restroom hand dryer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bacteria in bathrooms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bathroom bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bacteria from flushing toilet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-to-properly-use-an-airplane-oxygen-mask-3593900</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How to properly use an airplane oxygen mask 3593900]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — Southwest Airlines Flight 1380 suffered a massive engine failure on Tuesday, which forced the pilot to make an emergency landing. 
When the left engine blew apart, it sent shrapnel through the plane, killing one passenger, and leaving a hole in the aircraft, according to CNN. 

The hole caused the cabin to depressurize, and the oxygen masks to drop down. 

One photo from passenger Marty Martinez shows several passengers wearing oxygen masks incorrectly. 

To properly use the mask, pull down on the mask until the plastic tubing is fully extended. Put the mask over you mouth and nose and breathe regularly. 
At altitudes over 15,000 feet, people struggle to breathe and keep their blood oxygenated. They can develop a condition called hypoxia and lose consciousness within minutes, according to Business Insider. 

According to the Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association, symptoms of hypoxia include, nausea, apprehension, tunnel vision, headaches, fatigue, dizziness, blurred vision, tingling sensations, numbness and mental confusion.

Flight 1380 engine failure occurred at 31,000 feet, according to passenger reports.

The National Transportation Safety Board is currently investigating the incident. 3593900]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDFVXZHKMEFKBRTLJLRV9USGIAE5R3SKSIF5UTWANPRPDCWBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F3E/C2E/F3EC2EA3858940A7B31B35B779485041.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airplane oxygen masks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oxygen masks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to wear oxygen masks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypoxia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hypoxia symptoms]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-the-man-with-three-faces--what-is-neurofibromatosis-type-one--3593824</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['The man with three faces': What is neurofibromatosis type one? 3593824]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PARIS — French man Jérôme Hamon has become the world's first patient to undergo two face transplants. He suffers from neurofibromatosis type 1.

According to the Mayo Clinic, Neurofibromatosis 1, or NF1, is a genetic condition that causes tumors to form along nervous tissue. These tumors are typically benign, but in some cases can become malignant and cancerous.

Indicators of the condition include six or more flat, light-brown skin spots, small bumps on the iris, and bumps under the skin. The Mayo Clinic says signs typically appear around the age of 10. Other symptoms of NF1 are bone deformities, optic nerve tumors, affected individuals being below average height and perhaps having learning disabilities.

According to the BBC, Hamon's NF1 causes severe tumors to form around his face. 
Hamon underwent his first face transplant in 2010 but had to go under the knife again in 2017 after medication for a cold caused his body to reject the transplant. That was removed last November, leaving Hamon unable to speak, hear or see for several months.

Hamon remained like that in a Paris hospital until January when he received a second facial transplant, according to the BBC.  French media have called him the man with three faces. Despite all he's been through, he remains upbeat, telling French TV, I'm 43 and the donor was 22, so I'm 22 again.

Information from the Britain's National Health Service says NF1 typically affects one in 3,000 people. Worldwide it affects 3 million people.

A 2014 study by the Washington University in St. Louis found members of both sexes have almost equal chances of developing the condition, but it affects both differently. 
Females are at more risk for brain tumors and vision, while males may suffer more from learning disabilities.

There's no cure for NF1, but treatment of the condition can involve pain medication, monitoring, and for cancerous tumors, chemotherapy and radiation therapy. Surgery is used on both cancerous and noncancerous tumors. 3593824]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLAMCTSANKAIVTEB6IWX7SHGSIBRFKSLSPF3FKTKEEFADALKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2BE/7EA/2BE7EA09912CBEC6622F8E21474CD0E3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>128</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man with three faces]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jerome hamon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neurofibromatosis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nf1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neurofibromatosis type 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NF type 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ face transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ second face transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man 3 faces]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/baboons-used-barrels-to-break-free-from-research-center-3593663</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Baboons used barrels to break free from research center 3593663]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN ANTONIO, TEXAS — Four baboons in San Antonio proved to be quite a handful when they freed themselves from a research center last Saturday by climbing over a barrel and an enclosure wall. 

According to Texas Biomedical Research Institute, the facility holds about 1,100 baboons for vaccine tests and drug therapy. 

The enclosure area has inward-leaning walls to keep baboons from escaping, but the blue barrels filled with grains were recently added so animals can roll them around to shake out food. However, one clever baboon figured out how to place a barrel upright and use it to get to the top of the wall. Three other baboons saw this and joined in on the great escape. 

One baboon later decided to surrender and returned to the enclosure. 

Southwest National Primate Research Center's animal care team captured two of the three baboons, while the last one was caught after it was called back with verbal and hand-signaling commands.

To avoid another great escape, the institute decided to remove the barrels. 

The institute told Gizmodo the baboons were not being tested for meds that enhance intelligence, instead, the baboons in the corral are typically used for breeding.

In response to the incident, the institute said they have been caring for research baboons for more than 50 years. The baboons have played an important role helping develop life-saving drugs, therapies and vaccines, and helping scientists learn more about chronic human diseases. 3593663]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2JFVYIEA5EFGACCL6IAT9JAMECB5FIMAWIFPHKYKFMAIDREAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5E4/269/5E426922557F47E28F7ADB396A77EDEF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>96</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baboons escape texas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baboons escape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clever baboons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baboons climbing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baboons running away]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baboons funny video]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/genes-behind-fatal-heart-condition-identified-by-scientists-3593511</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Genes behind fatal heart condition identified by scientists 3593511]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Researchers say they have identified genes that are responsible for a fatal heart condition that can only be cured by heart and lung transplants.

Pulmonary arterial hypertension, PAH, kills half of those with the condition within five years, but little was known about its cause, according to the BBC. 

Scientists say they have now discovered five genes that cause the illness. The results were published in the Journal Nature Communications. 

PAH causes the arteries carrying blood from the heart to the lungs to harden and thicken, eventually leading to heart failure.

Researchers analyzed the genomes of more than 1,000 PAH patients and found that mutations in five genes were responsible for the disease. 

In people suffering from PAH, these five genes fail to produce the proteins that are needed for the structure, function and regulation of the body's tissues, according to the scientists.

Now that the genes have been identified, the next step will be to develop new ways to treat the condition. 3593511]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJKWIAAAAADA5DCEKAAWTK2BGMBS7FAMKZDFTGZDBRAFMWZAKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D3D/8B5/D3D8B5807C26475E9A5F7A4B5EE9C1A3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pulmonary arterial hypertension]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PAH]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PAH genes identified]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pulmonary arterial hypertension genes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PAH treatments]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PAH heart transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PAH lung transplant]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-how-sunglasses-and-smartphones-do-not-go-hand-in-hand-3594664</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's how sunglasses and smartphones do not go hand in hand 3594664]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[Polarized lenses can impact what you see on your smartphone.

According to Allaboutvision.com, polarized light tends to reflect from flat surfaces and can create dangers such as glare and reduced visibility. Polarized lenses combat this with a filter that blocks this kind of light. 

When worn, polarized glasses can affect the viewing of GPS devices and cell phones. 
Allaboutvision.com notes boaters and pilots wearing them have reported visual issues with LCD panels on important systems.

Popular Science writes that by rotating a smartphone 90 degrees in either direction, a user wearing polarized glasses can line up the glass and phone filters to make the screen viewable again. 3594664]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNFVDTUBAHAABRSLWIATLBGGJJETE35AEBW3HTSAJMA3BTYAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E91/A99/E91A9951D79A61772A7071D85F8EB523.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-21T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>84</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polarized sunglasses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sunglasses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smartphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uv light]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polarized lenses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polarized sunglasses and smartphones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how do polarized glasses work]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is polarization]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/materials-from-old-ny-bridge-to-be-used-for-artificial-reefs-3594567</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Materials from old NY bridge to be used for artificial reefs 3594567]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TARRYTOWN, NEW YORK — New York state announced a plan to use the demolished Tappan Zee Bridge to build new artificial reefs off Long Island's North Shore.

New York state Governor Andrew Cuomo announced Tuesday that 43,200 cubic yards of the old Tappan Zee bridge will be dumped into coastal waters off of Long Island.

In the first phase of the project, cleaned and recycled materials from the old bridge, steel pipe, and jetty rock will be submerged to build the artificial reefs. 

The artificial reefs will be expanded at six locations off of Long Island's North Shore. 

The artificial reefs will create an environment similar to a natural reef for fin fish, shellfish, and sea grass to regrow.

Governor Cuomo said the project is the largest expansion of artificial reefs in state's history and will boost Long Island's recreational and sport fishing industries. 3594567]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNFECIHBADAPVZRBVDW7LU4MEAEZSC2LVAAXGZEAAHR3AIHBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/73E/7B3/73E7B3B44B8E8DBF0DFA6B590D5086C1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-21T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial reefs long island]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tappan zee bridge demolition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tappan zee bridge new york]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ build artificial reefs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to build artificial reefs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ long island new york]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/backpacker-loses-tip-of-finger-after-australian-farming-accident-3594512</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Backpacker loses tip of finger after Australian farming accident 3594512]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KILLARNEY, AUSTRALIA — A British backpacker lost the tip of her finger after her hand got stuck in an onion peeling machine at an Australian farm. 

Rhianne Jacklin, 21, sustained the injury while working at Warwick Farms Killarney on a three-month stint, according to the Sun.

She was trying to clean the onion peeling machine, only problem was that she wasn't properly trained how to. 

After it happened, Jacklin said she ran around the building for three minutes before she found another coworker to help clean up her finger and bandage her hand. 
She was taken to Toowoomba Hospital for surgery, where excess bone sticking out of her finger was cut back and her finger skin stretched over the wound. 

Rhianne's right hand ring finger is now permanently one centimeter shorter. She says she's also suffered a bit of depression since the incident last week. 3594512]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIFKDKXAIARGBRUL5BA5L43GIES3E36AEAA3UTRBRGRZBZEAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/337/501/33750135961FD94C9B9AC18696C31A7A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-21T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ backpacker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ british backpacker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ backpacker farming accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ backpacker farming mishap]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ farming accident]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-arrested-for-being-a-very-bad-boy-after-deer-attack-rampage-3594310</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dog arrested for being a very bad boy after deer attack rampage 3594310]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ONTARIO, CANADA — A dog was behind bars in Canada on Sunday following a disagreement with a deer.

Finn, a mixed-breed, was walking off-the-leash on a trail with his human Reid Thompson and Thompson's girlfriend in Ontario, Canada on Sunday.

According to Fox News, Finn usually stays close by, but that day he caught whiff of a deer and went into hound-mode, ignoring commands to return.  Thompson told Fox News, Finn chased Bambi along a road, through a hospital and back onto another road.

He said the two animals tangled for a bit, before scaling a guard rail and coming to some ice.  But while Rudolph got away, Finn was put in the dog house after being nabbed by Canada's finest.

A photo of Finn behind bars inside a cop car went viral on Twitter, spawning #FreeFinn and dog vs deer memes galore.

Reportedly, the pup was later released, but his owners received a very un-Canadian talking to about animal control and keeping dogs on the leash. 

Finn meanwhile seems to be doing fine. No word on the deer though. Maybe next time buddy. 3594310]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6NFKDTWBAARAWKFLEDRXKJFGEES3RT7K6LFTGIDARGFPCTUAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/337/501/33750135961FD94C9B9AC18696C31A7A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-21T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[bad dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog v police]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[freefinn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ontario]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[canada]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog off the lessh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[bad dog compilation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog in jail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog in jail picture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog v deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog gets arrested by cops]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dog vs the police]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/lost-young-girl-rescued-by-loyal-dog-who-s-deaf-and-partially-blind-3596654</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Lost young girl rescued by loyal dog who's deaf and partially blind 3596654]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA — A family dog in Australia has proved again why dogs are a human's best friend when he stuck by a toddler who got lost in the bushland overnight.

Reported by Australia's ABC NEWS, 3-year-old Aurora was reported missing at around 3 p.m. on Friday after she wandered off from her home in Cherry Gully.

A search team made up with emergency services workers and local volunteers went out to look for Aurora, and resumed the search at early Saturday. 

Luckily, Max, a 17-year-old blue heeler who is deaf and partially blind, followed Aurora and stayed by her side as she slept outdoors while temperatures dropped to 59 degrees[c].

It was Leisa Bennett, Aurora's grandmother, who faintly heard her responding after she shouted out to her granddaughter while searching on Saturday morning.

Fortunately, the elderly Max led Leisa and police to Aurora, who only suffered small cuts and scratches.

Queensland Police were so impressed with Max's loyalty they have made him an honorary police dog. 3596654]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAWIXCXKMAFGACELEARX7LRM2JSZSAQAADF5UTWAZFWEBIGKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/717/655/7176558285FB44BABF9A5000168E9A69.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ family dog australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dogs are man's best friend]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toddler lost australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ loyal dog australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ loyal dog rescues toddler]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog stuck with toddler]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ queensland australia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-moves-1-5-bn-users-out-of-reach-of-new-eu-privacy-law-3596613</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook moves 1.5 bn users out of reach of new EU privacy law 3596613]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Facebook has moved more than 1.5 billion users out of reach of a new European Union privacy law, Reuters reported. 
Users outside the United States and Canada are currently governed by terms of service agreed with the social network's international headquarters in Ireland. 
The European Union's General Data Protection Regulation, GDPR, is set to take effect May 25. 

The new law allows European regulators to fine companies for collecting or using personal data without users' consent.

Facebook is liable under GDPR fines of up to 4 percent of its global revenue, around $1.6 billion, for any infractions, according to the Guardian.  
Facebook user data from Asia, Africa and Latin America will be transferred from the Ireland headquarter offices to main offices in California.   
The change affects more than 70 percent of the site's 2 billion-plus members. As of December, Facebook had 239 million users in the United States and Canada, 370 million in Europe and 1.52 billion users everywhere else. 3596613]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KICAMXZAK2JFAAR9BVDA3L44GEABVRT2K6LWXUZHKSPRMAKUAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F1A/D73/F1AD73F4DD3D47938042F0A995430E3B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>84</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EU privacy law]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EU GDPR]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ General Data Protection Regulation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook GDPR]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook user data]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/free-airline-apple-costs-woman-500-after-she-doesn-t-declare-it-3596598</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Free airline apple costs woman $500 after she doesn't declare it 3596598]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DENVER — A Colorado woman is mad after she was fined $500 for bringing an apple into the U.S.

According to Fox News, Crystal Tadlock was returning from France when the crew on her Delta flight handed out apples. Not hungry, Tadlock kept hers for later.  

Her carry-on luggage was selected for search at the airport, and a customs agent found the apple and fined her $500. 

Despite the fruit coming from an airline, U.S. Borders and Customs says all incoming agricultural items must be declared.

According to Fox 31 Denver, Tadlock plans on fighting the fine in court. 3596598]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKWKCTSA5ARCARUBBJAX7DYG2LVTS32A6LWMHAGKBPAPWTZLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/50D/D4D/50DD4D9B80824280A1379EE1A81DE66E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apples]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ usa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ customs and borders protection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bringing food into the us]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline snacks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us customs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us customs stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delta airlines]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/air-india-hits-rough-turbulence-injures-3-passengers-3596594</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Air India hits rough turbulence, injures 3 passengers 3596594]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMRITSAR, INDIA — An Air India flight from Amritsar to New Delhi last week experienced turbulence that left three passengers injured and caused a window panel to come loose. 
Air India Flight 462 was carrying over 240 passengers on April 19 for the 35-minute flight to the nation's capital, the Hindu reported. 

Airline officials said the plane took off at 2:50 p.m. and hit rough turbulence soon after at around 15,000 feet due to bad weather. 

The turbulence lasted for around 10-12 minutes. Three passengers sustained minor injuries and were treated at the Delhi Airport.

A window panel inside the aircraft also came loose during the turbulence, the officials said. 

India's aviation regulator, the Directorate General of Civil Aviation, and the Aircraft Accident Investigation Board are now investigating the incident. 3596594]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFEYKTKRDFMB3HLNKF7LDWNBJBRE35A2IATUCTAIGRIBCZKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/291/47F/29147F4CB170456E8CE09A70A6B12684.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Air India flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Air India flight turbulence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Air India turbulence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flight turbulence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Air India window panel]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/startup-plans-to-make-all-of-earth-viewable-in-real-time-3596557</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Startup plans to make all of Earth viewable, in real-time 3596557]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — A new startup backed by Bill Gates plans on developing a 500-strong satellite constellation that will make all of Earth viewable.

According to the Wall Street Journal, startup EarthNow plans to create a constellation of 500 half-ton satellites that will be launched in phases. Airbus, an investor in the company, will develop the satellites. EarthNow says these will use an upgraded version of the OneWeb microsatellite platform.

A press release from the company says each satellite unprecedented levels of processing power and more CPU than other commercial satellites. EarthNow says the satellites use 'machine-learning' to adapt and interpret what they are observing in real-time.

The company says the constellation will be used to monitor many areas, including: conflict zones, evolving storms, volcanic eruptions and illegal fishing. EarthNow also reckons the constellation could also be used to help media tell stories, for crop health evaluation, whale tracking and creating instant 3D models of towns or cities. 3596557]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABJAIY3TABIFIAKHBJLRZ6LSGICB5RZNAIDW5FICA5AFEVCVBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BD3/261/BD32618961334870B53FF93DA921D0A9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>118</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earthnow]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bill gates]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ softbank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satellite constellation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satellite network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth from space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ machine learning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial intelligence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ AI satellite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ machine intelligence]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gopher-tortoise-found-covered-in-red-paint-along-florida-road-3596530</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gopher tortoise found covered in red paint along Florida road 3596530]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LAKE COUNTY, FLORIDA — Florida's animal agency is looking for answers after a poor tortoise was found earlier this week near Orlando completely covered in what appears to be red spray paint.

According to Florida's fish and wildlife conservation commission, two people picked up a gopher tortoise on County Road 455 in the town of Montverde, about 30 miles west of Orlando. 

The pair then took the tortoise to a wildlife rehabber called Swamp Girls Adventures, the group took the tortoise in and named it Raphael, after one of the Ninja Turtles.

The group said they have been able to get the tortoise about 70 percent cleaned up after gently chipping away concrete and attempting to get the red paint off. 

According to FWCC, if toxins from the paint are absorbed, it can damage the tortoise's organs. The paint itself can also prevent it from getting nutrients from sunlight, and damagingly seal the tortoise skin. If the tortoise breathes the paint in, it can cause respiratory issues. 

Kim Titterington, who runs Swamp Girl Adventures, told FOX35 that the group hopes to help the tortoise recover completely and release him back into nature. Titterington also said she believes this wasn't an accident where the tortoise simply got too close to a painting site — someone intentionally colored him red. 

FWCC is appealing to the public to contact them with any information on how the tortoise ended up this way. 3596530]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVAAPAAHKJJRXACELMAWRKL4GZESRRT6ABJWTU3SK2MFKBZKAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/98E/425/98E4252CE1734E46AB1EEA3C618608CB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animals covered in paint]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spray paint animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spray paint tortoise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spray paint tortoise shell]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gopher tortoise florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gopher tortoise covered in paint]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lake county florida]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/keeping-livers-alive-improves-transplant-success-3596457</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Keeping livers 'alive' improves transplant success 3596457]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OXFORD, UNITED KINGDOM — Preserving livers in warm storage similar to body temperature rather than cold storage improves transplant success a clinical trial has found. 

Transplant livers are normally kept prior to surgery, however many become damaged and unusable as a result, according to the BBC. The findings were published on April 18 in the journal Nature. 

For the study, researchers kept donated livers alive in a perfusion machine, pumping the organs with blood, nutrients and medicines. 

The trial involved 222 liver transplants at seven European medical centers. It looked at cold transplants versus warm livers connected to a perfusion machine. 

The participants were randomly picked to receive a liver warm liver or one preserved on ice. 
The scientists found 50 percent less tissue damage in the warm livers. They also found that warm livers had a higher transplant success compared to cold ones. 

Only 16 out of 137 warm livers had to be discarded, compared to 32 out of 133 cold ones.

Researchers hope the study can help reduce the number of people that die waiting for transplants each year. 3596457]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLFKDCSARARPCA9BSPFRLDVGZAB5RKZAZDFMHKXAVFWPWZHAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A76/AA6/A76AA6589CE34203B4E4F6E3D5FCF685.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver transplants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm liver transplants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ perfusion machine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver perfusion machine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver transplant success]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver transplant failure]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-put-human-brain-in-mouse-rodent-still-dumb-af-3596426</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists put human brain in mouse, rodent still dumb AF 3596426]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LA JOLLA, CALIFORNIA — Scientists have successfully implanted baby mice with human brain cells, according to new research.

The findings were published in the journal Nature Biotechnology. The research could lead could potentially lead to new treatments for patients suffering from brain damage or brain disorders, according to the Salk Institute —  where the research was carried out.

Newsweek reports that researchers took brain cells from human fetuses, turned them fluorescent green and put them inside the brains of mice. 

Researchers also placed small plastic windows placed over animals' skulls to track how the human cells developed in their new environment. This was observed over a period of several months and human brain cells were observed to outnumber the mice brain cells in some areas, reports Newsweek. 3596426]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJLACDRAASKRKVTDB5DAZ7SCNEEB3FC5AAAWPHTRKFPFAAZFKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8C4/C1E/8C4C1EB75B654D71A3E8CBC685DCD944.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-24T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human brain in animal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human brain mice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mouse brain human]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weird science experiments]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mouse gets human brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ salk institute]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal experiments]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/police-tried-to-use-dead-man-s-finger-to-unlock-phone-3597678</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Police tried to use dead man's finger to unlock phone 3597678]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LARGO, FLORIDA — Florida authorities are now under fire for recently going to a funeral home and used a dead man's finger to try to unlock his phone as part of their investigation.

According to Tampa Bay Times, 31-year-old Linus Phillip was killed by Largo police after attempting to drive away before an officer could search him.

When Phillip's wife was at Sylvan Abbey Funeral Home in Clearwater mourning over the death of her husband, two detectives showed up with her husband's phone. 

The detectives were hoping to unlock the phone with Phillip's hand to get more information about a drug case that's linked with him. 

However, this didn't work.

Several legal experts said it was okay for the cops to do this as there's no privacy after death. However, Phillip's family said they were disrespected and disturbed by the police's actions.

Charles Rose, a professor at Stetson University College of Law told the Tampa Bay Times that dead men certainly don't have rights, but using a corpse at a funeral home for the drug case is questionable. 3597678]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABLFACCTAZBAPWZ7L2JRK9LWGZEV7UTRLSIF7TALA5ARKBAFBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/613/152/6131526638F04D1F92E9E5388117C121.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unlock phone with fingerprint]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ finger unlock phone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to unlock a phone that has a fingerprint]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ funeral home florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ largo florida]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/10-000-poached-radiated-tortoises-found-in-madagascar-house-3597606</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[10,000 poached radiated tortoises found in Madagascar house 3597606]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOLIARA, MADAGASCAR — Madagascar officials have arrested three people in southwestern Madagascar for a case of animal poaching after finding over 10,000 tortoises cramped inside a house. 

When authorities entered the house in Toliara, 9,888 of the radiated tortoises were alive and in poor condition, while 180 were dead.

Animal rescuers loaded the tortoises onto six trucks to transport to a wildlife facility. The process took several trips.

Radiated tortoises are an endangered species. There are about 3 million of them left due to the loss of forest land on the island, and animal poachers either sell locally as bushmeat or smuggle them overseas to Southeast Asia or China. 

Although the tortoises were looked after by a veterinarian, a week later about 574 of them had died from either dehydration or infection.

Two men and a woman have been taken into custody. The men were found burying dead tortoises on the property when rescue team arrived.

According to Turtle Survival Alliance, the tortoises left will be kept in captivity to keep them safe and alive. 

The rescuers think there’s a someone, or an organization behind the incident as they believe the house was just part part of a much larger operation, considering the vase number of tortoises that were poached. 3597606]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAFIYIDKADFEBCDL2LAK7U3MICERSZMLWPF3GCTK2NRIA3XKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BCF/F3D/BCFF3DD7BE9342999E5F003B3D2715FF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>85</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[animal poaching madagascar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[madagascar animal poaching]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[poaching in madagascar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[poaching radiated tortoise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[radiated endangered]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[animal poachers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/boy-steals-credit-card-goes-on-bali-vacay-after-fight-with-mom-3597525</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Boy steals credit card, goes on Bali vacay after fight with mom 3597525]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SYDNEY/BALI — A 12-year-old boy hilariously stole his mom and dad's credit card, tricked granny into getting his passport and jumped on a few flights to Bali all because of a fight with his mom. 

The boy was told by his mom that he wasn't allowed to go to Bali, so like any normal kid, he immediately hopped online and booked flights and a hotel room, according to the Guardian.

He then told his parents he was going to school, but instead rode his razor scooter to the train station, where he made it to the airport. 

He then used self check-in kiosk, jumped on a flight to Perth, and then another flight to Bali, the Nine Network reported.

When little man got to Bali, he checked into the Four Seasons telling the front desk he was waiting for his sister to arrive. 

His family had no idea he was living in up until his school and said he was absent. 

After quite a bit of hectic scrambling, they found out that he was in Bali, so his mom flew out to collect the boy. 3597525]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AFADRFKABACBRWKBKWZ6LUNABVRU33K6IW5TZDAEGR7DAKKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/257/6AF/2576AFE564594181B684642A31DE4D73.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy steals credit card]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy steals mom's credit card]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy goes to bali]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy flies to bali after fight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy goes bali vacation after fight]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uk-court-fines-youtuber-1-100-for-grossly-offensive-viral-video-3597507</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UK court fines YouTuber $1,100 for 'grossly offensive' viral video 3597507]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AIRDRIE, SCOTLAND — Scottish YouTuber Mark Meechan, aka Count Dankula has been fined 800 pounds, around 1100 bucks, for a making video he says was a joke.

This all goes back to April 2016 when Meechan decided to prank his girlfriend Sue. The Scots comic trained his girlfriend's pug Buddha to nazi salute to Sieg Heil and to react to the phrase Do you want to gas the Jews?.  

Meechan published footage of the canine to YouTube where it went viral. Some found it funny, some didn't.  Reportedly, he says the phrase gas the Jews 23 times, and that's the part people found offensive and the law took issue with.

According to the BBC, Meechan said  the joke was the juxtaposition of having an adorable animal reacting to something vulgar.

Evidently, Scottish authorities didn't find it funny. So much so, they charged Meechan with a hate crime. After a two-year court case, on Monday the judge found Dankula guilty of making a grossly offensive video that contained menacing, anti-semitic and racist material.  According to newspaper the Scotsman, the prosecution pointed out that the context of the video wasn't to be decided by Meechan, but by the court.

Meechan's joke was found to be grossly offensive under the UK Communications Act 2003, Section 127.  Specifically, the UK-wide law says someone is guilty of an offence that sends by means of a public electronic communications network a message or other matter that is grossly offensive or of an indecent, obscene or menacing character; or causes any such message or matter to be so sent.

What's deemed grossly offensive is left widely open to interpretation. The judge, in this case, fined Meechan around $1100.

Meechan received support from all fields, including from comedian Ricky Gervais, satirist Jonathan Pie, YouTuber Philip Defranco as well as writer and activist Maajid Nawaaz, Infowars's Alex Jones and also ex-English Defence League leader Tommy Robinson. 3597507]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DFAD3WKZBAAWTHBBLR39BCGSLVRUTRA6LFZGZKKBNWKVZFKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/878/9FF/8789FF85ED5AC1E7A1AB6095CB5D45B3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>169</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mark meechan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ count dankula]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ricky gervais]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nazi pug]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ free speech in the uk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ count dankula trial]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ count dankula sentence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ maajid nawaz]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ section 127 communications act 2003]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ free speech uk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ freedom of expression]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-ant-species-explodes-its-butt-when-their-colony-is-threatened-3597269</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New ant species explodes its butt when their colony is threatened 3597269]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE COLONY — Research published in the journal ZooKeys tells of a new species of exploding ant found in South East Asia's jungles.

Called Colobopsis explodens, the ant's body is filled with sacs of deadly toxic substance. They are minor workers in colonies.

A lead researcher in the study told the Washington Post, that these ants attack threats to their nests by biting them, and then moving their posterior toward its body.

The ants will flex their muscles so hard that their skin will burst and release the fluid all over the threat. Next, the threat would meet these massively insects. These are the colonies' major workers and act as the second line of defense.

They remained unknown until now because scientists simply didn't know until recent years know how many types of exploding ants there are, according to the Post. Earlier research in ZooKeys reckons there maybe at least 15 kinds, including Colobopsis explodens. 3597269]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLRIDZBA6LAADAXLZDR7LDVMRCSKSC5KSJRXHADK5GRKCRABB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D1B/3F5/D1B3F538385748D8932CBBB9751C6775.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>116</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exploding ants exploding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exploding ants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exploding ants in action]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colobopsis explodens]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exploding ants vs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nature]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ant colony defense]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ major ant workers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ minor ant workers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ queen ant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ant nest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ant colony]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/giant-plastic-collector-to-pick-up-great-pacific-garbage-patch-3597235</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Giant plastic collector to pick up Great Pacific Garbage Patch 3597235]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALAMEDA, CALIFORNIA — The Ocean Cleanup is building a giant plastic-scooping system in Alameda, California and plans to set sail as early as this summer to begin cleaning up the Great Pacific Garbage Patch.  

The Great Pacific Garbage Patch has an estimated 1.8 trillion pieces of plastics brought there by ocean currents and is roughly three times the size of France, according to an article published in Scientific Reports. 

The Ocean Cleanup, started by 23-year-old Boyan Slat, has designed a massive 2,000-foot long, floating tube that will serve as a barrier to trap plastic.

It’s made from HDPE plastic and is flexible enough to bend with the waves, but rigid enough to form a U-shaped barrier to trap floating plastics pollution, according to Fast Company. 

A nylon screen is attached underneath to catch plastics, but not be a threat to marine life. 

Large floating anchors, hundreds of feet below the surface, help steady the device so it moves slower in the current than the plastic, making it possible to pick up the garbage in front of the device. 

Ocean Cleanup spokesperson Joost Dubois said that when the final systems are sent out to the Pacific ocean, there will be 60 floating scoops in total. 

Boats will come every six to eight weeks to collect the plastics and take them to shore to be recycled. 3597235]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAWAACXKEBA7BARL5DWZ7JGMICS7RK7KVDAZTIEKZFAMVCWAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D1B/3F5/D1B3F538385748D8932CBBB9751C6775.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-25T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Ocean Cleanup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Great Pacific Garbage Patch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ocean plastics pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[giant plastics collector]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[microplastics pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[plastics cleanup]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kangaroo-dies-after-zoo-visitors-hurl-rocks-to-force-it-to-jump-3598082</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kangaroo dies after zoo visitors hurl rocks to force it to jump 3598082]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FUZHOU, CHINA — A 12-year-old female kangaroo in a zoo in southeastern China died after visitors had hurled rocks at her because of one thing — she wasn't jumping enough.

According to Chinese media, the 12-year-old female kangaroo was not hopping enough to amuse visitors at the Fuzhou Zoo in March. 

To make her hop, some made-in China genius decided to hurl rocks at the kangaroo, and when zookeepers showed up to stop the hurling, her left foot was nearly severed. The zookeeper tried to stop the crowd, but the crowd denied they had done such a thing.

The kangaroo was later seen lying battered and hooked to an ivy drip in its enclosure, and the poor thing later died due to internal bleeding.

Veterinarians discovered after the autopsy that one of the stones had ruptured the animal's kidney. 

For unknown reasons, the zoo said they plan to stuff and display the dead kangaroo.

This didn't stop these idiots from hurting the animals. Few weeks after the incident, a five-year-old male kangaroo luckily survived an injury caused by you-know -who.

The Fuzhou zookeepers stressed that these actions are against the rights of the animal and somehow people just don't get it and keep hurting them. The zoo now plans to install more security cameras hoping to prevent anything like this from happening again. 3598082]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KABRMAACKFPAABKDBJJFXK2HMWLV7RC6KRAWXURGKSNWXBAAAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2A8/956/2A8956AB37EE40C68B752A32BE26CBDE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>80</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ throw rocks kangaroo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese zoo kangaroo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese zoo visitors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese zoo visitors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocks kangaroo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fuzhou zoo kangaroo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fuzhou china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/aussie-scientists-find-new-dna-structure-3597987</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Aussie scientists find new DNA structure 3597987]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE GENETIC BLUEPRINT — Scientists have discovered a new type of DNA structure, according to research published in the journal Nature Chemistry.

The Independent reports that the structure has been sighted previously, but this is the first time researchers have found it inside living cells.

Normal DNA is made up of bases, coded as letters. These are adenine, thymine cytosine and guanine. Normally cytosine binds to guanine, and vice versa, but in the new structure cytosine was found to pair with cytosine.

According to the Independent, scientists reckon the new structure may be partly responsible for reading DNA and turning them into useful substances. Gizmodo reports they may act as a sort of switch for controlling gene expression, but could mean nothing at all. 3597987]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIARGCIAKNMRTACHLSKR59LRMIDETST7KSLR3GRBBREWEX32AD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CB2/CB7/CB2CB771D1C942FAAC00D11342D52774.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ i-motif]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new kind of dna]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna research]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna structure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ double helix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ double helix structure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gene expression]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna binding]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-nuclear-test-site-unusable-after-collapse-3598958</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea nuclear test site unusable after collapse 3598958]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOUNT MANTAP, NORTH KOREA — Chinese experts say the North's main nuclear test site has collapsed, which may be why Pyongyang suspended missile tests.

The South China Sea Morning Post reports that North Korea's last six nuclear tests were all carried out at the Punggye-ri testing facility under Mount Mantap.

During the latest test in September 2017, a bomb believed to have an explosive yield of 100 kilotonnes set off a powerful explosion. It caused an initial 6.3 magnitude tremor, and triggered several more earthquakes in the weeks that followed.

Geologists from the University of Science and Technology of China analyzed the region's seismic data and found that the blast vaporized surrounding rock, creating a 200-meter hole as the area collapsed in on itself.

A large section of the mountain ridge near the peak is also believed to have broken off as a result of shock waves.

Researchers from the Jilin Earthquake agency reported similar findings, and added that the collapse created a chimney which could leak radioactive fallout into the air.

Both studies concluded the testing site to be unstable and unusable.

The area is located close to the Chinese border. But while authorities say no increase in radioactivity levels have been detected, they will continue monitoring the surrounding region. 3598958]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6KRGXCWABJFAACCLMCR79LUMABSKRC7LWJFRTAEAVHACD3SBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FCE/C23/FCEC236A710D40C49883C83E1952BDE8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear test site]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear test site collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mountain collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mount mantap]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mantapsan]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/teen-has-to-wear-ankle-bracelet-for-posting-rap-lyrics-on-instagram-3598878</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Teen has to wear ankle bracelet for posting rap lyrics on Instagram 3598878]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LIVERPOOL, UNITED KINGDOM — A UK teenager has been charged with a hate crime for posting grossly offensive rap lyrics to Instagram. 

Last year Liverpudlian Chelsea Russell posted lyrics kill a snitch n**** and rob a rich n**** from I'm Trippin by Snap Dogg being to her Instagram. Last week that got her charged with a hate crime. The 19-year-old said it was a tribute to Frankie Murphy, a 13-year-old who was killed last year in a car accident. 

Russell told the court, many youngsters in Liverpool use the N-word to greet each other. An anonymous screengrab of her post with the racy lyrics was sent to the police's hate crime unit.

Officer Dominique Walker, a black woman who works within the hate crime unit, saw the post containing the racy Snapp Dogg lyrics, according to a news release from the Crown Prosecution Service. She told the court the Snap Dogg lyrics containing the N-word were grossly offensive and asked it not be repeated in court.

Officer Walker is the sister of Anthony Walker, a British teen who was killed in a Liverpool race hate murder in 2005. According to the Liverpool Echo, Russell told the court she copied the lyrics from a friends Insta, and that they were shared by thousands of people.

The judge found her guilty of sending a grossly offensive communication, under section 127 of the UK Communications Act 203

Sentencing Russell, the judge handed down the equivalent of a US$700 fine as well as an 8-week community order curfew, during which she has to wear an ankle monitor, reports The Liverpool Echo. 3598878]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6JFXDKWA5FAKBAWLMAAT9BGMBIE5RTZKJLW3HZKKAFRVXRHBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/27B/240/27B240023D6A4896863A8070EC9E3EEC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>115</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hate crime uk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ free speech]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chelsea russell]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snap dogg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snapp dogg i'm trippin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snapp dogg lyrics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rap hate crime]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uk free speech]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-solar-geoengineering-could-cool-the-planet-3598843</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How solar geoengineering could cool the planet 3598843]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE STRATOSPHERE — Solar geoengineering specialists reckon technology could cool the planet's temperature by using it to sulfur to the atmosphere.

Volcanic eruptions can cool the earth. This is because they emit sulfur dioxide, a UV repellent gas, into the stratosphere.

Earther reports that millions of high-altitude balloons carrying sulfur may also be an option. Another option, according to Earther, maybe to use aircraft such as the stratotanker to disperse the sulfur into the stratosphere, as the aircraft can already reach the required altitude. That altitude is around 6 miles from the earth's surface. 

Citing a leaked UN draft report on global warming, Reuters reports the organization's climate experts opined that solar geoengineering could be economically, socially and institutionally infeasible. 

Harvard's solar engineering head Gert Wagner told Earther that deployment of solar radiation management tech would be unambiguous proof of our miserable failure as a species to act as responsible planetary stewards. 3598843]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6JAMYIFA6LWKAZVKFLRRL2CGJLV7ERQK5AA5TZDAZFF5DIGAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/69F/ADA/69FADA04DAA04E878EC7DC85FDFB0942.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar geoengineering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ srm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar radiation management]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sulfur in stratosphere]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geoengineering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geoengineering and weather]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stratosphere]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stratotanker]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/security-flaw-makes-every-nintendo-switch-at-risk-3598758</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Security flaw makes EVERY Nintendo Switch at risk 3598758]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DENVER — Hackers have revealed how all Nintendo Switches can be made to run code through an exploit of an unpatchable flaw in the console's Nvidia Tegra X1 chip. 

The exploit is known as Fusée Gelée and was talked about by developer Katherine Temkin from ReSwitched, according to TechCrunch. 

It makes use of a vulnerability at the silicon level of the Tegra X1 chip's USB recovery mode. 

The security flaw could allow for unwanted data to be exfiltrated, leading to Switch game piracy. 

The problem is the flaw is unpatchable as the issue is with the hardware on the Tegra X1 chips. 

This means that millions of Switches will be permanently open to attack. Only new consoles with the code fixed at the factory will be safe from the exploit, according to TechCrunch. 3598758]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJNFVAIIB5FRTBIWBWPRRLUWGZCSKET3A6LFMFICAVEFTDTSLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/938/17C/93817C213C464BDE87E07C8894DD194B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Nintendo Switch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Nintendo Switch security flaw]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Nintendo Switch Fusée Gelée]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ReSwitched]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Nintendo Switch hackers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-burrito-size-rats-feasting-on-chipotle-trash-in-brooklyn-heights-3598602</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Burrito-size' rats feasting on Chipotle trash in Brooklyn Heights 3598602]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — Rats are growing bigger by the minute from feasting on trash outside a Chipotle restaurant in Brooklyn Heights. This has been witnessed by the fast food restaurant's fuming neighbors.

According to the neighbors, Chipotle workers dump bags of garbage in front of the eatery at around 6 p.m. every day, and that gives the rats just enough time to eat before the garbage men arrive. 

A resident told the Brooklyn Daily Eagle that he sees four or five rats going back and forth from garbage to the building next door under construction, and he wonders how big the rat tribe has grown. And one construction worker told the Brooklyn Daily Eagle that he spotted a giant rat that was bigger than a cat, or the size of a well stuffed burrito.

Chipotle's manager said the ratzilla situation happened only after a new construction at a nearby location started. The manager also said she has seen the giant rats biting through garbage bags and they are particularly aggressive to passers-by.

Brooklynites are urging Chipotle to put its trash in ratproof containers. Who knows, maybe it's only a matter of time before these giant rodents move on to their next target — humans.

Prevent that from happening, a company rep told the New York Post that they will start using secure garbage cans to keep these hairy monsters away. 

The Brooklyn Daily Eagle reports construction inspectors found signs of rats at the site back in 2015, but received a clean report just over a year later. The developer did not comment on the recent ratzilla incident. 3598602]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIWCYCXARAFICRWL5AAT7DRMMABVRT5AWPRZTIKKSNAXA3VKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8F9/575/8F9575854BC14DA6A636AAB1DCE2D187.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>93</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chipotle rats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chipotle rodents]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chipotle trash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brooklyn heights rats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chipotle brooklyn heights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rats chipotle trash]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-your-gut-bacteria-could-be-affecting-your-brain-3598577</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How your gut bacteria could be affecting your brain 3598577]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Recent studies have been looking at the link between the gut, specifically the microbiome, and its effects on the brain.

A study at Kyushu University in Japan found that germ-free mice had more stress hormones than mice with healthy gut bacteria, according to BBC. 

This led researchers to look at treating depression and anxiety through alterations in the gut microbiome.
How could gut microbes be affecting and reaching the brain? One possible route is through the vagus nerve, the connection between the brain and gut.

Another possibility is that gut bacteria break down fiber into short-chain fatty acids that can have effects throughout the body. 

Brain disorders have been linked to the immune system, and with 70 to 80 percent of the immune system located in the gut, treating the microbiome could be vital to finding effective cures. 3598577]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABLAGY3TANJFPBZ9LNKAV9BAGVASRSRMAZAWPU3TANNAABAEAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3EE/5B3/3EE5B318FDEE41458F94667B0726BC78.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut bacteria brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut bacteria mood]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microbiome]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immune system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut health]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/is-dark-chocolate-the-next-superfood--3600015</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Is dark chocolate the next superfood? 3600015]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — Dark chocolate may be giving your brain, immune system and eyes some benefits, according to three recently released small scale studies. 

According to ABC News, in one of the studies, subjects were told to eat 1.5 ounces of dark chocolate, and then their brain waves were analyzed on an E.E.G. machine. 

Researchers found an increase in gamma waves 30 minutes after consuming the chocolate. According to principal researcher Dr. Lee Burk, gamma frequency is associated with neurosynchronization, in other words neuroplasticity …. It is the highest level of cognitive processing. 

In another study led by Dr. Burk, scientists look at the effect of dark chocolate on the immune system. 

Subjects were again given a dark chocolate bar the first week. The following week, they had their blood work analyzed. Researchers say they found an increase in anti-inflammatory markers and infection-fighting T cells. 

Neither study was published, and both studies only had 10 participants. 

A third study published in the journal JAMA Ophthalmology investigated the link between chocolate and vision. 

In two separate tests, 30 subjects were given two chocolate bars, both dark and milk chocolate, and conducted vision tests roughly two hours later. 

Scientists found that after eating dark chocolate, participants had small vision improvements. 3600015]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IAAD3VASJAGDCHBBIW57URMFLS5S3ZA6PW5G3XB5DAECIJKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0E0/481/0E04815F47500C1846B06B50057E5623.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark chocolate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark chocolate brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark chocolate immune system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark chocolate vision]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark chocolate health benefits]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/pregnant-woman-trips-young-kid-and-gives-him-a-concussion-3599719</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Pregnant woman trips young kid and gives him a concussion 3599719]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BAOJI, CHINA — A pregnant woman in northern China was caught on a surveillance camera last Thursday deliberately tripping a 4-year-old boy.

This caused him to fall and suffer a concussion. 

The woman was having a meal inside a local eatery at the time when the kid ran into the restaurant, accidentally hitting the woman with a plastic door curtain on the way.

The woman got so upset that she opted to trip the kid as a revenge. 

The unidentified child was reportedly taken to a hospital by his mother for a check-up, where he was diagnosed with a mild concussion. 

The woman later turned herself in to the police and offered to pay the kid's medical expenses. And she was given a RMB$158 fine, which amount to about 24 bucks. Due to her being pregnant, she didn't have to go to jail. 

The child's mother said she's relieved the woman didn't have to go to jail, as she has suffered enough from cyber bullying. 3599719]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LFPCIFAICRKVKFL5DAR6LUMFJBRUTRKWJR3U3WBWPA5ATWLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F3C/986/F3C9860356CEF28E9AAFAC3751E38B3D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant woman trips kid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman trips kid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kid tripped]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ child tripped by woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant chinese woman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baoji china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-1992-plan-to-fight-climate-change-with-firepower-3599670</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The 1992 plan to fight climate change with firepower 3599670]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — U.S. researchers once devised a plan to cool the planet by firing artillery shells laced with alumina into the stratosphere.

In 1992, researchers for the National Academy of Science published geoengineering options that included artillery shells containing UV-reflective alumina and 16-inch naval rifles.

The plan would've seen these massive 1-ton shells half filled with alumina and half-filled with dispersal mechanisms and other materials. The scenario would see 40 10-barrel stations located on empty land areas or at sea due to noise, firing 5 shots per hour, for 24 hours a day for 250 days of the year.

The scenario also envisaged the naval rifle firing a projectile containing alumina into the stratosphere. Once there it there it would disperse the substance. Alumina, like sulfur dioxide, can  also reflect ultraviolet light.

The academy's Committee on Science, Engineering and Public Policy drafted the plan in a 1992 publication titled 'Policy Implications of Greenhouse Warming: Mitigation, Adaptation, and the Science Base'. 3599670]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAWPDKTKVCRCB3CBJKRI6DVGFJS3FKSKIDAXHACKNQWVVRBAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C86/985/C869858F4860C396E22399599B3A2876.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>95</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geoengineering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar geoengineering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artillery shells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alumina]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aluminium dioxide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar radiation management]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aluminium oxide]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-alexa-new-features-encourages-kids-to-be-polite-3599612</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon Alexa new features encourages kids to be polite 3599612]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE, WASHINGTON — Amazon has developed a new version of Alexa — its AI-powered voice assistant — to encourage children to say 'please' and 'thank you' when giving a command. 

Based on a research done by Childwise, kids who are used to shouting orders at Alexa, Google Assistant or other virtual assistants might become aggressive when they interact with other humans.

The research team said the kids they talked to said they never say please or thank you when talking to their devices.

The new feature encourages kids to say please and thank you, this will prompt Alexa to reply with various responses like thank you for asking so nicely or you're welcome. 

The free version of the FreeTime service offers functions like set bedtime hours, switching off certain services like voice-purchasing, and block songs with explicit lyrics.

If you're willing to pay $2.99 per month, you will have more functions like alarms with the voices of well-known cartoon characters, access to a huge selection of child-focused audio books, and exclusive use of software from Disney and National Geographic.

Alexa's voice-recognition software has also been updated to react to children's high-pitched voice, and it will be able to respond to Awexa for kids who can't yet pronounce the letter L.

The politeness feature is only available for Echo Dot owners that have the FreeTime function enabled. However, Amazon said they will evaluate and see if it's something people want to have on the main Alexa experience. 3599612]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AWXCRFKVERMVRVBWJAI744MZBETS35K5BWZHAEA6QRVDZHAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CD4/827/CD4827E5199E146141F0024F5350B833.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon alexa please]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon alexa updates]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon alexa children]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alexa kids]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alexa kids skills]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alexa please]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon echo dot alexa]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hackers-can-create-a-master-key-to-unlock-millions-of-hotel-rooms-3599551</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hackers can create a master key to unlock millions of hotel rooms 3599551]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HELSINKI — Finnish security researchers have found a way to gain access to entire buildings and hotel chains — all it takes is one keycard.

According to a press release from data security firm F-Secure, two of the company's consultants discovered a software vulnerability in Vision by VingCard electronic lock systems, which is used in millions of hotel rooms worldwide.

The pair wanted to find out if it's possible to open an electronically locked room without leaving a trace, and developed their own software to hack into the keycards.

They found that information from a single keycard, even an expired and discarded one, can be scanned and copied using a small device.

With custom software, it takes only a minute to decode the card and generate a master key, which can bypass any lock, allowing unrestricted access to any hotel or facility.

The two consultants have since worked with lock manufacturer Assa Abloy to fix the software flaw with an update, which was made available to hotels last February. 3599551]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NRIXAFB6LFIBZVBWJA5LSCNFJSIEAMAJIA3TZAARGRTDACKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F00/D6B/F00D6BAC8E0D42DC97993CC17BA11B8D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ master key hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hackers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ keycard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ key card]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hotel security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hotel keycard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hotel key card]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electronic lock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital lock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rfid reader]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-now-wants-to-deliver-packages-to-your-parked-car-3599535</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon now wants to deliver packages to your parked car 3599535]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMAZON LAND — Amazon announced a new service this week that can get your ultra unimportant purchases to you as quickly as possible — all you have to do — let couriers into your car. 

Instead of using smart locks and a cloud-connected camera to gain entry, Amazon uses embedded technology already in vehicles. 

The online retail juggernaut is partnering with GM and Volvo at first and offering the service in 37 cities across 'Murica. 

Packages that are too big or heavy, need a signature or are worth over $1,300 aren't eligible for in-car delivery.  

Sounds like an Amazon amazing plan. What could possibly go awry? 3599535]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIAFVYZAKREFGVKCBADW59BFNBJVRRKSKZDFZFKRAAAWVBRHKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6D9/428/6D9428E4D6645310C4E83CDCDD75317A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon delivery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon in-car delivery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Prime]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/young-girl-left-hospitalised-after-freak-accident-in-swimming-pool-3599480</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Young girl left hospitalised after freak accident in swimming pool 3599480]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SARASOTA, FLORIDA — Florida mother Lacey Grace is sharing her daughter's story in the hopes it will save the life of another child from dry drowning.

Earlier this month, 4-year-old Elianna Grace was enjoying some swimming time at her grandparents' house in Sarasota, Florida.

Elianna was playing with a pool noodle at the time, and reportedly put her mouth on the toy to blow when someone else simultaneously blew through the other end, causing water to shoot directly down her throat.

The child immediately vomited, but 30 minutes after, she appeared normal again.

Elianna later developed a fever that eventually subsided. However, a couple of days later, the fever returned.

When Lacey took Elianna to the doctor, she was advised to take her daughter to the nearest emergency room immediately.

Lacey said that Elianna's heart rate was running high, her oxygen level was low, and her skin was turning purple. 

A chest X-ray showed Elianna was suffering from inflammation and an infection from the chemicals in the swimming pool.

Elianna was diagnosed with aspiration pneumonia, also known as dry drowning, a condition that occurs when someone inhales water through the mouth or nose, causing water to enter the lungs.

Lacey says she read an article a year earlier about a Texas boy — the same age as Elianna — who died from dry drowning.

An updated Facebook post from Lacey showed her daughter in her hospital bed smiling and showing a thumbs up sign. Elianna now recovering at home and is expected to be fine. 3599480]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSIAMCZGASKAPVRWLZBFR94YGRCS7UT3KMDWMHICAEHWRWT3AC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1D3/8D8/1D38D83573E24056A1D2B10F1F1B6067.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>91</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dry drowning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dry drowning symptoms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dry drowning definition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dry drowning symptoms child]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ is my child dry drowning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dry drowning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dry drowning video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dry drowning definition]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mobilecoin-just-raised-30-million-for-mobile-payments-3599430</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[MobileCoin just raised $30 million for mobile payments 3599430]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — A new privacy-centric cryptocurrency called MobileCoin recently raised $30 million in a Binance Labs-led fundraising event. 

MobileCoin made the announcement in a blog post on Tuesday and said the entire amount is denominated in Bitcoin and Ethereum, according the TechCrunch. 

In a December whitepaper, Mobilecoin described the currency as an effort to develop fast, private, and easy-to-use cryptocurrency that can be deployed in resource constrained environments to users who aren't equipped to reliably maintain secret keys over a long period of time, all without giving up controls of funds to a payment processing service.

MobileCoin uses Stellar Consensus Protocol to record its transactions and will emphasize user privacy.  

The digital currency is designed so that mobile messaging apps like WhatsApp, Facebook Messenger or Signal can integrate with the MobileCoin wallet. 

In order to be considered a viable alternative, MobileCoin will have to compete with established mobile payment services like Venmo and Paypal. 3599430]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLWGCKUAMARKAAYB5DWX6JBMEDVXRK6A5DWZUTSKSPRVDAKKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BB1/6A0/BB16A000CB8D40D88D4FBC030648EB84.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MobileCoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MobileCoin fundraising event]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MobileCoin mobile payments]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ancient-swedish-massacre-unearthed-3600187</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ancient Swedish massacre unearthed 3600187]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SANDBY BORG, SWEDEN — Archaeologists have discovered the site of a massacre that occurred in Sweden.
  
Research published in the journal Antiquity details a 1500 year-old attack on the ringfort village of Sandby borg on the south-eastern Swedish island of Oland. To date, three of 53 houses have been excavated and the remains of 26 people have been found, including children. One of these contained nine bodies.

Those remains included mostly male adults, three children and an infant were found inside.

They were believed to have been slaughtered by raiders or a fire. Elsewhere on the site shows evidence of an elderly man who had fallen over a central fireplace. Researchers say he was unconscious or dead when he fell. The remains of various animals a horse, sheep, and a dog were also found on the site. 

Researchers found a plethora of weaponry including swords, spears and shields, as well as Roman currency and items. This part of Sweden was never part of the Roman empire, but was influenced by it. The study writes the massacre occurred during a period of great unrest and migration after the fall of the Roman Empire.  

The study notes that those responsible for events at the site may have been trying to establish themselves as a new local ruling elite. 3600187]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEBWCACULEDAACKDB6IA7KJHM2KSKS3ZKSLFMGACAZARPWK5AG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/174/2BA/1742BA49BB4E3B6D7A61C4D033DD6C5D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-04-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>121</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sweden]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sandby borg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sandby borg oland sweden]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sandby borg massacre]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient civilizations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient civilizations mysteries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient civilizations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ compilation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient history]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient haunted places]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ haunted village]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ haunted ancient places]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
