<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/los-angeles-battling-largest-brush-fire-in-city-s-history-3433751</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Los Angeles battling largest brush fire in city's history 3433751]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — Governor Jerry Brown declared a state of emergency in Los Angeles County on Sunday as firefighters continued to battle a 5,900-acre brush fire north of downtown Los Angeles. 

The fire, which began on Friday, has forced people out of their homes and shut down an interstate, CNN reported. 

The declaration will make sure state and federal assistance will be provided as fast as possible, according to the L.A. Times. 

Los Angeles Mayor Eric Garcetti already said the blaze was the biggest in the city's history in terms of acreage, the L.A. Times reported.  

Garcetti said on Saturday that 300 homes in Burbank and 180 houses in Los Angeles received evacuation orders, according to CNN. 

So far the fire has destroyed three homes in Tujunga, while two firefighters had to be taken to the hospital for dehydration. 

The blaze was only 15% contained by Sunday, with more than 1,000 firefighters now on scene.

There are 206 fire engines and nine helicopters dedicated to battling the blaze, Los Angeles Fire Department Chief Ralph Terrazas said at a Sunday press conference, according to CNN.

The blaze is believed to have been started by fireworks, according to the California Department of Forestry and Fire Protection. 3433751]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIWKCTXAEDRAC3CBJLW7LSAM6IBXUZQA6LR5HRKKBLFAWINBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C38/CE2/C38CE20E036303017BD97ACCAC3B3F8C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-05T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Los Angeles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Los Angeles brush fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Los Angeles La Tuna brush fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ La Tuna Brush fire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/unexploded-world-war-2-bomb-prompts-frankfurt-mass-evacuation-3433722</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Unexploded World War 2 bomb prompts Frankfurt mass evacuation 3433722]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FRANKFURT, GERMANY — Explosives experts in Frankfurt on Sunday defused a massive bomb — a remnant of the last World War more than 70 years ago.

CNN reports that the 1.4 ton HC 4000 bomb was found buried at a construction site close to Goethe University's Frankfurt campus on Tuesday.

The discovery prompted authorities to cordon off a 1.5-kilometer radius danger zone around the explosive. Over 60,000 people were evacuated from the area, which was home to hospitals, retirement homes, and the Bundesbank, Germany's central bank.

Dubbed 'Blockbuster', the British World War II-era bomb could reportedly generate an explosion capable of flattening an entire block.

Of the estimated 1.5 million tons of munitions dropped on Germany by Allied forces, some 15% failed to explode and ended up getting buried, according to the New York Times. Experts say over 2,000 tons of unexploded weaponry are found in the country each year.

Despite having a dedicated bomb-disposal unit, Germany's unexploded bombs remain a problem. The aging munitions could become more brittle and unstable, and are reportedly being spotted in harder-to-reach areas, reports the BBC. 3433722]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDWGXZHK5AWCCZVKBLRV6JGG2KB5R39AJLWRTAHA6LWMAIDKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D35/D68/D35D68B6F23E8847CF9004F6C8051F52.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-05T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ unexploded bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world war 2 bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world war 2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ german bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ british bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blockbuster bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hc 4000]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ explosion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ explosive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frankfurt evacuation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mass evacuation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cop-who-said-we-only-kill-black-people-gets-retirement-3433691</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cop who said 'we only kill black people' gets retirement 3433691]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COBB COUNTY, GEORGIA — A police officer set to be fired after he was caught on camera saying we only kill black people is being allowed to immediately retire instead.  

Lt. Greg Abbott was recorded on his dashcam telling a woman we only kill black people during a traffic stop on July 10, 2016, only four days after Philandro Castille shooting in Minnesota, the Atlanta Journal-Constitution reported. 

In the video, the driver appears nervous to grab her cell phone in front of the cop. 

But you're not black, Abbott says. Remember, we only kill black people. Yeah, we only kill black people, right?

The Cobb County Police Department had announced it was going to can Abbott last Thursday.

Abbott sent in a request to retire, and on Friday, Cobb County announced his request for immediate retirement was approved. 

Abbott is entitled to his full benefits, even if he would have been fired. 3433691]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KFKCZFARDRCAZXLZCRXLDRGREVXEAMKWPWXHICKBIAKWIBAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E5E/B6F/E5EB6FF93BEE4FC296B7EAF470063A16.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-05T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police dashcam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police officer caught on camera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cop caught on camera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Lt. Greg Abbott retirement]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-makes-atomic-boom-boom-again--3433612</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea makes atomic boom boom. Again. 3433612]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — North Korea conducted its sixth and most powerful nuclear test at the underground Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility on Sunday.

According to the U.S. Geological Survey, the underground explosion resulted in a 6.3 magnitude earthquake. Estimates put its explosive yield at 120 kilotons, reported 38 North.

There is speculation this weekend's test bomb will form the warhead component of the Hwasong-14, North Korea's inter-continental ballistic missile. This ICBM can reportedly hit Alaska. 3433612]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2JRGXZEANIWCCTEBAAR5LUSMFLV5EZQKIDR5URCKZFAVAZFAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F03/256/F0325638282CE2F050FA1CC2A814DD2B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-05T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>119</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North korea missile test latest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hwasong 14]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dprk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea nuclear missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[n korea explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[missile test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-selfie-app-could-detect-early-signs-of-pancreatic-cancer-3433575</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Selfie' app could detect early signs of pancreatic cancer 3433575]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Researchers at the University of Washington have developed a smartphone app that could detect the early signs of pancreatic cancer by analyzing users' selfies.

Bilirubin is a bile pigment produced when the liver breaks down old red blood cells. One of the symptoms of pancreatic cancer is jaundice, caused by an accumulation of bilirubin in the body.

The eyes are a really interesting gateway into the body -- tears can tell you how much glucose you have, sclera can tell you how much bilirubin is in your blood, Shwetak Patel, senior author of the study and a professor in computer science and engineering at the University of Washington said in a statement quoted by Medical Daily.

The BiliScreen app is used in conjunction with a 3D printed box that controls light exposure for the eye, or with paper glasses that helps calibrate color.

After the user has taken a selfie, the app's computer vision algorithms and machine learning tools can spot even the slightest increase in bilirubin levels in the sclera.

The app is designed to help people get early treatment if needed, however it cannot replace a blood test. 3433575]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIFVDZHAAEAKBRTB6PAV72GNFKSRSINA5BW5GTXAJLAVVKXKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/488/FCD/488FCD5B77ACD52D028C787E15631F12.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-05T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biliscreen app selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie app detects pancreatic cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medical app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pancreatic cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer screening]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer detection app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ university of washington]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/super-mario-s-not-been-a-plumber-for-a-long-time-says-nintendo-3434498</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Super Mario's not been a plumber for a long time, says Nintendo 3434498]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Everybody's favorite plumber, Super Mario, is no longer a plumber and hasn't been for a while, according to Nintendo.  Gaming website Kotaku reported the news earlier this week after happening upon the Japanese description of his Nintendo profile page. But despite this, it looks like he's at least keeping the uniform. 

KOTAKU
http://bit.ly/2eXPJTt

NINTENDO OF JAPAN
http://bit.ly/2wDIKqo 3434498]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNAPCTUBFIAPVKAB6LR774SMVDBVRILLSPW3UZEAVBFPAILLF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F4F/017/F4F017D59386189B2DE678F1D8B08FD6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-06T19:34:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Mario quits plumbing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mario retires from plumbing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mario plumber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super mario]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mario]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nintendo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plumber retired]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ princess peach cake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ there is no cake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tomonews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ news]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spectators-scorched-when-car-ignites-gasoline-mid-burnout-3434481</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Spectators scorched when car ignites gasoline mid-burnout 3434481]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA — Over a dozen people were seriously wounded after a car ignited fuel during a burnout competition in Adelaide, Australia on Sunday.

Friction from the tyres ignited the fuel, causing fire to spew from the wheels. According to Australian newspaper The Gold Coast Bulletin, 14 people were hospitalized. One person was critically wounded, according to Adelaide newspaper the Advertiser.

Organisers of the Red CentreNats competition stopped the event immediately after the incident. 3434481]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2IFEDAEAMCRCVZ7LEDFXKDUGMDV7RILKJJAXT3RBVFAZAZPAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F3B/FB0/F3BFB0841F1857BDC68B4A6098A72BAA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-06T19:34:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Burnout fails australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burnout fails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car burnout audience]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car burns out]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car burns people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burnout hurts people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mid-sized-black-hole-discovered-in-the-milky-way-3434473</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mid-sized black hole discovered in the Milky Way 3434473]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — New evidence has been found backing the existence of a mid-sized black hole, which was long-theorized to be the middle ground between single star black holes, and supermassive ones found in galaxy centers.

According to a the National Astronomical Observatory of Japan, a team led by Keio University professor Tomoharu Oka discovered a peculiar gas cloud called CO-0.40-0.22 near the center of the Milky Way that contained gas moving at vastly different velocities.

This, along with faint radio waves coming from the center of the cloud, suggest the presence of a black hole a hundred thousand times the mass of our Sun.

The radio signals detected from the cloud are similar to those produced by Sagittarius A, the supermassive black hole at the center of our galaxy.

The Japanese team hypothesized that the midsized or intermediate-mass black hole was formed from the core of a dwarf galaxy that had previously been absorbed into the Milky Way.

Scientists have long believed that giant black holes grow, in part, from the merger of small ones. So the discovery is especially significant since it's the clearest evidence yet of a black hole mass in between the two size extremes.

The team's findings have been published in the journal Nature Astronomy. 3434473]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6JRPXZFABIFMB3EBSJRI72CGFJERSRNLVAFPTAAK2IWCBZCAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/365/B8B/365B8B52695F9AFAC2C8641271E40F9A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-06T19:34:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Milky way]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ midsize black hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ intermediate mass black hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ singularity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ galaxy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nurse-arrested-for-refusing-to-draw-blood-considers-legal-action-3434464</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Nurse arrested for refusing to draw blood considers legal action 3434464]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY — The Utah nurse arrested after refusing to let a cop take blood from an unconscious crash victim wants to work on forging better ties between police and health care workers. 

The incident occurred on July 26 and was recorded on the officer's bodycam. In the footage, Alex Wubbels refused to let cops draw blood from a crash victim in a coma at the University of Utah Hospital burn unit, according to CNN. 

Though the man was not a suspect in the crash, police wanted a sample of his blood. 

Wubbels showed the police a printout of the hospital's policy on drawing blood, saying their request didn't meet the criteria. 

The policy said that before taking a blood sample, police needed either a judge's order or the patient's consent, or the patient had to be under arrest. 
 
The video then shows Wubbels being forcefully arrested for standing her ground. 

After sitting in the back of a squad car for 20 minutes she was released without being charged. Two cops have been placed on administrative leave pending an investigation. 

Online outrage prompted the Salt Lake City mayor and police to issue apologies to Wubbels. 3434464]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAWICACKIBRKBIXBJLRK6L4MRDEXS35AJKWTUTWKZBFCACYAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/47F/635/47F63550A592BDAB396C2B08072007E8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-06T19:34:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>119</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Utah nurse arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cop arrests nurse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police arrest Utah nurse drawing blood]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nurse drawing blood]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police bodycam]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/missiles-and-a-million-troops-north-korea-s-military-might-3434312</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Missiles and a million troops: North Korea's military might 3434312]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — Experts are assessing North Korea's military capabilities amid heightened tensions on the Korean peninsula following further ballistic missiles tests by Pyongyang.

North Korea is believed to have more than 1,000 missiles of varying ranges, according to the Telegraph. 

Military service is mandatory in North Korea for men and women, and the army has more than a million troops. 3434312]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5CFPYZFK5AFEBKDBSPARLDUMWIBKET6KACFVG3YBRBRABADKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/56B/073/56B073FF3A1AC158A65E8EF8DF8C5316.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-06T19:34:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>90</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dprk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea military]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea military power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea nuclear weapons]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/health-risks-high-gas-prices-in-the-aftermath-of-hurricane-harvey-3434239</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Health risks, high gas prices in the aftermath of Hurricane Harvey 3434239]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOUSTON — Hurricane Harvey may have moved on from the Lone Star State, but the damage it brought on Houston and other areas is still ever-present.

USA Today reports that Harvey may be the most expensive natural disaster to hit the U.S., with damage estimated at $190 billion, or a 1% hit to the GNP.

Gas prices have risen in the wake of Hurricane Harvey, as several oil refineries on the Gulf Coast were incapacitated by the storm.

Texans also face significant health risks from contact with floodwaters, which are potentially contaminated with bacteria from compromised wastewater facilities, and chemicals from toxic Superfund sites, according to the Washington Post.

Public water systems are likewise affected, and have rendered thousands of people with no access to safe drinking water. Residents are being advised to boil water before drinking, or to just use bottled water.

Massive flooding in homes and businesses may also cause mold growth, which in turn may exacerbate existing health issues.

Relief efforts are pouring in, but even so, the state's road to recovery looks to be long and slow, especially as floods in some parts of the state have yet to subside. 3434239]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2KWCYIEAZDFAVKHKFJR57LUGVCB3SRIK6KFXTIGAIARZB3WLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C45/632/C45632F41255D9368CE44D973DFD9630.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-06T19:34:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane harvey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[houston]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[texas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[flood]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[flooding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[floodwater]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[toxic chemical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[superfund]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[gas prices]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[mold]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[black mold]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[flood damage]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/burning-man-participant-dies-after-running-into-iconic-fire-ceremony-3434221</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Burning Man participant dies after running into iconic fire ceremony 3434221]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BLACK ROCK DESERT, NEVADA — Nevada authorities are investigating the death of a Burning Man participant who died hours after rushing past security and into the festival's iconic fire ceremony Saturday night.

According to the Burning Man website, the nine-day Burning Man festival ends with the burning of a towering 40-foot effigy made of wood. Past attendees have tried to run into the flames as a symbol of rebirth.

This year, a festival-goer named Aaron Mitchell, 41, broke through two levels of security guards protecting the area where the burn was taking place. Help was delayed as rescue teams had to avoid being hit by portions of the burning structure falling to the ground, but firefighters eventually pulled Mitchell out of the blaze.

Mitchell was immediately airlifted to the nearest burn centre at UC Davis Medical Center in Sacramento, California, where he was pronounced dead Sunday morning. The medical staff who treated Mitchell said he was not under the influence of alcohol, although a toxicology report is pending.

After the unfortunate incident, the Burning Man organization canceled scheduled burns through noon Sunday, but decided to proceed with the scheduled Temple burn Sunday evening. 

The organization has also made emotional support teams available for people who need counseling after the incident.

According to the Pershing County Sheriff, Mitchell was a 41-year-old US national who lived in Switzerland with his wife. 3434221]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFPXZIA5AFMVZSBMAW56JGGMBSZEC6AJIWTFABKEBRPAKRKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6F9/0D0/6F90D07D28AF4752BB9A4A120AF10C7B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-06T19:34:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Burning Man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burning man festival]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burning man 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burning man 2016]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burning man festival accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ burning man nevada]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nevada desert]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ festival]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black rock city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nevada]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/move-over-leto-leonardo-dicaprio-eyed-to-play-joker-in-origin-flick-3435382</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Move over Leto! Leonardo DiCaprio eyed to play Joker in origin flick 3435382]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GOTHAM — Acting megastar Leonardo Dicaprio is reportedly being eyed for the role of The Joker in an origin film about the Batman supervillain.

HOLLYWOOD REPORTER
http://bit.ly/2wGOGP9
http://bit.ly/2w5sZqj 3435382]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLFXCRDAAFAGD3FL5AR7KLUGEBETFCSKMBR3GKXK2LRCVRIKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CB9/EE8/CB9EE829137F4BD8338B734BE02C543E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-07T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>90</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Leonardo dicaprio joker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ leonardo dicaprio joker movie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ martin scorsese]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ todd phillips]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ batman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ superman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ joker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ joker origin movie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ups-s-poor-parcel-placement-traps-man-inside-his-own-apartment-3435355</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UPS's poor parcel placement traps man inside his own apartment 3435355]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBLIN, CALIFORNIA — A delivery man should leave your package either right in your hands or in a safe spot, and not trap you in your own apartment. 

A UPS delivery person unintentionally made a California man a prisoner inside his own apartment over the weekend when a package actually boxed him in. After discovering that he was unable to turn his door handle from the inside, Jessie Lawrence called his apartment's maintenance guy to help free him from this conundrum, SFGate reported.

Lawrence then realised that his door handle had been jammed by a package delivered by a UPS guy who left it inconveniently right under the outside door handle, rendering it unable to turn. Lawrence later recreated the set up and tweeted a photo of it to UPS.

Thanks to the power of Twitter, the tweet was quickly shared tens of thousands of times. Though the post has since been deleted, there are still plenty of screenshots floating around the Interwebs.

The tweet has also set off a series of responses of people sharing their own bizarre delivery experiences. Some debated whether the image was fake, theorizing the door could have still been opened even with the package stuck under the handle, as the door opens inward. While others were simply curious about what is inside the large box.

UPS Customer Support soon offered up a typo-filled apology to Lawrence via their Twitter account. 3435355]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKAIXZIAJKWEYAWKACWTKLUMEDERS3SKEAR3GRBAVBWCVIEKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2D6/5BB/2D65BB1B1D26DA8E79EA0DEB953EF024.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-07T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UPS]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups package handler]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups package handler job]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups package handler video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups fails compilation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups delivery driver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups delivery fails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ups delivery man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jessie Lawrence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Dublin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ California]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-hurricanes-are-classified-3435169</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How hurricanes are classified 3435169]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[U.S. — As Irma makes its way towards the eastern U.S., it has now been upgraded from a tropical storm to a Category 5 hurricane. 

Hurricanes are classified into five categories using the Saffir-Simpson scale, with the highest number representing the most powerful storm. 

Hurricanes are categorized based on wind speed. The wind speed is measured from an unobstructed area at a point 33 feet (10 meters) above the ground for one minute, according to the National Hurricane Center. 

The higher the category, the stronger the winds, and the more damage to be expected. 

Storms moving less than 38 mph are classified as a tropical depression, while those moving between 39 to 73 mph are considered tropical storms. 

In a Category 1 hurricane, wind speeds blow between 74 to 95 mph. Downed power lines, broken tree limbs, and minor home damage can be expected. 

With a Category 2 hurricane, wind speeds are between 96 to 110 mph. There can be extensive damage to houses and trees, while power outages can last for days or weeks. 

A Category 3 has wind speeds from 111 to 129 mph and the potential to cause devastating damage to roof decking and gable ends. 

In a Category 4 hurricane, wind speeds range from 130 to 156 mph and have the ability to cause catastrophic damage, with the possibility of leaving areas uninhabitable for weeks to months. 

The last is a Category 5, which has wind speeds of 157 mph and over. During a Category 5, there's a high percentage that a home can be totally destroyed. 3435169]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAARADICK6IRIDRTBSKA77L4M2JEXSRNKFKFVUALKIFRGATTLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/825/9DE/8259DE7173577C2AF9F63DEB79A5FECA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-07T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane categories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Category 5 hurricane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane categories explained]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/alien-hunters-detect-radio-signals-from-distant-galaxy-3435119</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Alien hunters detect radio signals from distant galaxy 3435119]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA — Astronomers last month reported detections of radio bursts from a far away galaxy.

Writing in the Astronomer's Telegram, scientists reported 15 fast radio bursts detected from a dwarf galaxy some 3 billion light years from our own. Scientists suggest the bursts may have come from a magnetar, which is a rotating neutron star with a strong magnetic field. 

Researchers also speculate that the bursts may originate from alien laser technology used to propel and power spacecraft, like wind powers sails on a ship, according to a University of California, Berkeley news release. That theory is similar to Breakthrough Starshot, an initiative aimed at propelling nanocraft to Proxima Centauri with Earth-based lasers.

Whatever they came from, researchers say that those signals began travelling from their galaxy over 10 billion years ago, when ours wasn't even 2 billion years old. 3435119]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSIFCAIGAZAARCARB6JATL4YGVABRRZLA2KAVHRHA2JAPAKYLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7E2/0C8/7E20C8CDCB6AF132B260FC3D09F04E64.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-07T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Alien radio broadcast]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien radio waves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien life found]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ proxima centauri]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laser technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ laser propulsion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nanocraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japan-preparing-for-evacuation-of-60-000-from-south-korea-3435014</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japan preparing for evacuation of 60,000 from South Korea 3435014]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Japan has started planning for a possible evacuation of the 60,000 Japanese citizens currently living in or visiting South Korea as tensions on the Korean Peninsula continue to rise. 

There are currently around 38,000 Japanese living in South Korea, while about 19,000 are tourists or short-term visitors, the Nikkei Asian Review reported. 

Tokyo is proposing four contingency plans: limit nonessential travel to South Korea, discourage all travel to South Korea, advise all Japanese to evacuate and encourage them to take shelter in place, according to the Nikkei Asian Review.

In the event of smaller military skirmishes between the Koreas, Tokyo would discourage all travel to South Korea, while concurrently urging citizens to leave using commercial aircraft.   

During a shelter in place scenario, Japan would need to work with Seoul. For example, if South Korean airports were taken out, the Japanese embassy would advise citizens to stay in place or seek safer shelter further south. 

South Korea has agreed to give Japanese in the country access to safes zones, such as designated subway stations, churches and shopping centers, a source told the Nikkei Asian Review. Tokyo has provided its citizens with over 900 such facilities. 

In the event flying is not an option, Japanese citizens could return by sea from the port city of Busan. Japan is currently in talks with the U.S. to have American forces transport evacuees to Busan.   

In response to Pyongyang's sixth nuclear test, Japan and the U.S. are looking to increase economic pressure on North Korea through an oil embargo and other measures. 3435014]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDWCXRGKEAFGAA9LMDA5KBBMIAVXFZMLVAFVH3SASIRMA3WKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5D1/D7D/5D1D7DDA87E372FED1A4685A279CA59A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-07T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Japan South Korea evacuation plan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Japanese residents South Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Japanese tourists]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sick-girl-uses-siri-to-rescue-family-from-hurricane-harvey-flood-3434983</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sick girl uses Siri to rescue family from Hurricane Harvey flood 3434983]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOUSTON, TEXAS — A critically ill 14-year-old girl in Texas managed to save herself and her family from Hurricane Harvey when she came up with the brilliant idea to call Apple's personal assistant — Siri.

Tyler Frank and her family woke up in the middle of the night on August 27 to find their home filled with water up to chest level, CNN reported.

To make matters worse, Tyler suffers from sickle-cell anemia[c], and she started to have what's called a sickle-cell crisis — parts of her body could not receive enough oxygen because her abnormally-shaped red blood cells were clogging her vessels and preventing oxygen from reaching parts of her body.

Stranded on their roof with water rising all around them, several failed calls to 911, and fruitless pleas for help on Facebook and Instagram, Tyler turned to Siri.

The first rescue helicopter arrived on August 28. The Coast Guard service team assessed the situation and informed the family that only the elderly were being taken at that time. Tyler used Siri again to call the Coast Guard, and thankfully, a rescue helicopter showed up for Tyler and her family early morning of August 29.

After being rescued, Tyler was first treated at by doctors in Pasadena, Texas, then she was taken to Memorial Hermann hospital and eventually back to Texas Children's Hospital, where she has been treated since she was a baby. 

Because of the hurricane, the Franks lost their home and car. For now, Tyler, her mother and her four brothers are staying in a room at a Super 8 motel off a Houston highway. 3434983]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZBRMYCVKWLWKXISLJIFXL2HNFIEXEAKAFPAXHZBAMDAGX37KH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/230/F8D/230F8D05551CD9F73013B85D2D4D3897.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-07T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>91</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Harvey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane harvey damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane harvey 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[iphone siri]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[siri responses 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[siri]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[apple siri]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Tyler Frank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Houston]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Texas]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/brazilian-war-photographer-revealed-as-con-artist-3436195</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Brazilian war photographer revealed as con artist 3436195]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INSTAGRAM — One man was such a good con artist that he managed to trick those who are supposed to be the most scrupulous about their sources — journalists. By and large, most people on social media and many in the media industry believed this man's false identity as a surf-loving war photographer.

Before being revealed as a con artist, the unnamed man went by the name of Eduardo Martins, an accomplished photographer who was not only handsome, but also a skilled surfer from Sao Paulo, and a survivor of leukemia.

Over the last three years, Martins said he worked as a United Nations war photographer, snapping events in the Gaza Strip, Syria and Iraq, where he has said to have witnessed the battle for Mosul against the Islamic State. 

Martins' photos were widely used by Al Jazeera, Deutsche Welle, the Wall Street Journal, BBC Brazil and image agencies such as Getty Images. In fact, those images were actually photos taken by other photographers who actually went to such war zones. He simply inverted the images horizontally with slight alterations. 

A BBC Brazil contributor in the Middle East named Natasha Ribeiro became suspicious after Martins contacted her. She later reached out to other Brazilian journalists working in the Middle East and learned that Eduardo Martins never existed. 

The UN and other groups whom Martins said he had worked for told BBC Brazil that Martins never worked for them, and none of them recognize his face. BBC Brazil later discovered that the images supposedly of Martins himself, were actually of 32-year-old British surfer Max Hepworth-Povey, who had zero knowledge that this was happening.

Once the con artist's work was called into question, he deleted his social media accounts and Whatsapp. However, before he went silent, he said that he was in Australia, and is going to travel the world in a van. 

BBC Brazil later learned that Martins had online relationships with at least six women, and none of them had ever met him in person. 

Although the con artist' true identity remains a mystery, what he did is arguably the most successful case of identity fraud after Frank Abagnale, Jr. 3436195]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AECFEDTULZDAPY3HL6LAI6LSNBJB5ET7LWIAZHCWKAAA7BK3AE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2C0/F8D/2C0F8D9744E9A731D4C88709CD010DED.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>136</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake news exposed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake news compilation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake photographer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fraudsters exposed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social media scams]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ scams]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram scams]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ war photographer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bbc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eduardo martins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brazil]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fake-russian-facebook-accounts-took-out-100-000-in-political-ads-3436092</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fake Russian Facebook accounts took out $100,000 in political ads 3436092]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Facebook says that is has uncovered a Russian-funded campaign to spread divisive social and political messages over its network. 

The company said $100,000 was spent on around 3,000 ads over a two-year period that ended in May 2017, the BBC reported. 

The advertisements did not support any particular candidate, but focused on immigration, race and equal rights. 

The ads directed people to 470 accounts that were spreading false news or were in breach of company policies, Facebook said in a blog post.

The accounts have all been shut down, according to Alex Stamos, Facebook's chief security officer. 

Facebook believes, though it cannot verify, that the accounts in question belonged to the Internet Research Agency, a pro-Russian group based in St. Petersburg. 

The campaign was discovered as part of Facebook's internal investigation after it was criticized for allowing the spread of fake news on the site in the lead up to the 2016 U.S. presidential election.

We looked for ads that might have originated in Russia, even those with very weak signals of a connection and not associated with any known organized effort.

This was a broad search, including, for instance, ads bought from accounts with U.S. IP addresses but with the language set to Russian — even though they didn't necessarily violate any policy or law.

In this part of our review, we found approximately $50,000 in potentially related ad spending on roughly 2,200 ads. 3436092]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNNRIDRJAFIAPYAWKFIFZKDYGMCV5R3RKJIW7HTRAZDFPCKZAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/299/212/299212BB647F75B3F6CDFB73C26C5162.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russian hacking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Russia-funded misinformation campaign]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook internal investigation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/boy-s-heart-stops-while-he-munches-on-a-hot-dog-3436058</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Boy's heart stops while he  munches on a hot dog 3436058]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ISTANBUL — A report in the medical journal Pediatric describes how a 9-year-old boy's heart stopped beating after he began eating a hot dog in Istanbul, Turkey.

He was later resuscitated.

Choking can lead to cardiac arrest in children, but in this case medical staff found the hotdog stimulated the boy's vagus nerve, which in turn triggered an abnormal rhythm that caused his heart to stop.

Upon further investigation and an electrocardiogram, he was found to have a rare life-threatening heart rhythm condition known as Brugada Syndrome.

The child was later implanted with a defibrillator to help regulate the abnormal heart rhythms via electrical impulses. 3436058]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KFECAFBZDACY3EBBJRX6DVGRDE5ET7KNIWXHRDAICWKWACBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/475/FE5/475FE5B84CC3DC6F2800A44356371C13.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Brugada syndrome]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot dog stops heart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cardiac arrest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart stops beating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/83-of-the-world-s-tap-water-contains-plastic-fibers-3436047</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[83% of the world's tap water contains plastic fibers 3436047]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — Plastic has not only been polluting the seas and oceans, but also most of the world's tap water, according to a new study.

According to an investigation by Orb Media, scientists tested water samples from a dozen countries on five different continents, and found that 83% contained microscopic plastic fibers.

The U.S. had the highest contamination rate at 94%, while Europe fared better at 72%.

The microscopic fragments are believed to be from clothes, plastic waste, tire dust, microbeads, and paint that have been flushed into water systems.

Synthetic fibers shed from clothes and carpets have also been known to contaminate the air and eventually make it to waterways.

Microplastics have been known to contain toxic chemicals, which could be released into the body when ingested.

Many studies have explored the impact of microscopic plastic particles on marine life, but none so far have focused directly on human health.

With the current state of Earth's plastic pollution though, someone had better get on it. 3436047]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KADRGDICLWLRICAWBJPFTKDSGVESTUTRAWJFZTAAK5ARCWREAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E5A/BC1/E5ABC10DE3B2FBBB77BBE1F1AA71D270.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tap water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contaminated water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contaminated tap water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic fiber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microscopic plastics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pollution]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/zika-virus-may-be-key-to-curing-deadly-brain-cancer-3436004</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Zika virus may be key to curing deadly brain cancer 3436004]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS — The Zika virus caused an epidemic of microcephaly in South America, but now scientists say it may be the key to defeating a deadly and hard-to-treat form of brain cancer.

According to a press release from the Washington University School of Medicine, glioblastoma is an aggressive brain cancer typically treated using surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation. But cancer stem cells often survive the treatment, and go on to produce new tumors.

The ability to create new cells is also seen in neuroprogenitor cells, which Zika targets and destroys. This prompted scientists to hypothesize that it may also be able to target glioblastoma stem cells.

Scientists infected tumors with one of two Zika virus strains, and found that both destroyed stem cells while bypassing other tumor cells.

Mice were then injected with either a saltwater placebo or Zika virus cells. Researchers found that those infected with Zika had smaller tumors two weeks later.

Mutations were also introduced into the Zika cells as an additional safety feature, rendering them still able to destroy cancer stem cells, but also easier to eliminate from the host body.

The findings indicate that Zika infection can be used to complement conventional treatment to eradicate the cancer. But though promising, the research still has a long way to go before it can be safely given the green light for human trials. 3436004]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMAAMXABLJJFCCATLEDW79UYGFJBZFANA6KWVFIGARARKV3TAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/20A/AFD/20AAFDADA587712FB60F8284F780999B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glioblastoma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zika virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer stem cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer cure]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spacecraft-as-thin-as-human-hair-will-clean-space-of-junk-3435974</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Spacecraft as thin as human hair will clean space of junk 3435974]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EL SEGUNDO, CALIFORNIA — NASA has awarded $500,000 for the development of an innovative new spacecraft that promises to get rid of orbital trash.

According to a press release from the Aerospace Corporation, space debris in the form of spent rocket parts, old satellites, shrapnel and other items are accumulating around Earth's orbit, which may make collisions more common.

To address this issue, NASA is looking to Aerospace's Brane Craft, a light, 3 foot-by-3 foot spacecraft that's thinner than human hair.

When deployed, the Brane Craft moves toward a piece of debris and wraps itself around the item. It then fires its thrusters and pushes back toward the Earth.

The spacecraft eventually lowers itself and the debris down to the atmosphere, where both are incinerated.

The Brane Craft is intended to be light and cheap enough that it can be sacrificed at the end of a cleaning mission.

But it may also have other applications beyond just collecting trash. The spacecraft is extremely fuel-efficient, making it fully capable of travelling long distances, perhaps to explore and mine asteroids or other space rocks. 3435974]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIBRPAAILFJRTDZ9KFPAK6JHMRCSRRRQKIDRVHCWKBLAADTXAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D0E/B40/D0EB402B4D4F62095F20E0EFF9FD478E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brane craft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space junk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space debris]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aerospace]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trash]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tinderella-ends-up-stuck-in-window-while-trying-to-grab-her-own-poop-3435779</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tinderella ends up stuck in window while trying to grab her own poop 3435779]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRISTOL, UNITED KINGDOM — A woman in Bristol takes the cake for most horrific Tinder date ever, after she had to be rescued whilst fishing her own poop out of a window.

On Tuesday, Liam Smyth started a GoFundMe page to help pay for his broken window, which got busted during the events of his memorable first date with the unnamed woman. 

In it, he relates how the evening started off romantic, with dinner at Nando's followed by wine and a Scientology documentary at his flat.

Things went awry when the woman took a dump in the bathroom and discovered that it wouldn't flush. Panicked, she picked up the turd and chucked it out the window into what she assumed was the garden. Instead, the poo fell into a gap between the window panes. Whoops.

Genius date decided she'd use her gymnastics skills to retrieve the runaway turd, and climbed headfirst into the gap. And while she did end up getting the poop out, she managed to get herself stuck in the process.

After trying to yank her out for about 15 minutes, the dude finally called the fire brigade for help. Firefighters came minutes later and freed the woman out, though not without destroying the window.

As replacing it is set to cost about 300 pounds, the dude has since taken his cause to GoFundMe.

His ridiculous first date story has raked in more than a thousand pounds on the crowdfunding site, and he says he'll donate the extra profit to two charities.

Of course, all the Twitterati want to know is when he and little miss poopy are gonna get together again. 3435779]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVBWXAIHLEHRRX3CBJJRI6JFGVDEXSKSKSKATFKWKZBAGAZELD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D12/3B0/D123B030263549035FADBAE969CF0710.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>87</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tinder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tinder date]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first date]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad first date]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first date horror]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ worst first date]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stuck in window]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ embarrassing date]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ embarrassing tinder date]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-would-the-u-s-conduct-military-battle-against-north-korea--3435715</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How would the U.S. conduct military battle against North Korea? 3435715]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON, D.C. — How would the U.S. military conduct a conflict against North Korea? 

A Washington Examiner commentary suggests that the U.S. would likely deploy large groups of its navy and air force to Japan, Okinawa and Guam.

A Stratfor analyst told Business Insider that they they'd also possibly maneuver submarines and ships closer to the North and target nuclear facilities through airstrikes.
Helicopter-deployed buoys would listen for North Korean submarines, which could be destroyed by more advanced American underwater craft.

Experts also reckon that the U.S. would not invade, but rather defend South Korea as the North Korean army charges the border. This scenario would also see U.S. special forces parachuting into strategic locations around Pyongyang for surgical strikes.

If, in the extremely unlikely scenario — North Korea hits Guam or another U.S. territory or ally — with a nuclear strike, the U.S. has the option to respond via land, sea or air. Most agree that the resulting American retaliation would lay waste to Pyongyang and kill thousands, if not millions. 3435715]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMARCXRJLNKWGC3ALSKF774XGEBS5U33LRDR3TIGAFIAABRJAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AD3/A4A/AD3A4A4E105AB0ADF8C3D591918041B8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Dprk v usa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[usa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[north korea usa who would win]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[south korea vs north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kim jong un vs donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/red-it-balloons-keep-popping-up-in-pennsylvania-town-3435699</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Red ‘It’ balloons keep popping up in Pennsylvania town 3435699]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LITITZ, PENNSYLVANIA — Looks like the police decided to clown around with the people of Lititz after they warned of red ‘IT’ balloons on sewer grates around town ahead of the new movie. 

The Lititz police department posted photos on Facebook of red balloons tied to two sewer grates along with a clownish message on Tuesday, the New York Post reported.

If you’re not sure why red balloons are scary, Google it. Oh sorry, we actually mean Google “IT”.

So, in Stephen King’s novel “It,” Pennywise — the scary-ass clown — happens to be a big fan of red balloons.  

In their post, the cops gave the prankster or pranksters an A for effort, but said they removed the balloons because IT ain’t funny.


Plus, police proposed people peruse posthaste Pennywise previews. They also advised the public to watch it with someone with the lights on and sound low. 

The movie hits theaters this Friday. IT looks pretty scary. 3435699]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AAMDAFLJJAKXZRBJPWZ74VMBKERRAILRAFRGAGKEBFPDT9LF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/078/37E/07837E1CA9EE481E82E399D77C89645A</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-08T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[It]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[It movie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[It 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Pennywise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[creepy clowns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Lititz Borough Police Department red balloons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[red balloons]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hackers-steal-personal-data-of-143m-people-in-equifax-breach-3437095</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hackers steal personal data of 143m people in Equifax breach 3437095]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTA — Nearly half of the United States has been impacted by a massive cyber security incident at one of the three largest credit agencies in the country.

NBC reports that credit reporting agency Equifax has announced that it suffered a massive data breach which compromised the personal information of 143 million Americans.

Stolen data included names, social security numbers, addresses, and birthdays. Credit card numbers of 209,000 consumers were also taken, along with the dispute documents of 182,000 others.

These personal details may well be used to engage in fraud and identity theft schemes, which Equifax was ironically in the business of protecting people from.

Hackers reportedly accessed the data in mid-May through a web vulnerability, and maintained access until July 29.

The data breach extends beyond the U.S., with Equifax saying data from people in Canada and the UK may have also been exposed.

Likewise, people who aren't customers of Equifax may also be affected, since the firm obtains information from credit card companies, banks, and other sources to determine a person's credit score.

The company is currently cooperating with the FBI, which is investigating the incident. They're also working with an independent security firm for extra protection. 3437095]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNJAICRJAWKAEAZ7BNPW7LBHGRASIUT5KFKWZHCYBRCRIACZAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/875/5D7/8755D79306BE0E765A5E729AFCDE5D89.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-09T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ equifax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data breach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyber theft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyber security threat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyber security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hackers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data leak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ identity theft]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/pregnant-woman-ends-her-life-after-family-refuses-c-section-for-her-3436978</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Pregnant woman ends her life after family refuses C-section for her 3436978]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHANXI, CHINA — Chinese netizens are furious over a pregnant woman who ended her life last Thursday after her family allegedly repeatedly refused to let her have a C-section to deliver her baby, regardless of the pain she was suffering.
When doctors examined the 26-year-old woman, surnamed Ma, she was already more than 41 weeks pregnant. They discovered that the fetus's head was very large, meaning it would be dangerous for her to undergo a natural birth, China's China Business News reported.

Doctors at the First Hospital of Yulin recommended to Ma and her family that she should have a C-section, but Ma's family refused and insisted on natural birth. 

In China, some surgeries can only be performed with the patient's family's consent, despite that, doctors repeatedly tried to convince Ma's family that she just would not be able to do it the naturally, but no no no, they apparently just wanted to have their way.

Even Ma pleaded with her family, begging for consent. Even though she was already experiencing pain from her pregnancy, her family refused the plead. Distraught and in excruciating pain, Ma later reportedly jumped from the fifth floor of the hospital, killing herself and her unborn child in the process. Chinese authorities ruled it was a suicide.

The incident has since sparked an uproar on Chinese online forums, with many questioning the family's decision. However, since the news broke, Ma's family has denied accusations against them, with Ma's husband claiming that he later did give the go ahead for the C-section. The hospital says as far as they know, no one from Ma's family gave their consent.

The hospital later released surveillance footage showing Ma kneeling on the floor, begging her family to grant their consent. In response, the family claims Ma was not begging, but merely kneeling because she was in pain, and that they did eventually give her what she wanted.

While it is not clear who's actually telling the truth, many Chinese commenters believe the family's lying. They believe the family is only trying to protect themselves now, and might even be trying to get some compensation money from the hospital in the process. 3436978]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEDAIXADKFKFAB3EBIAWT6JAMJIE5SCRKVAWTGCYANJAKCIGLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/08E/9B0/08E9B04FA89E4F442EFE9AF1D855AC07.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-09T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>121</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant women]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnancy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ c-section]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ natural birth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant woman gives birth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese family]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant woman in labor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant women pain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant women going into labor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yulin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sun-vomits-mammoth-solar-flare-knocking-out-hf-radio-on-earth-3436863</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sun vomits mammoth solar flare, knocking out HF radio on Earth 3436863]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — A massive storm over the sun on Wednesday discharged the strongest solar flare in ten years.

The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration says the X9.3 flare caused high frequency radio blackouts and navigational issues over the sunlit part of Earth.

According to NASA, solar flares take place when magnetic energy built up within the sun's atmosphere is suddenly released.

They impact everything on the electromagnetic spectrum, from radio waves to X-rays.[d] The energy released is equivalent to millions of 100-megaton nuclear bombs exploding at the same time. 3436863]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZDRCYIEKBIWKA3HBADR7KBFM6KVRSCRKNIAXUCTAECFGXZPBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/00A/41D/00A41D699395CC238128E7D41321E607.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-09T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar flare]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ x9 solar flare]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar flare radio effect]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ noaa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space weather]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-how-to-prepare-for-a-hurricane-evacuation-3436782</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's how to prepare for a hurricane evacuation 3436782]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORIDA — As Hurricane Irma makes its way toward the eastern U.S., residents have been preparing for the worst. 

In the event of an evacuation, here's what you can do to prepare, according to the New York Times.
Before leaving the house, make sure to pack an emergency kit with money, medication, a portable radio, flashlights and at least three days' worth of food and water. 

Designate a meeting spot with your family in case you get separated. Mobile phones may or may not work in affected areas. 

Make sure to photograph or scan important documents such as licenses, social security cards, passports, prescriptions and tax statements. 

Upload images online, so that you have backup copies. Store the documents in fireproof, watertight containers or bring them with you. 

The Food and Drug Administration suggests turning your refrigerator to the coldest setting, so that if the power goes out, items can stay cold longer. Even with no power, a freezer can stay cold for about 48 hours. 

Double check that dangerous chemicals like bleach, ammonia and drain cleaners are securely stored. Move electronics and small appliances as high up as possible. 
And lastly, clear the yard and board up your windows. Move or dispose of anything that could become a projectile if left on the ground. 3436782]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLFGYIDAEBWKBASLJPR77BCGIEBZE3ZKVAWRGRBAMBAMVIKKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/58C/715/58C7153F28DF924A4543C823FB5E0F11.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-09T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Irma evacuations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ evacuation preparation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emergency kit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane evacuations]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/seabed-life-doubles-in-ocean-warming-study-3436753</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Seabed life doubles in ocean-warming study 3436753]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRITISH ANTARCTIC TERRITORY — A team of British and American scientists investigating the impact of ocean-warming found that the amount of Antarctic seabed life doubled after a temperature increase of 1 degree Celsius.

Researchers placed heated panels on the seabed near the UK's Rothera Research Station on the Antarctic Peninsula, according to a press release from the British Antarctic Survey.

The panels heated the water a few millimeters above them for a year, with researchers checking in and photographing the area periodically.

Researchers found that the amount of sea life there had doubled after a rise of 1-degree Celsius.But after increase of 2 degrees Celsius, only certain species continued to grow. Encrusting bryozoan grew almost twice as fast under under the experimental warmer conditions.

Results of the study were published in the journal, Current Biology. 3436753]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIWKYZIAZCWPWA9L5DA5KLWMIESKRCZKNPAXUCWAAFRPWABKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7B0/E5C/7B0E5C30A35B71E66F2438A5EF02579B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-09T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antarctica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biodiversity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/circus-tiger-breaks-out-roams-around-burbs-gets-shot-by-police-3436566</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Circus tiger breaks out, roams around burbs, gets shot by police 3436566]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTA — A tiger shot and killed after wandering around a neighborhood and attacking a dog has been identified as a circus tiger named Suzy. 

The 6-year-old Bengal tiger was being transported by Feld Entertainment from Tampa, Florida to Memphis, Tennessee, CNN reported. 

Suzy somehow managed to escape from a transport truck carrying 14 of the big cats some time after Tuesday night. 

The company didn't realize Suzy was gone until after the truck arrived in Tennessee. They then contacted law enforcement.

Meanwhile, Suzy gave residents a pleasant wake up call around 6 a.m. Police received at least two 911 calls from people who saw her near an interstate ramp, according to Henry police Capt. Joey Smith, the Atlanta Journal-Constitution reported. 

The bengal tiger then wandered her way into some neighborhood backyards.

Brittney Speck woke up to a ton of police outside her house and her dog going nuts in the backyard. When she went into the backyard, she saw Suzy in a neighbor's backyard by a minivan.  

Speck then went to call 911, but while she was doing that, the tiger jumped the fence and tried to attack Speck's dog Journey. 

Journey was running around just as the police arrived on scene. Just as Suzy jumped on the dog, the police shot the tiger dead. 

Authorities have been in touch with the tiger's owners and the investigation is ongoing. 3436566]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2KFAYZEAMAFPCRSLWKAX7LRNBIEZFC9KMDWZGZEKIFR5BTYKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C3B/A51/C3BA513043A1D567CDC04F10A7A874B7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-09T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>84</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tigers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ circus animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ escaped animal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ when animals attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animals on the loose]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/missing-minnesota-girl-swims-across-lake-to-escape-captors-3438081</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Missing Minnesota girl swims across lake to escape captors 3438081]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CARLOS , MINNESOTA — A Minnesota teen has finally been reunited with her family after enduring 29 harrowing days of sexual and physical abuse.

The Twin Cities Pioneer Press reports that 15-year-old Jasmine Block disappeared on August 8, after family acquaintance Thomas Barker tricked her into coming with him to help with a family situation. At his home, Barker and housemate Joshua Holby allegedly restrained Block with zip ties before assaulting and threatening her with weapons.

A third man, Steven Powers, got involved two weeks into the teen's abduction, after he stopped by the men's home.

The three men repeatedly assaulted the teen sexually and physically, and also reportedly tried to kill her on multiple occasions.

Following  a close call with police, the teen was moved to an abandoned house in rural western Minnesota.

It was from here that she escaped, after the men went to get pizza and left her alone for the first time in a month. She knocked on several homes in the area before swimming across a nearby lake to get help.

She lost her pants and shoes during the swim, but was luckily found by a farmer, who recognized her as a missing girl and helped her call the police.

Barker, Holby, and Powers have all been arrested, and are currently being held in jail for kidnapping, false imprisonment, and assault. 3438081]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AABRMD3TKFLA7AIRLMAA572GMWJE5EZKLWPR3HZFKEFAXBRLKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7A2/FD7/7A2FD7BD1DAF1DF15C1F29F1EC82BA06.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-11T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kidnapping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ abduction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ assault]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ captivity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ abuse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ minnesota girl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missing girl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jasmine block]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thomas barker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ josh holby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steven powers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-woman-slips-out-of-cuffs-leads-police-on-crazy-car-chase-3438078</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Texas woman slips out of cuffs, leads police on crazy car chase 3438078]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LUFKIN, TEXAS — A Texas woman led officers on a high-speed chase on Saturday after she slipped out of her handcuffs and tore off in a police SUV. 

Lufkin police were responding to a 911 call about a suspected shoplifter on Saturday afternoon, ABC News reported.  

Cops chased down the suspect, 33 year-old Toscha Sponsler. They handcuffed her and placed her in the back of the police vehicle. 
While the cops went through her bag outside, Sponsler took off her seat belt, and slipped off her cuffs. She then climbed through the window partition into the driver's seat. 

Sponsler then sped off and led officers on a dangerous 23-minute car chase with speeds reaching up to 100 mph. 

Police said throughout the chase they could see the woman reaching for the mechanically locked shotgun in the SUV. 

The pursuit finally ended after a state trooper gave Sponsler a love tap to send her patrol vehicle spinning. 

Sponsler was taken to Angelina County Jail where she's being held on an $18,000 bond, authorities said.  

The Lufkin Police Department posted an edited video of several dashcam and bodycam videos of the incident to Facebook. 

Sponsler faces charges of escape causing serious bodily injury/threat of a deadly weapon, aggravated assault against a public servant, possession of a controlled substance, evading arrest with a vehicle with a previous conviction and unauthorized use of a vehicle. 3438078]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWJRADIHAFIA3BTALJIRVKJFMRASKEZIKVAFMUACKZDRRAIHLE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/25A/88F/25A88F80F57E6D260D20BD9375C5DE94.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-11T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police bodycam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police dashcam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Lufkin Police Department]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman escapes handcuffs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman steals police car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car chase]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/american-nuke-sniffer-deployed-to-japan-after-north-korea-nuke-test-3438922</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[American nuke sniffer deployed to Japan after North Korea nuke test 3438922]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OKINAWA, JAPAN — The United States and Japan have both deployed nuke sniffing aircraft following North Korea's sixth and most powerful nuclear test.

On September 3, the DPRK conducted a weapons test at the underground Punggye-ri Nuclear Test Facility, with the explosion resulting in a 6.3 magnitude earthquake.

According to Stars and Stripes, a U.S. WC-135 Constant Phoenix was deployed from Offutt Air Force Base in Nebraska, landing at Okinawa's Kadena Air Base on September 5.

Commonly referred to as a nuke sniffer, the aircraft uses external flow-through devices to collect air particles on filter paper, measuring them onboard for radioactivity.

The nuke sniffers are also equipped to collect whole air samples inside holding spheres, to be analyzed later on the ground.

The North's nuclear test likewise prompted Japan to send three T-4 jets to collect dust and air samples for radiation testing.

Japanese C-130 transport planes will also be checking for airborne radioactive gases, though the risk of the underground tests releasing toxic radiation is generally low, according to 9news. 3438922]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJRGYIABBLFKCITL6LFZ7DUMMEV7RCRKADF5UZGAFJF3DZAAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/78D/D35/78DD35F9C9F17BA77782865764DF8EC4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-12T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuke sniffer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ WC-135]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ WC135]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ constant phoenix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radioactive fallout]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear fallout]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radioactive test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hydrogen bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear testing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kawasaki T4]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ T4 jet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-exactly-is-a-storm-surge--3438793</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What exactly is a storm surge? 3438793]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORIDA — A storm surge is an enormous mound of water that accumulates and is pushed ashore by hurricane winds. 

It is one of the deadliest and most destructive threat from a hurricane, according to ABC News 

Storm surges are responsible for around half of hurricane deaths since 1970, according to the National Hurricane Center, USA Today reported. 

The National Weather Service only started issuing storm surge alerts this hurricane season. 

About 1,000 miles of coastline from Tampa Bay to parts of South Carolina could experience a storm surge. Forecasters warn of a 10- to 15-foot surge in the Naples area and 5 to 8 feet around Tampa, ABC News reported. 

Storm surge watches and warnings are not included with hurricane alerts because hurricane winds and storm surges don't always occur at the same place or same time, said Rick Knabb, former director of the hurricane center, USA Today reported. 

During a storm surge, people should evacuate, while for wind warnings, they can stay in place as long as the structures is stable and away from flood-risk areas, Knabb added. 

A storm surge watch is issued when there's a chance of flooding, while a warning is issued when flooding is expected. 3438793]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLRGXACBSLFAYKAKEAR7KBFGZCE7RRKABKAZGTWAADRXDZLBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C8D/11F/C8D11FCD1AFAED12B4B9FF874B37905D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-12T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[storm surge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[storm surge explainer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[storm surge warning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[storm surge watch]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/people-dressed-like-it-are-freaking-people-out-inside-movie-theaters-3438686</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[People dressed like 'It' are freaking people out inside movie theaters 3438686]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[IN THEATERS — The most recent movie adaptation of Stephen King's horror novel, It, broke box office records and raked in over US$117 million during its opening weekend in North America, coming in only behind Disney's Beauty and the Beast and Marvel's Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2.

Among the droves of theater-goers who went to see the flick were some who were dressed up like the film's titular character, thoroughly creeping out other fellow patrons. 3438686]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIWGDRJBIDAMDZVBIDR37SHGVEBKRK9K2PWRHAAASLAABK6KH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/24F/DC1/24FDC1792964BB4A870AB55342C5CC10.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-12T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[It]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[creepy clowns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[scary clowns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[horror movies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[clown makeup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[clown outfit]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-s-plans-for-second-hq-sparks-bidding-frenzy-3440110</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon's plans for second HQ sparks bidding frenzy 3440110]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Amazon has announced it was looking to build a second headquarters in North America, setting up a bidding war amongst U.S. states and Canadian provinces.

The online retailer will reportedly spend north of $5 billion on the project that could employ up to 50,000 people over two decades, reported the New York Times.

Potential American cities for Amazon's so-called HQ2 include Los Angeles, San Francisco, Salt Lake City, Austin, Dallas, Denver, Detroit, Memphis, Atlanta, Baltimore, Boston, Washington D.C and  New York.

In Canada, Toronto and Vancouver are speculated in the running as well. 3440110]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRARMYAGKJJFPWZWBJPR57SCMECB5RT5AVARZHIFASIAEBCWAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/768/4AC/7684AC9E834CB3D02D1F10018B8C5AA4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Amazon new headquarters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new amazon hq]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon head quarters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jeff bezos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ where is amazon new hq]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hemingway-s-six-toed-cats-made-it-through-irma-in-one-piece-3439817</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hemingway's six-toed cats made it through Irma in one piece 3439817]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KEY WEST, FLORIDA — All of the descendants of Ernest Hemingway's cats survived Hurricane Irma. 

The 54 six- and seven-toed cats along with 10 brave workers from the Ernest Hemingway Home and Museum in Key West are all okay, the New York Times reported. 

As Irma approached last week, a full evacuation was issued for the Florida Keys. Jacque Sands, the general manager at the museum, ignored the order and stayed put.
Sands said she felt that she had an obligation to make sure the cats and the grounds made it through the hurricane. 

She also knew that the cats would be her early warning system, as they would come inside once they sensed the drop in barometric pressure. The 18-inch-thick limestone walls of the house helped a little too. 

In total, 10 employees stayed behind and help look after all the little furballs during the storm. 3439817]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLAGDAHAWLRPAASLRDWZKDUGRDERU32KJLAZTCYKIDRTCRFKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/84F/736/84F73642D07BC15882F9BAA07930DE2C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Irma damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Ernest Hemingway's cats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hemingway's cats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[six-toed cats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma animals]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chicago-teen-found-dead-in-hotel-walk-in-freezer-near-o-hare-airport-3439581</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chicago teen found dead in hotel walk-in freezer near O'Hare Airport 3439581]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — A 19-year-old woman was found dead inside a walk-in freezer at a Rosemont hotel after she went missing from a party. 

Kenneka Jenkins was discovered in a freezer in a vacant area of the Crowne Plaza Chicago O'Hare Hotel & Conference Center and pronounced dead at 12:48 a.m. Sunday, the Cook County medical examiner's office said, the Chicago Tribune reported.

Jenkin's mother, Teresa Martin, said police told her that it appeared as if Kenneka let herself into the freezer while drunk and died inside. 
An autopsy was performed Sunday, but it's not yet clear if foul play was involved. The cause and time of death have yet to be determined.  

Police are now reviewing a Facebook video that appears to show Jenkins at a 9th floor party hours before she went missing. Authorities said they have identified most of the people in the video. 

Investigators have also gone over surveillance video and are talking to other potential witnesses. 

The medical examiner's office said it was waiting on toxicology results and further by investigation by police. Toxicology tests often take weeks or months to complete.

Jenkins' family, however, is questioning the police account of what happened. 3439581]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IAACKWANKAEWAXLIBAK74YMBIBRRAIAZBWRFALKIBFVWZAKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/689/7C2/6897C2808F20E53A71714430AB07CE41.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walk in freezer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ freezer accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kenneka Jenkins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kenneka Jenkins Facebook live video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Crowne Plaza Rosemont]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/powerful-hurricane-irma-sets-meteorological-records-3439555</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Powerful Hurricane Irma sets meteorological records 3439555]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORIDA — Despite recently being downgraded to a tropical storm, Hurricane Irma broke several meteorological records as it rampaged through the Caribbean and Florida.

CNBC reports that Irma began as a tropical storm, but quickly strengthened to a hurricane in the middle of the Atlantic. It generated the most accumulated cyclone energy by a tropical cyclone ever recorded — more than 18 entire hurricane seasons since 1966.

Irma clocked in 185 mile-per-hour winds for 37 hours, which is the longest time a tropical cyclone has maintained winds of that intensity.

It was the strongest storm to hit the Leeward Islands, the first Category 5 hurricane to hit the Bahamas since 1992, and Cuba since 1924.

It's also the first major hurricane to make landfall in Florida since Wilma in 2005.

The hurricane prompted the largest evacuation in the Bahamas, with 5,000 leaving the islands. Some 6.3 million Floridians were also instructed to evacuate.

With Irma and Harvey just days apart, 2017 also marks the first time the U.S. was hit by two category-4 hurricanes in one season. The combined cost of damage brought about by the storms may also be one of country's most expensive.

Hopefully though, the worst is over, especially since experts say September 10 marks the peak of this year's Atlantic hurricane season. 3439555]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKRIX3SA2IFAARXLNIRX6DXMBIEXFIKA2PF7TCWANLRCAZCBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B02/D71/B02D71B0E33C26CB8C6A22D4FF1609DC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>85</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[tropical storm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane harvey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[natural disaster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[bahamas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[caribbean]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hurricane-irma-literally-sucked-some-beaches-dry-3439482</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma literally sucked some beaches dry 3439482]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORIDA — Videos and photographs documenting how Hurricane Irma sucked water away from several coastlines have gone viral online.

The phenomenon takes place when a strong hurricane creates low pressure, which draws water into the core of the storm, according to the Washington Post. For the next few hours, or possibly days, the storm actually changes the shape of the ocean. 3439482]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KECAADZDK6KAIVZRL5CWXLDVG2KSZRT4K5AAZUABAICF7ARJKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FF4/BF4/FF4BF4FFFC1386FAD58C7FB3DBF9A7DF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[storm surge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[beach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricanes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[hurricane rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[heroes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Bahamas]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-sells-all-her-things-to-pay-for-pet-s-life-saving-surgery-3439470</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman sells all her things to pay for pet's life-saving surgery 3439470]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A dog owner in London is willing to give everything she owns just to save her beloved pet yorkie-chi Snoopy.

The Guardian reports that Dolly-Ann Osterloh met Snoopy, a yorkie-chihuahua, nine years ago, when she rescued him from a kill shelter in New Jersey. The poor pup had been abandoned by a family after Christmas, and found in a trash bin. Since his rescue, the pair have been inseparable.

But during a vet check up to assess Snoopy's breathing difficulties, he was diagnosed with mitral valve disease, and given only a few more months to live.

Poor little fella has had to take medication 11 times a day to help with his condition, and can only be saved through surgery.

Osterloh had chanced upon a pioneering treatment by a team of Japanese and French surgeons in Paris, that could reportedly restore Snoopy back to health. Problem is, the surgery costs an eye-watering 37,000 pounds and needs to be paid in cash. And even with her savings, a bank loan, and donations, Osterloh still came up short.

To make up the rest of the money, the 32-year-old former actress opened her London apartment for 24 hours and put all her belongings up for sale.

Thankfully, the tactic worked. Osterloh now has the money to pay for her precious pet's surgery, and may even have extra from her GoFundMe page.

Seems Snoopy is finally set for his September 19 surgery in Paris. Get well soon, buddy! 3439470]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6KWEXCWAZDFGVASKBJAZ6D3MRBERST4KSJRVTIGA6KWVBABAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5AA/F11/5AAF11393F64957BA65141985D80AE95.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>85</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mitral valve disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snoopy's big heart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snoopy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yorkie chihuahua]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yorkie chi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yorkie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chihuahua]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dolly ann osterloh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog heart surgery]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/height-could-determine-risk-of-getting-blood-clots-3439342</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Height could determine risk of getting blood clots 3439342]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MALMÖ, SWEDEN — Taller people might be at more risk of suffering a blood clot, according to new research.

The Swedish study investigated multi-generational data from over 2.5 million siblings of varying heights. It was published in the journal, Circulation: Cardiovascular Genetics.

Women shorter than 155 centimeters — or 5 feet, 1 inch — were at lower risk  of suffering a blood clot, as were men shorter than 160 centimeters — or 5 feet, 2 inches. Women taller than 185 centimeters — or 6 feet, 1 inch — and men taller than 190 centimeters — or 6 feet, 2 inches, were at a higher risk.

Deadly blood-clotting usually occur in the lower half of the body, but can also take place in the brain and lungs.

The lead researcher of the study suggests that height should be included in risk assessment for blood clots, just as other factors, such as weight. However, exactly how height and blood clots are correlated remains unknown. 3439342]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LFVD3VAVHAIARYBMDAV7DXGREEXRAQLWIWMHICKABAZVTSBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A45/21A/A4521AB4993F51D740C08B578D6DACF8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tall people problems]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taller people blood clots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood clot risk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood clots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ health risk of blood clots]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-delivers-her-own-baby-at-home-because-of-hurricane-irma-3439335</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman delivers her own baby at home because of Hurricane Irma 3439335]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MIAMI — A woman delivered her own baby at home because paramedics were stuck during Hurricane Irma. 

The pregnant woman was at her home in Little Haiti on Sunday morning, the Miami Herald reported. 

Paramedics were unable to head out during the hurricane, so a dispatcher had to walk the woman through delivering her baby over the phone, Assistant Fire Chief Eloy Garcia said, according to the Miami Herald. 

We weren't able to respond. So she delivered the placenta, also. Dispatch told her how to tie it off. She's stable at home, Garcia said. We made contact with the assistant medical director here. Talked things through. 

The mother and her baby girl were later transported to the hospital by rescue workers. 3439335]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AFGAIFKMDRVAATLZDW76LXMAAVZEZKK2LRVGADAWIRTCTXAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C28/0B6/C280B6A11D7B96B80AB190DB33733D16.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-13T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>42</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Imra flooding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hurricane Irma baby born]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[woman delivers own baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Irma newborn baby]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/a-fatberg-longer-than-the-tower-bridge-is-blocking-sewers-in-london-3440335</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[A fatberg longer than the Tower Bridge is blocking sewers in London 3440335]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — A 250-meter long fatberg weighing 130 tons has been discovered blocking a sewer line in London. 

The huge mass of congealed fat, wet wipes, diapers, oil and condoms formed in a sewer tunnel in Whitechapel, the BBC reported. 

Thames Water officials said it was one of the biggest blockages they had seen before and that it would take three weeks to remove, according to the BBC.

Fatbergs form when people put things they shouldn't down toilets and sinks. 

The fatberg weighs as much as 10.5 school buses, or a blue whale.

The length of the fatberg is actually 6 meters longer than the 244-meter Tower Bridge. 

Workers began removing the mass this week. Eight workers will use high-pressure hoses to break up the mass, then suck up the pieces into trucks and then transport the waste to a recycling station. 3440335]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNWPDRHBAAA7DIYBBJA5LBFMZASKERKKEDF7GRGK5BWCVABBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C66/9A6/C669A62CD489D7697D8B328AA29904D4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-14T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatberg blocking sewer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatberg formation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatberg London sewer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Thames Water fatberg]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mcdonald-s-employee-fired-after-going-off-on-customer-3440319</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[McDonald's employee fired after going off on customer 3440319]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHARLOTTE, NORTH CAROLINA — A McDonald's manager has reportedly been fired after being seen in a video that a woman posted to Facebook. The clip features the employee being rude to the woman at a drive-through window, and making remarks about Donald Trump before asking the woman if she could spell deportation. 3440319]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEDFCAIDKVDAACTDLJIF79BCMEDEXR35KIARZGZBK5CAKCTVBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/03B/98C/03B98CE6731575EDA586C19A33445CC6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-14T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>192</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ McDonald's]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Donald Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deportation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rude remarks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fired]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pink slip]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Charlotte]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Carolina]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/un-approves-new-tougher-sanctions-on-north-korea-3440270</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UN approves new tougher sanctions on North Korea 3440270]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED NATIONS — North Korea is facing a new round of sanctions, after the United Nations Security Council unanimously approved the decision on Monday.

The New York Times reports that in the wake of the North Korean regime's latest and largest nuclear weapons test on September 3, the UN adopted a U.S.-drafted resolution aimed at preventing the country from fueling and funding its weapons program.

The resolution will restrict oil imports into the North by prohibiting the sale of natural gas and setting a 2-million-barrel-a-year cap on petroleum products.

There will be a ban on textile exports, which are North Korea's second-biggest exports, earning the country nearly $760 million in 2016.

New measures will also be put in place to prohibit North Koreans from working overseas, cutting off the $500 million in revenue generated by heavily taxing 93,000 citizens sent abroad to work.

The original resolution pushed for a full oil embargo, and included an asset freeze and travel ban for North Korean leader Kim Jong Un. These were removed after negotiations between the U.S. and China. 3440270]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DAIAIFKWJRAXIWKBLA57USG2KS3S37AVAR3GCTA2IWGWRQBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F38/953/F38953F1C97A3639054CC341AFE5AF8C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-14T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ un sanctions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oil imports]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ textile exports]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ un security council]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/russia-japan-rail-bridge-would-connect-europe-to-tokyo-3440248</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Russia-Japan rail bridge would connect Europe to Tokyo 3440248]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MOSCOW/TOKYO — Rail passengers on the Trans-Siberian Express may soon be able to travel from London, across Europe and Russia, and beyond to Japan under new plans from Moscow.

The plan involves the construction of a bridge or tunnel between Russia and Sakhalin, and from there, a bridge to the Japanese island of Hokkaido, reports the Siberian Times.

The bridge between Japan and Russia would reportedly be 28 miles in length across the Pacific Ocean. 3440248]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLFMXRDAVAWXC3CLFLWXK4VMVBERRALKJLF7GABBWJARVACBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/478/6B3/4786B373F0FAFE1556F66F9B5CA45DBF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-14T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Russia japan bridge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mega rail project]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bridge across pacific]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mega projects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hokkaido]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sakhalin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russian mega projects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ...]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/third-world-parasite-plaguing-rural-alabama-county-3440119</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Third world parasite plaguing rural Alabama county 3440119]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOWNDES COUNTY, ALABAMA — Hookworm, disease that is typically associated with developing nations, has been found to be plaguing poor areas in the southern U.S.

According to a press release from the Baylor College of Medicine, 34.5% of 55 stool samples taken from Alabama's Lowndes County tested positive for a species of hookworm called Necator americanus.

Households in the county are poor and lack basic sanitation, with waste often discarded in the backyard. Residents exposed to the raw sewage may become infected with hookworm, which enters the human body through the feet.

The parasitic worm attaches itself to the walls of the small intestine, sucking the host's blood and causing anemia, weight loss, impaired mental function, and stunted growth in children.

The disease is a problem even for those who can afford to install their own septic tanks.

Sewage problems run rampant in Alabama's Black Belt region. The area's loamy soil prevents water from draining into the ground, and heavy rains often cause septic systems to overflow or back up.

Parasitic infections like hookworm are treatable with medication, but unless sanitation conditions improve, people will just get re-infected with the disease. 3440119]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNKRIDIBA2JRZC3FBACRZLU3NFKERE34ABJFXHAHKWJARACYBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5FF/4BC/5FF4BC0AAA4D4B4FD3443A20ACC99E2C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-14T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hookworm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ worm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ parasite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poverty]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sewage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ raw sewage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sewage problems]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sewer line]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ septic system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ septic tank]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anemia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iron deficiency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black belt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lowndes county]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alabama]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/boeing-snaps-up-contract-to-begin-work-on-next-u-s-presidential-jet-3441354</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Boeing snaps up contract to begin work on next U.S. presidential jet 3441354]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO/WASHINGTON  — The U.S. Air Force has contracted Boeing to begin design work on presidential aircraft.

According to an Air Force news release,  the U.S. government purchased two Boeing 747-8 jetliners as part of their plan to develop a new Air Force One aircraft.

Under the contract, Boeing will design modifications for the 747-8s.  These will reportedly include an executive interior, meeting rooms, medical facilities and other features of the current presidential aircraft.

According to Reuters, the planes were previously ordered by Transaero, a now defunct Russian Airline. 

According to Defense One, the design will also need to have defensive countermeasures, including a hardened exterior capable of withstanding electromagnetic pulse from nuclear explosions.

The Air Force plans to spend around $3.2 billion on the next presidential aircraft, reported Defense One. 3441354]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIRIAKXAWJR7CIVBADW77JCGFLSRRINKSJWXGTWBSIAEB3RAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A40/83F/A4083FECED23C720152DBD302DE3BD46.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-15T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[us air force one]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[air force one]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[air force 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[new air force 1]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[boeing air force one]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[air force one cost]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[air force one upgrade]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-air-force-brought-in-to-battle-mosquitoes-post-harvey-3441347</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. Air Force brought in to battle mosquitoes post-Harvey 3441347]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TEXAS — Texas officials asked the U.S. Air Force to spray coastal regions of the state in order to combat swarming mosquitoes in the aftermath of Hurricane Harvey. 

U.S. Air Force C-130 cargo planes started spraying insecticides over three eastern Texas counties during the weekend and plan to expand to other counties over the following weeks, said officials from the Texas Department of State Health Services (DSHS), Reuters reported. 

The C-130 cargo planes flew from an air force base in San Antonio and joined two smaller planes. 

About 1.85 million acres have been treated as of Tuesday, the department said. The plan is to spray 6 million acres in total.  

Officials hope the spraying will prevent mosquito-borne illnesses as well as protect emergency response workers and residents from swarms during cleanup efforts.

The Air Force is using an organophosphate insecticide called naled, according to Quartz. Naled acts as a neurotoxin that targets adult mosquitoes, according to Newsweek. 

The health department sprays about 16 million acres a year with the insecticide. It is frequently used after disasters to deal with mosquitoes. 

Health officials urged residents to dispose of standing water, use repellant and wear long-sleeved clothing outdoors. 3441347]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACFGDRCKACAABCEKBLFR7LWMZBB7UZKKSIRTURHKVCAIWZGAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2D8/F75/2D8F75A1961617AD17FD613AF5AF0D67.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-15T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Harvey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ US Air Force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Harvey clean up]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquito-borne illnesses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Zika]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ West Nile Virus]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-biggest-ever-wind-farm-is-set-to-be-built-off-the-british-coast-3441234</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The biggest ever wind farm is set to be built off the British coast 3441234]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON/COPENHAGEN — Danish energy firm DONG will construct the largest ever wind farm off the British coast over the next 5 years.

The wind farm is to be built 90 miles of the British coast. When completed in 2022, the wind farm will have a capacity of some 1.4 gigawatts.

According to DONG, that's enough energy to power some 1.3 million British homes.

The project is expected to create 2,000 jobs over its duration. 3441234]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADWMDCTKMAREBKDBSLATL2FMFKBTRANAJPW5TIAA6IAIVAHAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/104/73D/10473DAA199A2C2A0F15A2D1A6697302.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-15T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>37</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mega projects]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biggest wind farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind farm renewables]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ planet earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DONG energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DONG uk]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-are-the-symptoms-of-a-silent-heart-attack--3441111</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What are the symptoms of a silent heart attack? 3441111]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — Heart attacks may not always be defined by crushing chest pains, and can sometimes strike with little to no symptoms.

The BBC reports that a heart attack, or a myocardial infarction, occurs when a clot blocks the flow of blood and oxygen to the heart, which damages or kills heart muscle cells. The most common symptom of this is pain or discomfort in the chest area.

But research has found that at least 45% of attacks are 'silent', occurring with less intense symptoms, and thus undetected. Silent myocardial infarctions have been known to strike men more than women.

Symptoms are often mistaken for other conditions, and include fatigue, dizziness, nausea, and pain in the neck, jaw and arm.

Silent heart attacks are usually identified using an electro or echocardiogram, which detects damaged heart tissue, according to Harvard Medical School.

Patients who have suffered a silent attack are at a higher risk of having a second one, or succumbing to sudden cardiac arrest.

Doctors stress the importance of getting checked even if the symptoms may not seem serious. At the end of the day, it's better to be safe than sorry. 3441111]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNNWGDRBB5CAAVRUBJIW7LDXMMBV7ERQAWIAVUZBK2LATATYKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3ED/AF7/3EDAF76E38634EC8EC158673B81B596F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-15T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ silent heart attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ silent killer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SMI]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ silent myocardial infarction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood clot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ symptoms]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/inside-japan-s-ultra-luxury-shiki-shima-train-service-3441082</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Inside Japan's ultra luxury Shiki-Shima train service 3441082]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — The Shiki-Shima Train hit Japanese tracks on Monday May 1st 2017.  

The service, operated by East Japanese Railway Company, chauffeurs passengers around North-East Japan on 2 and 3-day trips. It departs Tokyo's Ueno station on a on a 800-mile round trip that stops in Shiroishi, Matsushima, Aomori, Horisaki, Ichinoseki and Naruko-Onsen before returning to Ueno.

The Shiki Shima travels at 110 kilometers per hour — 3 times slower than Japan's so-called bullet train, the Shinkansen.

It comprises 10 cars. These include 1 car for deluxe and Shiki-Shima suite passengers, 5 cars for regular suite , 2 observatory cars, a lounge car and a dining room.

It's observatory cars allow passengers to sit back and take in panoramic views of the Japanese countryside.

The train's 17 suites can accommodate 34 passengers. Guests have the option of staying in a regular maisonette type suite, or deluxe or the Shiki-Shima suite.

The Shiki-Shima's dining room also lets guests view the passing scenery while traveling. It's  and a menu designed by a Michelin star chef.

The service is proving very popular. It's currently fully booked until next April and prospective guests currently need to apply online to join the journey. 3441082]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIWGYZCAVCFCVIUBABAZK2GM5DS3SKZKJPR3UZDAEGWEVK6AD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A80/55F/A8055FA4351E6C70C44C74B3D6712B0B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-15T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Luxury train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shiki shima train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ueno]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luxury trains of the world]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ultra luxury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travel in japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan east railway company]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientist-develop-gaydar-ai-that-can-tell-sexuality-from-profile-pics-3440946</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientist develop 'gaydar' AI that can tell sexuality from profile pics 3440946]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA —  Researchers from Stanford University are facing backlash this week after developing an artificial intelligence that they say can identify sexuality based on dating profile photos

Critics worry the technology could be replicated by governments of countries where gay people are prosecuted.

The AI was used as part of a study that was to be published in the Journal of Personality and Social Psychology. It is currently being held for review regarding ethical concerns, reported Science Alert.

The AI scanned publicly available photos from dating websites to identify whether the image's subject was gay or not. In total, it looked at 130,741 images. It proved more effective than the study's human judges. On the whole, the AI was able to identify gay women with 74% accuracy and gay men with 81% accuracy.

Researchers say the AI was able to do this by looking at transient features, such as nose shape and hair style. It only looked at white people aged between 18 and 40.

The Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation and Human Rights Campaign called for people to debunk it, citing multiple flaws in the study. 3440946]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIRCAIAAWLA7BAWBBJA37DRM5AV5E33LSJFRFAHABKWKCRCKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2B2/86D/2B286DA46420E48082724E6AB866E899.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-15T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>93</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Gay robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ai can tell if you are gay]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gaydar study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ real life gaydar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gaydar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stanford]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/san-diego-streets-power-washed-to-fight-hepatitis-a-outbreak-3440906</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[San Diego streets power washed to fight Hepatitis A outbreak 3440906]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO — At least 16 people have died and more than 400 have been hospitalized following an outbreak of the deadly hepatitis A virus in 'America's Finest City'.

According to the San Diego County Health and Human Services Agency, the Hepatitis A virus is spread through contact with a fecally contaminated environment, or person to person. It attacks the liver, and can be fatal.

Roughly two-thirds of those infected are homeless and/or drug users.

NBC San Diego reports that to combat the spread of the disease, city crews have begun powerwashing the streets with a bleach solution known to kill the virus. Street spraying has been scheduled three times a week, every other week.

Officials have already set up hand washing stations in areas where the homeless congregate, and deployed an additional 40 around the county.

Free vaccinations are also available and recommended to anyone frequenting downtown. Hepatitis A vaccines work by prompting the body to produce antibodies against the disease.

San Diego's precautionary efforts are modelled after those implemented in Los Angeles, where it proved effective.

In addition to street-spraying, installing hand-washing stations and administering vaccines, city officials are also looking into providing more bathroom access downtown. 3440906]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IFAC3VARDRKCIUBMARZK2FNFIEXRT2AVCFMFIKK2LREXADAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/923/3AE/9233AE631D117B97749D0427DE1B64FB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-15T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hepatitis A]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hepatitis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hepatitis outbreak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ san diego]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homeless]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vaccine]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spacex-and-boeing-are-driving-new-space-race-at-nasa-3442209</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[SpaceX and Boeing are driving 'new space race' at NASA 3442209]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — NASA says it may soon be able to launch astronauts from U.S. soil to the International Space Station. 

Important project milestones are coming up for NASA's two commercial crew partners: Boeing and SpaceX, according to AP. 

Several flight tests, including manned missions, are slated for 2018.

Boeing is working on the CST-100 Starliner. The spacecraft is designed to send up to seven astronauts to the space station. Three Starliners are currently in production, with one planned to carry astronauts next year.

SpaceX, which has flown cargo missions to the space station with its Dragon spacecraft,  plans to use the Dragon 2 to send astronauts to space. 
The Dragon 2 is the latest version of SpaceX's Dragon capsule model, which can carry seven astronauts.   

Boeing and SpaceX must show that both of their systems are ready to start regular flights to the space station in order to meet NASA's requirements. 

SpaceX has its first test flight set for February, while Boeing's launch is planned for June. 3442209]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIFACTSARBRCXI9BJJA37DYM2JBRFKSAJLF5U3SBVCFCBIHBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/526/222/5262226337155429868DAFA0C27DEA0B</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-16T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ International Space Station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX Dragon 2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Boeing CST-100 Starliner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX v Boeing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new space race]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-launches-another-missile-over-japan-3441860</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea launches another missile over Japan 3441860]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA — North Korea fired off a ballistic missile over northern Japan today.

The missile was reportedly fired from the district of Sunan in the North Korean capital of Pyongyang, and flew about 3,700 kilometers — reaching an altitude of 770 kilometers.

The US Pacific Command assessed that it was an intermediate-range ballistic missile, although this conflicted with reports from Japan, which is still analyzing the situation. 3441860]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJKRPCRAAFKACAATLADRK6LVMSJBTR35KAAFMGZAARBFGDZPAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8B3/A30/8B3A3049EDA97B51C9A382162950B242</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-16T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>138</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ missile launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ intermediate-range ballistic missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United States]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kim Jung-un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shinzo Abe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Donald Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ potential war]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playing chicken]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/longer-bouts-of-sitting-could-lead-to-an-early-death-3441815</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Longer bouts of sitting could lead to an early death 3441815]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — Health experts have long warned against the perils of sitting all day, but a new study suggests the length of time spent inactive in between bouts of movement also matters.

According to the study published in Annals of Internal Medicine, hip-mounted accelerometers measured physical inactivity in nearly 8,000 Americans aged 45 years and older, for a period of 10 days. Researchers found that the participants were sedentary for 12.3 hours out of a 16-hour waking day.

When measuring bout length, it was discovered that subjects who sat for longer periods at a time were more likely to have died at the end of the study period than those with shorter sitting spells.

Findings indicate that moving around for every 30 consecutive minutes of inactivity may significantly decrease the risk for death.

The study did not explain how sitting increases early death, but experts suggest inactivity exposes the body to higher blood glucose levels, which leads to problems like diabetes, heart disease, or stroke.

Prolonged sitting may also weaken the abdominal muscles, hip flexors, and glutes.

It could also lead to a lack of circulation in the legs, potentially resulting in blood clots forming in the veins — a condition known as deep vein thrombosis.

Alas, working out after a long day of sitting in an office chair may not necessarily undo its ill effects. The best way to lengthen your lifespan, it seems, is to move about as often as you can. 3441815]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDFVCAHKIERGYRVBRAWTKBFGRAE7EAMKSLFTTIBKIGWADZEAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FDD/F21/FDDF2141A9037D938E3E278D92C55AC9</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-16T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>89</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prolonged sitting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sitting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sedentary behavior]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sedentary]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ movement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exercise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood glucose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blood sugar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep vein thrombosis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weak muscles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tattoo-ink-could-be-messing-up-your-immune-system-3441809</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tattoo ink could be messing up your immune system 3441809]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTA — Tattoo ink may leave microscopic particles that can circulate in the immune system and end up in the lymph nodes, a new study finds.   

Scientists wanted to determine the effect tattoos had within the body, particularly the lymph nodes, the Atlanta Journal-Constitution reported. 

The study, published in Scientific Reports, examined lymph nodes and skin samples from deceased donors: four with tattoos and two with no tattoos, according to Smithsonian Magazine. 
Using X-ray fluorescence to identify ink particles and Fourier transform infrared spectroscopy to detect biomolecular changes in surrounding tissue, scientists found traces in the subjects with tattooes and none in the lymph nodes of the non-tattooed subjects.   
They discovered stained lymph nodes in two of the subjects, one with blue ink and one with green. 
Researchers found elevated levels of metals including aluminum, chromium, iron, nickel and copper in the nodes and skin. 

The study concluded contamination could lead to chronic enlargement of the lymph nodes and long-term exposure to toxic compounds. 

The scientists say the next step will be to study what particular health effects ink particles may cause. 3441809]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KWXXRFAEEFCDKABMDRXK4YGVBVZF3SK6KF5UAABWJATYRCBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8C6/AD8/8C6AD874CCB16BBDD851E17C5334E261</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-16T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tattoo ink]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tattoo ink toxic metal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tattoo ink immune system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tattoo ink lymph nodes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cassini-probe-is-set-for-its-saturn-plunge-after-titan-goodbye-kiss--3441793</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cassini probe is set for its Saturn plunge after Titan 'Goodbye Kiss' 3441793]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — NASA's Cassini spacecraft is now on course for its last mission that will see it dive and disintegrate into Saturn's atmosphere on Friday. 

Cassini has been traveling around Saturn and its moons for 13 years, but it is finally running out of fuel, so NASA wants the probe disposed of properly, Space.com reported.

The probe sped within 73,974 miles (119,049 kms) of Titan on Sept. 11 in a flyby meant to lower the spacecraft's orbit enough to ensure it will crash into Saturn's atmosphere, NASA officials said, according to Space.com. 

The main purpose of this last mission is to make sure that Cassini does not contaminate the moons of Titan or Enceladus with Earth microbes. 

Scientists think the two moons could possibly support life. Enceladus has an ocean of liquid water underneath its icy shell, as well as hydrothermal hot spots in the ocean.

Titan is also believed to have a subsurface water ocean. The moon also has lakes and seas of hydrocarbons on its surface.  
   
Once Cassini enters Saturn's thick atmosphere, it will take approximately five to six minutes for the probe to fall apart and melt. During its last dive, the probe will be sending data back to Earth in real time for researchers to analyze. 3441793]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIRMAICAWKRVXRSLJIRT7URM6KV7RAQKSLA3TKRAWKRTBKZKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DCB/165/DCB1650A9C2A4C2BA412B25306F4899F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-16T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cassini space probe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cassini spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA Cassini probe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cassini Grande Finale]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cassini]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Titan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Enceladus]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/stargazers-will-try-to-make-contact-with-aliens-in-2018-3443098</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Stargazers will try to make contact with aliens in 2018 3443098]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE COSMOS — A group known as Messaging Extraterrestrial Intelligences, or METI, will in 2018 attempt to message alien life.

According to CNET, most concur the message should consist of physics and math as these are forms of knowledge aliens likely hold in common with humanity.

However, many scientists, including Stephen Hawking, worry that such a message could put Earth in danger. 

Previous attempts to communicate with alien civilizations have included sending out the formula for alcohol, and Craigslist advertisements, reported CNET. 3443098]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDAMXAHLSJFEAAVB5DAK943MZEVRR35KEDRXHTSKEGRKCC3LC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/602/BC8/602BC8B0E7E0A8B04AB20985BA631016</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-18T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meti]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contacting aliens]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ speak to aliens]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien communication]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien communication attempt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stephen hawking aliens]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/india-is-building-its-first-bullet-train-with-a-whole-lot-of-help-from-japan-3443094</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[India is building its first bullet train with a whole lot of help from Japan 3443094]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AHMEDABAD, INDIA — India has started building a high-speed train system with the help of Japanese technology and finance.  

The network will stretch 508 kms from Ahmedabad to the financial center of Mumbai, and was announced Thursday by Prime Minister Narendra Modi, the Guardian reported. 

The country plans to invest $19 billion to construct the new bullet train line. Japan will fund more than 80 percent of the project, over $14 billion, by providing a 0.1 percent interest loan to be repaid over the next 50 years. 

The line is expected to be finished by 2023 and will cut travel time between the two cities down to three hours from the current eight. 

The Modi administration claims that the project will create 36,000 jobs in India, according to the Guardian. 

The bullet train can carry 750 passengers at an average speed of 250 kph, with a top speed of 320 kph. 

Analysts say constructing the bullet train will give a boost to infrastructure development in India’s quickly-developing western industrial region and help with economic growth. 3443094]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLRGYKSBWLWPBZXLWJRILBCGEBSXEC7AFJRVGTSANKWMAANKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AC1/019/AC10197E18812C9E5ED3B93564B105F7</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-18T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[India bullet train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[India high-speed train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Japan India bullet train]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Indian Railways]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Shinkansen Technology]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mit-develops-tech-to-pack-several-vaccine-doses-into-a-single-shot-3444045</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[MIT develops tech to pack several vaccine doses into a single shot 3444045]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — The Massachusetts Institute of Technology has developed a drug delivery method that packs multiple doses in a single injection, and could soon make multi-shot vaccines a thing of the past.

According to the MIT News Office, engineers used biodegradable polymers used in implants, sutures, and prosthetic devices, and pressed them into silicone molds to form tiny cups each measuring 400 micrometers across.

The cups are filled with vaccine and covered with a lid made from the same polymer. Heat is applied to fuse the cup and lid together, sealing the vaccine inside.

Varying its chemical makeup allows the polymers to degrade at specific times, though all are delivered simultaneously via a single injection.

Inside the body, the vaccine is released once the cup degrades. Lab tests on mice showed the polymer cups successfully releasing their payload in 9, 20, and 41 days, without prior leakage.

Researchers say the new technology could benefit patients in developing nations, who are often unable to travel frequently to health care facilities to complete their shots.

It may also allow newborns to be given an injection carrying one or two year's worth of vaccines, minimizing stressful, tear-filled doctor's visits for kids and parents alike. 3444045]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASNWVAKXBAERTAIXBADFT7LWM5BBKEANKZDWZGREANJFMWIEAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3B5/FC8/3B5FC84541CFAFDECBD5759187600AC2</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-19T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>80</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ injection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polymer cup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vaccine cup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ timed vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MIT]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/plastic-eating-fungus-discovered-in-new-study-3443951</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Plastic eating fungus discovered in new study 3443951]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KUNMING, CHINA/PAKISTAN — A new study published in the journal Environmental Pollution discusses a fungus that breaks down plastic materials.

A group of researchers from the Kunming Institute of Botany in China found aspergillus [h]tubingensis[i], a common soil fungus, at a dump in Pakistan. Under laboratory conditions it was shown to break down plastic in weeks, not years.

The fungus used its roots to break apart the plastic, but its effectiveness was found to be influenced by other factors such as temperature and pH levels.

Aspergillus tubingensis was previously found in patients with lung conditions such as cystic fibrosis, according to a 2016 study in the journal Medical Mycology. 3443951]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NWGDIEBAAAKDIVLEBAZKDWGEEEZRT4LVAF7GZCKBJAIDCUKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E3B/F0D/E3BF0D1C7AE73385A371F72364CBE24F</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-19T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic eating fungus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aspergillus tubingensis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ environmental pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mycology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kunming]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mexloop-hyperloop-design-could-connect-42-million-people-3443925</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mexloop Hyperloop design could connect 42 million people 3443925]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY — A new Hyperloop system being proposed by Mexican consortium Mexloop could reduce traveling time between Mexico City and Guadalajara to 38 minutes.

Mexloop's design is one of the 10 winners of the Hyperloop One Global Challenge, Inhabitat reported.

The Hyperloop would connect 42 million people in four major cities in Central Mexico: Mexico City, Querétaro, León and Guadalajara.

The proposed system would stretch 330 miles, and would take about 38 minutes the travel the entire route.

Stations would be located close to airports, rail freight hubs and train stations in order to maximize transportation infrastructure efficiency, according to Hyperloop One. 

Mexloop says the Hyperloop would help the economy as well as ease traffic congestion. 

According to Mexloop, a Hyperloop system would only be two thirds of the cost of a high speed rail system. 3443925]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVCFMXZHK5CWGCRRLRAFZKDTMABBXS3SKJJWZHZGANJAECAKKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/08D/E1E/08DE1E5E6A3711BBE6FCE1722AEC4D5E</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-19T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mexloop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop One]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mexloop Hyperloop design]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop One pod]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/third-hand-cigarette-smoke-found-damaging-to-organs-3443836</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Third-hand cigarette smoke found damaging to organs 3443836]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RIVERSIDE, CALIFORNIA — Most people are familiar with the ill effects of first and second hand smoking on the body, but a new study has found that even third-hand exposure to tobacco smoke poses a health risk.

According to a study published in Clinical Science, third-hand smoke comes from exhaled cigarette residue getting absorbed into surfaces, causing toxins to accumulate in like clothing, curtains, carpets, and furniture.

Bystanders can be exposed to the toxins through skin absorption, with children especially vulnerable since they are in close contact with household surfaces.

Researchers found that mice exposed to sections of fabric imbued with third-hand smoke were found to have liver damage after just one month. They suffered further molecular damage to both the liver and brain after two to six months.

The exposure also increased insulin resistance in the mice, and upped the release of the stress hormone epinephrine, making them prone to type-2 diabetes and immune fatigue.

Though the research was conducted on animals, it nevertheless draws attention to the dangers of cigarette smoke even on a third-hand basis.

Further studies should investigate the effects on humans, and possibly determine what effect long-term exposure will have on the body. 3443836]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IFVYAFAMEWIX3ELBLFX6JHMVBBVR35KAAFRGALAJJAIAKWAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/61E/B4E/61EB4EDF221DED78F1F4A8F0B8575C75</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-19T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ third hand smoke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smoking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cigarette smoke]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mice experiment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ diabetes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immune fatigue]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/swedish-commuters-are-using-hand-implants-to-pay-for-train-tickets-3443705</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Swedish commuters are using hand implants to pay for train tickets 3443705]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[STOCKHOLM, SWEDEN — Around 3,000 Swedish commuters have had biometric microchips implanted in their hands in order to pay for train tickets. 

Swedish rail company SJ first introduced the alternative pay option in June, according to BBC. 

Commuters who elect to have the RFID chip implanted under their skin are able to have their ticket loaded onto the device. 

The implants use Near Field Communication technology similar to contactless credit cards or mobile payments. 

When activated by a reader device a few centimeters away information can be transferred between the them using magnetic field induction. 

The train conductor then scans the microchip with a smartphone to complete the ticket transaction. 

The rail company does not implant the chip for customers. People need to have the procedure done own their own. 3443705]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFIRMCZDAJKRGCKELEBA37JBGIBB3RT9K2JW3G3XA2KREWIAAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/162/044/1620448783368F6B4EA7C7A59592A474</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-19T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RFID hand implants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RFID chip implants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sweden RFID commuters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train commuters chip implants]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/asia-s-glaciers-shrinking-by-a-third-in-2100-threatens-water-supply-3443667</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Asia's glaciers shrinking by a third in 2100 threatens water supply 3443667]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UTRECHT, NETHERLANDS — With asian glaciers facing a massive melt by the end of the century, millions of people are at risk of water shortages — and it's all thanks to global warming.

According to the World Wildlife Fund, the high mountains of Asia lie in a region surrounding the Tibetan plateau, and contains the largest store of permanent ice outside the North and South poles.

Meltwater feeds into major rivers like the Indus, Yangtze, and Mekong and are used for drinking, hydroelectric power, and irrigation.

Reuters reports that researchers from Utrecht University predict that Asian high mountain glaciers will lose a third of their mass by 2100 if the global temperature rises 1.5 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels. If temperatures increase 3.5, 4, or 6 degrees, losses could reach 49, 51, and  65%, respectively.

Glacial loss could affect the region's water supply and lead to shortages. At the same time, accelerated melting could trigger intense flooding, especially when combined with climate change-induced heavy rains and super typhoons.

High-warming scenarios carry worse consequences, including massive sea-level rise, floods, droughts, loss of species, and even disease.

The only way to avoid such a dismal future is by minimizing global temperature rise, and for that, we need to double, even triple efforts to combat climate change. 3443667]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNKRMYABA2KWIXZ9LMDR7L4SNBJVZS34K2IAZUTSAIBWMAAQKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E47/41A/E4741A3BD495DD0CD02FA9008C144612</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-19T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asian glaciers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ melting glaciers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glaciers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glacial melt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high mountain glaciers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water shortage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paris agreement]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/us-japan-and-south-korea-air-forces-show-off-air-superiority-3445248</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[US, Japan and South Korea air forces show off air superiority 3445248]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO/WASHINGTON/SEOUL — Aircraft from the U.S., Japanese and South Korean air forces were involved in military drills this week in response to the North Korean missile launch over Japan on Sept. 14.
 
According to a U.S. Pacific Command news release, 4 American F35Bs and 2 B1-B bombers, along with 4 Korean F15s and 4 Japanese F2s flew in sequential military drills this week.

South Korean and American aircraft dropped live munitions at the Pilsung training range in South Korea.

The exercises were conducted in response to North Korea's missile launch over Japan on September 14, according to the news release. Japanese and American aircraft flew over waters near the south west coast of Japan. 3445248]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDRIX3ULSKWGVCAKEDFX6LWGWJBVRAMAEDWZTAKKVDAZVIBBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ADC/D2A/ADCD2A116184460892F619EBA8EF6E67.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-20T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North korea missile test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[us air force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[japan air force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[south korean air force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[kim jong un]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/massive-antarctic-iceberg-the-size-of-delaware-is-now-adrift-at-sea-3444840</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Massive Antarctic iceberg the size of Delaware is now adrift at sea 3444840]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA — A massive iceberg around the size of Delaware has broken off from Antarctica and is now floating out to sea.

Recent satellite photos show the A68 iceberg appearing to move away from the Larsen C ice shelf, the Independent reported. 

The iceberg is over 2200 sq miles, weighs approximately a trillion tons and has a volume twice that of Lake Erie, according to Scientific American. 

Professor Stef Lhermitte, of Delft University in the Netherlands posted the images on Twitter with a caption, After some initial back-and-forth movement, Larsen C's iceberg A68 seems on drift now. 

Experts now believe the iceberg will float northeast and slowly make its way out into the open seas of the Southern Ocean, Business Insider reported. 

Scientists are concerned that A68 could break up into smaller pieces and then drift into shipping lanes. Pieces too small to track by satellite could pose major risks to passing ships.    

Some researchers have said the calving of the iceberg was a normal event, not caused by global warming, according to the Independent. 3444840]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEBWICKULACRCW3ABACRI7D3MECS3FK4AWPW7HZHAAGRMC3YBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2B8/BC5/2B8BC5DF633F46B2AA0C1E6555A95A35.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-20T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ A68 iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Larsen C ice shelf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Antarctica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ A68 iceberg adrift]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/venus-mysterious-night-side-revealed-for-the-first-time-3444623</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Venus' mysterious night side revealed for the first time 3444623]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — For the first time ever, scientists are studying Venus' mysterious night side, and have found that it's vastly different from its day side.

It takes Venus 225 days to revolve around the sun, and 243 days to fully rotate on its axis. As a result, 'night' and 'day' on the planet last a longer time than on Earth.

So far, the day side has been studied extensively, but the night side has been notoriously difficult to observe, until now.

According to the European Space Agency, Venus' atmosphere consists of strong winds blowing 60 times faster than the planet's rotation. This super-rotation has been assumed to be uniform in both sides, but new data from the Venus Express spacecraft shows the winds are more chaotic and irregular on the night side.

Night side clouds formed large, wavy, filament-like patterns not seen in day clouds, and are dominated by stationary waves, which remain still and do not move with the atmosphere.

Stationary waves were thought to form specifically over steep, mountainous areas, but were recently detected in the planet's southern hemisphere - an area with low elevation. 

The waves were likewise assumed to be rising up through the cloud from the surface, but were mysteriously missing from the lower and intermediate cloud levels.

Scientists have yet to explore what this means, but will likely need to come up with new, updated models of Venus to help them figure it out. 3444623]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMARCYKSLJIFKBKELNPAX6BAG2JBKETSKNLRXH3RABLFAWZCAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/096/472/096472EC234D053EB6DCE3A9F084BE1A</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-20T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ venus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ night side]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ planets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ outer space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ milky way]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ astronomy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ european space agency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ venus express]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/jupiter-or-saturn-may-have-been-the-cause-for-life-on-earth-3444581</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Jupiter or Saturn may have been the cause for life on Earth 3444581]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BORDEAUX, FRANCE — A study published in the journal Icarus, suggest that Earth's water is a simple byproduct of giant planet growth.

During the formation of gas giants such as Saturn or Jupiter, they enter a period of rapid growth. This destabilized nearby water-rich space rocks known as planetesimals[e], bringing them into the planetary orbit.

Next, the gravity there would have propelled these to the inner or outer solar system.
The researchers speculate some were sent in an inward direction, toward some early form of Earth and seeded it with water. 3444581]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2IRIYZEBJKWPBCFKFJA37D3GMEVXRRLKIAWTTZEAJIFKBAKAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6D9/1FA/6D91FA88AEECEB93F4ABFBF9790A82E5</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-20T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ where did water come from in the universe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ did water come from space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ planetesimals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ h20]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ origin of water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/colorado-route-selected-for-hyperloop-one-project-3444432</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Colorado route selected for Hyperloop One project 3444432]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DENVER — Hyperloop One announced Colorado would be one of the 10 finalists in its global competition to identify the best potential Hyperloop routes.  

The Colorado Department of Transportation is working with the Hyperloop company to carry out a feasibility study for the proposed route between Cheyenne, Denver and Pueblo, Techcrunch reported.

The feasibility study could cost up to $1 million and take years to complete, CBS 4 reported. 

The proposed route would stretch 360 miles and link 10 urban centers around the state, with the potential to connect over 4,800,000 people, according to Techcrunch. 

A Hyperloop trip from Denver to Pueblo would take 15 minutes, while Denver to Fort Collins would only take 9 minutes. Denver to Vail would also be 9 minutes. 

Three other U.S. routes were chosen by Hyperloop as finalists: Chicago-Columbus-Pittsburgh, Miami-Orlando and Dallas-Laredo-Houston. 

Hyperloop One plans for its first functional prototypes to be running as early as 2020. 3444432]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJACDTXBFIAMWZRBWLFTL2CGWIBVURILVCF5HCXAIGAMBRFKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/22B/993/22B9936E1BF0807B62A4BD6A2249B263</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-20T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop Colorado]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop One]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop One Global Challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hyperloop Denver]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/138-dead-after-powerful-earthquake-hits-central-mexico-3445441</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[138 dead after powerful earthquake hits central Mexico 3445441]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY — A 7.1 magnitude earthquake killed more than 100 people in central Mexico on Tuesday.

According to the Los Angeles Times, 44 buildings collapsed and 30 people were killed in Mexico City. Millions of Mexicans are currently without power.

Soldiers, police officers and firefighters, as well as residents are working to save people from damaged buildings.

Earlier this month an 8.1 magnitude earthquake killed 98 people in south Mexico. 3445441]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLAMCICAJLACBRVBSLA7KDUMABEXFIQA2JAXFIDKEDAKWIMAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/57D/222/57D222EBD7DF67207E8ACFB35FCEB8FF</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-21T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>34</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mexico earthquake 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earthquake in mexico]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ central mexico]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mexico city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ natural disaster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earthquakes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sea-lice-wreak-havoc-on-worldwide-salmon-supply-3445413</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sea lice wreak havoc on worldwide salmon supply 3445413]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE OCEAN — Parasites infestations at salmon farms across the world are causing prices of the fish to surge.

According to an Associated Press report on ABC, parasitic sea lice have infected salmon farms in Canada, Scotland, Norway, the United States and Chile.

Once a parasite infects the salmon, it becomes inedible. Previously, salmon were fed a pesticide to defend against the sea lice. This was effective until 2009, when the lice began to overcome it and spread internationally. 3445413]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLFXYZHAIFWPVCEB6KAVK2GMMBSTFALKFLWMH3WA5ARPBIFKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0A4/A28/0A4A28A12DEC894EFE2A4AC247282463</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-21T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>39</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea louse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea lice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ salmon lice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ salmon demand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ salmon prices]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ salmon louse]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nfl-hopes-new-high-tech-helmets-will-help-reduce-concussions-3445399</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NFL hopes new high-tech helmets will help reduce concussions 3445399]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — This NFL season about 70 players are wearing a new state-of-the-art helmet designed to lower the risk of concussions. 

The Vicis Zero1, which sells for $1,500, was specifically designed to soften the blows NFL players take to their heads during games, CNN Money reported. 

The NFL and NFL Players Association have tested dozens of different helmet concepts in recent years with the Vicis ranking highest in safety, according to CNN Money. 

The helmet is made of four different protective layers. The outer shell is made from flexible thermoplastic that compresses to absorb shock, then rebounds, much like a car bumper. 

Next is a layer of more than 500 polymer columns that can twist and move laterally, reducing the impact of rotational acceleration, a major cause of concussions, the Washington Post reported.  

Underneath that is a hard inner shell that helps prevent skull fractures and brain hemorrhages. Below that is a layer of memory foam to provide the player comfort.  

About half of NFL teams have put in orders for the Vicis helmet. NFL players get to choose the helmet they wear from an approved NFL list.  

The NFL has been looking to address concussions, especially as the league as faced increasing scrutiny. 

Medical experts and players are concerned that repeated concussions increase the likelihood of developing chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE), a degenerative brain disease. 3445399]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJKWMAAAAEDARVCDBJPA5L4SMECBXRIMLVBRZGKXK5CAAAAPBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6CC/A10/6CCA10B0394B01D5E6B8C0110FC4696C</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-21T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NFL Vicis Zero1 helmet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Vicis Zero1 helmet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Vicis helmet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NFL concussions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ football concussions]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dubai-green-lights-world-s-largest-concentrated-solar-power-plant-3445229</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dubai green lights world's largest concentrated solar power plant 3445229]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES — The Dubai government has approved an extension to the world's largest single-site solar farm. 

The government has given the green light to a 700-MW addition to the Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Solar Park, New Atlas reported. 
The solar park is located about 50 kms south of Dubai, with the first phase inaugurated back in 2013, according to New Atlas. 

It currently has 2.3 million photovoltaic solar panels with a 200-MW capacity. Capacity is expected to grow to 5,000 MW by 2030. 

Developers say the park will eventually cover 214 sq km with a 260-m solar tower taking center stage.

The solar plant produces power by using lenses and reflectors to concentrate sunlight in order to heat fluids, which then in turn produce steam to drive a turbine. 

An advantage to this type of solar system is that it's more flexible because energy can be stored as heat and used as needed. A drawback is that they are more expensive than photovoltaic solar plants. 

Construction of the new extension is set to begin in 2020. The contract was awarded to a consortium of Saudi Arabia's ACWA Power and Shanghai Electric. 3445229]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIWAYCSAVAFIBIUL6IRZ72HGEBBTSAIKBPWMGRBARDFPACSBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1E1/B56/1E1B5661EDA6E30D8DD884FD5239514B</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-21T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Concentrated Solar Power plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Concentrated Solar Power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Dubai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mohammed bin Rashid Al Maktoum Solar Park]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/photo-of-seahorse-swimming-with-dirty-cotton-swab-goes-viral-3445224</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Photo of seahorse swimming with dirty cotton swab goes viral 3445224]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INDONESIA — Justin Hofman, an American photographer and activist for U.S.-based environmental conservation group Sea Legacy, was snorkeling recently in Sumbawa Island when he snapped a photo of a seahorse clutching a dirty cotton swab. He posted the image to his Instagram account, where it has since gone viral.

In his post of the photo on Instagram, Hofman expressed his worry about the future of marine life and how our actions will shape the planet we live in. 3445224]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFPDIIAADRKVIVLJKA79DSGEBV5SRLKACFMHAFKFKRAAKRKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1D1/182/1D11825DB98E48EDD53378FD12D46A39</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-21T19:34:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seahorse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Indonesia Justin Hofman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sea Legacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snorkeling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cotton swab]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic waste]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spirit-airlines-plane-spews-parts-after-detroit-takeoff-3446452</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Spirit Airlines plane spews parts after Detroit takeoff 3446452]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT — The Federal Aviation Administration is looking into why a Spirit Airlines plane was spewing parts after a takeoff on Monday night. 

The Spirit flight from D-town to Hot-lanta was forced to return to Detroit Metro Airport after experiencing engine failure, according to the FAA, the Detroit Free Press reported.  

The plane was able to land safely without incident, but unfortunately, dumped a bunch of engine pieces into the yards of Detroit residents. 

The FAA sent investigators to look into what went wrong and to examine the recovered engine parts. The investigation should be concluded in the coming weeks. 

According to one passenger on the flight, the plane was about 5,000 feet in the air when there was a large bang that caused aircraft to shake and shudder. 

The passenger said the right engine was on fire, sparking and losing pieces. 

And here we thought it was just Spirit trying to save some money by getting rid of plane engines. 3446452]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDFMDIHLVGAAVAYBBIWXL4XMECS7UTRKNLF3UTRK2LAGBIAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F28/F56/F28F56FA7239FB0A819CB6BAE7310CC2</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spirit Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spirit Airlines engine failure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spirit Airlines plane spew parts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline problems]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/thank-you-and-farewell-kind-patrons-3446313</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Thank you and farewell kind Patrons 3446313]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[The is our last Patreon video. 

It's been a ride and we'd like to thank all those who joined us along the way. 3446313]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IAMCIFBNPAIB3CLEAFZ6BCGEASIST3AEARVHIEKIDFIBZJAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/794/98D/79498D30460E3C8067F89957680DCB77</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[patreon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[farewell patreon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[patreon than yous]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[tomonews patreon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[patreon video]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/google-buys-part-of-htc-r-d-team-for-1-1-billion-3446216</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Google buys part of HTC R&D team for $1.1 billion 3446216]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIPEI — After tons of rumors, leaked memos, and article after article of intense speculation, the news is out: Google is buying HTC —  at least part of it.

Reuters reports that the Taiwanese smartphone maker suspended trading of its shares on the Taiwan Stock Exchange Thursday, pending a 'major announcement.'

That announcement involves Google forking over $1.1 billion for part of HTC's mobile division, which includes a non-exclusive license for HTC IP, and a chunk of the R&D team that's been working on Google's Pixel phone.

About half of HTC's R&D people will soon be Googlers. The other half will stay on at HTC to work on their next flagship phone.

Guess the original smartphone maker doesn't want out of the game just yet, even after plummeting from the top spot in 2010 to this year's pitiful 0.6% global market share.

HTC's quiet brilliance did bounce back with the Vive, largely considered the best virtual reality headset on the market.

The company was also responsible for the the ravely reviewed Pixel and Pixel XL phones in 2016, as well as the Pixel 2, which will be unveiled in October.

Despite its lack of home runs, HTC does have a reputation for producing excellent hardware. Google is hoping to get the hardware-software synergy that's been the iPhone's secret sauce.

With the deal expected to be done by early 2018, here's hoping the tide will soon turn for HTC. 3446216]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDWXD3XLRAREVITBBPRIKJFNAEEXRKRABKA5FCWAAAFGVKVKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1C5/AC2/1C5AC207C974C123C064D2A1B491BB17</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>87</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ htc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tech]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smartphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pixel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ made by google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acquisition]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-find-magma-source-in-italian-supervolcano-3446210</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists find magma source in Italian supervolcano 3446210]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NAPLES, ITALY — Scientists have located the magma source of an Italian super volcano that's considered one of the most dangerous in the world.

Campi Flegrei is a volcanic caldera to the west of Naples which last erupted in 1538, but was responsible for a series of small earthquakes in the 1980s, according to a new study published in Scientific Reports.

Researchers have long puzzled about where the caldera's magma was coming from, and have now pinpointed the location of a hot zone about 4 kilometers under the nearby city of Pozzuoli.

From 1982 and 1984, rising gas and magma caused ground in the crater to swell, but was prevented from rising to the surface by a deep rock formation. The magma instead spread out laterally, causing minor earthquakes.

The caldera has grown hotter since, and with pressure building, scientists fear it could soon erupt and put the entire region at risk.

Volcanologists cannot say for sure what the scale of any future eruption could be, but are closely monitoring Campi Flegrei. 3446210]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZCAGYIEL6MWABITLWPWXKLXGRDSTEAKA5AFTHTXK2JAABZBAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/787/C6E/787C6EB01155305E94E4F68547034953</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ campi flegrei]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ volcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ volcanic eruption]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supervolcano]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ magma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eruption]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ magma reservoir]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earthquake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ natural disaster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pozzuoli]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ naples]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hard-nerf-gun-bullets-cause-serious-eye-injury-3447395</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hard Nerf gun bullets cause serious eye injury 3447395]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Doctors at a London eye hospital are warning against the dangers of nerf guns, after at least three people reportedly suffered serious injuries from getting hit in the eye.

CBS reports that nerf guns are toys that shoot soft foam projectiles. Legitimate replacement bullets are recommended and widely available, but generic ones are cheaper. They're also harder, and have more potential to cause injury.

Nerf video tutorials abound online, with some giving instructions on how to modify the toy gun to make it shoot faster and farther.

According to three cases reported in the British Medical Journal, patients who were hit in the eye reportedly complained of blurred vision and pain.

Doctors soon discovered their eyes were inflamed, and blood was pooling in the anterior chamber. Both the cornea and retina had also developed swelling.

Fortunately, after being given eyedrops, their sight returned to normal after a few weeks.

Such eye trauma may not always lead to permanent vision loss, but could result in a long-term condition like glaucoma. Experts recommend wearing safety glasses to minimize the danger. 3447395]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJFCCTSBEAAXVRRBSJAV94SGWKSXUZQA6PRXGIDKZAWIBAKAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FE7/604/FE7604D2F1BDA3036870DC76EDBBE4A4</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nerf gun]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nerf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye injury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toy gun]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uveitis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hyphema]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ safety glasses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ safety]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ccleaner-supply-chain-malware-targeted-tech-companies-3447292</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[CCleaner supply chain malware targeted tech companies 3447292]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — A Windows utility tool meant to clean and optimize PCs has instead exposed hundreds of thousands to malicious software.

According to a report from Cisco's Talos Intelligence research team, hackers embedded malware into the CCleaner software, exposing nearly 700,000 to an attack.

The compromised CCleaner version was distributed between August 15 and September 12, and taken down shortly after it was discovered.

Data from the malware's seized command and control center shows it specifically targeted high-profile tech firms. It scanned and profiled infected machines, and sent system information to an external server.

If a system met the malware's requirements, a second payload would be deployed to create a backdoor which the attackers could use to spy and steal company intel.

Researchers examining the malware describe it as complex and sophisticated, evidenced by the fact that it went undetected for weeks.

Though a partial list of affected companies was released, there's no news yet on the damage the malware may have caused.

Avast, the company that owns CCleaner, says it's working with authorities to identify the perps and other servers they used in the attack. 3447292]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6JFEDCWBEBR3DZVL6LARKDUMEDBKST7KVBRVGCTBSLRIWC9AF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EC7/AB3/EC7AB32092319850BE4207F08A2BD6CB</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malware]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CCleaner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ data breach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tech companies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malicious software]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supply chain malware]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Avast]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/airlines-made-44-6-billion-in-extra-charges-last-year-3447027</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Airlines made $44.6 billion in extra charges last year 3447027]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES  — The world's greediest and biggest airlines raked in around $44.6 billion in passenger fees and commissions last year. 

Some budget airlines get over half their total revenue from charges for bags, food, entertainment and other extras — aka — things that used to come with your flight.

Airlines around the world are increasingly making more and more money from fees, frequent flier programs and commissions for directing customers to hotels and car rental companies, according to a new study from IdeaWorksCompany, the LA Times reported.

The $44.6 billion bamboozled by the 66 biggest airlines was a 10% increase over 2015, according to the study. 

Over the past 10 years, airlines have increasingly turned to charging you for stuff that used to come with your flight. 

The biggest airlines made an estimated 9.7% of their revenue from B.S. charges. 

Budget airlines derived an even bigger chunk of their cash from fees and commissions. For example, Spirit Airlines was at 46.7% while Frontier Airlines was at 42.4%.

Spirit actually charges you for almost 40 different extras, such as 2 buck to print a boarding pass at an airport kiosk and up to $50 to choose a seat. 
Word is, Spirit is looking into getting passengers to pay extra for engines and even pilots. Okay, maybe not. But who knows.   

Anyone know when that Hyperloop gets finished? 3447027]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAWXDRCLIFA7VA7LJKAR7LSGREB5RTRAFJFXHTYK5CAIACXAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9E3/16D/9E316D469CCD8ED2147803F694917DFF</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>89</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline fees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline ancillary fees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport fees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baggage fees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ budget airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spirit airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frontier airlines]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-girl-born-with-heart-outside-her-chest-3446993</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Russian girl born with heart outside her chest 3446993]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RUSSIA — An eight year old girl suffers from a rare congenital condition and is currently stateside seeking treatment. 

Virsaviya Borun, born in Russia, suffers from thoracoabdominal syndrome. 
The condition, also known as Pentalogy of Cantrell, affects five in one million people. Her heart is covered by a thin layer of skin and she's missing part of her chest bone, a diaphragm and abs.  

Borun has to be careful everywhere she goes, for obvious reasons. 

Her mom launched a crowdfunding campaign to raise money for her medical bills in 2015 which raised over 70 grand. 

Unfortunately, after traveling to Florida for an operation, doctors told the young girl her blood pressure was too high. 
 
So, while Borun works on getting her blood pressure down, she's still just busy being an overactive eight-year-old. 3446993]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIFICKSBMCRRWZSLVDFR74YGRDVTRZNKSLFMHICAEBFPAKZAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FF9/D2C/FF9D2C69281770378F6AD491D017DB96</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Heart conditions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ girl heart outside chest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ girl born heart outside chest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pentalogy of cantrell]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thoracoabdominal syndrome]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/body-s-bad-fat-could-be-transformed-to-fight-obesity-3446982</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Body's 'bad fat' could be transformed to fight obesity 3446982]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS, MISSOURI — The body's bad fat could be made to transform into brown fat by blocking specific proteins, researchers have found. 

The majority of fat in the body is unhealthy white tissue found around the waist, hips and thighs, the Guardian reported.  

Smaller amounts of brown fat located around the neck and shoulders are packed with mitochondria that generate heat by burning up excess calories. 

Scientists from the Washington University School of Medicine found a way to turn white fat into beige fat, a healthier fat with some weight loss capabilities, in lab mice. 

Our research suggest that by targeting a protein in white fat, we can convert bad fat into a fat that fights obesity, Dr. Irfan Lodhi said. 
Beige fat was discovered in adults in 2015 and found to behave like brown fat. Researchers found that by blocking the PexRAP protein in mice, white fat was transformed into calorie burning beige fat. 

Lodhi's team says the next step is to find a safe way to block the PexRAP protein in humans. 3446982]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDFPCTULVDAXAIUBIDFXLDXGNLSTS33AEAWVHCTBSLRCC35KE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/058/17D/05817DF3676AA4D61EE66DC4FBFA5B57</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[white fat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[brown fat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[beige fat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[PexRAP protein]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[lab mice]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-gets-slingshot-power-up-in-most-epic-game-of-asteroids-ever-3446970</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA gets slingshot power-up in most epic game of Asteroids ever 3446970]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE FINAL FRONTIER — NASA's OSIRIS-Rex spacecraft will fly by Earth on Friday as part of its mission to investigate the Bennu asteroid.

According to the space agency, OSIRIS-Rex will slingshot around Earth, and in doing so, use the planet's orbit to get a 8,500 mile per hour speed boost to help it on its journey to Bennu.

The Bennu asteroid was discovered in 1999. Its 500m height is taller than Taipei 101, one of the tallest buildings in the world. 

NASA believes investigation of it may lead to a deeper understanding of some of the universe's most fundamental questions. 3446970]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFKWMDCUBZDR3AAYB5BFZL4SGEEEZSZMLRAFZGKTAEBAPAAQAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A81/C05/A81C055080CA606428F76A7487E00D60</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa space craft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gravitational slingshot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ osiris-rex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bennu asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gravitational slingshot animation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uk-to-invest-88million-in-america-s-mega-science-project-3446951</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UK to invest $88million in America's mega science project 3446951]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The UK pledged an $88 million investment toward the U.S. government's yet to be completed subterranean particle physics experiment this week.

The Deep Underground Neutrino Experiment, also known as DUNE, begins at the Long Baseline Neutrino Facility at the Fermilab in Illinois. 

It ends 800 miles away at the Sanford Underground Research Facility in South Dakota.

When finished, it'll produce the world's highest-intensity neutrino beam using the Fermilab's proton accelerator.

This beam will travel westward through the Earth's mantle to South Dakota where scientists will gather data on the neutrino particles.

Scientists believe the DUNE project could lead to a deeper understanding of these weightless subatomic particles and how the universe came to be. 3446951]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMARCAAJLJIACAZRBNIAI9JGGIDSZSRMKJLF5HRFK2KWIDRMKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DA1/5B0/DA15B00032A40C3F75F7371FA28FF5B0</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fermilab]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fermilab uk investment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dune project]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep underground neutrino experiment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DUNE]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neutrinos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what are neutrinos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sanford lab]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surf lab]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spirit-airlines-plane-spews-parts-after-detroit-takeoff-3446828</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Spirit Airlines plane spews parts after Detroit takeoff 3446828]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DETROIT — The Federal Aviation Administration is looking into why a Spirit Airlines plane was spewing parts after a takeoff on Monday night. 

The Spirit flight from D-town to Hot-lanta was forced to return to Detroit Metro Airport after experiencing engine failure, according to the FAA, the Detroit Free Press reported.  

The plane was able to land safely without incident, but unfortunately, dumped a bunch of engine pieces into the yards of Detroit residents. 

The FAA sent investigators to look into what went wrong and to examine the recovered engine parts. The investigation should be concluded in the coming weeks. 

According to one passenger on the flight, the plane was about 5,000 feet in the air when there was a large bang that caused aircraft to shake and shudder. 

The passenger said the right engine was on fire, sparking and losing pieces. 

And here we thought it was just Spirit trying to save some money by getting rid of plane engines. 3446828]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LFCAKVBVAAABIXKBLRTKDTGVDS5RCSKNKFVHACA5GAGCKSAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B3E/224/B3E2249FBED8D431D3B14B873B585AC0</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spirit Airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spirit Airlines engine failure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Spirit Airlines plane spew parts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline problems]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-discover-octopus-town-near-australian-coast-3446804</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists discover octopus town near Australian coast 3446804]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JERVIS BAY, AUSTRALIA — The gloomy octopus is widely thought to be an antisocial creature, but new research may change this thinking.

A study published in the journal Marine and Freshwater Behaviour and Physiology details the discovery of a site in close to Jervis Bay, Australia's occupied by 15 of the creatures.

Scientists observed complex social behavior in the creatures, including, mating, mate defense, as well as eviction from the site and exclusion of octopuses from the group.

The study provides scientists with a deeper understanding of one of nature's most difficult to study creatures. 3446804]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLFXXAJBVFFTDRXLWIFZLUSGZASXSZNAFPA5HRDBSIWIYKWBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FDD/488/FDD4882DCCB12EDD0C5B4CD09FBE00A7</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ octopus city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ octopus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ octopus city australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gloomy octopus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ octopus behaviour]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jervis bay]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-announces-new-travel-ban-on-eight-countries-3448898</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump announces new travel ban on eight countries 3448898]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — The Trump administration has unveiled an updated travel ban that blocks certain foreign nationals from entering the country.

According to the proclamation released by the White House, beginning October 18, new U.S. travel restrictions will be implemented for visitors from eight countries — an expansion of the controversial travel ban that took effect in January.

The original ban included Iraq, Iran, Syria, Somalia, Yemen, Sudan, and Libya. Iraq and Sudan have been removed, while North Korea, Chad, and Venezuela were added to the list.

The new rules vary per country, but will not affect legal permanent residents, nor those who already hold a valid U.S. visa.

Restrictions on Venezuela focus on government officials and their families.

Despite not being included in the ban, Iraqi citizens will reportedly face enhanced scrutiny when visiting the country, reports Reuters.

In justifying the ban, officials claim other governments had met U.S. requests for biometric passports or information on terrorists and criminals, but that the eight banned countries failed to do the same.

Trump's initial travel ban has been widely criticized for religious discrimination, but despite the addition of non-Muslim nations into the new ban, critics believe it is still, essentially, a Muslim ban. 3448898]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMBRIYCSK6IWGAAULFKFT7UUNAESZSIQKEDFPGCTAFIFTCZJLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CC6/624/CC6624A1844D5A2213DF5B4CD1C824C9</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travel ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travel restrictions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ passport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ white house]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-tried-to-criticize-the-nfl-and-nba-it-didn-t-work-so-well-3448839</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump tried to criticize the NFL and NBA, it didn't work so well 3448839]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — President Trump criticized NFL players who lodge protests during the national anthem and encouraged offended snowflakes to walk out of games. 

Last Friday at one of his campaign rallies in Alabama, he said, Wouldn't you love to see one of these NFL owners, when somebody disrespects our flat, to say, 'Get that son of a b***h off the field right now. Out. He's fired! He's fired!' 

Trump said the protests are hurting the game. The Commander and Cheese also said referees are ruining the game by calling 15-yard penalties for beautiful tackles.

What happened next? The entire athletic world, including NFL owners, joined together in solidarity and gave Donald Trump a collective middle finger. 

Teams and NFL owners across the league on Sunday gave an unprecedented show of solidarity and support during the pregame anthem. 
In other sports news, Trump also decided to uninvite the NBA Champion Golden State Warriors while singling out Stephen Curry for having doubts. 
Only thing is, the Warriors already decided that they weren't going to go and the White House knew it. Either way...looking good Trump. 

Players young and old from all over the sporting world have come out to blast the president. 3448839]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNNFXXZBBZHFIVRWKAAFZKLSNEBSTURLA5DA5GAGAFIW5CRBAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/88C/17E/88C17E1C02E8E7C94F21BB3513BEAE1B</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>96</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ President Trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump criticizes NFL]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump uninvites Warriors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Warriors not going to White House]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NFL anthem protests]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/far-right-surge-to-third-place-in-germany-election-3448798</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Far right surge to third place in Germany election 3448798]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BERLIN — German chancellor Angela Merkel has secured her fourth term as Germany's leader, despite massive gains by the country's far-right.

According to the BBC, Angela Merkel's CDU-CSU coalition won with 33 percent of the vote, while the social democrats took around 20 percent and the far right AfD secured 13 percent.

The result will likely see a governing coalition between Merkel's conservatives and the fourth place Free Democrats, reported the BBC.

The election saw the heavily anti-migrant Alternative for Germany, or AfD, take third place in the vote. They want to close Europe's borders, install identity checks in Germany and ban minarets. The party also believes Germany isn't compatible with Islam. 3448798]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDFKCRBKIAAKW3HKBKR3LUTM5DBVFILKJLFTGIHAFIAAWTZLG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/398/380/398380CC8C59C0BBDEB4AE6A6E701BAB</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ germany election]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is afd]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ afd]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alternative for germany]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ germany elections]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Berlin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ germany election 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ democratic systems]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/human-ken-doll-detained-in-dubai-wants-to-be-barbie-3448730</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Human Ken doll detained in Dubai, wants to be Barbie 3448730]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES — Human Ken doll Rodrigo Alves had some trouble with Dubai immigration, after his plastic features got called out by the facial recognition software.

The Sun reports that body-obsessed Alves has been on a quest for plastic perfection. Over the years, he's blown half a million dollars to get nipped and tucked more than 50 times.

With so much surgery and so little time, even his official documents can't keep up. So while jet setting to Dubai recently, he got detained for looking nothing like his passport photo.

He had to wait three hours before being let into the country, though apparently that's not the first time it's happened.

Doctors have warned the 34-year-old not to get anything else fixed, but it seems Ken might be holding out for one last bang before he retires.

Claiming he doesn't want to end up a saggy old man, Alves says he'll pull a Caitlyn Jenner and get a sex change in his 50s.

So while his chicken and eggs are the only real part of him left, they need to go because Barbie's comin'.

But really, the more important concern is... what kind of barbie will he be? 3448730]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIAAPAAAKSJA7BZVBIAATK4WMECS3ET5A6KWMFIHAVGA5BZFKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/062/99B/06299BE6A40624A3568C904E3AB3FD37</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human ken doll]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmetic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dubai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dubai airport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immigration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sex change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ caitlyn jenner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ barbie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ken]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic doll]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-use-sunlight-to-turn-co2-into-water-and-ethanol-3448706</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists use sunlight to turn CO2 into water  and ethanol 3448706]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA — Scientists at the Berkeley Lab in California have developed technology that can convert carbon dioxide into ethanol using sunlight.

The research was published in the journal, Energy & Environmental Science. The study employed low amounts of solar energy in a copper-silver nanocoral cathode to produce the ethanol.

Reducing CO2 to a hydrocarbon end product like ethanol or ethylene can take up to 5 volts, start to finish, explained the study's lead author Gurudayal in a Berkeley Lab news release. Our system reduced that by half while maintaining the selectivity of products. 3448706]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIBWKCIAK5AAMBZXBSJARL4YM5DBIERQA6IW7HZBKIGA3WRAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4E3/871/4E387102DC3527351D849D183F781E87</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turning co2 into oxygen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial photosynthesis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ co2 to h2o]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon dioxide to ethanol]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon dioxide]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/60-of-plastic-pollution-in-oceans-comes-from-just-five-countries-3449553</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[60% of plastic pollution in oceans comes from just five countries 3449553]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — Plastic waste is slowly but surely taking over the world's oceans, and the bulk of them apparently comes from just five Asian countries.

According to a study from Ocean Conservancy called Stemming the Tide, 55-60% of plastic polluting the oceans comes from five countries: China, Indonesia, Philippines, Thailand, Vietnam.

Uncollected and mismanaged waste on land accounts for about 80% of the 8 million metric tons of trash that flow into the oceans each year.

Environmental organization Greenpeace claims corporations are also at fault for selling products in single-use plastic packaging, especially in so-called 'sachet economies' like the Philippines.

Various studies have shown that plastic pollution negatively impacts marine animals, and may be indirectly affecting humans through the food chain.

Fortunately, improving waste management practices in the five countries can result in a 45% reduction of global plastic waste leakage by 2025.

In tackling plastic pollution, everyone has a role to play. From governments and big conglomerates to the people on the street — every bit helps. 3449553]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLWACKUAZCAMXI7KBJW57LXMJLSIF3ZLSPF3TILKJLARDAEAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D50/CA4/D50CA42EFA3984CEB48187F3AF437237</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic waste]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic trash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indonesia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ philippines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thailand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vietnam]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-microsoft-just-made-a-4-000-mile-long-data-cable-3449369</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook, Microsoft just made a 4,000-mile-long data cable 3449369]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BILBAO, SPAIN /  VIRGINIA BEACH, VIRGINIA — Microsoft, Facebook and Spanish telecommunications giant Telxius have just completed work on a massive continent-to-continent underwater cable.

According to a Microsoft news release, the Marea undersea cable is comprised of eight pairs of fiber optic cables, encircled by copper, a layer of hard-plastic and a waterproof coating. 

The subsea cable stretches over 4,000 miles from the U.S. east coast at Virginia Beach, to Spain's north coast at Bilbao. 

When laying the cable, engineers had to account for an average depth of 11,000 feet and hazards including coral reefs, earthquake zones and active volcanoes.

The cable can transmit a maximum of 160 terabits per second. That's the equivalent of 71 million streaming high definition videos. 3449369]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIAFACRAKECAKAAXBMDR77SCMWLV5RANA2LW7UCSK6LFVAAFBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FB4/FF0/FB4FF0740F06AA4B66118E666FD6EAB8</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep sea cables]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ subsea cable]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marea cable]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microsoft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ telxius]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-would-a-hydrogen-bomb-blast-affect-the-pacific-ocean--3449362</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How would a hydrogen bomb blast affect the Pacific Ocean? 3449362]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — As the war of words between the United States and North Korea continues to escalate, Pyongyang hinted last week that it may test a hydrogen bomb in the Pacific Ocean. 

It could be the most powerful detonation of an H-bomb in the Pacific, Foreign Minister Ri Yong-ho told reporters at the United Nations General Assembly in New York, the Atlantic reported. 

If a hydrogen bomb did hit the Pacific, it would detonate with a blinding flash, while producing a massive mushroom cloud. The immediate fallout would depend on the height of detonation.  

The initial blast would instantly kill most fish and marine life in the blast area.  

The explosion would send radioactive particles flying through the air and into the water. Wind also has the potential to carry the particles hundreds of miles. 

The smoke created at the strike zone could potentially block the sun, hurting organisms that utilize photosynthesis. 

Radiation would lead to severe health problems for surrounding aquatic life. 

Humans could also be affected if radioactive fallout reaches land. Particles could contaminate air, water and soil. 3449362]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLFIXRJA5AFKAIXKEDATL2GMZAB3SK9LSPWTUZKK5DW3VIHKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/95E/288/95E288934E290CBDE71BEBBD7B840F0A</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hydrogen bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hydrogen bomb test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hydrogen bomb test Pacific Ocean]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-s-lung-cancer-turns-out-to-be-playmobil-toy-he-inhaled-as-a-kid-3450570</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man's lung cancer turns out to be Playmobil toy he inhaled as a kid 3450570]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PRESTON, UNITED KINGDOM — A UK man found out the hard way that the weird, dumb things you do as a kid do come back to haunt you.

The Guardian reports that the unnamed 47-year-old went to see a specialist after coughing and feeling sick for a year. 

Doctors spotted a mass in his lung which they initially thought to be a tumor.
But when they went to biopsy the mass, they discovered it wasn't cancer, but a miniature toy cone.

When presented with the tiny specimen, the man realized it was his long-lost Playmobil traffic cone, which he claimed to have inhaled as a 7-year-old.

Doctors believe the boy's body adapted to the foreign object, and absorbed it into the lining of the lung, where it remained for the next four decades.

It's not uncommon for children to accidentally swallow or inhale small objects, but it is pretty darn strange to be feeling the symptoms so long after the actual deed.

Still, the old chap is pretty lucky. His cough has nearly cleared, he doesn't have the big C, and he's got his old Playmobil back. Definitely winning at life, at least for now. 3450570]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2LWEAIEA5BR7AAYLBJA37LTGECVZRTZAVAWMHCRARAREBRHAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/598/40D/59840D263E0942CEA259299285E25B7E</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lung cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playmobil]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playmobil toy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lung tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lung mass]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic toy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toy in lung]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ inhaled toy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aspirated toy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-turbines-harness-electricity-from-wave-energy-3450540</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese turbines harness electricity from wave energy 3450540]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OKINAWA, JAPAN — Japanese researchers have come with special technology that can not only capture energy from waves, but also help protect coastlines.

According to the Okinawa Institute of Science and Technology, a team led by Professor Tsumoru Shintake plans to set up energy-harvesting turbines near tetrapods, which are concrete structures placed along the shore to weaken the force of incoming waves and prevent erosion.

The turbine has five flexible blades modelled after dolphin fins. It's supported by a stem that's anchored to the sea floor with mooring cables, which, like the blades, is flexible and can bend under pressure.

Inside the turbine head is a magnet electric generator, which transforms wave energy into electricity. The electricity is sent back to the shore via cables, to feed into the grid.

Using turbines on just 1% of Japan's coastline can generate roughly 10 gigawatts of energy, equivalent to about 10 nuclear power plants.

Apart from tetrapods, the turbines can also harness electricity near coral reefs.

They're built to be safe for marine life, with blade speed carefully calibrated so that any animals caught in them can escape unharmed.

The team is currently preparing to install two half-scale model turbines that will power LEDs as part of a commercial demonstration. 3450540]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJWICZAAMCRKAZ9LWIA7LSBMEBE7FZMAFPA5GTRAVDARWCWBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/3FC/26B/3FC26BA24DBE809A499BEDE1562CEF92</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turbine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wave energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wave energy converter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electricity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sustainable energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ energy source]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tetrapods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shore erosion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ erosion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ okinawa]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/massive-fatberg-causing-sewers-to-overflow-in-baltimore-3450352</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Massive fatberg causing sewers to overflow in Baltimore 3450352]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE — A massively disgusting fatberg has been found lurking in the sewers of Baltimore. 

The lump of congealed fat, wet wipes and other stuff you shouldn't flush down the toilet is growing and causing sewers to overflow. 

The Baltimore Department of Public Works said on Monday that it discovered the monstrosity earlier this month between Baltimore Penn Station and the 1700 block of Charles Street, the Baltimore Sun reported. 

So far, the fatberg has been responsible for a dry weather sewer outflow that discharged 1.2 millions gallons of sewage into the Jones Falls. 

The fatberg has mostly been scraped off and transported to a landfill. 

Apparently B-more has quite a few fatbergs lying around its sewers, although the other ones are smaller in size. 3450352]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZBWECKVKMBRPBZVLRAFT6LRGIASRSC2A2LWZFKYKABWIBTVBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A2C/97C/A2C97CC47A309A5C5A053C7760E6517E</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatberg sewers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Baltimore fatberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ congealed fat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ congealed oils]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/loot-eus-maximus-man-caught-smuggling-1-kg-of-gold-in-his-rump-3450325</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Loot-eus maximus! Man caught smuggling 1 kg of gold in his rump 3450325]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COLOMBO, SRI LANKA — A man from Sri Lanka is 1 kg lighter after he tried to smuggle that much gold out of the country. 

SKY NEWS
http://bit.ly/2xH6DQu

THE GUARDIAN
http://bit.ly/2fm52F2 3450325]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDWGAKUK5BA7BR7LZCRR6BFMJJSZSC6KJLFZFIBARBRKVAEKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E55/B25/E55B257996632942B0F2A78E1EF7E746</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man caught smuggling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smuggling gold]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smugglers busted]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ caught smuggling sri lanka]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ caught smuggling airport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colombo]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/thousands-of-bees-seen-swarming-over-indonesia-airplane-s-wing-3450319</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Thousands of bees seen swarming over Indonesia airplane's wing 3450319]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH SUMATRA, INDONESIA  —  A Citilink Indonesia plane reportedly landed at around 11:40 a.m. and was heading toward its parking spot when passengers noticed their vessel was surrounded by a swarm of bees.

The bee swarm formed a thick black cloud and clung to the plane's wing as they created a nest.

According to Citilink's vice president, the bees were later removed from the aircraft when water was sprayed onto the wing with a fire hose.

The removal process only caused a 90-minute delay.
 
The vice president theorized that what logging practices that have disrupted the bees natural habitat may have forced them to look for a new home. 3450319]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNFMDKTBIDRGAKAKADW5LSGGJLSTRCSKFIF7GZAKABWEBKUBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/670/307/6703070B796D2BFB53B5F4B8DEC4B811</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Bee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee attacks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee swarm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north sumatra]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indonesia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-s-border-wall-prototypes-begin-construction-in-otay-mesa-3450305</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump's border wall prototypes begin construction in Otay Mesa 3450305]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OTAY MESA, CALIFORNIA — Construction began on prototype designs for a border wall in a fenced-off area in Otay Mesa on Tuesday. 

Eight different designs will be constructed over the next 30-days, the San Diego Union-Tribune reported. 

Four of the prototypes will be concrete, while the other four will be made of various materials. All of the walls will be between 18 to 30 feet high and 30 feet long, according to the San Diego Union-Tribune. 

Six contractors from across the country have been chosen to build the prototypes. Bids for the prototypes ranged from $300,000 to $500,000. 

The construction site is about 1.5 miles east of Erico Fermi Drive. It is several miles east of the Otay Mesa Port of Entry, reported the San Diego Union-Tribune. 

The border wall project is underway despite lack of congressional funding. Estimates for the cost of the border wall have ranged up to $38 billion. 

The Department of Homeland Security is planning to pay for the prototypes with internal funds taken from other programs. 3450305]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIFCY3TAAAFCVTHKFIFT6LVMZEE7RC2KZAWZGREKAGAACRCAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9B8/ED1/9B8ED1DA4172C79AA6E0525A01DFAB54</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump border wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border wall prototypes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Otay Mesa border wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border wall construction]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-gets-bitten-by-venomous-snake-inside-virginia-restaurant-3450181</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman gets bitten by venomous snake inside Virginia restaurant 3450181]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FREDERICKSBURG, VIRGINIA — A Virginia woman hoping to get a big, juicy steak instead got a substantial helping of snake, with a side of venom.

The Free-Lance Star reports that while walking through the foyer at Longhorn Steakhouse with her family, Rachel Myrick's left foot got chomped on by an unlikely culprit. Thrice.

Initially thinking she got stung by a bee or hornet, Myrick groped her foot and realized to her horror that there was an 8-inch copperhead snake attached to it. After quickly shaking it off, her boyfriend and son stomped on the snake to kill it.

They then called 911, but left the dead snake on the floor so the EMTs could confirm what it was.

Waiting for help was excruciating, as Myrick's foot quickly began to swell. When the swelling later spread all the way to her hip and thigh, doctors gave her antivenin.

She has since been released after spending over five days in the hospital, but says the recovery will take about three more months. Ouch.

Copperhead bites aren't fatal to humans, but they're pretty painful.

The restaurant still doesn't know how the snake got in, but suspect it may slithered in from a retention pond down the hill. Probably wanted a nice, juicy steak, too. 3450181]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLFEDZJAZBRCBIVLSLFR6LVMZAEZFK7A6PFXTIEK5CWMCINKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EA5/A4C/EA5A4C8B4F7D1D455CE6F965E31802C5</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snake bite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ copperhead snake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snake in restaurant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snake venom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antivenom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antivenin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swollen foot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ venomous snake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virginia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ longhorn steakhouse]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/meet-the-super-pooch-giving-mexico-hope-after-deadly-earthquake-3450177</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Meet the super pooch giving Mexico hope after deadly earthquake 3450177]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY — Images of an adorable Mexican Navy rescue dog named Frida have gone viral on Twitter.

The Los Angeles Times
http://lat.ms/2hu14yx

Inhabitat
http://bit.ly/2ypmxfo 3450177]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AACFEDKTKRBRGBIRLECR77LTGVDSVRRILRDRZHZHAMAAKACSAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8D1/BF5/8D1BF509558148280504733842CC2643</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog saves people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog saves lives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frida mexico]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frida dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rescue dog mexico]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero dogs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ people saved by animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero dog stories]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/after-15-years-in-vegetative-state-man-responds-to-nerve-stimulation-3451506</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[After 15 years in vegetative state, man responds to nerve stimulation 3451506]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LYON, FRANCE — After being in a vegetative state for 15 years, a French man is showing some signs of consciousness after neurosurgeons implanted a vagus nerve stimulator in his chest, according to a study published Monday in Current Biology.  

The man, now 35, was involved in a car accident when he was 20 that left him unconscious, 

The vagus nerve extends from the brain to other parts in the body, including the heart, lungs and gut. 

Vagus nerve stimulation is already used to treat people with epilepsy and depression. 

Researchers wanted to test the ability of vagus nerve stimulation to restore consciousness in a person in a vegetative state. 

Patients in a vegetative state show no signs consciousness, mental activity or motor function, according to CNN. 

People in a vegetative state can occasionally open their eyes, however this is just a random physiological response. 

Vagus nerve stimulation begins with implanting a device in the chest and running a wire under the skin. This wire connects the vagus nerve and the device. The device sends electrical pulses along the nerve to the brainstem, which in turn transmits these impulses to certain brain areas.
  
Researchers found that after one month of stimulation, the patient’s attention, movements and brain activity significantly improved. 

The scientists are now planning a larger study to confirm and extend the potential of vagus nerve stimulation. 3451506]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IFKC3WBICRIWCFLSJRR9DVGZCSZSK5AVDRVURKASKACBKUAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/F1F/4BE/F1F4BEBB841448E993E24CAF9D7E89D6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[vagus nerve stimulation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[vegetative state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[vagus nerve]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[coma]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-dragged-off-southwest-flight-over-dog-allergy-complaint-3451329</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman dragged off Southwest flight over dog allergy complaint 3451329]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE — Another day, another passenger gets dragged off a plane. Surprisingly though, everyone seems to be on the airline's side on this one.

The Baltimore Sun reports that the commotion on the Southwest flight from Baltimore to L.A. began when a passenger complained about two dogs on her flight, claiming she was deathly allergic.

The 46-year-old woman demanded that the two animals be removed from the plane, but they couldn't, since one of the dogs was a service animal. 

She couldn't provide a medical certificate stating she was fit to travel, and was then asked to deplane, but refused. 

So as with most in flight kerfuffles, law enforcement had to step in. 

What followed next was some dramatic and pretty aggressive manhandling down the plane aisle, to the horror of the other passengers. At one point, the woman claimed the cops ripped her pants, and insisted she could walk on her own.

Officers pushed and pulled the uncooperative woman all the way off the plane, where she was then arrested and charged with disorderly conduct. 

The dragging definitely triggers major David Dao flashbacks, but the public isn't so sympathetic with this lady, who has been identified as Anila Daulatzai, a professor at the Maryland Institute College of Art. 

Many netizens pointed out that she was in the wrong for not being prepared, and that for someone who claimed to have a life-threatening pet allergy, she sure as heck didn't want off the puppy plane. 3451329]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJWEX3XBEBFIWR9BWPATLSBGIEBXF3SABJW3HRBAIARAVAKAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5E6/86E/5E686E8A27FDD85A241BDC2D9E392CDA</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>103</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ southwest airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman dragged off plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pet allergy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog allergy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deathly allergic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline drama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dragged off plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ david dao]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united airlines]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-kept-isolated-for-8-months-in-mars-simulation-3451220</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists kept isolated for 8 months in Mars simulation 3451220]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MAUI, HAWAII — A team of scientists have finally returned to civilization after completing a NASA-funded isolation experiment to simulate life on Mars.

NASA reports that the six-person HI-SEAS Mission V crew lived in a dome on the Mars-like landscape of Hawaii's Mauna Loa volcano for eight months.

The dome was equipped with a kitchen, bathroom, common area, and six individual bedrooms. Though not confined to the inside, the crew were required to don spacesuits whenever they went outside.

While in the habitat, the crew conducted scientific research, equipment testing, and resource tracking. They also had to learn to prepare food using dehydrated and shelf-stable ingredients.

Communications with the outside were subject to a delay of 20 minutes — the same amount of time it takes for signals to reach Mars from Earth.

To better understand the psychological impacts of a long-term space mission, they were fitted with sensors that gauged their moods and monitored interactions with other members.

The mission is the fifth in a series of six studies designed to help NASA select crews that can do well on an expedition to the red planet. The sixth and final HI-SEAS mission will also last for eight months and is slated to begin in January 2018. 3451220]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNAPAIDABLR5AR7BWLRZ72FGFJEZF36LWPATGZHBWJWABIEAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/77F/FD0/77FFD0AA873F0B5E707D231080E32627</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life on mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ isolation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ experiment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ simulation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ psychology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mauna loa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hawaii]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-hack-lets-hackers-control-atms-remotely-to-make-it-rain-3451203</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New hack lets hackers control ATMs remotely to make it rain 3451203]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO— Japanese cybersecurity firm Trend Micro has published a white paper detailing how hackers can remotely control ATMS.

According to Trend Micro, cybercriminals target banking staff with phishing emails. If a worker accesses the email, this allows the hacker to steal their identity. The hacker then uses the stolen digital credentials to enter the banking network where they begin to comb it for data on their target.

This is known as lateral movement. The hack is commonly seen in places where banks' main networks and ATM networks are not separated. Once that data is acquired, the hacker gains access to ATMs. They then order machines to dispense so-called jackpot amounts of cash to standby mules, waiting to collect.

Hackers using this technique have kept away from ATMs in the US and Canada, but Trend Micro expects the threat to become stronger in the future. 3451203]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANKACCTSB2IRKAZRL2IRKKLYMIABTSAQKEDFZTICA6JRGAABKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D67/268/D67268ADB7A3A44AE72A17FB9A236353</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ATM Hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New ATM hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ATM hack 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trend micro]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ATMs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ATM cyber security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trend Micro]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyber theft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ATM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Virtual skimming]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/worker-falls-down-40-foot-hole-at-trump-prototype-border-wall-site-3451162</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Worker falls down 40-foot hole at Trump prototype border wall site 3451162]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OTAY MESA, CALIFORNIA — A worker who wasn't paying attention fell down a 40-foot hole at Trump's border wall prototype construction site in Otay Mesa. 

The worker escaped without serious injury and eventually went back to work, according to U.S. Custom and Border Protection spokesman Carlos Diaz, NBC San Diego reported. 

The man was digging the foundation for one of the wall prototypes at the time. Apparently, a double layer of plywood was supposed to prevent these types of accidents from occurring. 

The construction worker was practicing excellent workplace safety by walking backwards and not looking where he was going. 

He fell into the 40-foot hold around 10 a.m. 

He was hoisted out of the hole and checked for injuries on scene. As he was okay, he got back to work. 

Construction of eight wall prototypes began this week. Six contractors from across the country have 30-days to complete their walls. 

As to who's going to pay for all this in the end...clearly it's without a doubt going to be Mexico. 3451162]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKWMXZJB5DFIVZ9BJLRVKBCGVEETRK7K2PWMURDAJKAIBKVAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/686/994/686994F0B15C8CD86BCB034FB0AF9ADD</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump Border Wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Border Wall prototypes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump Border Wall prototypes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ construction worker falls down hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man falls down hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Otay Mesa]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-president-trump-played-the-nfl-with-tweets-3451155</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How President Trump played the NFL with tweets 3451155]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — What seemed like Fox-inspired tweets from the commander-in-chief, were actually a series Twitter touchdowns that stole NFL Sunday from the NFL, and took #nationalanthem into overtime. 3451155]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IAMDTVBJLACVTELZDR594RMMESXFINKRCAZHAKAMBRIV3XBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FE7/916/FE791673898DAE52D3F1FDD260B09FB6</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nfl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ donald trump]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump v nfl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nfl kneeling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ national anthem]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kneeling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GOP]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-investigates-the-effects-of-space-radiation-on-human-body-3451003</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA investigates the effects of space radiation on human body 3451003]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — One of NASA’s biggest challenges in designing a mission to Mars is how to protect astronauts on the long journey through space.

NASA’s Human Research Program is researching how space radiation affects the human body.

“One of our biggest challenges on a mission to Mars is protecting astronauts from radiation,” said NASA Space Radiation Element Scientist Lisa Simonsen, reported Science Daily. “You can’t see it; you can’t feel it. You don’t know you’re getting bombarded by radiation.”

Space radiation has enough energy to violently collide with nuclei that make up spacecraft shielding and human tissue, according to Science Daily.

The collisions cause both the shielding nuclei and space radiation to break-up into several different types of new particles known as secondary radiation.

NASA is currently investigating the effects of galactic cosmic rays (GCRs) on the human body.

One of the main difficulties is that it’s hard to simulate space radiation on Earth. Lab doses of radiation could be stronger and given for a shorter time than actual conditions in space. 3451003]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKFPAAJBZDR7CIWBNPA76D3MFJS3ECZKSKWPUTSANJWEWRBAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D18/9B1/D189B18DABDA4B25BA26111C5357CD7D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/your-heart-could-be-the-new-passcode-for-your-phone-3450891</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Your heart could be the new passcode for your phone 3450891]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BUFFALO, NEW YORK — Researchers at the University of Buffalo have developed a new biometric tool that scans your heart to unlock your phone or log onto your computer.

Scientists have designed a system that uses a low-level Doppler radar to identify the shape and size of a person's heart, Gadgets Now reported. 

The system needs eight seconds to record the shape and person's heartbeat. It then continuously monitors the person's presence. 

Researchers claim the system poses no health risks as the radar system uses very little power. 

It is a passive, non-contact device, so people don't have to spend time authenticating themselves.

The heart scanner works on individuals up to a distance of 30 meters (98 ft). 

The team now says they will work on shrinking down the system so it can be installed onto computer keyboards and smartphones. 3450891]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIFGXAABIBWPCCHLVBAV6LUGVEETFK3ABIW3FIDAFJRIYIKKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BD9/EA1/BD9EA15607782E2D710464D6DDF2C354</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart phone passcode]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart computer passcode]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biometric tool]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biometric heart tool]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mega-iceberg-breaks-up-with-antarctica-3450883</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mega iceberg breaks up with Antarctica 3450883]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA —  A massive iceberg broke apart from of the Pine Island Glacier in Antarctica this week.

The break has scientists worried that Pine Island Glacier's behavior might be changing, reported Weather.com.

The area that broke apart is said to be 4.5 times the size of New York's Manhattan island.

Loss of ice from the glacier contributes to a 1 millimeter rise in the world's oceans, every eight years. 3450883]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AABWKXCTLECWPBA9BVDWZ9LSGNJEXFIQABJRXTKXKIDAMCK3KA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5AE/32D/5AE32D9BBE1151358E8101BDF5ED2717</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>32</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iceberg breaking off glacier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ icebergs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ manhattan iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antarctica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iceberg melting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super iceberg]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-how-a-robot-tax-may-work-in-the-uk-3452133</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's how a robot tax may work in the UK 3452133]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRIGHTON, UNITED KINGDOM — Calls from the British Labour leader Jeremy Corbyn to publicly manage automation this week have led to speculation he is looking to tax robots, but how would that work?

Replacing workers with robots, means less salary and more profit for businesses, but also less taxes on salary for the state to collect. Any robot tax would likely need to fill this gap in public finances.

The Institute for Fiscal Studies estimates that the British government will collect £716.5 billion for the tax year 2016 to 2017. According to the IFS figures 43.1 percent, or £308.6 billion, of this is contributed by the 30 million people in the British workforce.

Separately, a PWC study estimates that 10 million British workers may lose their jobs to automation. If permanent, and not counting the amount the government may save from automation, this would lead to a shortfall of £92.6 pounds, or 30%, in what the British state collects.

A flat robot tax may help fill this gap. However, calls for automation to help people live comfortably via state-provided benefits — such as a universal income — may well see automation taxes rise. Such a move would likely scare off private industry from investing in the United Kingdom. 3452133]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFLWIYIDAMAWEB3CB6PRT72AGWLSZUZLLSPA5G3WKVGWCAIAAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6D5/144/6D5144B350D547EB2EC381AB7F903830</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[taxing robots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[robot tax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[jeremy corbyn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[automation tax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[auto tax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[taxing machines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[labour conference]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[technology tax]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/earth-formed-via-planetary-collisions-new-research-suggests-3451945</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Earth formed via planetary collisions, new research suggests 3451945]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — Two new studies published in the journal Nature may have shed some light on how Earth's strange chemical make-up came to be.

The Washington Post reports that the solar system began some 4.6 billion years ago as a swirling disk of gas and dust. This all came together to form rocks, planetesimals, and eventually, full-sized planets.

Scientists have long been puzzled by the difference in composition between Earth and the meteorites believed to have formed it. The answer, it seems, lies in Earth's explosive history.

Early Earth often collided with other planetary bodies, with the impact generating enough heat to turn rocks into either magma or hot vapor. 

One study, led by a University of Bristol geochemist, calculated that planet lost 40 percent of its mass from this process.

A second study, from Oxford University, combined Earth rock with volatile elements such as gold, silver, and zinc oxide, and heated it to 1,300 degrees Celsius. After cooling the rock, they discovered that the volatile elements had evaporated.

This same vapor loss was found in samples from Mars and the asteroid Vesta, suggesting that the phenomenon occurs in similar-sized bodies. 3451945]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFJFMXRDAZBWKWAUKFKRIK2BMZDBVSTZLRDAXGZHBRAWGXANAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1BC/A52/1BCA52A51D740CCEF2E85EF0DFCEA6C1</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth formation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ accretion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ planetary accretion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ planet formation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth composition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ outer space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meteorites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chondrites]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-may-be-able-to-diagnose-cte-in-players-while-they-re-alive-3451791</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists may be able to diagnose CTE in players while they're alive 3451791]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOSTON — Researchers may have found a way to diagnose chronic traumatic encephalopathy (CTE) in football players while they are still alive. 

CTE is a progressive brain disease caused by repeated trauma to the head. It usually shows up years after taking repeated blows to the head, and can lead to symptoms like confusion, depression, aggression, memory retention, and other forms of cognitive degeneration, according to Quartz. 

Currently, CTE can only be diagnosed through an autopsy. Researchers have found that people who had CTE displayed abnormal clusters of the tau protein throughout the brain.
Doctors believe the tau protein is responsible for killing off neurons.  

Researchers at Boston University wanted to look for other markers in people suffering from CTE. 

Scientists found that people with CTE showed elevated levels of the protein CLL11 in both spinal fluid and the blood around the brain in the skull. 

They believe the CLL11 protein helps the smallest blood vessels in the brain move oxygen. Higher levels of CLL11 could mean these blood vessels are leaking, which may lead to CTE symptoms. 

The team at Boston University is now working with a biotech company to develop a blood test to detect CLL11 and diagnose living players. 

More research still needs to be conducted on the CLL11 protein to confirm it isn't linked with other kinds of neurodegenerative diseases. 

There's no cure for CTE, but early diagnosis could give players a chance to mitigate the disease. 3451791]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKWPAAJAEBA7ARSLJKFR74RNBJSVRK3ABPAZHZAKBKFABZQBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/145/70C/14570C6D89F4E0CCA53CF6FB0DE66088</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-09-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[CTE]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[CTE diagnosis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[chronic traumatic encephalopathy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[CTE football player]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[CTE symptoms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[football concussions]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
