<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/computer-bug-grants-too-many-american-airline-pilots-x-mas-off-3494954</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Computer bug grants too many American Airline pilots X'mas off 3494954]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FORT WORTH, TEXAS — A computer bug in American Airlines allowed way too many pilots the chance to take the fronight between December 17 and December 31 off.

As a result, the airliner is facing a shortage of pilots this festive period, putting thousands of Christmas flights in jeopardy.

American has got some pilots in reserve, but is offering pilots 1.5 times normal pay to come back for the holiday season.

Reportedly, it may impact flights from Charlotte, Salt Lake City, Dallas, Boston, Miami, New York and Philly. 3494954]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAWCCACLIAAPBISLVCWR7BBGSJEZRT3LWIWZGCXAWNWMDRBAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BAE/709/BAE709B2A2D9266A0EB681D9B2A24E07.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T11:01:10+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ american airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pilot landing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aa pilots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ american]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas vacation pilots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ going home for christmas]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-how-the-bitcoin-bubble-could-pop-3494826</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's how the Bitcoin bubble could pop 3494826]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — Cryptocurrency Bitcoin swelled to $11,000 per coin on Wednesday, prompting intense speculation about the latest bubble and how and why it could soon pop.

According to Bloomberg, developers divided on how to upgrade the Bitcoin network have led to fragmentation of the original currency into different versions, too much of which could be a problem. 

Bitcoin's history of being used to buy illicit materials from the dark web means regulators are watching and could crackdown any time, especially if it grows big enough to impact a nation's monetary policy.

As an intangible asset, Bitcoins have previously been targeted by hackers, and may again fall victim to digital theft.

Though the value bitcoin is volatile, at the moment, it's at an all-time high. But because the supply is virtually limitless, there is a risk of collapse in value if demand should ever go down.

Experts have likened the bitcoin craze to the dotcom bubble, Tulip Mania, and other economic bubbles — all of which burst spectacularly.

If they're to be believed, Bitcoin's downward spiral is only a matter of time. 3494826]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWKRACIHB2IRMAKCLECW59SBNEBV5UT2AAAWMFIEAZHWPYRLKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/429/8A1/4298A132127FC8CCEB511EF14A990E8A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T08:58:25+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin bubble]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ currency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ economic bubble]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin cash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin gold]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin bubble burst]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin bubble pop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin crash]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/why-meghan-markle-will-not-be-princess-meghan-after-wedding-3494658</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Why Meghan Markle will not be Princess Meghan after wedding 3494658]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON, UK — Meghan Markle, the Suits star will soon become a member of the British royal family after her recent engagement with Prince Harry, however, the TV star will not be known as Princess Meghan when she ties the knot with Prince Harry next year.

Markle does not have royal blood in her ancestry, same as her future-sister-in-law, Catherine Middleton, who was later named Her Royal Highness, Princess William of Wales.

Royal blood is the key to determining how a princess is named. So if the queen grants them a royal dukedom, Prince Harry and Markle may be known as the Duke and Duchess of Sussex, or Markle could otherwise be named Her Royal Highness, Princess Henry of Wales.

Prince Harry and Markle are set marry at St George's Chapel at Windsor Castle next May and the couple will embark their first visit in Nottingham on Friday, Buckingham palace has announced. 3494658]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJLAGYIABWJFEVR9LFJFXLBFGMESTSRQKFKFPFKTAMFRKAIMAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C0F/92B/C0F92BEC64C3277918E7CA7D0CE4BDF9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T06:28:32+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ royalty]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ royal family]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prince harry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meghan markle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ engagement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weddings]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rings]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/giant-asteroid-3200-phaethon-will-pass-close-to-earth-3494645</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Giant asteroid 3200 Phaethon will pass close to Earth 3494645]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — NASA has announced that a giant space rock will be passing close to Earth next month, but assures everyone that the fly-by is friendly, and not cause for concern.

CBS reports that 3200 Phaethon is an asteroid with a diameter of 3 miles that has been labelled 'potentially dangerous' because its orbit crosses paths with the Earth.

Phaeton will be the closest to Earth on December 16, when it is projected to be within 6.4 million miles or 27 lunar distances of our planet. It hasn't gotten this close since 1974, and isn't expected to swing by again until 2093.

Phaethon may be named after a Greek demigod who nearly destroyed Earth, but those worried about a catastrophic collision can rest easy, since the giant rock is in a relatively stable orbit, and isn't a threat.

Astronomers believe the asteroid to be the parent body for the annual Geminid meteor shower, which happens when the Earth passes through Phaethon's debris field. 3494645]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACFAAACL5AR7WZ9LBKWRK4WNEDBISAIKVDWTTZEAMGAIWKTKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/52C/A48/52CA489DB00970402D8FCCD1A7AE72C5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T06:18:21+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3200 phaethon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid passes earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid orbit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid collision]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space rock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geminid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meteor shower]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geminid meteor shower]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/origami-inspired-soft-robotic-limbs-are-crazy-strong-3494603</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Origami inspired soft robotic limbs are crazy strong 3494603]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — Researchers from the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Harvard University have developed origami-inspired artificial muscles that can lift up to one thousand times their own weight. 

The devices could be used on next-generation soft robots, to be deployed within the body or outer space, the LA Times reported. 

The scientists wanted to make robots that were soft and compliant yet had strength similar to hard-bodied systems. 

The group used origami techniques to create muscle-like devices that could allow for limb flexibility without the need for hard parts. 

They made devices that could shorten, curl, twist or bend when compressed and sealed them in a polymer bag and filled them with air or other fluids. 
Vacuuming the air out then allowed for movement to grip, lift and twist objects. 

The team discovered the origami muscles could squeeze down to a tenth of their original size or lift up to a thousand times their own weight. 

Soft robotic limbs could be used in the future on small scales within the body or on large scales for outer space construction. 3494603]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6JACDAFBFIAGAKCKBJR5LDTGVDV7RZNLWJW3TKRBVFWCVRFAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/321/A66/321A660983E332FA57E55AF19BBD04D8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T05:17:00+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>40</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial muscle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soft robots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soft robotic limb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ origami inspired robots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ soft robotics]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/supermoon-to-light-up-the-night-sky-on-december-3-3494593</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Supermoon to light up the night sky on December 3 3494593]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOMONEWS MOON BASE — Budding astronomers will be able to take in a super moon this on December 3.
 
During a supermoon event, the lunar body can become bigger and up to 30% brighter.

This is because the moon orbits closer to the Earth than it does in a regular orbit.

NASA advises that a supermoon is best viewed outside a city due as powerful urban lights can diminish how bright it actually is. 3494593]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARCFIX3XL5CWIAZXL2LRV9JANFKBVURIKVAFRTAFAMARPBINAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BCC/276/BCC276C685164E6AE053BF7465BB46CD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-11-30T05:04:05+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>33</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super moon 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supermoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supermoon lunar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supermoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moon in the sky]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ supermoon nasa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/teen-says-she-got-50-surgeries-to-transform-into-angelina-jolie-3495873</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Teen says she got 50 surgeries to transform into Angelina Jolie 3495873]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN — An Angelina Jolie ultra-fan from Iran is going viral after journeying through a thousand cuts to look like her idol.

19-year-old Sahar Tabar claims she's undergone over 50 surgeries to to achieve her shocking transformation. She also lost a ton of weight in her quest to be as slim as Jolie, and now weighs just 88 pounds.

Tabar has been posting photos of her new look on her Instagram account, which has amassed nearly 500,000 followers.

Netizens have been pretty brutal with their comments, saying she looks more like Tim Burton's 'Corpse Bride' than a Hollywood star.

Others aren't buying the crazy plastic surgery schtick, and believe she's using makeup and prosthetics to exaggerate her features. If she is, then those are some mad skills.

One user on Reddit is convinced she's using photoshop too, after spotting weird distortions in some of her photos.

Whatever it is, if internet fame was the end game, then she definitely got her 15 minutes. 3495873]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2LWECZEA5ERXYAUKBPRTLBGGFIEREZNABJW7TZCBRFAMYAHKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E6A/073/E6A073BDD5EA23C6A5FA56E590DFF4EC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ angelina jolie lookalike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ celebrity lookalike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extreme plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ makeup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthetics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ corpse bride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sahar tabar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extreme body modification]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/get-your-justin-trudeau-christmas-calendar-now-or-don-t-3495864</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Get your Justin Trudeau Christmas calendar now, or don't 3495864]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['Murica — Apparently a thing this Christmas is a Prime Minister Justin Trudeau Calendar edition called 'My Canadian Boyfriend'. 

The calendar was spotted at various places around the U.S. over the weekend.  
On Amazon, it is described as a true celebration of the man, the myth, and the meme that is Justin Trudeau.

The calendar maker said he wanted to create something different. 

A few people noticed the calendar over the Twittersphere. But not that many. 

At least he's better than Trump. Meh. 3495864]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABJFKDKTAIHA3YRTBBIR59D3MBKE7U34K2LW3GZEKZHAAXREAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0DD/961/0DD9612763A244EAAA5706DE72E41DDD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>36</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ justin trudeau]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ calendar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ justin trudeau calendar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canada]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canadian prime minister]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uk-says-yes-to-over-the-counter-viagra-sales-3495795</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UK says yes to over-the-counter Viagra sales 3495795]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM — Britain has decided to green light Viagra sales without a prescription. 

Pfizer announced on Tuesday it's planning to release the non-prescription version in the spring of 2018 under the name Viagra Connect. 

The little blue pill will only be available in pharmacies, and pharmacists will have to determine if the individual is really in need.  

So far Viagra is the only ED medicine to be reclassified to over-the-counter. 3495795]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZAACAKVKBNACCCHKBPAR9U4MMEBZEAKLRDA3URDAAFWMARIKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0A9/D18/0A9D187064D03A1D8E7C79672C484E17.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK pharmaceutical sales]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK medical sales]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK over the counter sales]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ over the counter medicine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ over the counter sales]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pfizer]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/robots-are-stealing-all-the-good-jobs-3495486</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Robots are stealing all the good jobs 3495486]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — Looks like 400 to 800 million people worldwide could be out of a job by 2030 thanks to good old automation. 

McKinsey Global Institute looked at 800 different jobs across 46 countries and found up to 20 percent of the global workforce could get kicked to the curb. 

Wealthy countries like the US and Germany will have to retrain about one-third of their workforces. 
Factory workers and fast food workers are in the most danger. 

Poorer countries won't have to worry as much about the rise of the robots — for now. 

Other jobs in jeopardy from automation are mortgage brokers, paralegals, accountants and office administrative workers.    

Jobs that require more of a human touch like doctors, teachers, bartenders and lawyers should be okay. Wait a second — the world could always use FEWER lawyers. 3495486]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JRMDCVANPRZDITBSJRI9SCMIDSZR39LSLAXFCSAMAAEBRAAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B2E/475/B2E4752381E676D39C6F5649981F59EF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot workers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot automation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot factory workers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot fast food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot accountant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot real estate broker]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-crack-yeti-samples-it-s-a-bear-and-a-wee-bit-of-dog--3495478</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists crack Yeti samples: It's a bear (and a wee bit of dog) 3495478]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BUFFALO, NEW YORK — Wicked science coming out of Buffalo, New York says the abominable snowman isn't much of man at all.

Scientists at the University of Buffalo, New York used their mad skills to analyze 9 so-called Yeti samples from several museum and private collections. Turns out those Yeti samples were just bears and a dog.

That's one Asian black bear, one Himalayan brown bear, six Tibetan brown bears and some pooch's tooth.

According to CNN, previous research looking at suspected yeti hair samples found they came from ancient polar bears, dogs and other bears. 3495478]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNNWVDRJBMAR5DAVKFIRK6DUMBKB3SCSLRBWRT3SABPFAWZHBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C19/D0D/C19D0D591294A8722809D52EB4D1110D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big foot myster solved]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sasquatch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yeti mystery solved]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptozoology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yeti]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snowman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ himalayan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yetis are just bears]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/morons-behind-traveling-butts-instagram-arrested-in-thailand-3495472</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Morons behind 'Traveling Butts' Instagram arrested in Thailand 3495472]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BANGKOK, THAILAND — Two American tourists were busted by Thai authorities after taking photos of their behinds in front of a sacred Buddhist temple. 
Joseph and Travis Dasilva posted full moon snaps at the Wat Arun temple to their Instagram account Traveling Butts. For some reason, the account is now deleted.

These two buttheads had the creativity to take pictures of their rear ends at tourist spots around the world. They had more than 14,000 people dumb enough to follow them. 

Unfortunately, their trip has now been tainted after being arrested Tuesday night at a Bangkok airport and face public indecency charges. 
Beavis and Butthead caused quite the uproar after their photos were shared widely online, which led to a police investigation. 
The couple thought they could slip through the crack, but ended up landing right in it instead. 
The two each had to pay a $150 fine and have been handed over to immigration. 

Officials are now deciding if Moons over My Hammies will be busted under Thailand's computer crimes act which carries a punishment of up to five years behind bars. 3495472]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCAAYCVKSNWZDIRBNPRI6JGMBJBTRRLKMCFZHZGKEFFPBAHKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A44/CEE/A44CEE6F1DBCFA244F12066DD4B90293.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-02T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ American tourists]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ American tourists arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tourists arrested Thailand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wat Arun temple]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Joseph Travis Dasilva]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/musk-s-boring-company-bids-to-build-chicago-express-travel-pods-3497550</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Musk's Boring Company bids to build Chicago express travel pods 3497550]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — Elon Musk's Boring Company has put in a bid to build an express transit link between O'Hare airport and downtown Chicago. 
Chicago Mayor Rahm Emanuel announced the city would be accepting proposals to build an express service from the airport to downtown last Wednesday, according to Newsweek.  
Soon after Musk tweeted, The Boring Company will compete to fund, build and operate a high-speed Loop connecting Chicago O'Hare Airport to downtown. 

The loop would be a system of tunnels underneath the city that would use electric pods rather than a vacuum tube like the hyperloop concept. 

The proposed route would be less than 20 miles and would need to take less than 20 minutes, according to Mayor Emanuel. 
The Boring Company will need  to present plans on design, finance, construction, operation and maintenance of the Loop system. No taxpayer funding will be made available for the transit project. 3497550]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJKAPCIAA6IRMDZTB6JWR7DTMRCETFC4ABIWZHTRKAHWIAZFAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6C4/104/6C4104BA4E1DD865F959D3F6A83E0B94.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Boring Company]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Elon Musk Boring Company]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chicago O'hare electric pod transit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chicago travel pods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chicago airport transit system]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/canadian-model-might-get-eye-removed-after-botched-tattoo-job-3497466</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Canadian model might get eye removed after botched tattoo job 3497466]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ONTARIO, CANADA — A Canadian model could be losing one of her eyes after a botched procedure left it swollen and purple.

The Washington Post reports that months ago, Catt Gallinger had her sclera stained by a tattoo artist who was also her then-boyfriend. The artist was horribly inexperienced. He didn't mix the ink with saline, and used a large needle instead of a small one.

The injection went too deep into the eye, delivering too much undiluted purple ink in one go, and resulting in an infection. Gallinger felt intense pain shortly afterward, and began leaking purple ink from her eye.

She was prescribed antibiotic eye drops, which only helped spread the infection. Soon, a clump formed around her cornea and her eyes swelled shut.

Doctors were supposed to operate on the 24-year-old so they could cut out the lump, then do an amniotic tissue graft to replace lost tissue. But when Gallinger attempted to go in for surgery without sedation in November, she suffered the worst panic attack of her life.

The missed operation has put her at a higher risk of eye loss, and though sedated surgery is still a possibility, she claims she's now considering eye removal.

Gallinger has been open about her ordeal, and hopes it will serve as a cautionary tale to anyone wanting to get similarly risky procedures done.

The Ontario government has since added a ban on cosmetic eye tattoos to avoid more cases like Gallinger's. 3497466]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIWADZAAIDAADRVLNJWTKBFGNKBVFC9LWLFXURKAJNAEBRQKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/47E/C7E/47EC7E642D533EED1AB0A68796E7EBD1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>84</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eyeball tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye infection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ purple eyes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sclera tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sclera stain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tattoo gone wrong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ scleral pigmentation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ body modification]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/brown-bear-steals-rifles-from-hunter-goes-rogue-in-siberia-3497380</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Brown bear steals rifles from hunter, goes rogue in Siberia 3497380]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[IRKUTSK, RUSSIA — A wild bear turned the tables on a hunter after making off with not one, but two of the man's firearms.

The 57-year-old had taken refuge at a remote cabin in Siberia's Irkutsk region, and was out getting water when a brown bear snuck into his sanctuary, according to the Siberian Times.

The animal seemed taken with some hunting rifles, and latched on to them. When the man returned, he spotted the bear and quickly ran into the woods, where he hid for several hours.

By the time he came back to the cabin, the bear was gone, but so were his Vepr carbine and IZH shotgun. For the next few days, the hunter searched the taiga for his guns, but failed miserably.

He finally called the cops, who are now investigating the bizarre incident. So far, they've found bite marks on a plastic bucket, and scratches on some logs at the cabin.

No leads on the rifle-stealing bear, though, who's probably out somewhere having fun at getting to be the hunter instead of the hunted.

Meanwhile, the actual hunter is facing a fine and could forfeit his right to buy and use guns for a year. All thanks to a gun crazy bear. 3497380]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2JWVYAEAAGFGARXKACRTLUWMIBBVRT4AFPWVU3TASNWMWIKAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/43A/5DC/43A5DC3B02C99F26CDE077FE6ED01ED1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brown bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ siberia brown bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ guncrazy bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armed bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ siberia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trigger happy bear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armed and dangerous]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bear on the loose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hunting rifles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rifles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hunter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cathay-pacific-crew-saw-nk-missile-blow-up-from-plane-3498376</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cathay Pacific crew saw NK missile blow up from plane 3498376]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEA OF JAPAN —  A crew on board a Cathay Pacific flight saw a North Korean missile blow up over the Sea of Japan last week.  

Cathay Pacific CX893 was en route to Hong Kong from SF on November 29, when the crew saw the missile from their plane as it was passing over Japan, CNBC reported. 

The crew watched the DPRK missile blow up and fall apart during re-entry. 

They immediately contacted Japanese air traffic control to report the event.

Cathay says it has no plans to alter its routes in the region.

It's not like you really have to worry about the North Korean missiles anyways. It's the US ones you need to watch out for.   

Pyongyang's launched its latest ballistic missile test last Wednesday despite international sanctions and warnings. 3498376]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NRICKVB6IRPBATLAAFX94SGMEBZRRNKSKW7T3WBVAFTCZEBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AA4/367/AA4367752DE8934C499078CCA2125046.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Korea test]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ North Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cathay Pacific North Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cathay Crew saw missile fall apart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cathay Crew North Korea missile]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/doctors-fired-after-baby-wakes-up-on-the-way-to-his-own-funeral-3498294</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Doctors fired after baby wakes up on the way to his own funeral 3498294]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI — A hospital in India is in very hot water after doctors mistakenly declared a newborn was a goner — when he really wasn't. 3498294]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMAFPXRJKRBFIWZUKFJFX7URGFKVZU35AVAW7HAAA5FA3CZLBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/110/F1D/110F1DA2585C0D2417541A968B44A3AC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ premature baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twin babies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ preterm babies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby wakes up]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby funeral]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ max hospital]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby in a bag]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uk-cop-uses-bare-hands-to-stop-van-from-falling-off-bridge-3498255</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UK cop uses bare hands to stop van from falling off bridge 3498255]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[YORKSHIRE, UNITED KINGDOM — A UK cop is being hailed a hero after stopping a vehicle from falling over a bridge using just his bare hands and sheer determination.

According to a press release from the West Yorkshire Police, the van had been driving through icy conditions on the A1(M) in Yorkshire when it skidded off the road and was left dangling precariously over a motorway bridge.

When traffic officer Martin Willis arrived on the scene, he realized the driver was still trapped and hanging upside down in the van.

Not willing to let the van fall over the edge, Motorway Martin grabbed hold of a wheel to keep the vehicle from swaying. He held on for 15 minutes until help arrived.

The rescue operation took two hours, but ended with the 22-year-old driver being rescued, and the van being pulled to safety. The poor driver suffered serious leg injuries and was immediately taken to the hospital.

Motorway Martin, meanwhile, is getting applause from all corners of the internet, for acting swiftly and saving a man's life. 3498255]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJWPDZBA5BACW3FLEDWTL2BGECBTERMK6PWMU3YKIAAVBIEAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DB1/023/DB1023DD56C2336160FA1DA6A7E5338B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero cop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero police officer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super cop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super strength]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motorway martin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uk cop]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/indian-man-found-with-263-coins-and-100-nails-in-his-stomach-3498039</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Indian man found with 263 coins and 100 nails in his stomach 3498039]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DELHI, INDIA — Doctors in India who first thought they were treating a man with abdominal pain were shocked to find coins and nails in his stomach.

After complaining of abdominal pains for about a month, 32-year-old Maksud Khan was admitted to Sanjay Gandhi hospital in Delhi on November 19th.

Doctors initially thought Khan was suffering from food poisoning, but then they soon discovered that the cause of his pain was far more serious. The X-ray and ultrasound result revealed multiple metal objects in Khan's abdomen ranging from coins to razor blades. 

Khan underwent surgery on November 24 to remove the metal objects, during which a laparoscope was used to find them all. Doctors discovered 263 coins, 1.5 kg of nails, shards of glass, stones, shaving blades, and a rusted iron shackle inside Khan's abdomen.

Doctors said Khan is now in stable condition, and is expected to heal without any long term damage. However, after talking to Khan's family, doctors believed the incident is caused by Khan's depression. 3498039]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMBWVCRJK5HRIW3DKFLRX94RGVESVET5LRBWVHZDBREF3WALLH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D60/8F8/D608F890286DD2C068F123A4F3360FD2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ depression]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ india]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ delhi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ food poisoning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eating disorder]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/grandmother-hilariously-mistakes-an-opossum-for-one-of-her-cats-3498026</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Grandmother hilariously mistakes an opossum for one of her cats 3498026]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KANSAS — An animal-loving grandmother in Kansas was found to have an opossum hanging out among her stray cats. 

Eric Hertlein's grandmother has a big heart, especially for our furry little friends. She's set up a nice spot in her enclosed porch with beds and food, the Dodo reported. 

Looks like she's also been caring for a clever little imposter for the past few months.
Her grandson Eric dropped by for a visit recently. When he went to check on the cats, his kitty-sense started tingling. Right there among the felines was an opossum chilling in his own bed. 

When Hertlein asked his grandmother about the little dude, she said she had named him Tete and that he'd first come to her house when he was an orphaned baby looking for food. 
So naturally, she took the opossum in. Since then, he's be coming back for the grub and witty conversation. 
Eric's grandmother really thought Tete was just a cat at first, but when she finally did see it was an opossum, she said, well, he hasn't bothered me yet, so I'm OK with him being here!
Hey, if granny says it's cool. It's cool. 3498026]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIAWPCRIKVBAIVIRBWIWRKDXMREVTSCRA6IWMU3WAVHAAWKSAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EB5/1B8/EB51B872A797C5E2675CD43979BEF1D2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ opossum mistaken for cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sneaky opossum]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ grandmother mistakes opossum cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ grandmother opossum cat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stray cats]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/massive-bubble-of-hot-rock-rising-under-new-england-3499016</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Massive bubble of hot rock rising under New England 3499016]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW ENGLAND — First 150 characters of description should repeat as many keywords from title as possible. Do not exceed 150 characters in first graf. This is so that the subscribe link appears above the dropdown bar.

Idyllic New England could eventually become a hotbed of volcanic activity, after scientists find a huge bubble of hot rock beneath the region.

Using data from earthquake measurement devices, Rutgers University researchers analyzed the speed and direction of seismic waves to visualize subsurface conditions.

According to a university press release, they detected a massive upwelling of hot rock under Vermont, New Hampshire, and Massachusetts, after noticing the area was noticeably hotter than neighboring regions.

Though the hot mass is slowly and steadily rising, it will take millions of years before it reaches the surface and reshapes the area's geography or create a volcano.

Scientists say what's happening in New England may be similar to the onset of the Yellowstone supervolcano.

It emphasizes how intricate and dynamic the Earth's subsurface features are, and definitely warrants further study. 3499016]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLWMYIIBRAFMAAUBBKRRLD3GIEBRF34KVCFRH3SAEFWRBIJAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DF7/175/DF717551767943D3BCC01EE06D415507.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot rock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ magma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new england]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ magma rising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ molten rock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ volcanoes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ volcanic activity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seismic waves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seismic measurement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ geology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EarthScope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Rutgers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flu-season-is-going-to-suck-this-year-3498952</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flu season is going to suck this year 3498952]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — The flu has arrived early in North America, as officials worry this season's outbreak could be severe. 

According to the Center for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), the percentage of patients reporting flu-like symptoms reached the 2.2 percent threshold by late November, indicating flu season had begun, USA Today reported.

Experts believe the U.S. could be hit hard by the H3N2 strain, the same strain behind Australia's especially bad flu season. 

The flu vaccine has been shown to be 10 percent against H3N2, according to a research paper in Eurosurveillance.  

Flu vaccines cause antibodies to develop in the body around two weeks after vaccination, according the the CDC. 

These antibodies then help the body fight against virus infections that are in the vaccine. 
The seasonal flu vaccine is designed to protect against influenza viruses researchers predict will be the most common during the upcoming season, the CDC reported. 3498952]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASIFVD3XBMGAIVKHLADF7KDTNFIBVUZLKBKR3UTTAVGF5YZDBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EE2/3CF/EE23CF9318C02AAF9076259F4F588239.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu shots]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flu vaccinations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ H3N2 influenza strain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ H3N2]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/human-ken-doll-is-getting-his-60th-surgery-even-if-it-kills-him-3498910</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Human Ken Doll is getting his 60th surgery, even if it kills him 3498910]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRAZIL — Rodrigo Alves, the Human Ken Doll — is on the spotlight again after announcing his 60th surgery to remove his ribs to make him slimmer. 3498910]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAFKYZDLMBWIVI9LNPR77BFGWLSZRT7A6IAVT3RA6PWVXCTBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/49F/7A7/49F7A7CCA6DC30231F373F7A0E7EBC1B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>90</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human ken doll]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rodrigo alves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ribs removed surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ribs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ribs removed for smaller waist]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-patents-self-destructing-delivery-drones-3498850</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon patents self-destructing delivery drones 3498850]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Amazon has been granted a patent for self-destructing delivery drones in case of mid-air emergencies. 3498850]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIWMDICBIAAMBAVBMAFR9D4G2IE7ET4KVDRTFAKKFQRZCKVAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/95C/374/95C374213B5A1ED72B189DAECBCE2944.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>37</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon delivery drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon self-destruct drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon patents self destruct drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon delivery]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-call-for-ban-on-glitter-calling-it-a-global-hazard-3498829</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists call for ban on glitter, calling it a global hazard 3498829]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Environmental experts are calling for a ban on everyone's favorite sparkly decor — saying it's hazardous to the environment. 3498829]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKFVX3TB5GFAATCBNIWZL2HMABBVFK3AEARVTCXASNF3DIBBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DEA/289/DEA28914305C4F75A210425CCA613691.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  glitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic trash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microbeads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glitter ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glitter hazard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ all that glitters]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/engineers-create-world-s-first-living-tattoo-with-live-bacteria-3500049</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Engineers create world's first 'living tattoo' with live bacteria 3500049]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — A team at MIT have successfully created the world's first living tattoo, using ink made from live bacteria. 3500049]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJWGDIAA5CA3WASBWJARKDYGNIEXRAKKWKFVGRHBRDAPVRHLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/77C/B0E/77CB0E4176884C25BF781F146B026FB5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ living tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ live bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D printed tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bacteria tattoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sensor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemical stimuli]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hydrogel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bio ink]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/crytocurrency-mining-market-nicehash-hacked-for-68-mil-3499898</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Crytocurrency mining market NiceHash hacked for $68 mil 3499898]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INTERWEBS — The crytocurrency mining marketplace NiceHash has been hacked — for around $62 million in Bitcoin. 

After multiple reports of users complaining about emptied NiceHash wallets and a 12-hour service outage for 'maintenance,' NiceHash was nice enough to announce that there had been a security breach involving NiceHash website.
The company didn't disclose how much was stolen, however a wallet address passed around by NiceHash users suggest as many as 4,736.42 BTC were jacked, according to CoinDesk. 

The NiceHash team urged users to change all their passwords. What great advice. 

NiceHash is currently working with authorities, but the chance people who lost money will get any of it back are slim to none. Shout out to Mt. Gox! 
NiceHash was started in 2014 as a marketplace for miners to rent out their hash rate to others. 

The market cap for BitCoin is currently worth over $225 billion. The cryptocurrency's price has been skyrocketing all year, with the price currently sitting around $14,300. 3499898]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDWMDZBKMAR7BAWLMDAVLUUNBLSVUT4A2LATGAAAIFWRYT9BD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C56/E62/C56E62C04BF44C55A21BB9953E08D535.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NiceHash bitcoin hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NiceHash hacked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mt. Gox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/all-electric-autonomous-shipping-container-set-to-sail-by-2020-3499892</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[All-electric autonomous shipping container set to sail by 2020 3499892]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORWAY —Two Norwegian companies have teamed up to build the world's first all-electric, autonomous container ship. 

Norwegian company Yara and maritime technology company Kongsberg have said the vessel will be ready by late 2018, according the New Atlas. 

The state-of-the-art ship will transport chemicals and fertilizers from a Yara production plant to nearby towns. 
The plan is for the boat to first be operated by a crew in 2018, before transitioning into remote operations in 2019 and then fully autonomous by 2020. 
By transitioning to an all-electric shipping pathway, Yara can cut down 40,000 truck deliveries a year, which translates into reductions in nitrogen oxide and carbon dioxide emissions. 3499892]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNRPCRDB6IAVAZXB5BA77UYMZDSZRK7AJPW7HABKIGRRXIAAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1A8/A1F/1A8A1F4CDF33426CBAB75E9C636DED7D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ container ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ all-electric container ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ autonomous container ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ autonomous vessels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shipping vessel]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-zoo-visitors-tricked-into-paying-to-see-inflatable-penguins-3499682</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese zoo visitors tricked into paying to see inflatable penguins 3499682]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GUANXI ,CHINA — A zoo in China tried to bamboozle its visitors with inflatable penguins, and the other animals weren't that impressive either. 3499682]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIWICIHAVBRTWRSLRDAT9DTGVASVUZMAIDFPTZLAWNRADRQKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/803/ADB/803ADB17D55B4406BBD3CF1F6862C0B6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ inflatable penguins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ inflatable animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake zoo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zoo animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ zoo in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake stuff]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tricked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/skydiving-santa-crash-lands-on-beach-while-delivering-present-3499636</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Skydiving Santa crash lands on beach while delivering present 3499636]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GULFPORT, FLORIDA — A Santa Claus in Florida attempted to skydive and deliver a present, but failed spectacularly and ended up crashing on a beach. 3499636]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSIAPCIGASIATAAXLAAA39BAGSJBVFKSKSLFRT3RANQR3BKSKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E74/C26/E74C26BB00724472BD4046AE6F29D903.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skydiving santa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skydiving fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skydiving]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ santa claus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elf on the shelf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas charity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/air-force-developing-emp-missile-that-could-knockout-nk-rockets-3500830</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Air Force developing EMP missile that could knockout NK rockets 3500830]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The U.S. Air Force is developing a new, non-lethal cruise missile which officials say could knock out North Korean missiles. 

The system is called the CHAMP, which stands for Counter-electronics High Power Microwave Advanced Missile Project. 

It's a high-powered microwave weapon that can be delivered on an air-launched cruise missile from an American bomber, according to CNN. 

The Champ system is designed to fly at low altitudes into enemy airspace and send out strong electromagnetic impulses in order to jam enemy control-and-command systems. 
Cruise missiles fired by the enemy would then splash down in the ocean. 

The system is still in the development phase and also has drawbacks. Although non-lethal, the missile looks similar to the nuclear-capable variant and could be mistaken as an act of war if spotted by other countries. 
Another obstacle for the CHAMP system is that military equipment often has redundant wiring and insulation to protect from electronic attacks. The system would need to be able to disable all those electronics in order to successfully bring missiles down out of the sky. 3500830]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACFEAICLZEACVCFB6IFRL4TMBJE5SIKK6JFMHAEK6IWIXIDBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/01B/E6A/01BE6AB68ABFFA9AE2626B664104B447.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CHAMP missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CHAMP missile system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EMP weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CHAMP cruise missiles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/insta-sets-up-alert-system-to-warn-about-animal-abuse-content-3500429</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Insta sets up alert system to warn about animal abuse content 3500429]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Photo-sharing website Instagram this week instituted a new alert system to warn users of images that maybe harmful to animals.

The site said in a blog post whenever a user searches for something associated with harmful hashtags receive an alert warning them of how the content maybe potentially to animals.

They rolled out the feature on Monday this week in a bid to teach users about how the content can hurt animals. 3500429]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5BRMDIFLFPA3AZ7LVAAR7LUNEBSTSTSKBPFXHRFAIDFEAAFAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8D8/305/8D8305F4880A4EDEAACD6609ABE0C038.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram animal selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal selfie on instagram]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ instagram alert system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photo sharing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photos of animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfies with animals]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-world-s-biggest-nuclear-fusion-plant-is-now-50-complete-3500412</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The world's biggest nuclear fusion plant is now 50% complete 3500412]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FRANCE — Construction on the International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor (ITER) in southern France has reached the important halfway milestone.
The ITER project consists of 35 nations working on the most complex reactor ever built, consisting of over one million different components, Newsweek reported.  

Fusion energy looks to replicate the same process that powers the sun by converting hydrogen atoms into helium through a process that occurs at extreme temperatures, the Guardian reported.   

The ITER hopes to use hydrogen fusion controlled by massive superconducting magnets to create heat energy that can drive turbines to produce electricity. 
The energy produced would have zero carbon emissions, and could potentially be done at low cost if the production scale is large enough.

The reactor will have to be able to sustain temperatures 150 million degrees celsius — 10 times hotter than the sun's core. 
The massive donut-shaped tokamak reactor will be surrounded by giant magnets that take superheated plasma away from the metal walls of the container. This requires the magnets to be cooled to -269 degrees celsius. 

The next milestone for the project will be to get to first plasma by December 2025 in order to prove the concept is viable. 3500412]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABLFCD3TBRFR7WRTBNPAR94VGSLV5RZKK6IF5GAFAMBRTVAHKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6A4/BB1/6A4BB1BF5F6F446990A0D5FC031A9B5B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear fusion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ITER]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ITER fusion project]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ International Thermonuclear Experimental Reactor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear fusion energy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/service-dog-gets-triggered-by-musical-cats--3500361</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Service dog gets triggered by musical 'Cats' 3500361]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — Chaos erupted at a performance of 'Cats' on broadway, after a canine audience member got triggered by one particularly feisty feline.

Humans dressed as cats who sing and dance for two hours may be a hit for most people, but man's best friend apparently doesn't like it. Sorry, Andrew Lloyd Webber.

Page Six reports that during a recent performance at New York's Neil Simon Theater, a service dog got away from its owner and sprinted toward the stage during the opening number.

The animal was particularly unhappy with the show's flirtatious female, Bombalurina, and caused a ruckus onstage when he began chasing after her.

Fortunately, an usher managed to grab the dog before it caused any real trouble, and returned it to its owner. No animals or humans were hurt in the incident, and the show went on smoothly afterward.

But while the production company seemed to have laughed the encounter off, people online are genuinely pissed. Netizens think the service dog was fake, pointing out that a legit one wouldn't have acted that way.

Then again, the pup could still be in training, and well- it probably failed. 3500361]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6KFAYCWBZFFZARULZART9BGGJKSTRCZKBPR3G3RARBRTBREBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/300/597/30059760F310467DB5F28C605E44C9A4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cats the musical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ service dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ theater dog]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ broadway musical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake service dog]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/deep-sea-footage-shows-hypnotic-dance-of-a-deep-sea-spider-3500332</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Deep sea footage shows hypnotic dance of a deep sea spider 3500332]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GULF OF MEXICO — Researchers with the NOAA[b]'s Okeanos Explorer spotted a remarkable sight of a deep sea spider waltzing in the deep sea water during their third dive of their Gulf of Mexico 2017 mission. 3500332]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIBWGXAILEEWRCTDBJKF5KJCMMEVTST2A6LAVHADAICRAA3RKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5B2/E33/5B2E3314902C4493B8EF1CD83DBB439A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>40</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[deep sea spider]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[caught on video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[noaa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Okeanos Explorer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[deep sea creatures videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[deep sea creatures]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[deep sea videos for kids]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-thinks-dude-is-in-the-wrong-line-for-first-class-he-s-not--3500295</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman thinks dude is in the wrong line for first class (he's not) 3500295]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ARLINGTON, VIRGINIA— A photo of a woman who thought a man was in the wrong place when he was waiting to board his first class seat has gone viral.  

According to Emmit Walker's Facebook post, he was waiting in a priority line to board first class seating when the woman approached him.

Apparently, because of how Walker looked, she thought he was in the wrong place.  Walker says he pulled out his first class ticket and told her he was in the right spot and she could board after him.

Walker claims she wouldn't let it go, saying, he must be military or something, but we paid for our seats so he still should have to wait. But Walker retorted with a clap-back of epic proportions that, he says, had everybody in line clapping. 3500295]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KFAXAFBZFFRBR9BIDAK7LWMRCSTRC6LRDA3GZBKNKWMA39AA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D5A/286/D5A286FBB1F34FD4A5C3678D4F1A518E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ judgemental people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facebook stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ judging someone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ emmit walker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline stories.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/patreon-to-charge-fans-more-to-fund-their-favorite-creators-3500275</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Patreon to charge fans more to fund their favorite creators 3500275]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Patreon has made some changes recently to how it lets fans funds their favorite creators.  

The long and short of it is, creators will earn more money but their patrons - those who fund them through the site - will be charged 2.9% more, plus 35 cents. 

So say you're backing someone with a pledge of $1. From December 18, that's next Monday by the way, you'll be charged around a buck 38. More than a third of what you pledged. And that's all before VAT is added on. 3500275]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AACFMXTTLZGFVW3DLIDFR74XM6KVTFIMKSIFPGRKKEEWKBZAAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/76A/A04/76AA044014884ADFA6A57306D7AFD631.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-09T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>88</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ patreon changes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fan funding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ patreon update]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ patreon changing funding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ patreon]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/electron-rocket-attempts-second-test-launch-from-new-zealand-3502620</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Electron rocket attempts second test launch from New Zealand 3502620]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MAHIA PENINSULA, NEW ZEALAND — The Electron rocket launch from New Zealand had to be postponed after weather conditions and orbital traffic proved less than ideal.

The New Zealand Herald reports that the electron rocket known as 'Still Testing' is currently at a launch site in New Zealand.  It's 17 meters long and can carry a 150-kilogram payload into orbit.

The rocket will be launched into space from the Mahia Peninsula, with the first stage scheduled to separate and fall into the Pacific two and a half minutes into the flight.

Three shoebox-sized satellites will then be released at 8 minutes, 31 seconds.
The single Dove Pioneer CubeSat is an Earth-imaging satellite, while the two Lemur-2 satellites are used for weather mapping and ship traffic tracking.

Rocket Labs successfully launched its first Electron rocket in May 2017, though it failed to reach orbit.

The company originally planned three test flights, and will run a third test launch if needed. 3502620]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLACXZGBWIFCDCHLFJR7KLWGFKVZF32LWLWTTIGAWKFAARCAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/8D6/9A0/8D69A07AC2E44D38198180155CAFF5A8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electron rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electron launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocket launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new zealand rocket launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocket labs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ still testing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dove pioneer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lemur-2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cubesats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satellites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ payload]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocket]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/wall-street-can-t-wait-to-short-bitcoin-3502455</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Wall Street can't wait to short bitcoin 3502455]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — With Bitcoin up over 1,500 percent this year, Wall Street traders are itching to get in on the action. But not to buy Bit, they want to short it. 

The largest U.S. options exchange, CBOE Holdings, announced that it's teaming up with the Winklevoss twins' Gemini Trust Co. to create Bitcoin derivatives.

CBOE will use Gemini's bitcoin data to create futures on bitcoin. Essentially, this will allow a lot more investors to bet on the movement of Bitcoin without actually having to own any of the underlying asset — Bitcoin. 
This is where it gets interesting. Short selling Bitcoin can be way riskier than owning the asset yourself. When you own the asset, the most you can lose is your initial investment.

When you short sell an asset (Bitcoin), your losses could be infinite, limited only by how high the price goes. 3502455]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJFPC3SBEDACA3ABBIAR9SGM6JB7SC3K5CFTGCRAREFCAZHKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/736/688/736688F424A0DCC069ED6F48A4831FEB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin price]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin futures]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin derivatives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gemini Trust Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Winklevoss Twins Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CBOE bitcoin futures]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chunky-squirrel-steals-pricey-holiday-treats-3502333</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chunky squirrel steals pricey holiday treats 3502333]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MAPLEWOOD, NEW JERSEY — An American squirrel — aka a real fat one — was caught on camera nabbing expensive chocolates and some lip balm from a Jersey family's porch.  

Every year, the Boudreaux family leaves out a bundle of Christmas, sorry, holiday treats for delivery people on their doorstep.  They put out candy, snacks, tissues, hand warmers and other treats. 

Michele Boudreaux said they've never had any issues until this year when she noticed the basket was raided shortly after she placed it outside. 
She said the thief was only taking the expensive treats, including 25 Ghirardelli chocolate squares. 
The family put up a hidden camera to see if they could catch the perpetrator in action. They were more than a little surprised to see it was actually a super chunky squirrel.

Michele then later actually ran into Chunk mid-heist and watched him clear out their chocolate yet again. Oh yeah, he also took a Carmex lip balm. 
The chocolate has now been placed in a jar, but Michele still leaves out some squirrel treats for Chunk too. 3502333]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KWVAAFBZFRVB3ABMBA3LDRMSJVXSAKKEDF5HKRK2JFCC3TBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/026/655/02665566D7FDB8339453291950F39149.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fat squirrel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chunky squirrel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel stealing chocolate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel stealing expensive chocolate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squirrel steals pricey goods]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scottish-council-gets-big-brother-on-x-mas-bans-gifts-to-teachers-3502270</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scottish council gets big brother on X'mas, bans gifts to teachers 3502270]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FALKIRK, SCOTLAND — Kids in Falkirk, Scotland have been forbidden from gifting their teachers Xmas presents. 

Falkirk Council and the British tax authority equate gifts to teachers as bribes, meaning kids can no longer graft their way into good Xmas grades.   

One school asked parents via letter to instead give teachers a card and not gifts. 

The ban on Xmas gifts to teachers has angered parents, with some saying the practice was harmless. 3502270]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LFACKVBVARGWRVLWLA36JCM5DB3SIKAJLWVHAFBVAAGCZGBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/previews/47F/345/47F345B27D2341099CE326677A870FD2_3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas ban scotland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falkirk council]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas presents for teachers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ scotland teachers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ teacher gifts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hmrc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas cards]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ santa claus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rudolph]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cat-banned-from-library-gets-face-time-with-college-president-3502224</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cat banned from library gets face time with college president 3502224]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST.PAUL, MINNESOTA — A cat named Max in St.Paul, Minnesota became famous after getting himself banned from a local college library. 3502224]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMAFADZBLMARKWRRLVDRR74TM6JVRSRMLWIAVTIAAEBAKBZBKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1CE/9C2/1CE9C2FDC8E5E6BABC0238B41A2E3BE6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>86</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ orange cat videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat library]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ macalester college]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ macalester college president]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat sneaking into library]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat sneaking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ st.paul]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ minnesota]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hero-runs-into-burning-wildfire-to-save-a-poor-rabbit-3502151</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hero runs into burning wildfire to save a poor rabbit 3502151]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LA CONCHITA, CALIFORNIA — As wildfire blazed through California, one man's random act of kindness toward a helpless creature instantly made him everyone's hero. 3502151]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAFAX3ULMAWCDAVBVDRILUWM5BVZFK5KSPFRGRLA5EAPAIGAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/476/C68/476C68ACC4493CEB66281C3B071D7E93.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ california wildfire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wildfire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ everyday heroes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man saves bunny]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man saves rabbit]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-gets-crescent-shaped-eye-damage-from-staring-at-eclipse-3502144</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman gets crescent-shaped eye damage from staring at eclipse 3502144]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY — A woman found out first hand how a solar eclipse fries your eyes, after coming away from the Great American Eclipse with a crescent-shaped eye burn.

CNN reports that on August 21, Nia Payne had gone to her boyfriend's workplace at Staten Island to see the eclipse. She peeked at the sun with her naked eye for a few seconds before borrowing glasses from a woman nearby.

The 26-year-old didn't know what eclipse glasses were supposed to look like, but claims the sun still seemed bright through the pair she had on.

Hours later, she noticed her vision getting blurry, and she began seeing a weird dark spot. She lost partial vision in her left eye the next day.

Doctors examining her eyes were shocked to find that the damaged area in the left retina was crescent-shaped, making it look exactly like the eclipse.

They suspect that the glasses she used were either defective or fake, which allowed solar radiation to penetrate through and cause retinal damage.

The condition, known as solar retinopathy, is permanent and is currently untreatable. Instead, Payne has had to retrain her vision to cope, but she'll probably have a permanent crescent-shaped void in her sight for the rest of her life. 3502144]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLWVXTUBRFWAAIXBIARZLBFGJJEXSZLLSIWXTIHAWJAXAZAAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D58/B0E/D58B0EBF04887A011803664ACBC3EF1D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-12T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eclipse eye damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eye damage eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ great american solar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar retinopathy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eclipse glasses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar radiation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crescent spot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark spot]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/southwest-airlines-passenger-threatens-to-kill-everyone-on-plane-3503259</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Southwest Airlines passenger threatens to kill everyone on plane 3503259]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES — A woman was arrested and charged after she threatened everyone on board a Southwest Airlines flight from Portland to Sacramento. 3503259]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFIWVC3UA5GRVA3HLJJRX9JGNACVTFZKLRBWZHAGA6IRIATSBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BBD/D0C/BBDD0CA0DEB548608665499F266A825D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[unruly passenger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Southwest Airlines passenger]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Southwest Airlines passenger arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[passenger restrained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[airplane passenger]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/port-authority-bomber-was-a-isis-inspired-loser-in-a-basement--3503114</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Port Authority bomber was a ISIS-inspired 'loser in a basement' 3503114]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY — The man responsible for the attempted suicide bombing on the Big Apple's Port Authority tunnel came to the U.S. 6 years ago via so-called chain migration.

According to the New York Times, Akayed Ullah came to the U.S. in February 2011 from Bangladesh via, what officials call, extended family chain migration. He is the nephew of a American citizen.

Ullah is said to have lived in Brooklyn as a legal permanent resident with his parents, brother and brother's wife. His father died some time ago, reported NBC New York, citing a witness talking to News 4.

The 27-year-old also stayed at an apartment building on Ocean Parkway in Kensington. It's here he's believed to have assembled the explosive, reported NBC New York.

From March 2012 to March 2015, Ullah held license to operate as a for-hire driver but not as a yellow taxi driver, Taxi and Limousine Commission spokesperson told ABC 7 New York. Prior to the attack, he worked as a electrician at a building site in Manhattan, reported the New York Times.

Ullah told investigators his attack was inspired by Islamic State. He claimed to have watched IS propaganda videos, read extremist literature and learned how to make explosives online, NBC New York reported, citing law enforcement officials

U.S. President Donald Trump blamed lax immigration for the attack. According to the New York Post, he said chain migration was incompatible with national security and called on congress to end it. 3503114]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJAPY3SASIF5AI7KBJARK4TGZBSVUZQAZCAXTICKRDFCWIIKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C9A/DF3/C9ADF3561B7601CCD453C482675E231A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new york port authority attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ port authority bombing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ akayed ullah]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ who is akayed ullah]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ port authority bomber background]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new york attack 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bangladesh bomber new york]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-is-building-the-world-s-largest-surveillance-network-3503070</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China is building the world's largest surveillance network 3503070]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — China is building its surveillance network, and could soon be keeping a close eye on each and every one of their 1.3 billion citizens.

The Straits Times reports that roughly 176 million AI-equipped surveillance cameras are currently installed all over China, with the number set to increase to 626 million by 2020.

Citizens' ID profiles, social media photos, and other personal details are being filed in a database and connected to security cameras nationwide.

The advanced surveillance system uses facial recognition technology to instantly identify the name, gender, and age of any pedestrian, and the type and color of any vehicle.

The same technology is being used by commercial and private institutions for financial dealings, keyless entry, and even to thwart toilet paper theft.

The system can also scan faces and compare them with the police database, allowing authorities to locate and apprehend criminals at large.

The network claims to boost safety and security and reduce crime, but has ironically been dubbed Skynet, after the futuristic AI from the Terminator films.

That Skynet ended up trying to exterminate humanity, but maybe the Chinese version won't end up being such a nightmare. 3503070]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASKRPDTXANIA7ATFLZARZKD4MRDVXS3RKNLW7UZEAZEFKBKUAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C23/F46/C23F46FC7C62417696DEF11E43B96956.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mass surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surveillance state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police state]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big brother]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skynet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cctv]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surveillance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surveillance network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big brother is watching]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-s-bed-bug-extermination-attempt-results-in-building-fire-3503062</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman's bed bug extermination attempt results in building fire 3503062]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CINCINNATI — Ten people are now out of their home after an unidentified woman reportedly thought it wise to try and exterminate bed bugs with alcohol near an open flame last Friday night.

Total damage for the fire was reported to be almost a quarter million bucks.

Building resident Kamaron Lyshe livestreamed the blaze on Facebook. Writing on a GoFundMe page, he says he and his two brothers lost everything. 

Reportedly, this is the second time in 2 weeks that a Cincinnati residence has gone on fire while someone was trying to kill bed bugs. 3503062]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMDRPACSKFIACWITLSJRRL4VGZDVZF3ZKSPWMHTWBWJAPBAEKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FF0/D4A/FF0D4A8551754377A412F3BF5C2A947B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how not to get rid of bed bugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bed bug infestation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bed bug infestation facebook livestream]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bed bugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cincinnati bed bugs]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-company-developing-drone-to-combat-workaholics-3503057</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese company developing drone to combat workaholics 3503057]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Japanese security firm Taisei is working on a music drone to help curb the crazy overtime Japan office workers put in.

The drone, by Taisei, will reportedly play Scottish folk song Auld Lang Syne whenever it is time to go home. The song is also used by Japanese stores to indicate its closing time, reported the BBC. As if that wasn't enough, the drone will also be kitted out with video cameras to record anyone working late.

Auld Lang Syne was penned by Scottish poet Robert Burns in 1788. 3503057]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDWPAIBKEAAABKELVAF5L2GNACSKRCRKWKF5UAAABIRCWANBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/60F/30E/60F30ED767D94252AE581C0E2FF53AD3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taisei]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ music drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ overworking in japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ overtime in japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan work life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ music drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ auld lang syne]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ auld lang syne drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robert burns.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/suspect-detonates-homemade-bomb-in-new-york-subway-3503036</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Suspect detonates homemade bomb in New York subway 3503036]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY — A Bangladeshi man set off a homemade explosive device in one of Manhattan's busiest transit hubs, in what authorities are calling a terrorist attack.

According to the New York Times,the incident occurred in the underground passageway between the Port Authority Times Square subway stations.

27-year-old suspect Akayed Ullah had strapped a pipe bomb to his body using velcro and zip ties, and detonated the device around 7:20 a.m.

The powder-filled pipe was ignited using a Christmas light bulb, matches, and a 9-volt battery, but failed to detonate properly. One cap was blown off, but the rest of the pipe remained intact.

Ullah sustained burns and lacerations to his hands and abdomen, and was taken to the hospital after being subdued by police. Several others received minor injuries.

The suspect claimed the bombing was done in retaliation to U.S. airstrikes on the Islamic State in Syria, and says he took inspiration from similar Christmas attacks in Europe. 3503036]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IWMCZFA5ARVWA7LRAF77DXMZEE5ECRA6JFXHRDA6LAECAGAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C02/44C/C0244C83ADD34B3EBF0A3FAE18E9E141.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new york incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ port authority incident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new york attack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new york subway]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ akayed ullah]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/you-need-to-film-yourself-doing-the-invisible-box-challenge-3503009</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[You need to film yourself doing the Invisible Box Challenge 3503009]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — If you've spent anytime on Twitter lately, you've probably noticed the latest internet challenge.

It's called the Invisible Box Challenge. It involves an invisible box, too much time on your hands and something to film yourself with. 

First take your invisible box and then put in on the ground. Be careful where you put it, because it could be a tripping hazard. 
Next find your imagination. If you don't have your own, borrow someone else's. 

Then, place one foot on the invisible box and step over it. Easy as pie. Okay, maybe it's not that easy. 
Hey, it beats dumping a bucket of ice over your head, and it's eco-friendly. 3503009]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIBWACIIKVDRRVRWLBLRX7U3M5AS7URNK2IAVGCWAMAAEAKVAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/7B7/04E/7B704E3E44974F75B80017BDF4A80B8E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ invisible box challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet trends]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ internet challenges]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ invisible box]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cheerleader invisible box challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ texas cheerleader perfects invisible box challenge]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/police-dashcam-captures-fireball-shooting-across-the-night-sky-3502992</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Police dashcam captures fireball shooting across the night sky 3502992]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HAMILTON, NEW JERSEY — A dashcam video posted by the Township of Hamilton Police Department caught a fireball on December 2. shooting across the skies over New Jersey on December 2nd as it lit up the night sky. 3502992]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLFMY3UAAAW5VIRBSLRKKD3GFJETFK7K2LR5G3SAADAEDILAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/CF7/8AB/CF78AB3E718542ADA84E35225D7DE4BE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-13T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fireball videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fireball falling from sky]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fireball falling on dashcam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ things falling from the sky 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weird things falling from the sky]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police dashcam videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hamilton Police Department]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New Jersey]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cryptocurrencies-are-so-hot-right-now-3503895</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies are so hot right now 3503895]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — Virtual currencies continue to gain in value as Bitcoin hit another all-time high on Tuesday, as investors now hope to break the $20,000-mark. 

The interest in Bitcoin has also helped other cryptocurrencies hit record highs as well, Business Insider reported.

Both litecoin and ethereum hit all-time highs Tuesday morning. Ether reached $600 a token, while Litecoin gained more than 40 percent to $312. 

Due to the huge surge in traffic, cryptocurrency trading platform Coinbase had to temporarily halt trading on litecoin and ethereum. 

Coinbase's status page showed both cryptocurrencies were experiencing major outages.  

The 10 largest cryptocurrencies were all trading in the green on Tuesday, CoinMarketCap reported. 

But as digital currencies continues to set new records, many analysts are concerned that the speculative bubble will eventually burst. 3503895]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KFEXCVAEEFMVTHBVBAT6LVMIAE5F35KNPWTFIFK2JFEAILKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C18/309/C1830939751D4940AAC56EDAEDC14090.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ethereum]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Litecoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Coinbase]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital currency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digital coins]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/a-quarter-of-millennials-would-consider-dating-a-robot-3503891</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[A quarter of millennials would consider dating a robot 3503891]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PARIS — A new survey about technology says a quarter of millennials would date robots.

The report, by French advertising firm Havas, surveyed 12,000 people.  Of those, more than one in four 18- to 34-year-olds reckon it would be pretty normal to date a machine.

It looked a people from 32 nations across the globe. Reportedly, men were very interested in botting up. British men were the most eager to get down and clunky. 3503891]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LFKAKVAMHR7DZTBMAARK2HGIDS5ET2AWPFPUADBVDWPAANAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4C9/0C3/4C90C34298494672BEAAEF0CE5DAB43E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot love]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot relationship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marrying a robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dating a robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man dates robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman marries robot]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cctv-shows-brainless-phone-addict-walks-into-parking-garage-3503827</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[CCTV shows brainless phone addict walks into parking garage 3503827]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NANJING, CHINA — A CCTV footage posted by Pear Video shows a woman mistakenly walking into a hospital's parking garage while texting. 3503827]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLWCCKUAIFRPAASLFPWZK2BGZASTRAMKNPF7TKRKNLFMACXKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/639/B4F/639B4F10CC3B4367A23B290F6C999F30.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phone addict]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ addicted to phone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smartphone addict]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walking into parking garage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ people walk into parking garage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nanjing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/jerusalem-s-different-holy-sites-%0Aexplained-3503771</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Jerusalem's different holy sites, 
explained 3503771]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JERUSALEM — President Trump has announced that the U.S. will recognize Jerusalem as Israel's capital, a controversial move that may spark turmoil in the area.

Jews and Arabs have fought over the city for years, both claiming it as their capital. But what's the big deal with Jerusalem, anyway?

According to the Washington Post, the city of Jerusalem is sacred to the world's three major religions: Judaism, Islam, and Christianity.

Jews flock to Old City to worship at the Western Wall, which is the last remnant of an ancient Jewish Temple.

Islam's third holiest site, the Al-Aqsa Mosque, and the Dome of the Rock, are both in Jerusalem. It's also where the prophet Muhammad is believed to have ascended into heaven.

For Christians, the most sacred site is the Church of the Holy Sepulchre — believed to be where Jesus was crucified, buried, and resurrected.

The holy sites are governed by different bodies, with only the Western Wall directly controlled by the Israeli government A Muslim religious organization is in charge of the Islamic sites, while different Christian groups manage the Church. 3503771]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJWPAKXAZGR7BCHLFPRV7UTGEDSZRIILWJFMGAFKZDACARPBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/24E/343/24E34321F0374BEC9B11ADC0EF3FDDEE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jerusalem]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ holy city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ old city]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jerusalem holy sites]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ israeli palestinian conflict]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ israel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ palestine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ islam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ judaism]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christianity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ religion]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-rooftop-climber-falls-62-stories-goes-splat-3503740</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese rooftop climber falls 62 stories, goes splat 3503740]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHANGSHA — A Chinese climber attempting to climb a building to take some selfies failed. 

Wu Yongning apparently made short videos of himself hanging out on top of skyscrapers, and had some followers on China's Twitter knockoff Weibo. 

Rooftopping involves climbing tall city buildings without safety equipment. And of course selfies are mandatory. 

Looks like he was participating in a rooftopping challenge on November 8 for $15,000, when the rooftop turned out to be too challenging. 
Unfortunately for Wu, rather than dominating the skyscraper, they were scraping him off 62 stories below. 3503740]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIRMCZAASPAKARRLICRV9SCMRBBXRK2KMBR3GKXK6KAPWKWAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C33/C37/C33C3740DE574751B9AF03A584032454.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese rooftop climber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese rooftop climber stunt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rooftopping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wu Yongning rooftopping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Wu Yongning climber]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/star-wars-fans-like-jar-jar-binks-more-than-kylo-ren-3503723</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Star Wars fans like Jar Jar Binks more than Kylo Ren 3503723]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[A GALAXY FAR, FAR AWAY — The world is set to go Star Wars nuts this week as the franchise's latest installment hits.

Fanboys are geeking out as 66-year-old Mark Hamill returns to his role as saga icon Luke Skywalker for the first time since 1983. He's said to be training Rey from Episode 7, while good space dudes duke it out with bad space dudes.

Speculation about the plot as been disrupting the geek force all week. Especially after Hamill retweeted an image showing Frank Oz, better known as Yoda, with the line Would this be considered a SPOILER?

According to Comicbook.com, a Morning Consult poll among fans revealed that  Vader-wannabe Kylo Ren is less popular than Darth Jar Jar. That same poll also revealed that Yoda, Chewie and Luke are jointly the second most popular character. 

Princess Leia, portrayed by the late Carrie Fisher, was number 1. 3503723]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIAWEXZAKREFKDZVLWLF76JAMAEBIFAIKWKFVTAFKMBRVARFKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/61B/1DC/61B1DC03A04E46EB9C8273D143B6D33F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars episode 8 jar jar binks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jar jar binks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kylo ren]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mark hamill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ millenium falcon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars 8 spoilers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yoda]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frank oz]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/video-shows-motorcyclist-just-barely-escape-getting-squashed-3504822</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Video shows motorcyclist just barely escape getting squashed 3504822]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WORLD — A motorcyclist is lucky to be alive after almost getting pancaked by oncoming traffic after getting smashed into by a careless driver. 3504822]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAFGXRCKVEWKWIVLJJWZKDUM2IBVSC4AAARVGTYAVCFCDTRAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9BD/9F8/9BD9F8B08AFF41ACAA771F56E7750DC2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motorcycle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motorbike]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motorcycle accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motorcycle fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motorcycle accident survival]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motorcycle near miss]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/orcas-are-having-a-whale-of-time-hunting-great-white-sharks-3504704</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Orcas are having a whale of time hunting Great White Sharks 3504704]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNDER THE SEA — The bodies of five great white sharks washed up on the South African coast and local scientists reckon orcas are to blame. 3504704]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNAAXACB6NFPWZYBBJF794WMJJSKRRLAIAR3TABKMDWAWKTAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E7C/64C/E7C64C4FF59F4A03B34F7AAB83024668.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ orca v great white shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ orca great white shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ orca fighting great white shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ orca v shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark v whale]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine dynamics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south africa]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-is-gathering-dna-from-millions-of-xinjiang-residents-3504624</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China is gathering DNA from millions of Xinjiang residents 3504624]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[XINJIANG, CHINA — A human rights organization has found that China is gathering DNA from a region that's home to a much-oppressed ethnic minority. 3504624]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBJFGYICA5EWEVATLMARV6JBMMCBIFC3K5DAZTAAA5BAEBCUAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DEF/A3E/DEFA3EB435A94837ABBDC28CF1765EDD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>93</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human rights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china human rights]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human rights watch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xinjiang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uighurs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uyghurs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china dna database]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china dna collection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna database]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dna sample]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biometric data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fingerprint]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iris scan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police database]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flight-diverted-after-dude-starts-munching-on-other-passengers-3504480</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flight diverted after dude starts munching on other passengers 3504480]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES / LAS VEGAS — A snappy passenger forced a LA to New York Jetblue fight to divert on Sunday. 3504480]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NWKX3VBZHWIBAULNJFT6LXMBKB7S35K2KFMTZAK6KFEAK2KG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4E6/43B/4E643BCC6ADE4EAA851C272013D95E08.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man bites passenger flight diverted to las vegas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jetblue passenger kicked off plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  jetblue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ los angeles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ las vegas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new york]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  passenger goes crazy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chunk-of-ice-from-plane-falls-through-homeowner-s-roof-3504457</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chunk of ice from plane falls through homeowner's roof 3504457]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN BERNARDINO, CALIFORNIA — A chunk of ice fell from a passing plane and through a San Bernardino couple's home roof, landing in their bedroom one Sunday night. 3504457]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IAAAKWAWNA5A3EKFLRK7LVMMCV7S36A2KFZUZFAVDFABAHAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BAF/90A/BAF90A47E71E4863B13BCD780BC7D3B9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice fall from plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice from plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice falls through home roof]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice ball fall from plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice ball fall from sky]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ claudell curry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ San Bernardino]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ California]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/englishwoman-loves-chandeliers-so-much-she-s-engaged-to-one-3504444</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Englishwoman loves chandeliers so much she's engaged to one 3504444]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LEEDS, UNITED KINGDOM — A woman from Britain has a thing for lights, so much so, she got engaged to one. 

Amanda Liberty said she popped the question to her favoritest chandelier on Valentine's Day.
You can't control who you fall in love for and things just went from there, Liberty said in a recent interview. 
The 33-year-old first saw the light of her life on eBay last year, and it was love at first light. 

Her fiancée Lumiere is a 30-inch-wide antique chandelier from Germany. 

Even though she's hitched to Lumiere, Liberty still snuggles up with the rest of her 25 chandeliers on the regular. 

Liberty first got into lights after purchasing her first chandelier. No word on if the lights get into her. Either way, the future looks bright for the happy couple. 3504444]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KICAAXAAKFNFPBAUBVCWRLDTMMDERRKRA2PFPGZHBVEAIDIDKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D0C/F4C/D0CF4C22044C420BBDE5B1A63EDE35BB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wedding]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marriage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ engagement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman engaged chandelier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman marrying chandelier]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/did-scientists-just-find-the-world-s-oldest-living-creature-not-exactly--3505366</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Did scientists just find the world's oldest living creature? Not exactly. 3505366]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GREENLAND — News claiming that scientists found a Greenland shark that is 512 years old and possibly the oldest living creature is way off mark.

The Science study they all link too is actually from last summer. Writing on Instagram, the study's lead author Julius Nielsen said, Please note that we have not found any sharks to be 600 or 500 years old. Nielsen explained the shark in question was estimated to be between 272 years old and 512 years old. 

Though the Greenland sharks are always cool, whatever the weather. They chill in frozen waters, and aren't apex hunters like other sharks. These fish live like vultures, scavenging fish, or even the remains of reindeer and polar bears. 3505366]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASKWXX3XBZHWKXIWLWIRZ7LVM2KVZEZMKEBW7HTWABJWIVIQKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2A4/31D/2A431D49B6FB43CBA4BF864C365BCF0E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oldest living animal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oldest living shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oldest creature alive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ greenland shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 500 year old animal]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/net-neutrality-is-dead-but-now-isps-can-start-innovating--3505284</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Net Neutrality is dead, but now ISPs can start 'innovating' 3505284]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The FCC voted on Thursday to can Obama-era net neutrality rules.

Net neutrality required ISPs to offer equal access to all web content without charging people for higher-quality delivery or giving certain websites preferential status. 

Supporters of the repeal say it will free up internet providers to innovate. 

Opponents worry the internet is going to start looking a lot more like cable TV. Broadband providers could start splitting the internet up into different packages. 

Without net neutrality, some are concerned the internet could be split into a fast lane with big internet and media companies, and a slow lane for everyone else. 3505284]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DFAYCWLVCFEDZXLNPA36BBNFIE7RCZAEAAXTIGAVBAGW33AH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DE6/E39/DE6E390567994438BA9F5A77CEDC52A3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Net Neutrality]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Net Neutrality repeal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Net Neutrality gone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ FCC Ajit Pai]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ajit Pai Net Neutrality]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Net Neutrality fast lane slow lane]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uber-accidentally-charged-passenger-18-518-for-a-ride-3505237</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Uber accidentally charged passenger $18,518 for a ride 3505237]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TORONTO, CANADA — Uber is apologizing to a Toronto customer after they accidentally charged him over $[d]18,000 on December 8. 3505237]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANNFXX3SAEHWKXIXBBPWR6DWGSIB7EZIAFJATURFA5CRIC3XBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/764/C03/764C0320B9554E7BB8B3E389A945B29B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uberX pricing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber pr crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber driver problems]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber overcharged me]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber expensive ride]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toronto]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/surgeon-admits-marking-patient-s-livers-during-transplant-3505230</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Surgeon admits marking patient's livers during transplant 3505230]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM, UNITED KINGDOM — Some doctors get up to all sorts of no-good when you're old cold on the surgery table.

The Telegraph reports that liver surgeon Simon Bramhall was quite the Zorro, using an argon beam to mark his initials on the livers of two patients during transplant surgery.

Argon bean markings aren't harmful to the liver and normally disappear over time. One female patient's liver didn't heal properly though, and another surgeon was shocked to discover the initials during a follow-up operation.

Bramhall was suspended immediately after the discovery, but ended up resigning later after going through disciplinary hearings.

The surgeon has since pleaded guilty to two counts of assault by beating for marking his patients, and will be sentenced on January 12.

But while most doctors were scandalized, one of SB's former patients think it's not such a big deal, since at the end of the day, it's more important to save lives.

Still, that's some twisted sense of narcissism. 3505230]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDWMDTXLRBAACR9LWPFX9JFGECVZEZIA2LWZHTTAEBWPBRLKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/124/6BC/1246BC3AC9CD4F06A2B0DFF9DA4CB8AE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgeon marks patient]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver markings]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver surgeon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ simon bramhall]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/meet-the-dracula-tick-that-drank-dinosaur-blood-3505139</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Meet the Dracula tick that drank dinosaur blood 3505139]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OXFORD, UNITED KINGDOM — New research in the journal Nature Communications discusses how ticks fed on feathered dinosaurs.

The newly discovered species of tick is called Deinocroton draculi, meaning Dracula's terrible tick.

The ticks were found inside 99-million-year-old lumps of amber from Myanmar. Two of the ticks were found with a dinosaur feather. One was wrapped around it. 

Researchers say the finding the is the first direct evidence that ticks fed on feathered dinosaurs. 

Scientists suspect the feather belonged to an unknown type dinosaur or a ancient bird species called enantiornithine. 3505139]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IAAYAFBNKFEAISLBKAXL2CM2KB5UZKA5BW3H3YAEBAGCAFBD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BAF/750/BAF7500D2EBC45F7A8D7C813C1839C1A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ticks drinking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dinosaur ticks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dinosaur tick]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prehistoric ticks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Deinocroton draculi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oxford]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dinosaur drinking tick]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/maryland-hamburglar-arrested-after-theft-video-goes-viral-3505126</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Maryland Hamburglar arrested after theft video goes viral 3505126]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COLUMBIA, MARYLAND — A woman who robbed a Mickey D's through a drive through window turned herself in after footage of the theft went viral. 3505126]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZARGDTVLJLRAXIVLVAA57BGGFJS3SK6KWPAXGCYAVEAKVZCBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0AC/8BE/0AC8BE4052F84B70A9EF9C7E88A3A72D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-16T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ McDonalds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ McDonalds Hamburglar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Maryland Hamburglar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Maryland Hamburglar arrested]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ real life Hamburglar]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-keeps-on-developing-bases-in-the-south-china-sea-3506022</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China keeps on developing bases in the South China Sea 3506022]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — China has kept on developing military bases in the South China Sea throughout 2017, a think tank has claimed in a new report.

A new Asia Maritime Transparency Initiative report says China has continued developing its bases in the South China Sea. 

The country has reportedly installed wind turbines and a helipad at Tree Island, and towers on Triton Island, Reuters reported, citing the AMTI report. AMTI says China has continued development of Subi reef, creating underground tunnels for ammunition storage and installing further radar technology. 

On Fiery Cross Reef, China has created underground tunnels for supply and ammunition storage, as well as a high-frequency radar array. The report says that China also created underground storage tunnels, missile shelters and radar arrays on Mischief Reef. 3506022]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADWEDKTKABRGYKDBSPFRLUYMJKE5F33K5DFMFAKA5AWIB3YAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/ED1/B3D/ED1B3D64893FD7D18E0BCB375D13DDED.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ south China sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ military bases]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amti]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mischief reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ subi reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ triton island]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/robotic-blimp-drone-to-explore-giza-pyramid-hidden-chamber-3507397</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Robotic blimp drone to explore Giza Pyramid hidden chamber 3507397]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PARIS — Researchers are developing a blimp-like drone that can explore a newly discovered hidden chamber in the Great Pyramid of Giza. 

Research institutions Inria and the French National Center for Scientific Research are designing the drone to squeeze through a 1.5-inch hole, before unfolding and inflating, Digital Trends reported. 

The main challenge is to insert a complete exploration robot in a hole that is as small as possible, Inria researcher Dr. Jean-Baptiste Mouret told Digital Trends. It's important to use a hole as small as possible because we want to leave as few traces as we can. This is what we call 'minimally invasive robotics.' We chose a diameter of 1.5 inches because it is a good trade-off between the size of the hole, the kind of machines that can bore holes, and the current robotic technologies.

The blimp model was chosen over conventional multi-rotor drones because it's safer the surrounding environment during exploration. 
The blimp drone can make contact with obstacles without damaging the monument. They are also more stable than multi-rotor drones, which is important for taking photos in low-light conditions. 

The camera equipped drone will be remotely operated by radio, however can also operate autonomously via small onboard sensors. 3507397]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLFMX3XAZCWMCASKAAAT9LVGSLSZUT2ABIWZUCRA6JWIBC5AB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/31E/B44/31EB447A687F423898089EB4D08A89EF.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Great Pyramid Giza]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Great Pyramid Giza hidden chamber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robotic blimp drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blimp drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mini blimp drone]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-administration-bans-cdc-from-using-big-boy-words-3507380</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump administration bans CDC from using big boy words 3507380]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The CDC actually received a list from the Trump administration banning certain words from appearing in the 2018 budget documents.

According to the Washington Post, CDC officials were treated to a 90-minute Trump-based presentation on the seven banned words.

Apparently, the Drumph administration is scared of words like diversity, fetus, transgender, vulnerable, entitlement, science-based and evidence-based.

Instead of saying science-based or evidence-based, these boneheads gave suggestions like this, the CDC bases its recommendations on science in consideration with community standards and wishes.

And over at the State Department, rather than saying sex education the term is now sexual risk avoidance. Huh!?  
Maybe Trump should just ban all words over two syllables and force everyone to speak in superlatives. 3507380]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKAMYIIASKWAY3DBSLRR6LTGJKB3FK9A5DFMGABKFIWCVT2AF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D81/560/D8156026568A4C8CB630B8225CE647D5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CDC word ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Trump CDC word ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Center for Disease Control word ban]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science-based]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ evidence-based]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-macaques-like-to-get-it-on-with-the-deer-3507373</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese macaques like to get it on with the deer 3507373]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MINOO, JAPAN — When Japanese male macaques were spotted mounting female Sika deer back in January, some passed it off as misdirected mating.

But when it became clear females were getting in on some action too, one thing's for sure: macaques really like to do it with deer. 

According to a study published in the journal Archives of Sexual Behavior, adult male macaques often reject their adolescent female counterparts, so the ladies in heat end up turning to another species for satisfaction.

They thrust and grind their lady bits on the backs of their stag mates, which only tolerate them because they get groomed in return.

Females get pretty excited, and were seen making squeaking sounds, biting their stags, and pulling on their antlers. Some were observed intruding on a session and displacing the original partner. They're also very demanding, and throw tantrums if the deer walk away from them. 

Japanese macaques are known to have playful interactions with deer, and sometimes use them for transport. Scientists say the relationship may have started out this way, and that the monkeys were awakened at some point and continued to use the deer 3507373]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNFPYZDBICFEAKCLZDA77UUMRBBISKZKSJRZUZEBWIRPAACKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/690/17E/69017E6A731C47EEB0656242CAE30C11.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ monkey mating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ monkey deer mounting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ monkey deer japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japanese macaque]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japanese monkey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sika deer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ japan deer]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-visitors-furious-over-fake-butterfly-exhibition-3507164</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese visitors furious over fake butterfly exhibition 3507164]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GUANXI, CHINA — Organizers decided to take fakeness to the next level by presenting a fake butterfly exhibition. 3507164]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLRGDRBA6IAGAISBNLR5KLWMNIBKST9AZDA5TIBKEDRGCKVBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E1E/8B9/E1E8B927EDB945DFAEB8CEA0501D0CE2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake chinese exhibition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake butterfly in a jar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china fake exhibition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china fake market]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake butterfly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ guanxi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/watch-this-video-of-a-panda-enjoying-a-carrot-snack-3507138</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Watch this video of a panda enjoying a carrot snack 3507138]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — There's something really satisfying about watching this panda enjoy his carrot snack. 3507138]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KECFGYZDKRAFEYCDKBIFTL4UNFIB5EAKAJKA3UAEK2KWEAZHLB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0BE/B5C/0BEB5C02CBB94B87B6C78C67573C961F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pandas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda eating carrot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda snack time]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda eating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese panda]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/alibaba-will-soon-sell-cars-via-gigantic-car-vending-machines-3507072</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Alibaba will soon sell cars via gigantic car vending machines 3507072]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HANGZHOU, CHINA — Alibaba will soon sell cars through gigantic vending machines, and give their users the opportunity to try before they buy.

According to CNET, customers use Alibaba's Taobao mobile app to scan a car they want to test, and are asked by the system to pick a color, enter basic information, and take a selfie.

At the automated car vending machine, facial recognition matches the customer with their car order, which is then dispatched from storage.

Customers are given three days to test-drive the vehicle, after which they can buy directly through the app, or arrange to test drive a different model.

The company is planning to open two facilities in January 2018, one in Shanghai and another in Nanjing.

The service is limited to users who have a sesame credit score of at least 700, and belong to the higher tiers of the Alibaba 88 membership program.

To curb abuses, users can only test a model once, with no more than five test drives within the first two months of signing up. 3507072]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDAPXTUK2KFPYCEKBKR572CMJJB7E37KIARZHZCKRBAMVKSAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/759/52A/75952ABB165C4267A3114AC6F9161E34.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alibaba]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car vending machine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car mall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tmall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant vending machine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taobao app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mobile app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ test drive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ car test drive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/eighth-planet-discovered-orbiting-around-distant-star-kepler-90-3506989</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Eighth planet discovered orbiting around distant star Kepler-90 3506989]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — An AI algorithm sifted through data from the Kepler space telescope and uncovered an eighth planet in the Kepler-90 star system.

Google AI has discovered another planet orbiting Kepler-90, making it the first star known to support as many worlds as our sun, according to NASA.

Though Kepler-90 is sunlike and its system is similar to ours, all eight planets' orbits are closer to their star than the earth is to the sun.

The new planet, dubbed Kepler-90i, is 30% larger than Earth, and completes an orbit around its sun every 14.4 days.

But with a rocky landscape and a surface temperature of over 800 degrees Fahrenheit, the planet is likely not habitable.

Astronomers say it's possible that more planets are lurking around Kepler-90. They are planning to use the Google AI to analyze more data to hopefully uncover more exoplanets both in Kepler-90 system and beyond. 3506989]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NRMCCVBNKRKXCCBJLRZKDYMEEVZST7KFLA5HTWKNLAMDRALE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/00E/D02/00ED025EF9B04B078A4CC789B69D18D3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kepler]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ planet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new planet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exoplanet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kepler-90]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kepler-90i]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ AI]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google AI]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial intelligence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kepler space telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ planet hunting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/twitter-takes-the-web-back-to-1984-3508224</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Twitter takes the web back to 1984 3508224]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Twitter began deleting and suspending users under new guidelines laid out by the site this week. 

Certain groups and users from all sides of the supremacy rainbow were kicked off the social network platform.

By closing these accounts, isn't America's Weibo just drawing more attention to these people and their screwball ideologies?

Elsewhere, Gab.Ai., a self-described pro-free speech platform like Twitter, is reportedly gulping up ex-Twitterers and new users from the left, right and center. 3508224]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLRCAICBWNA7BIULZBAV9D3NFLVRUT5AJJF7TKWKNJWVWCUKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/221/877/2218773DF01D49D19DD97FB2945322D3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter censorship policy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jack dorsey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter censors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter deleting tweets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter removing verification]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter speech rules]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jack dorsey]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter censoring users]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ twitter deleting followers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/israeli-bus-company-to-invest-millions-in-electric-road-tech-3508148</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Israeli bus company to invest millions in electric road tech 3508148]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TEL AVIV, ISRAEL — Israel transit service Dan Bus Company will invest $2.2 million in technology that turns regular roads into electric power sources.

Electric buses in Tel Aviv currently need to be charged via cable at departure stations, but this could soon be unnecessary, reports Globes.

ElectRoad has developed technology that powers vehicles from the road while driving, using conduction coils to wirelessly charge them through magnetic induction.

With this innovation, there is no need for batteries or cable charging. It also boasts zero emissions, high efficiency, and low cost.

The startup will be focusing on public transportation, and will begin with laying charger coils underneath designated lanes to power the buses traversing the road daily. Eventually, ElectRoad says it may even be possible to share energy between vehicles. 3508148]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJRGY3XBFMFCWKFLIBAR6BCGRDV7F32KNKR3T3XKSJR3CICAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/08A/671/08A671528F9C49F2B07A98623E6A06CB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric road]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric bus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electroad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wireless charging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ israel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ israel transportation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dan bus company]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-to-demote-posts-hunting-for-likes-3508137</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook to demote posts hunting for Likes 3508137]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Facebook said on Monday it's going to start demoting posts that are just fishing for likes. 
As Facebook has grown in size, so has the annoyingness of their News Feeds. Users are increasingly getting bombarded with irritating posts that tell people to like, share or comment.
This method is mostly used by brands and companies looking to expand their footprint. 
The social media giant has tweaked its algorithms to detect posts that are merely engagement bait and says it will show them less in the News Feed. 

Facebook said it will have stricter demotions for repeat offenders. 

The changes will be put in place over the next few weeks to give publishers some time to come up with other ways to game the system. 

The question we are really wondering though is, who still really uses Facebook? 3508137]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSIAPDZGBJPACDRYLADAX7JBMSKS7FILKBPR3TIGAZDACWABAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A63/48F/A6348F7645AB4E928CB6599106EAC32C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook Likes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook fishing for Likes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook spam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook engagement bait]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook engagement baiting]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/deadly-alabama-rot-hits-uk-dogs-after-muddy-forest-walks-3508066</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Deadly Alabama Rot hits UK dogs after muddy forest walks 3508066]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE BRITISH ISLES — Alabama rot, a fatal flesh gnawing skin disease, is claiming the lives of dogs all across the British Isles. 

According to Vets4Pets.com, many cases of Alabama Rot have been reported across the British Isles over the last several years. The disease is fatal to 9 out of 10 infected dogs.

The cause remains unknown, but one commonality is that most reports come from dog owners who walk their pets in the countryside.

British government information says the disease can present itself as skin lesions, ulcers and red patches of skin. In most cases, it eventually progresses to kidney failure.

Dog owners are advised to avoid muddy forest areas and to clean their pet's paws and legs thoroughly after a walk.

Thousands of UK dog owners walk their pets regularly in forests and only a small number of dogs are afflicted with Alabama Rot. 3508066]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASNFCCTXAAFAIWCHKECRK94SNFKSXRIIAFLW3GAEKECRAAAPKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/781/6D6/7816D6320DCB45C2875E1DA51B39B27B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alabama rot in dogs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alabama rot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ British dogs walkers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog owners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ walking dog in forest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what is alabama rot]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/rotten-tomatoes-audience-score-of-the-last-jedi-maybe-fake-news-3508043</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes audience score of The Last Jedi maybe fake news 3508043]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOLLYWOOD — The Rotten Tomatoes audience score for the Star Wars: The Last Jedi could be fake news, if claims by a Facebook user are shown to be true.

Sitting currently at around 56%, the fan claims to have hacked it with an army of fake bot accounts and the claim may not be without merit. 

Bleeding Cool news found Last Jedi reviews in the audience reviews section of of the Shape of Water's RT page. This could easily have been a few misprogrammed bot reviewing the wrong film.

We took a closer look at some of these user profiles.

On the user ID pages of most of these negative reviewers, we were presented with Page Not Found.  Evidently, these could be the bots we're looking for. 

Bleeding Cool News also reports that the rate of audience reviews for The Last Jedi has been incredibly fast.

Thor Ragnarok has 80,000 audience ratings and it's been out for over 6 weeks. Justice League has over 116,000 user ratings in a month. The Last Jedi meanwhile got over 100k user ratings in just a few days. 3508043]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJFCCRABAFAIDZYLSKAXLUTGRDB7ERLA5DFPUAGAABF5CCXKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C35/F97/C35F97A11F6F4257B00DB94324D2B86C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ last jedi rotten tomatoes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars fans get mad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars fans will find funny]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ last jedi reviews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ luke skywalker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ george lucas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars fans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fanboys]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ star wars geeks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jj abrams]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ riann johnson]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mark hammill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kylo ren]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/3-dead-in-catastrophic-amtrak-train-derailment-in-washington-3508022</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[3 dead in catastrophic Amtrak train derailment in Washington 3508022]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUPONT, WASHINGTON — Several are dead and many more injured after a train on a new Amtrak service route derailed in Washington.

The New York Times reports that on Monday morning, Amtrak Train No. 501 was on its inaugural run from Seattle to Portland with 77 passengers and seven crew members onboard.

While approaching a curved overpass around 7:33 a.m., the lead engine ran off the track and sent passenger coaches tumbling onto Interstate-5 below.

Thirteen of the 14 cars were derailed — some crashed into several vehicles on the road, while one was left dangling over the highway. According to the Washington State Patrol, least three are confirmed dead and over 100 are injured.

Passengers say they felt a wobble before suddenly being catapulted forward. Some had to kick out the windows to escape, since the emergency doors didn't work properly.

It has yet to be determined if the crash was due to speed, but the train was reportedly not using positive train control technology, which automatically slows trains exceeding speed limits.

Washington Governor Jay Inslee declared a state of emergency following the deadly derailment, while Amtrak temporarily suspended service south of Seattle. 3508022]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABJWIDCTBEHREVRRLJKF5LSCMRBBRRK3AZDA3TZEKRDF3ARLAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/DD0/D08/DD0D0892DAE14F199255108ED194FB56.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amtrak derailment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amtrak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cascades]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train derailment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ train crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatal train crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amtrak derailed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amtrak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us train crash]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/miss-iraq-getting-death-threats-over-selfie-with-miss-israel-3507956</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Miss Iraq getting death threats over selfie with Miss Israel 3507956]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[IRAQ — The Miss Universe Pageant contestant Iraq has been getting threats after she posted a selfie with Miss Israel on Instagram. 3507956]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRARCDZGLNNACAITBNIR37DVNBJE7EC2AJIWXHCYARAAGX3RBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C79/3FF/C793FFE92DAC43BA58B826926D2A0E34.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Miss Iraq Sarah Idan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Miss Israel Adar Gandelsman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ miss iraq universe 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sarah idan miss universe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sarah idan miss universe 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sarah idan miss universe iraq]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iraq]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/your-smartphone-may-be-giving-you-brain-cancer-%E2%80%94-or-not-3507931</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Your smartphone may be giving you brain cancer — or not 3507931]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SACRAMENTO, CALIFORNIA — The California Department of Public Health (CDPH) released a set of new guidelines last week dealing with cell phones and radiation risk. 

The department issued a guidance on how to reduce exposure to radio-frequency energy released by cell phones, despite hard evidence that exposure poses any health risks, Ars Technica reported. 

Some studies have suggested long-term use of smartphones could be linked to brain or salivary gland cancer, low sperm count and headaches, according to the CDPH, KQED reported. 

The guidelines suggest to avoid holding your phone to your head when talking on it. Send texts instead of talking. 

Avoid carrying your phone in your pocket, bra or belt holster. Carry it in a bag or a backpack. 

They also suggested to avoid using your phone with its sending high levels of radio-frequency energy, such as when you're driving, streaming content or when your signal is weak. 

Try not to keep your phone by your head while you're sleeping. 3507931]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJAADZBBBNRCAARLZCR39D3GSKE7RK9KACF7UAFK5ER7XALKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9D5/0CA/9D50CAE9A2A0D50C1C5B42584D0DA039.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ California cellphone guidelines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radio-frequency energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radio-frequency energy exposure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cellphone risks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smartphone risks]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hero-saves-baby-boy-abandoned-on-the-side-of-the-road-in-brazil-3509111</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hero saves baby boy abandoned on the side of the road in Brazil 3509111]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RIO DE JANEIRO — A newborn baby boy will live to see his first Christmas, and it's all thanks to the Good Samaritan who saved his life.

Globo reports that the hero traffic worker had been working in Rio de Janeiro's North Zone, and was on the way to a bathroom when he spotted something in a grassy area.

To his surprise, a baby boy was lying in the long grass with his umbilical cord still attached.

He quickly called for help and wrapped the newborn in his vest. Police officers soon arrived and took the baby to the hospital. Doctors say the boy is doing well, and was born just days shy of the standard 40 weeks.

Police are currently conducting an investigation to identify the child's parents, and find whoever left him on the side of the road.

The area he'd been left in, Barro Filhos, is one of the poorest parts of the city, and it's believed he was abandoned shortly before he was found. 3509111]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NAADZFB2JAKACHKFPFXKBBM2LVZURMA2KW5H3WAJIWRBIEKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/EC7/048/EC7048D7D8C4400DAA1252F6BAC5F3D1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>54</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ good samaritan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ newborn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ abandoned baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ abandoned newborn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brazil baby]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/women-throw-down-at-chuck-e-cheese-3508918</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Women throw down at Chuck E. Cheese 3508918]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INDIANAPOLIS — Two women became the stars of a Chuck E Cheese slobberknocker in Indianapolis that went viral over the weekend.

According to the Indianapolis Star, the very unfriendly exchange took place at the Washington Square Mall. 

There, a customer captured footage of the ladies' playground behavior and posted it to Facebook in an now deleted post. Diners and staff attempted to separate the two, but couldn't.

Authorities were called, but the women reportedly left before they arrived. 3508918]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNFPCTTBZCRADATL6IAZLBHMEBSIEALABJFVTAKKBJRXY3ULG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0C0/FFA/0C0FFA2890C4494C9E4284D1958AB6BB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chuck e cheese caught on tape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chuck e cheese disagreement]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chuck e cheese caught on camera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chuck  e cheese videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chuck e cheese video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indiana chuck e cheese]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indianapolis chuck e cheese]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-is-coming-for-your-face-3508727</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook is coming for your face 3508727]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Facebook announced on Tuesday it will soon be introducing new facial recognition features in order to give users more tools to manage their identity on the platform.

People will soon be able to activate facial recognition with an on/off switch to enable three different features, according to a Facebook blog post. 
First, Facebook will alert you when pictures of you are uploaded even if you have not been tagged in them, Gizmodo reported. 
Second, Facebook will notify you if your face is being used in a profile picture. 
Third, visually impaired users can now hear aloud the people tagged around them in group photos. 
To activate these features, users will have to authorize Facebook to access, store and match their face data with all uploads across the social media platform. 3508727]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AACAKWKSJRXVCCL2PR5KLWMIESKRCZKNPAXUCWAEEATAZDKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/515/698/515698FB13244BC58D19A0CA458D6367.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial recognition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial recognition data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ face data]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biometric data]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/deer-family-wanders-into-grocery-store-to-do-some-shopping-3508714</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Deer family wanders into grocery store to do some shopping 3508714]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FORT COLLINS, COLORADO — A doe was seen wandering into a Colorado general store, probably planning to do some Christmas shopping for her family. 3508714]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIAWPXZIKVCWCBKDLVDRIK2CMAEVTRK5KBJWVFKXA6JA7WIGBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/629/82D/62982D7F50314E56B2B1492BBB0AEE61.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deer walking into store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deer family walking into store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ photo of deer walking into store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deer shopping in store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deer caught walking into store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ general store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fort collins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colorado]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uber-accused-of-espionage-bribing-in-explosive-letter-3508688</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Uber accused of espionage, bribing in explosive letter 3508688]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO — Uber may have risen to the top, but apparently it got help from illegal places, at least according to a doozy of an accusation letter from an ex-employee.

CNN reports that said employee had worked on counter-narcotics ops in Colombia, and even went to war in Iraq, before he was recruited to help Uber keep an eye on its rivals.

It was ruthless and infinitely sketchy in obtaining trade secrets, spying, eavesdropping, and impersonating drivers just to get a leg up in the competition. They doled out the bribes, mostly to government official to unblock markets and make the climb to the top easier.

To top it off, the company went to great lengths not to get caught. They used burner phones, vanishing messages, and secret servers so nothing would be recorded.

But you know, life finds a way. 3508688]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZAFPAAEKRCRVWRRLNKW772AMAEVZRZNA5DF7FADKMARXWABAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0F9/339/0F93393C6C304D7C94C5637CA087F61E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ illegal uber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber spying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jacobs letter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ espionage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bribery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hacking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber lawsuit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ waymo]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-is-now-flying-douchey-tourists-to-antarctica-3508648</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China is now flying douchey tourists to Antarctica 3508648]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HONG KONG, CHINA — China claims it has flown its first commercial flight to Antarctica carrying 22 tourists. 
The trip consisted of a 15-hour flight from Hong Kong to South Africa, refueling in Cape Town and then another 5.5 hours to Antarctica. 
After reaching Antarctica, it was another five to six hours to the South Pole, where the plane landed on a 1.5-mile long runway carved into the ice, the BBC reported. 

The Chinese tour operator claims Chinese tourists no longer have to book through foreign agencies.  

Although the trip from Cape Town onwards is actually organized and run by tour operator White Desert. White Desert regularly flies trips to the pole. 
So in reality, the Chinese are running the tours in cooperation with other foreign agencies.  

Chinese tourists now make up the second largest group of tourists to the eighth continent, second only to U.S. tourists. 
The number of Chinese tourists in Antarctica has grown from 100 in 2008 to 3,944 in 2016. 3508648]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMCFEYKSKAAFPAKHKAAAKLBGMRDETERILRAAZU3XA5AWVWAMBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D62/5C2/D625C2BD4EC54345BD194EE3D9F86ED1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Antarctica commercial flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Antarctica tourism]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Antarctica flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese tourists]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mit-researchers-create-glow-in-the-dark-plant-3508599</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[MIT researchers create glow-in-the-dark plant 3508599]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS — MIT researchers have engineered a plant that can glow in the dark from the same enzyme fire flies use to glow.

According to an MIT news release, scientists laced watercress plants with the luciferase enzyme. 

They envision the plant being used as a desk lamp replacement, but say it could possibly be applied to street lamps in the future.

Details of the research were published in the journal Nanoletters. 3508599]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5CFIDRFKADAIBIUKFKRKLSFGJJVTRALKWIFZGIDANJATWT5BD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/002/B8A/002B8A04F7CC4C479FCF701BC5EDF7F2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>33</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glow in the dark plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glowing plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ desk lamp plant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MIT]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glowing flower]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ firefly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how do fire flies glow]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kpop-star-jonghyun-s-suicide-reveals-depression-perils-of-fame-3509753</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kpop star Jonghyun's suicide reveals depression, perils of fame 3509753]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL — Kpop star Jonghyun from popular idol group SHINee has died in an apparent suicide, highlighting the pressures of super stardom in South Korea.

The Korea Herald reports that the singer's sister had received foreboding 'farewell' messages from him on Monday afternoon and alerted emergency responders. They found the 27-year-old unconscious in his apartment and rushed him to the hospital, where he later died.

Jonghyun had been in the public spotlight for almost a decade, and had been struggling with depression. In a long suicide note sent to a friend, he wrote that his doctor blamed him for his condition, citing his personality.

The Korean entertainment industry is notorious for being high-pressure.

Kpop idols sign on at a young age and are subjected to intense training. Agencies control every facet of their lives, from what they wear and eat, to who they communicate with.

High standards are set for the stars' public behavior and appearance, but even so, they are often judged and nitpicked on social media.

Jonghyun's suicide warns of the dark side of fame, and the ruthless conditions in the industry that desperately need to be changed. 3509753]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAARPACTKJIACAATB6LWZ9UTGREE7FZMKBPRXGACKZERRWKYAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/361/138/36113817F5AE4C7E9457F3AE9DB24FD5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jonghyun]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shinee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kpop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korean idol]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kpop boy band]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korean music]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korean wave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hallyu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ idol]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/female-employees-forced-to-slap-each-other-to-build-team-spirit--3509505</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Female employees forced to slap each other to build 'team spirit' 3509505]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NANCHANG, CHINA — A beauty salon in China attempted to motivate its employees by forcing them to slap each other at the company's annual event.

According to China's Caijing magazine, the annual event in Nanchang, Jiangxi province, was to celebrate Jinhuayuan[b] Beauty Salon's 14th anniversary.

An employee told Caijing magazine that the bizarre practice was aimed at strengthening team spirit, and every year the boss has something different planned. 3509505]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIFIDAAAMBR3CZTB5CWZ9LVM2IBRFINLRDWRUZGKZEARAAAAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4A2/9B1/4A29B1DD5CCE483CA2BD10A9BA37F1C7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese company slapping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese employees slapping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ employee slapping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ women slapping faces]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ people forced to slap faces]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese beauty salon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beauty salon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-shortest-day-of-the-year-in-the-north-is-right-around-the-corner-3509485</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The shortest day of the year (in the north) is right around the corner 3509485]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EARTH — The winter solstice arrives on Thursday, making it the shortest day of the year in the Northern Hemisphere. 
The Earth's axis has a 23.5-degree tilt, which is responsible for the seasons. 
As Earth makes its way around the sun each year, the Northern Hemisphere spends half of the year tilted slightly towards the sun during summer, and half the year tilted slightly  away during winter, the New York Times reported.  
The winter solstice will occur at 11:28 a.m., the moment the North Pole is tilted farthest from the sun and the South Pole is tilted closest to it, according to the Baltimore Sun. 
Although it's the shortest day of the year in the north, the length of daylight varies by longitude and latitude. 3509485]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6LWED3WARCR5WZ7BACR3KJBGVBSRFZMABLAXTZGBVDR7ARPAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/E5F/40A/E5F40A20054C4541AA91C01A0A479954.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ winter solstice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solstice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ winter solstice explainer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shortest day of the year]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/wearable-tech-nail-lets-you-literally-talk-to-the-hand-3509436</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Wearable tech nail lets you literally talk to the hand 3509436]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — British telecom O2 has unveiled a prototype for a new wearable gadget that bridges the gap between fashion and tech.

Mobile News reports that O2 has teamed up with London beauty brand Nails Inc. to create the 'Mobile Nail', a wearable tech nail that can be used as a phone handset.

The Mobile Nail pairs with a phone using bluetooth, and allows the user to answer a call, redial the last dialled number, or play music. The tech nail is also customizable, and can be modified with different nail art designs.

Along with the unveiling of Mobile Nail, O2 published its 'Future of Mobile Life Report', which predicts that embeddable and wearable tech will advance to such a degree that the human body will replace smartphones by 2049. 3509436]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AWCYAFKIDF3C3CKEAWTLURMMBBVSC2AICFTTKYKSLAXAZDKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/79E/E6F/79EE6F5D6E154E089B4D204AFAE41EEB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>48</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wearable tech]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tech nail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mobile nail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ O2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wearable technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nail phone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nail inc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bluetooth]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/baby-born-after-being-frozen-as-an-embryo-for-24-years-3509375</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Baby born after being frozen as an embryo for 24 years 3509375]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KNOXVILLE, TENNESSEE — The longest known frozen human embryo to result in a successful birth was born last month in Tennessee.

Emma Wren Gibson was born on November 25 from an embryo that was cryogenically frozen 24 years ago, CNN reported. 
Emma's parents, Tina and Benjamin Gibson, chose embryo adoption after realizing they were unable to have children.  

The Gibsons selected Emma after viewing around 300 donor profiles listing basic genetic information about the genetic parents. 

They were surprised to find out the age of the embryo when it thawed on March 13 at the National Embryo Donation Center. 
The embryo that led to Emma was created for in vitro fertilization by an anonymous couple and placed in cryogenic storage on October 14, 1992. 
The previous record was set in 2011 when a New York woman gave birth to a boy born from an embryo created 20 years earlier, the Washington Post reported. 3509375]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBNFGCACBECATBCDLVCRTKLRGRBBISAKKBPAZFAEAIEW7WZGKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/37B/423/37B423D8583040939A344C2994FF5A88.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-22T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby born]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frozen eggs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryogenically frozen]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-to-stop-flagging-fake-news-because-it-doesn-t-work-3510619</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook to stop flagging fake news because it doesn't work 3510619]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — Americans who get their fake news from Facebook will no longer have to see red flags next to their favorite stories. Yay!!! 

In December 2016, Facebook started showing a disputed warning next to stories deemed fake by third-party fact checking websites. 

However, research on correcting misinformation has shown that putting a strong image, like a red flag, actually just entrenches deeply held beliefs.    

Facebook's new master plan is to now show related articles next to the fake stories. Because people with entrenched beliefs always like to read other views. 

But is Facebook really to blame for all this fake news nonsense? Maybe the U.S. should stop producing so many gullible idiots. 3510619]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIDRGAIIKWJR5AAYLBJA594TGVDB5EZLK5AWPHIAA2IAKBZCBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/95F/CFD/95FCFD1F87FAE23D1AADF660EA86427D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook fake news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook fake news flags]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook fake news fact checking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook fake news related articles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/suspect-driver-drags-policeman-for-half-a-mile-in-florida-3510472</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Suspect driver drags policeman for half-a-mile in Florida 3510472]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FLORIDA — Police bodycam footage shows the moment a driver drags a Florida cop for half-a-mile.

According to CBS Miami, veteran officer John Cusack approached Thomas Cabrera on Tuesday morning over a suspected overdose.

Cusack reckoned Cabrera was holdin' and tried to get in the vehicle.

That's when Cabrera came too put pedal to the metal. He drags officer Cusack for around half-a-mile.

Cusack, aged 38, eventually fell from the vehicle and took a very rough looking tumble.
He got some injuries, but is looking to return to work soon.

As for Cabrera, he led cops on a high-speed rush hour chase, before he and someone else in the car were eventually nabbed.

Crabbera was charged with an attempt on an officer's life, as well as fleeing and eluding officers. 3510472]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCFCACVKZAR7AKDBSIAK74UGVBEZEZNK6JF7T3SKADFGWIEKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/AFF/165/AFF1654609594A288095799FAD041EA2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cop dragged by car]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ driver drags policeman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police bodycam 2017]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cop dragged by suspect's car caught on tape]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cop dragged by suspect]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crazy police chases]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high-speed chase]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/police-and-firefighters-rescue-horse-from-frozen-pond-3510437</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Police and firefighters rescue horse from frozen pond 3510437]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RAY TOWNSHIP, MICHIGAN — Police footage shows the moment Michigan deputies and firefighters help save a trapped horse's life. 

According to a post on the Macomb County Sheriff's Office Facebook page, the animal took a fall inside an ice covered pond.

Police say they responded to the call at 9.30 am Wednesday December 13 at a residence in Ray Township. Deputies tried to help the horse out with ropes, but the animal couldn't get it's leg on top of the ice. 

During the course of their rescue, one of the officers actually fell into the icy pond with the horse.  The officer quickly got back out and managed to continue working to save the horse. He wasn't hurt.

They eventually pulled the horse out after breaking parts of the ice where it was struggling. Police say the animal was seen by a vet and was uninjured. 3510437]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2KRCXZEA6IWIXCALJPAXKLXMEDSKSANABKWZT3YAVERABALAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/1E2/C09/1E2C0987F9434FD78ADC63CC38DCA0AE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>128</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police save animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ firefighters save animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal rescue video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal rescue stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ happy animal stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal rescue videos 2017]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sea-turtle-gets-caught-in-53m-worth-of-blow-3510420</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sea turtle gets caught in $53m worth of blow 3510420]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EASTERN PACIFIC— The U.S. Coast Guard this week rescued a sea turtle caught amongst 1.8 tonnes of floating yayo worth an estimated $53 million.

According to a post on their Facebook, the Coasties spotted the wired reptile earlier this week while on patrol in the Eastern Pacific and went to help it out. 

They set the turtle free, but said he received chafing to its neck and flippers. 3510420]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJNAGAAIBBJR7DKCLWLAT9DWMRBSKFAKKJLFMGRGAWKAMVRHKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5FF/0AC/5FF0ACEB291E429DA3B30BA7641C1780.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>44</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us coast guard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea turtle caught in net]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea turtle caught in web]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reptile stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea turtles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eastern pacific]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/what-is-toxic-shock-syndrome--3510393</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[What is toxic shock syndrome? 3510393]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — In 2012, model Lauren Wasser lost part of her right leg to a rare but potentially life-threatening condition which she claims came courtesy of her tampon.

Toxic shock syndrome is typically associated with menstruating women, and is caused by toxins from the Staphylococcus aureus bacteria, reports the Washington Post.

TSS is linked with tampon use, since the synthetic fibers and high absorbency provide the ideal breeding ground for the bacteria.

According to Mayo Clinic, symptoms include gastrointestinal distress, a sudden high-fever, low blood pressure, a sunburn-like rash, and redness of the eyes, mouth, and throat.

Toxic shock progress rapidly, and can lead to kidney failure. Though fatal, it is treatable with antibiotics and fluids if diagnosed early. 

Another variety of the syndrome is caused by group A streptococcus bacteria, with those having cuts or burns, or having had recent surgery especially at risk.

Toxic shock syndrome is rare enough that there's little information on how to prevent the onset of the disease. 3510393]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMDRICABKWKAPDZSL5BFR9BAMZCB3SZNAZDW3TIGARDRGVAKKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/701/BE5/701BE5CE6A5B4050AAC30B91496C63E8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  toxic shock syndrome]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tss]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ staph]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ staphylococcus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strep]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ streptococcus menstruation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tampons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic shock]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kidney failure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flue like symptoms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ staph bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strep bacteria]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-charged-350-for-leaving-honest-hotel-review-3510371</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman charged $350 for leaving honest hotel review 3510371]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NASHVILLE, INDIANA — A guest at an Indiana “hotel” claims she was charged $350 and threatened by a lawyer after writing an honest and negative review.

Luckily, the questionable business practices at the Abbey Inn & Suites in Brown County caught the eye of the Indiana Attorney General’s Office, which filed a lawsuit on Dec. 15 alleging the inn violated the Indiana Deceptive Consumer Sales Act, CBS News reported. 

Katrina Arthur and her hubby stayed at the inn in March 2016 and were treated to a nightmare from start to finish. 

The room was in shambles, but luckily they had hairs and dirt in the sheets. 

The sweet aroma of sewage permeated the air, the water pressure was non-existent and the AC was busted. The staff were also nowhere to be found. 

After their stay, Katrina got an email from the inn asking for her to write an online review, which she did and blasted the establishment. 

For her troubles? The inn charged her $350 bucks. Between Sept. 2015 and Nov. 2016, the Abbey Inn actually had a policy in place that let them charge people for writing bad reviews. Naturally, it was almost impossible to find little piece of info.  

Hopefully Arthur will get her $350 back. 

The moral of the story, when you see that an inn’s two biggest selling points are hot tubs and a wedding chapel (in that order), stay someplace else. 3510371]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDFCYIHKRAWEAARKFIRZK2ANBLVREANABJR5TACASIAKWKSAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/354/7C7/3547C79EFEEE437A96F7467C0AFB6E51.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[online reviews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[online hotel reviews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[writing online reviews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[woman charged writing negative review]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-is-reportedly-adding-anthrax-to-icbms-3510342</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea is reportedly adding anthrax to ICBMS 3510342]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE NORTH — Pyongyang's dictator has Asia on edge, after new reports suggest he is adding certain chemicals in intercontinental kabooms. 

Reportedly, the North holds 5,000 tons of anthrax in stockpiles and is testing it out on rocket armaments.

The news comes after it was revealed last month that Pyongyang had constructed a projectile that could reach Washington. 3510342]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NWMXRFBEDFKCIUKBLRI7JAMSJS3RRKA6PFZFCYBVBRIAIMKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/19E/A33/19EA3330EFA6480E834225C4E17FCC2B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocket man]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dprk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pyongyang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korea news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim jong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trump v kim]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/access-to-steam-community-blocked-in-china-3510338</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Access to Steam Community blocked in China 3510338]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEHIND THE GREAT FIREWALL — Reports coming out of China this week say that Chinese Community Party have blocked Steam community access in the country. 

The Steam store is still accessible, but the writing may very well be on the wall for Valve-run gaming website. And if that's the case, Valve will be feeling the pinch. Reportedly, millions of their customers come from the PRC. 

PUBG was banned in the country, but was allowed back in only after Tencent agreed to help make the Chinese version, socialist friendly. 3510338]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMDAIC3SKSKAIYZULZARIKLYG2JE5ST3AVBWRTALA5EFCWTWLG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/85C/75C/85C75C70C3534CB293A9C6F05778124A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam blocked in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam community access]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wegame]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam community]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam blocked]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese gamers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tencent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jack ma]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fake-chinese-cop-arrested-for-body-slamming-student-3510330</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fake Chinese cop arrested for body slamming student 3510330]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHAOGUAN, CHINA — A man in southeast China who claims to be a cop was caught in public assaulting a student for damaging his vehicle. 

The bizarre incident took place on December 19 in Shaoguan, Guangdong province. 

The unnamed man, who claims to be a cop was seen beating the crap out of a student and body slammed him for throwing rocks at his vehicle. The student was also forced to kneel down and apologize to the man in public by slapping his own face repeatedly. 

The cop was later arrested by local authority, and the real cop found out he's actually just a security guy working for an insurance company. 3510330]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5DFPCKWKRDRMYKEKADF792HMZABXSIQABIW3HZDKEDAAAZHAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/5E8/371/5E83719F2EBA4FE49C2F7CBF5DA391C1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-23T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>43</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese cop body slam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese cop body slam student]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ student gets body slammed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake cop in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china fake cop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ body slammed in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ guangdong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-cash-me-outside-teen-pays-off-mom-s-65-000-mortgage-3513171</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Cash Me Outside' teen pays off mom's $65,000 mortgage 3513171]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOYNTON BEACH, FLORIDA — 'Cash me outside' girl Danielle Bregoli is dishing out Christmas miracles this year, and no one is happier than mom.

TMZ reports that the 14-year-old presented her mother with a $65,000 check to pay off the mortgage, in what is arguably the best Christmas present ever: debt relief.

Bregoli posted a video on Instagram of her handing over the gift, and mom responding with teary-eyed disbelief.

It's a touching display, especially since the relationship between the Bregoli ladies was once fraught with stealing, aggression, and a bunch of other drama.

The younger Bregoli became an overnight viral sensation in 2016, when she went on the Dr. Phil show and uttered her now-famous catchphrase.

The teen was savvy enough to capitalize on her fame, selling merchandise and charging for TV and event appearances. She's currently pursuing a music career, and now goes by the rap name Bhad Bhabie.

Though judging by her Christmas surprise, we'd say Bhabie really ain't so Bhad. 3513171]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADRICCTK6QAABIRLFPAR7UTMREBRSK4KADF5G3YAICAEVAEKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/494/EF3/494EF34ACD0D404FB301232C749E8D6F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>80</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cash me outside]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ danielle bregoli]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bhad bhabie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas miracle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dr. phil]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ best christmas present]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ best christmas gift]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cash me outside girl]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ daughter of the year]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/clerk-scares-off-knife-wielding-robber-by-pulling-a-gun-3512985</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Clerk scares off knife-wielding robber by pulling a gun 3512985]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEWPORT, MICHIGAN — With all the guns floating around the U.S., this Einstein from Newport, Michigan decided to try and rob a gas station armed only with a knife. 

Video released by Michigan State Police shows the smooth criminal entering the BP at 10:40 p.m. 

The guy pulls his knife and demands cash. The clerk reaches behind the counter like he's going to take out money, but instead pulls out a piece and points it right at knife man. 
The robber does a quick reassessment of the situation and chooses to high tail it out of the store. 

Police say the suspect is a white male with brown hair between 5'5 - 5'7 and drives a light-colored grey or tan, older model mid-sized car. 

Luckily, few people fit that description so this should be pretty open and shut for the police. 3512985]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAARCYCTKFNWIWAWBSKAK7URGIAETFZQAJPFTGZGAAARPCK2AE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/474/4AC/4744AC03681342338545627C52A4E51E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clerk defends store]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clerk fights off robber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robber runs away]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BP gas station]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/two-heterosexual-best-friends-get-married-to-avoid-inheritance-tax-3512871</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Two heterosexual best friends get married to avoid inheritance tax 3512871]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBLIN, IRELAND — Two straight best friends decided to get hitched in order to avoid paying around $60,000 in inheritance tax. Ah — true love. 

Best pals Matt Murphy, 83, and 58-year-old Michael O'Sullivan decided to keep things simple with a small ceremony at Sir Patrick Dun's Hospital Registry Office.

Murphy had planned to give his house to his best friend, but was surprised to find out how much the inheritance tax would be. 

The two have been bros for over 30 years. O'Sullivan currently crashes at Murphy's place and acts as his caregiver. 

After a friend jokingly said they should think about marriage, O'Sullivan and Murphy had their eureka moment and decided to take the plunge. 3512871]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNFGDCTBIERIBRTLIBFRLUTGVCSXRRKAAAFVGAFK2IAGX3SAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/84F/3EE/84F3EE1B4EF84CEF9C62EA0BBD6B4609.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ best friends marry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ best friends marriage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Ireland best friends marry]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ inheritance tax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marriage to avoid inheritance tax]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/wild-truffle-found-growing-on-paris-rooftop-3512861</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Wild truffle found growing on Paris rooftop 3512861]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PARIS — Wild truffle was found growing on a Paris rooftop, making it a first for the city.  
The foodie's fungus was discovered chillin at the base of a hornbeam tree in a hotel rooftop garden close to the Eiffel Tower, the BBC reported. 

Food connoisseurs are excited because truffles are usually found farther south in warmer climates, where they are dug up by specially-trained dogs or pigs.

The type of truffle found in Paris isn't the most prized, but it still goes great with scallops, sausage or potatoes.  

The 25-gram winter truffle was taken to the National Museum of Natural History. 

Paris has been pushing for more urban gardening, and has a goal of developing about 100 acres of office and building rooftops over the next two years. 
Well, now that you can grow truffles up there, they'll probably be a lot more volunteers. 3512861]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFCACTKZFRRVISB6LFXL4SGICBIEALKWLFRHKTAFIFIXZQAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/202/B32/202B32F92B35459C935E1C47E264ED06.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ truffles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild truffle paris hotel rooftop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild winter black truffle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild truffle Paris rooftop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ truffle growing paris rooftop]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/airport-facial-recognition-scans-draw-scrutiny-for-violating-privacy-3512842</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Airport facial recognition scans draw scrutiny for violating privacy 3512842]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA — A report has found that an airport biometric program is improperly gathering data on Americans, and violating their privacy.

According to a report from the Georgetown Law Center for Privacy and Technology, the Department of Homeland Security has installed facial scanners in nine international airports across the U.S., as part of their biometric exit program.

The program is part of efforts to nab travelers who are overstaying their visas, or using fraudulent documents. Passengers' faces are scanned at the boarding gate, and matched to a DHS database for verification.

Face scans are mandatory for foreign nationals, but U.S. citizens on international flights can opt out and have their documents manually checked.

It's unclear though, if American passengers are being informed of this option.

According to Homeland Security's own data, 1 in 25 travelers are erroneously rejected by the system despite using valid credentials.

The technology also reportedly had high error rates, and often inaccurately identified women and African Americans. 3512842]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNFGCIDBIERCWRYLVAAZ6DSMVAETEC3AVDWMUZKKFKWPDKSKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/C09/20F/C0920F12B14297409B1C5F036D2C9ECA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial recognition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial scanner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ face scans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biometric exit program]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ violation of privacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homeland security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dhs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cbp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport scanner]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ privacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biometrics]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/male-rub-on-contraceptive-goes-into-human-trials-3512755</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Male rub-on contraceptive goes into human trials 3512755]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROCKVILLE, MARYLAND — Government researchers in the U.S. are getting ready to test a topical contraceptive gel designed to lower sperm production.

The clinical trial will begin in April and run for around four years, and will be the largest study conducted to test a hormonal form of male birth control, MIT Technology Review reported. 

Researchers at the National Institute of Child Health and Human Development are working on a hormonal gel that reduces sperm count when applied to the skin. 
The gel contains two synthetic hormones — nestorone and testosterone. 

The nestorone blocks the testes from making enough testosterone to produce normal levels of sperm. 

The synthetic testosterone is needed to prevent hormonal imbalance caused by the nestorone.
More than 400 couples in the U.S., the U.K., Italy, Sweden, Chile and Kenya will participate in the clinical trial. 

Couples will use the treatment for over four months while their sperm levels are checked.  
Men in the study will take home a bottle of the gel and rub around half a teaspoon of it on their upper arms or shoulders every day. The gel takes about a minute to dry. 
According to researchers, the gel can lower sperm count for about 72 hours. 3512755]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJFGY3SAIEWPARWLZDR7LBCMVASXF35KSKR3FIKAAAWIBIGKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/434/588/43458831FCB74F639CD233E5392DE156.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>43</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medicine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ clinical trial]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ topical gel]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/apple-admits-to-intentionally-slowing-down-older-iphones-3512719</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Apple admits to intentionally slowing down older iPhones 3512719]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CUPERTINO, CALIFORNIA — Data from a benchmarking firm confirmed long-held suspicions that Apple has been intentionally slowing down older iPhones.

The tech giant has confirmed as much, but claims it's not a conspiracy theory to get you to buy their newer models, and is instead a battery issue.

CNET reports that lithium-ion batteries degrade over time, and can only hold an 80% charge after 500 charge cycles. This, along with cold climate or a low charge, affects performance.

Older iPhone models tend to draw more power than their batteries can handle, which can cause the device to suddenly and unexpectedly shut down. To prevent this, Apple's new iOS update throttles CPU speeds on older models, in order to limit how much power is drawn from the battery.

A number of users have worked around the issue by replacing their batteries, which reportedly restored the phones to their normal speed.

Critics have slammed Apple for its lack of transparency, pointing out that users should have been informed of the issue and possible solutions. Most mistakenly believed they needed to upgrade to newer models, when really, a battery replacement would have sufficed. 3512719]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AFIC3WKAHAGAIYB5CWTKJHNFLSXERQLVCFVH3SABKRCBKTLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/61A/E7E/61AE7EC90E414A5DAC9B03AC899B70C9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ apple]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone update]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ software update]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone speed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ power usage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battery life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone 6]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone 6 plus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iphone 7]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ conspiracy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ obsolescence conspiracy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/great-american-eclipse-created-bow-waves-in-our-atmosphere-3513789</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Great American Eclipse created bow waves in our atmosphere 3513789]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SPACE — The total solar eclipse in August 2017 left bow waves in the Earth's upper atmosphere, like a boat sailing through water. 
On August 21, researchers from MIT's Haystack Observatory and the University of Tromsø in Norway were able to find the first unambiguous evidence of atmospheric bow-waves.  
The team published their findings in the journal Geophysical Research Letters. 
The bow-wave theory says that a total solar eclipse will create high-pressure pockets under the moon's shadow that then slice through low-pressure air as the path of totality moves across the planet. These air pockets then generate small bow waves in the atmosphere.
During the August eclipse, the scientists collected data from around 2,000 satellite sensors placed across North America. 
They detected tiny bow waves in Earth's ionosphere, the section of the atmosphere that begins 37 miles above the surface. 
The researchers said their study, reveals complex interconnections between the Sun, Moon and Earth's neutral atmosphere and ionosphere. 3513789]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMDFAAAJLVFRXVARKBJF56DSGIEBVSIIKRAR3UZAAIBRCWIMBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A27/422/A27422E843524720ADD2A1A5364DB63D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bow wave theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bow wave phenomenon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total solar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar eclipse bow wave theory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total solar eclipse bow wave phenomenon]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fake-chinese-cop-arrested-for-body-slamming-student-3513636</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fake Chinese cop arrested for body slamming student 3513636]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHAOGUAN, CHINA — A man in southeast China who claims to be a cop was recently caught in public harassing a student for damaging his vehicle. 

The bizarre incident took place on December 19 in Shaoguan, Guangdong province. 

The unnamed man, who claims to be a cop was seen harassing a student and introduced him to the ground for throwing rocks at his vehicle. The student was forced to apologize to the man in public and punish himself.

The cop was later arrested by local authority, and the real cop found out he's actually just a security guy working for an insurance company. 3513636]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNAGCCTAFMAGBZVL2KWRL4XMBJS5SC4KVDFPFALAZBRKVZKKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/916/2EB/9162EB34324C4F77A61AA85825F53B16.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>43</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese cop body slam student]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese cop harassing students]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ student gets harassed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake cop in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china fake cop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[guangdong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-claims-united-gave-away-her-first-class-seat-to-texas-rep-3513596</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman claims United gave away her first class seat to Texas rep 3513596]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOUSTON — United Airlines is again embroiled in a controversy after a passenger said she was booted from her seat to make room for a Texas lawmaker.

The Houston Chronicle reports that on December 18, Jean-Marie Simon was in Houston, waiting to board the last leg of her round trip D.C. to Washington flight.

Simon bought first class tickets and was supposed to be in seat 1A, but the gate agent who scanned her ticket found that it wasn't in the system, and asked if she cancelled her flight.

Her seat had apparently been taken, and she was given a $500 voucher and reseated in Economy Plus.

Simon soon found out that her seat had ultimately been given to U.S. Rep Sheila Jackson Lee, a Houston democrat. Another congressman on the flight also told her Jackson Lee made a habit of bumping passengers off flights, and it was the third time he'd personally seen her do it.

Simon also says a flight attendant approached her after she snapped a photo of Jackson Lee, and threatened to have her removed if she caused problems.

Responding to the incident, Jackson Lee claimed she never asked for special treatment, before then saying Simon may have easily targeted her as an African-American woman.

Simon flatly denies the racism accusation. She has since written United CEO of her ordeal, but only received an apology from a resolution manager.

The 63-year-old private school teacher has yet to receive a formal apology from the company. 3513596]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKWEAAJBZERXCZWBIARI7SHGMDBRRTZAAAW3TKYARDFAWC4KC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/9F8/B32/9F8B322ABC7B46019417CE332FC9D5DB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ united airlines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sheila jackson lee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ democrat rep]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ houston rep]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ us congressman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ abuse of power]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/argentinian-toddler-drinking-puddle-water-sparks-outrage-3513587</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Argentinian toddler drinking puddle water sparks outrage 3513587]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[POSADAS, ARGENTINA — A photo of a girl, probably no older than 3,drinking water from a puddle in Posadas, Argentina went viral earlier this month.

An image of those horrible circumstances went viral and brought international shame, outrage and criticism towards Argentina. It was was photographed by a local journalist who had stopped at a nearby traffic light.

The image was then shared with others in Posadas, including UNICEF aid worker Migue Rios who eventually posted it to Facebook.

Reportedly, the girl is from Mbyá Guarani community. They're one of Argentina's several indigenous groups. 

According to reports, journalists in the area banded together and got some water for the kids. Rios also said that the girl in the photo was seen by medical staff afterwards.

Argentina, a Southern Hemisphere country, itself is currently in the height of its summer. 
It's also currently embroiled in mass protests over controversial social reforms. 

Both the World Bank and CIA data list Argentina as one of the most unequal countries on the planet. Reportedly, Myba kids are sent by families into Posadas to beg for money. 3513587]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIRAC3TBJNRAWA7BWJR7LU3M6JB7RK4AWJATGAGK5DAVARPAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/62B/48E/62B48EAE815D483D8679BCD6B1B7A96D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>91</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ girl drinks puddle water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ argentina girl puddle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toddler drinks from ground]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beggar children]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ indigenous people in argentina]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ posadas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mbya Guarani]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-love-hospital-dispels-mistresses-from-extramarital-affairs-3513541</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese love hospital 'dispels' mistresses from extramarital affairs 3513541]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI —  A so-called love hospital in Shanghai, China is taking a very direct approach to solving couple's problems.

Their solution? Eliminate the creepin' lover's mistress via mistress dispelling. 

And, according to the BBC, there's 33 ways the Weiqing Love Hospital can accomplish that. 3513541]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNNAGDIJAFMAMB3AB5BAV9BHGWKB5E33K5ARVUCTAIDAXBZEAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/70B/4F3/70B4F35E813A46DD9E0D2B5C78F650C0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese love hospital]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marriage counselling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ relationship healing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mistress dispeller]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weird china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Weiqing Love Hospital]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shanghai]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spacex-rocket-launch-leaves-ghostly-glowing-trail-in-sky-3513499</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[SpaceX rocket launch leaves ghostly glowing trail in sky 3513499]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VANDENBERG AIR FORCE SPACE, CALIFORNIA — SpaceX launched the Falcon 9 rocket last Friday from California's Vandenberg Air Force Base.

After the launch, social media was flooded with photos and video, with some speculating that the strange phenomenon could have been from a UFO. Even the CEO himself poked fun at the situation.

According to space and astronomy newsite Space.com, the rocket was carrying 10 Iridium[b] Next communications satellites into orbit. The launch was SpaceX's 18th and final mission of 2017. The impressive 18 successful launches became a new record for SpaceX, as it had never pulled off more than 8 successful orbital launches in a single year. 3513499]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNNRACZJABNRAVIXB6LR36LRGFJV5ERQAFKA5HZLBWKFCBK9BA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/D4A/CAB/D4ACAB3AFE1D984157E84077AF866FB0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>309</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falcon 9 launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falcon 9 rocket launch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ falcon 9 rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elon musk rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rocket launch off]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vandenberg air force space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ california]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ana-flight-returns-to-lax-after-flying-hours-with-wrong-passenger-3514417</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[ANA flight returns to LAX after flying hours with wrong passenger 3514417]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — All Nippon Airways (ANA) has apologized to 226 passengers that were treated to an 8-hour flight to nowhere. 

ANA Flight 175 was set to fly from LAX to Tokyo, but four hours into the journey, the crew discovered an extra passenger on board. 

Two brothers with similar names were booked on separate flights on two separate airlines to Tokyo, but somehow both got on ANA Flight 175.  

Model and TV personality Chrissy Teigen happened to be on the flight with her hubby with the pipes, John Legend, and gave live tweet updates as the eight hour u-turn unfolded, according to CNN. 
Yeah, it must have been horrible sitting in first class for eight hours and then having the media write stories about your ordeal - first world problems.  
What Teigen should have done is made John give the 226 passengers a little in-flight concert. Now that would have been an epic flight to nowhere. 3514417]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLWEDKSAECAZAZWLVCRK72FMNJV5SALLSKF3HIEKNLRIWIAKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/21A/5DD/21A5DD4FAE277506761F8564E7DB0186.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ANA flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chrissy Teigen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ John Legend]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ANA Flight 175]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flight to nowhere]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/penn-woman-shocked-with-whopping-284-billion-electric-bill-3514361</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Penn woman shocked with whopping $284 billion electric bill 3514361]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ERIE, PENNSYLVANIA — Over the Christmas holiday break, a 58-year-old Pennsylvania woman received an electric bill that costs more than $284 billion.

Luckily, her son called the electric company, Penelec, before she made December's minimum payment. The company acknowledged the bill was a mistake and changed the balance to the correct amount: $284.46. 3514361]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASKWCXCXAMDWTDTHLSPRZ9DSMAEBVET9AZBW7HKTKFKACC3TAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/B75/232/B752329654F9835D10BABAD1256F6705.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric bill payment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crazy electric bill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ crazy expensive bill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ expensive electric bill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ electric bill too high]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ utility bills for a house]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Penelec]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Erie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pennsylvania]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/gaming-addiction-to-be-listed-a-mental-health-disorder-by-who-3514288</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Gaming addiction to be listed a mental health disorder by WHO 3514288]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GENEVA — For the first time ever, gaming addiction is set to be classed as a health issue by the World Health Organization.

Currently termed ‘gaming disorder’, the condition will be listed in a 2018 update version of the International Classification of Diseases. 

A draft version of the definition, says symptoms of gaming disorder can include continuation or escalation of gaming despite negative consequences. 

The addiction can also shown by the gamer exhibiting impaired control over gaming, and by more time being given to gaming to the extent that it takes precedence over other important life aspects.

These symptoms have to go on for a year for diagnosis to be assigned, but that time can be shortened depending on the severity of the symptoms. 3514288]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AFGACWKZCRCAI9BNKFT9U3M5EE5F3SLWJF5HALKZBFCWT2AB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BFD/1EE/BFD1EEA1A99A417E8520D5D9A980906C</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[gaming addiction symptoms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[gaming addiction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[game addiction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[gaming addiction symptoms and withdrawal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[gaming addiction who]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[can you be addicted to videogames]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[gaming health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[gaming mental health effects]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spinal-implant-helps-chronic-pain-sufferers-control-aches-3514277</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Spinal implant helps chronic pain sufferers control aches 3514277]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHICAGO — Small spine implants can help numb pain in patients dealing with chronic aches and agony.

The technology, by Abbott Laboratories, works by the patient receiving an battery-powered implant into their body that stimulates an area of the spine called the dorsal root ganglion. 

Pain processed by the body there can be counteracted with electricity from the device. The implant is operated via remote control. 

A patient with chronic pain told Bloomberg the implant doesn't eliminate pain completely but can help make something they can live with. 3514277]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDRCCTUKFLRXAZXLBIAK944GJKVXURLLRDW3FCSAEDWPBIAAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/2D1/CB2/2D1CB2CE74C252F29B8D4AE0A887D72D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>41</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pain elimination]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spine implant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chronic pain elimination]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pain implant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ abbott laboratories]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/utah-deputy-punches-through-frozen-pond-to-save-8-year-old-3514264</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Utah deputy punches through frozen pond to save 8-year-old 3514264]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW HARMONY, UTAH — A Utah deputy is being hailed a hero after bravely jumping into icy water to save a drowning boy.

The Salt Lake Tribune reports that the 8-year-old had been chasing his dog over a frozen pond late Monday when he suddenly fell through the ice. Another boy saw what happened and ran for help.

Sgt. Aaron Thompson arrived first on the scene, and immediately attempted a rescue — punching through the ice to create a pathway to the victim.

When the ice got too thick to punch, Thompson stomped on it to get it to break, and soon jumped into the water to search for the missing child.

The boy had been in the water for about 30 minutes before Sgt. Thompson finally found him beneath the ice, roughly 25 feet from the shore. He was airlifted to a nearby hospital, where he is still being treated.

Thompson suffered cuts and abrasions on his arm, and symptoms of hypothermia, but has since been treated and is expected to be back at work by next week. 3514264]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2JACDCVASLR3BZSBNJF5L4RMWJBKRIIABLW5GIKK5DRGVKYKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/4A0/6A5/4A06A563F5984D41A80B385BB0EE6F17.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy falls through ice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ frozen pond]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drowning rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ daring rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero cop]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hero deputy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ icy pond]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/florida-man-goes-rocky-on-atm-for-giving-him-too-much-dough-3514252</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Florida man goes Rocky on ATM for giving him too much dough 3514252]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COCOA, FLORIDA — A Florida man has been charged with criminal mischief after he reportedly assaulted an ATM machine. 
Michael Joseph Oleksik, 23, was arrested after a three-week investigation into the incident which took place at the Wells Fargo branch in Cocoa on Nov. 29, USA Today reported. 

According to the police, surveillance footage shows Oleksik having a disagreement with the touch screen that got physical, real physical. 
At one point, Oleksik introduced his fists of fury to the machine, which ended up costing at least $5,000 in damages. 
Oleksik called the bank a short time after the throw down and told them the ATM had dispensed too much money. 
He said he was in a hurry for work and didn't know what to do.

Wells Fargo was then kind enough to have Oleksik arrested and charged. 3514252]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVDFGAAHKACRCDZSLJJATL2CMVDSVRRNKVBR3UZAKEDAEBIGAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/068/117/0681172777A94559911A9F10EF5E6147.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>47</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida man charged]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida man beats up ATM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ florida man attacks ATM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ATM malfunction]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nyc-to-have-tightest-security-ever-for-new-year-s-eve-celebrations-3515264</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NYC to have tightest security ever for New Year's Eve celebrations 3515264]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW YORK — New York City is planning to have the most security ever for the annual New Year's Eve celebration in Times Square.   

Police said this year they would send more rooftop observation teams and counter-snipers into more buildings, the New York Times reported. 
Authorities will be patrolling hotels in the days prior to New Year's Eve. 
The NYPD is also attaching reflective markers on the outsides of buildings, so in the event of an attack, officers can more quickly locate shooters. 
The police will also deploy explosive-detecting dogs. 
Sand trucks and blocker vehicles will be positioned to stop cars or truck attacks. 

New York usually deploys around 5,000 police officers for New Year's celebrations, but this year, the numbers would be higher, police said. 3515264]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEDFMCIDK5ARTBZULICRT72GMWKS3U36ABJF3GZCARCWIB3YAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A61/0AD/A610AD95403D53CC31D632199E2B7DBA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>46</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York New Year's Eve security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New Year's Eve security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New Year's security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New York Times Square]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Times Square New Year's security]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fbi-investigating-bros-who-got-on-wrong-lax-tokyo-flight-but-how-on-earth-did-it-happen--3515208</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[FBI investigating bros who got on wrong LAX-Tokyo flight, but how on Earth did it happen? 3515208]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[L.A. — The FBI may charge two brothers who allegedly boarded an L.A. to Tokyo flight with the same boarding pass, reports ABC News. 

The flight was forced to turn back four hours into its journey when airline staff discovered an unauthorized person.  

The mishap happened after a pair of Tokyo-bound brothers, booked on different flights, were somehow allowed onto the same ANA flight on December 26.

According to ABC News, the feds allege that one used a duplicate boarding pass to do so. Law enforcement told CNN that the brothers had similar names. 

While this case is suspect, there have been genuine flight mix-ups in the past.

Aviation expert Buck Rodger told CNN that there are three checks for passengers. These are boarding gate checks, in-flight destination announcements and assigned seating. Rodgers said that a combination of faults from these can create a flight mix-up.

Federal investigators are looking into the case but have not charged anyone, reported the BBC. 3515208]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNFXCRHBMGAVWCDL2JWT9U3NBKSVSKZKFIAXHRHAZDRAACUAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/FD6/79C/FD679CCF07A2BD68F58B61C97BCA5145.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>106</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ what happens if you get on the wrong plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ana]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boarding the wrong plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ getting on the wrong flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ got on the wrong flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ got on the wrong plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ USA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airline ticket stories]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/vietnam-sets-up-cyber-force-to-combat-wrongthink-3515118</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Vietnam sets up cyber force to combat wrongthink 3515118]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HO CHI MINH CITY, VIETNAM— Vietnam has tasked 10,000 members of a new military internet unit with countering wrong online views online.

Dubbed 'Force  47', the unit has been set up during a crackdown on critics of the country's one-party communist regime, Reuters reported.

Force 47 censors are already operating in several sectors, Tuoi Tre reported, citing a quote from Colonel General Nguyen Trong Nghia recorded by newspaper.

In every hour, minute, and second we must be ready to fight proactively against the wrong views, said the General, reported Reuters, citing Tuoi Tre.

Data from internet watchdog Freedom House lists Vietnam is one of the worst places in the world for internet freedom. According to Human Rights Watch, the country jailed 19 bloggers and activists in 2016.

Around half of its 90 million-strong population are connected and it is said to be one of the top 10 countries for Facebook users by numbers. 3515118]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6JWMXRFAIAWVD3HKAAATLDUGMABXEC6AWPWRUCRBVDFCBAJLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/BD7/562/BD75624DA845AEF231A3F5AA8588080A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>50</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vietnam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vietnam force 47]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vietnam internet taskforce]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vietnam internet policy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thought police]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wrongthink]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/first-long-distance-charging-system-gets-fcc-approval-3515036</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[First long-distance charging system gets FCC approval 3515036]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN JOSE, CALIFORNIA — A San Jose startup's long-distance charging system has just gotten approval from the Federal Communications Commission. 

Energous announced on Tuesday that it received consumer safety certification for its midfield transmitter, which puts it one step closer to commercial availability.

The Wattup midfield transmitter converts electricity into radio frequencies, and can be attached or embedded into a desktop computer monitor.

Wattup can charge devices fitted with a receiver from a distance of up to three feet.

It can power multiple gadgets simultaneously, including computer accessories and personal devices, and automatically stops charging when the battery is full.

Energous also has a far field transmitter, which can reportedly power up devices from as far as 15 feet away, but has yet to receive FCC approval.

The company is set to showcase this new technology at CES 2018, which will run from January 9 to 12 in Las Vegas. 3515036]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6NWID3WBIBR7VARLFJRZL4YNFKB7UT9AFJFMTICK5AFCBIKAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/34B/068/34B068827FC4A235CFC515698868AF4E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ long distance charging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wireless charging]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ midfield transmitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ energous]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wattup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wattup transmitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wattup midfield transmitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battery life]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/alien-looking-viper-sharks-found-in-taiwan-3514977</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Alien-looking viper sharks found in Taiwan 3514977]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAITUNG, TAIWAN — Scientists recently discovered a rare species of shark that resemble aliens off the coast of Taiwan.

Scientists from Taiwan's Fisheries Research Institute (FRI) caught five of the mysterious creatures off the coast of Taitung County's Donghe Township.

First identified off the coast of Japan in 1986, viper sharks, or Trigonognathus[b] kabeyai, have only been found off the coasts of Japan, Hawaii, and Taiwan. 

Its Latin name refers to the shark's triangular, forward-extending jaws, and glowing markings on the shark's body. It isn't known if the markings are meant for communication or for attracting prey. 3514977]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLRMCAIA2IRRWAYLECRT7LSMEEE5ET4K2PWTFKRAVBFEXCSAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/6FD/933/6FD933AEB3F8F64E2BE8C0B767A8E3A0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>39</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien looking shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rare viper sharks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viper sharks taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rare sharks taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mysterious sharks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alien sharks close encounters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taitung]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/disneyland-power-cut-leaves-customers-feeling-very-un-disney-3514893</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Disneyland power cut leaves customers feeling very un-Disney 3514893]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE HAPPIEST PLACE ON EARTH? — Several areas of Disneyland in Anaheim, California were hit by a power outage on Wednesday. 

According to the Huffington Post, the park's monorail stopped, as the It's a Small World ride. The outage cut power to all of Toontown and parts of Fantasyland, reported local media outlet ABC 7.

The power did eventually come back on, but many customers were left feeling irked by the experience. 3514893]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARCFGCKXKVCATWZTLFJAR7DUGRBEXEC6KNLR5HKWAMARACRMAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/0B4/25D/0B425D074AC128AB8389CDAC18E4F144.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ power outage in disneyland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ powercut at disneyland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ power outage at disneyland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disneyland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toontown]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fantasyland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ theme park power cut]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ power cuts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ power cut stories]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-suspected-of-developing-anthrax-bio-weapons-3514866</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Korea suspected of developing anthrax bio weapons 3514866]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — Reports from South Korea have raised fears that Kim Jong Un's government may be putting viruses on their ICBMs.

CNN reports that one of at least four soldiers who defected from North Korea was found with anthrax antibodies in his system, suggesting he was either vaccinated, or exposed to the virus at some point.

The North has also reportedly begun testing loading anthrax into intercontinental ballistic missiles, to determine whether the bacteria can withstand the high temperatures of atmospheric reentry.

Anthrax is caused by exposure to Bacillus anthracis spores. It causes flu-like symptoms, and can kill 80% of those exposed within 24 hours, unless antibiotics are administered.

South Korea's Centers for Disease Control and Prevention bought 1,000 doses of anthrax vaccine for agents or civilians. The Blue House — South Korea's executive office — has an additional 350, ordered by the previous government.

Fears of a biochemical attack come just weeks before the South is set to host the 2018 Winter Olympics. 3514866]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWJWIXZHAIBWXARTLWKAK7LUMVDSISCRAADWMFADBVAR3DRCKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A87/95B/A8795BFE3B12C3981232D25315E01FE3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anthrax]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biological weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bio weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biological warfare]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea missile]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north korea weapons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anthrax vaccine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anthrax threat]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-ruined-300-000-worth-of-art-after-great-date-with-lawyer-3515688</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman ruined $300,000 worth of art after great date with lawyer 3515688]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HOUSTON — A tipsy Dallas woman on a first date with a Houston trial lawyer went on a rampage and destroyed at least $300,000 worth of his art.

Lindy Lou Layman, 29, was arrested on Saturday on criminal mischief charges after her date with Anthony Buzbee ended with a sting, according the AP. 
Buzbee claims Layman got blasted on their date, so after he took her to his house, he called her an Uber.
Layman refused to leave and played a game of hide and seek. After being found, Buzbee called a 2second Uber.

That's when Layman apparently went bananas and tore down several paintings — including two Andy Warhol works together worth a million dollars — and poured red wine over some of them too. 
She also tossed around a couple of $20,000 sculptures and introduced them to the floor. 3515688]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIWADZCAMCACCKDKFIFT9LXMVCBXET4AWKAXHTSANKR3VT7BH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/A90/DCA/A90DCA5FB8F46AC185F377FCE083E5CE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-31T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first dates]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first date fails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman ruins art]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman ruins $300]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[000 art]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad first dates]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-carolina-family-saves-christmas-twice-in-one-night-3515602</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North Carolina family saves Christmas twice in one night 3515602]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CLEVELAND COUNTY, NORTH CAROLINA —  A family in North Carolina had an eventful holiday, saving Christmas twice, for two different families.

CNN reports that Crystal Travis and daughter Tori were driving home from visiting relatives when they came across a house fire and immediately jumped out to help.

The mother-daughter duo came to the aid of a couple and their small kids, right before a propane tank exploded on the porch.

Thankfully, no one was harmed, and the family even managed to save some Christmas presents from the inferno.

While this was going down, dad Roger was 20 miles away, and had just come across some folks trying to perform CPR on a baby. Luckily, he was able to use his skills as an EMT to revive the child.

It was the craziest day ever for the Travises, but while some may call it a coincidence, they prefer to think of it as a miracle. 3515602]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIWXCRCAMHRIBR9LWKFRLD3MVCS3RIKAVBR3U3TAMCRIWZJKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/397/E62/397E6298D00825CDF458C722DA73453F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2017-12-31T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas miracle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ saving lives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas eve rescue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas eve]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ house fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ christmas house fire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CPR]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mouth to mouth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EMT]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
