<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/where-is-kim-jong-un-trump-can-t-say--3992585</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Where is Kim Jong-un? Trump Can't Say? 3992585]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA — Quoting U.S. Secretary of State, Mike Pompeo, the BBC wrote that U.S. officials 'haven't seen' North Korea's leader since the 36-year-old last appeared in state media on April 12th; his absence has led to mass speculation that he was seriously ill, however, officials in South Korea later said such reports were untrue. 

In the many theories surrounding his absence from his adoring public, there have also been suggestions that he is waiting out the coronavirus at a sea resort.

When asked by Fox News to comment on the recent reports on Kim's health, Pompeo said on Wednesday, 'We haven't seen him. We don't have any information to report today, we're watching it closely.'

'There is a real risk that there will be a famine, a food shortage, inside of North Korea too.'

And on Monday, Trump claimed that he had a, 'very good idea' about Kim's condition, but added, 'I can't talk about it.'

Kim Jong-un failed to appear for the celebration of his grandfather's birthday on April 15th, an event that he has never missed.

However, none of the claims that have made headlines surrounding his disappearance can be substantiated.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3992585]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFJWVDIDAREAMVKCL6PFZ94TNEEEXSC5LSPWMHAALIHAAAILK2CWGVCRAV7W3BT5PS2UKACMARHA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/3DFA3ECDFD7C4A00FB9B87E3CDE64210.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1682969703&amp;Signature=Sqbouu5D9CO3%2BTO36aEZVBWATyFqnxX07qj8z0PIAcPwd9%2BG2UEVzASqnDhOerp6fYULP8senTBi7GiAA5ReBCeIp6rIpjBbiDmVGhS2GSGL0MZygdSOneuKV1oryqHmgyhb2JyoOyUfzYM2QG%2Fvhe8J1w10%2B7rztOXd57xD5Igw4FMGdwcSHYB1UF0HZ%2B9Em7Sxw1Ch0Ye9gaY55iB%2FYDhU%2FUuoP%2BouguUlpjms%2BS4QJF50jiiikYipcTpFBC%2BS1VeNUAjrHqvlngd5tCz5CLrlosAfsS8voxQD1t230HAgcHn1xF%2FIc0V88QCjeGlGqd0PaPS9zWEXe1O88x%2B01Q%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-04-30T08:44:54+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>130</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/migrating-sea-turtles-find-empty-beaches-a-rare-chance-to-thrive-3992494</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Migrating sea turtles find empty beaches, a rare chance to thrive 3992494]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MIAMI — Thousands of sea turtles are currently migrating to nesting grounds on beaches across the southeastern United States, just in time to enjoy a rare break from human interference as coronavirus lockdowns keep people indoors.

Experts interviewed by CBS News expect sea turtles to thrive amid the lack of human activity and pollution as beaches are deserted thanks to stay-at-home orders. 3992494]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDFKDTXKEDRKDAWL6LAIK4VGIDE5RZNKACFPFIDBZHAPAT3AJAAPWZBKV7FAB35PW6XAATMAMEB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/C3CD3CEB55E69EAB655646CADF0B51F8.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1682969703&amp;Signature=bPSOIoeXwpDCmKU6C62fSQNFl6jzkAwsfkmsL4C0vnxyJqxQEHyv4jlP38dlYYx%2F%2FTOnmVBhcWEJFOoo4eW6vrJf386T2EmpOCp%2BRZiJ3tOSDrEMYRLiDZn2kW8byxFPR1dExtQP6yMBAPPxD%2BLQoac1jt7B4sqGyyidPGSKAAGv0NLbxlS4HSjuZxDoWgMHXzvRlR8uJl62wLEYt0Te3Z9y3m%2BvhKzE3GFHdbo%2B%2FztHu84jkxwD3q%2B30oHDXj5sY9xw8F407TNVmm1E1uaNEFIfk0K6AOea2yxXriAGf1jPIkgWBb8w4Ys65iEXovCDSoJdv8H%2FMOzx%2Fr%2BggIWgKA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-04-30T04:33:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>93</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[sea turtles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ good news about the environment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ positive news about the environment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea turtle migration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pollution in the ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic in the ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turtles eat plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ghost nets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ghost gear]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-ocean-is-changing-more-now-than-in-the-past-10-000-years-3992452</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The Ocean Is Changing More Now Than in the Past 10,000 Years 3992452]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — According to research published in the journal Geophysical Research Letters, scientists have discovered significant changes in the Atlantic Ocean's ecosystem that might have been caused by shifts in ocean circulation.

To examine changes in the ecosystem, researchers used a plastic tube to take samples from sediments in the ocean floor. Scientists then studied the fossil plankton available in newer and older sediments.

Results show that changes in the ocean's water circulation have caused a decline in cold water plankton and a rise in warm water species in southern Iceland as the flow of warm water has overtaken cold waters.

Scientists who participated in the study believe that these shifts have caused some fish species, such as mackerel, to travel northward.

Results also showed that warm water is now reaching the Arctic. Scientists note that this could be aggravating the melting of sea ice there. The shift in the direction of the warm water currents could also affect key fisheries in the U.S. and Canada. 3992452]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLAGDCUAFIRPWRVBRAARKDXMFLSVSK5LRDWZHIHBAEAXBAAAWCFEV3VKI6WTYAPQS4UKVZ9KNPB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/3A1BA6F7BB39DD1D238F5EDC346118E4.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1682969703&amp;Signature=h9%2BxGhSnIdL55O75fMdK5bj0mxc6AvS4Cf6fRagL5Mqvzsqp8RT6wcI%2BQyB4I7qmO0A9%2BWx48LgcwSD5%2BcwmYLpkJNh0bvaVXP%2FeQu5n%2FXqhb3orOSCtQcvqPvj7WGPhrDw3s8T9am5knw5TpHVX1WQuL2SwsRstEFnhV8N7HbZI5w8r9A%2BgE7CS5QjAQKkzw1JOZsbFuKms5Wyx5ArcaKjUj%2Btf5mDyM0JBM8NRc86n4iOiUE3TUB7HzVSLvDYI84yHxpxzJZmnF%2FYE2MMGrYinbE9rCPrRmz1zU6TNSSEHB5LaKZBhfxmOs%2BiMIXPwVOCBSxmd6duDX9WmAOkanQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-04-30T01:11:20+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>119</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plankton]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oceanography]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paleoclimate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine ecology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fossils]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seabed fossils]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atlantic ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean circulation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/locust-plague-threatening-food-security-in-east-africa-3992817</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Locust plague threatening food security in East Africa 3992817]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EAST AFRICA — East African countries could be facing a food crisis as waves of locusts have hit crops in the region since the end of 2019, according to a report by the Globe and Mail. A third wave of the insects is expected to hatch and spread in June and July.

Just one locust can travel 150 kilometers in 24 hours and is capable of eating its own weight in crops each day.

A small swarm of locusts, which would be around 40 to 80 million, can cover about a square kilometer and eat the same amount of food consumed by 35,000 humans in a day.

On top of crops being impacted by the waves of locust plagues, Stephanie Hanson, senior vice-president of One Acre Fund, told the Center for Strategic and International Studies that farmers' incomes have also been affected due to restrictions put in place during the pandemic, which limit their capacity to sell food in local markets.

The pandemic has also made it difficult for farmers to get rid of the locusts. Hanson noted that pilots in Kenya who fly pesticide aircraft are required to land at local airports before the national curfew is lifted. 3992817]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJWXYZAAZEWEVTABBPFRLSGMFJSKRIQAJLAZFAGBAFAVACTB2CWMB3YKFVAXWRIQMUXPWA5KWNA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/0D85F0C15CC943F25D265D3A74F4AD8F.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683056102&amp;Signature=GEf8d%2FwiLmmyYw%2BB5%2FXRUTt6BV%2BZXNYpLWmI8hGr4Om0aixBGQIti3uXfUGEFOZ%2BazTeFGDsG3eOO6S7fU77T7VvRQecCPNcIPOCMhFaQ2LWkQ2FARYeKz1lYH86GnvPAlCP4j20U9x32fdzo6FhGNuS4s0%2FEliod2fCR49puH%2Ff0cQIyYKhsZ6QTDJEXPHlwz%2FY9L%2Bn9y79oH5dyP25Hp8%2B9dyhHRfomU4NX9XSujeFYT9DwiTN49I3reZ1pWIcjch8%2BOCFZtfu9ZB%2BfXGgP9qNctkLWOrU9fyrVQOfqsAXp52gnrG5RCg9ipSgxAOoupPRYC5NrQhdQK8V1OzRSg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-02T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>120</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ east africa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ environment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ africa coronavirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ food and agriculture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ east africa locusts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ east africa locust plague]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ locust plague]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ food shortage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus curfew]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/north-and-south-korean-troops-exchange-gunfire-in-the-dmz-3993801</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[North and South Korean troops exchange gunfire in the DMZ 3993801]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL — North and South Korean troops exchanged small arms fire in the demilitarized zone on May 3. 

Citing a statement from the South Korean joint chiefs of staff, the Korea Herald reports North Korea fired first but inflicted no casualties on South Korean forces.

According to the Yonhap News Agency, North Korean troops fired multiple shots at a South Korean outpost early in the morning, while the garrison returned two shots.

The South Korean military states North Korea apparently fired unintentionally.

The state-funded news agency cites the military as saying the morning's fog would have obscured firing targets. 

Additionally, the ground occupied by North Korean troops offered no tactical advantage over the outpost.

The 155-mile or 250-km-long DMZ is heavily defended by mines, fences and guard posts, and rates as the world's most militarized border. 3993801]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEDAMDZDKFKAKAA9LJKAXKBHGRBEZR37AECAXURFBZGAAXRIKIQAGWRGK2WW5WIKF62XICAWB5GA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/EC07516A726EA4390E8F9BCC84EA3726.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683315303&amp;Signature=V0E7oVyDfFSNgNl0bYjOCii71vKQtyxIgOM3WXX02CIwHoHSNHyvC5nI7946jvasBHHeDj7m1IhxHIhJ78ysM3N09tQcZULftfGNIU5zo3i3ks9EJjiJG9WdpzpXLvoLJfP%2FN6H46rmMT2S93KG5q61%2Bxe6Fe1XsDB82HWh4H1sFj0Uyf4WsK322dgR%2FYyk%2FayfMrZ2uu7r0HhnNcmuQgn%2BBMR2BwO%2FaBptb1GtNjDMJOKWPg5iGblEJMIplIALXUE%2BGPyECT3BkRqVgWIyfyg9oMokXBe5bJeeK0m6ewPoFS9wSRgOfVsHScuRen6xxrjGHeQOjBQPM8knyYlhdxg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-05T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>97</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[North Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ South Korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exchanged gunfire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DMZ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 38th parallel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ border skirmish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ international relations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ defense]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-world-s-largest-iceberg-is-drifting-away-from-antarctica-3993781</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The world's largest iceberg is drifting away from Antarctica 3993781]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOUTH ORKNEY ISLANDS — It looks like the beginning of the end for the world's largest iceberg, the BBC reports. 

New satellite images show Iceberg A-68 lost a 175 square km chunk of ice, which will likely be called Iceberg A-68c, between satellite passes on April 21 and April 22, according to images from the Copernicus Sentinel-1 mission.

Iceberg A-68 broke off from the Larsen Ice Shelf in July of 2017 and remained largely intact for three years as it drifted past the Antarctic Peninsula in the Weddell Sea. Today it is around 5,000 square km, almost four times the size of Greater London. 

Currents in the Southern Ocean are now pushing the iceberg past the South Orkney Islands into increasingly warmer waters. 3993781]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5BWCDRFKRBRIDZXBNPAXLSGMIDBTRK6LRCFVGIKB6NFEWK7K5QFKBTXKSVAXVKZQ23XMAZ2A6PB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/C252E07D6E3D6B34BE0A07F1B8BF0E13.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683315303&amp;Signature=S9FmM1MrhQI%2Fryq8uJG9IFIdOHM1P3urJhou%2F72%2BwNOLO6A64%2B3zwLPXJ3S4rvWW4CH6HSYMzHSYkuPppuDT1k9erZstTUjKK54bQuVdM5chu7HR%2BjYyU38kaHVU6mPL5EggRFdCCs6A6g6dXLayvSYQRnJGBUH%2FcKuqEVQ%2BThIBuPVFn4V1lp5B%2FDf23vunGtyxRMB7DZk2H2H%2FHk6W6jLLkKSmzSE2kqKUT3lgYl2YsRJbSoNXm73m0%2Fp20fJR%2FuO7rWEtm2dSXXkl6%2Bp7W11jiH3N7svrOaKEX4eU5A3%2BKHUAYkhodcYAzx9R0UNvK26z8%2BqnmY46hcffAvPikA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-05T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>96</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Iceberg A-68]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Iceberg A68]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Iceberg A-68a]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Iceberg A-68c]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ A68 iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ A68]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iceberg collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ icebergs breaking off]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iceberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice berg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sumter-woman-arrested-for-licking-hands-and-touching-items-3993736</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sumter Woman Arrested for Licking Hands and Touching Items 3993736]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[Sumter, North Carolina — A woman has been arrested after video footage emerged of her licking her hands and touching items in a restaurant and grocery store. 

On Saturday, Sumter Police were called to an IGA grocery store on a report of a suspicious person. Police found the woman, 38-year-old Shenir Gibson Holliday in the parking lot and determined she matched the description of the woman wanted by Sumter County deputies.

According to WIS News, when they looked at the surveillance video inside the store, officers said it showed her licking her hands and coughing before pulling on freezer doors and touching food items; the video also showed her doing the same thing in the dry food section. 

The arrest comes after the Sheriff's Office put out a red alert looking for a woman that matched Holliday's description who licked her hands before touching things at a Sub Station II. 

In that incident, a woman wearing sunglasses and a low-zipped Champion jumpsuit entered the restaurant and ordered food and a drink, but not before licking her fingers with her tongue. 

According to the deputies' report, the woman licked her fingers as she was getting the money to give to the cashier.

Deputies said as her sub was being made, the woman licked her palm and rubbed her hand over the store's debit machine; she was also seen licking quarters and putting them in the tip jar before she left the store without her food.

As the woman left the store, she confessed, 'It's in God's hands now.

Police charged Holliday with aggravated breach of peace and food tampering and gave her a citation for a violation of the state's 'home or work' order.

The Sheriff's Office also charged her with aggravated breach of peace and food tampering for the Sub Station II incident.

On Sunday, her bond was set at $100,000 and she was ordered to undergo testing for COVID-19.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3993736]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABNWVXTTBREFABI7LMCW5KDRGMCE7ST2KFJRZGIGBWMFMWIEKRKRKWT5KNWRZW34PS4DIVZWB6MB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/04123CBDA854D1B4C9D30D38FA923545.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683315303&amp;Signature=grP8u4nY6TAgjirZ3%2B7Kf8hB4KyyHWYDa6gqB90Ze0j%2BTmkiWdpx5hf3aYvRbZRRzVVCoprWv6neJzIF58d7z8z%2BaLBivD2TE2Re0DO7XXaHZUdzVAVDkOxzPh2BBTEh9h4aiaOzn9%2FErpvd%2F7DTfUUGgSF1CgmScGLIgVgjkRRBXINZDDt7%2FFvp1ALXJ87vELrr1L%2Bn10qTN0x%2BZw2aP1%2BQmVQDGDek3K5L8XpkAUhhUYcSa4HY0svhU901j0IJks%2FjeiGPloMvBKOfhMHqzx%2BhGGeFrFzwTccwagssC%2BJ3TxDw%2BirD2p95zvt0jFrB4rYpBSIpmNodiH%2FJ84WcTg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-05T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>129</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/madonna-claims-she-is-immune-to-the-coronavirus-3993667</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Madonna Claims she is Immune to the Coronavirus 3993667]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LISBON, PORTUGAL — The 61-year-old 'Like a Virgin' singer says she wants to breathe in 'COVID-19 air' because she has the antibodies to protect her from contracting the disease.

The singer said on Thursday in an Instagram video, 'I took a test the other day and I found out that I have the antibodies, so tomorrow, I'm just going to go on a long drive in a car, roll down the windows and I'm going to breathe in the Covid-19 air.'

She added, 'I hope the sun is shining. I have not been wanting to write lately but that does not mean I'm not thinking, thinking about what I want to write or want to say.'

The 80's icon known for decades of tabloid attention-seeking, appears to be claiming that following a test, it has proven that her immune system has already seen the coronavirus without symptoms. 

In a previous navel-gazing video that is part of what she's dubbing her 'Quarantine Diaries', the pop star branded the coronavirus 'the great equalizer' whilst perching nude in a milky bathtub filled with rose petals. 

She said that the pandemic doesn't care if you are rich or poor.

She said, 'That's the thing about COVID-19. It doesn't care about how rich you are, how famous you are, how funny you are, how smart you are, where you live, how old you are, what amazing stories you can tell.'

Madonna then attended a birthday party on Saturday, and in a video clip, at least eight people are seen gathered in close proximity despite social distancing rules.

The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention or 'CDC' says it is still unclear whether antibodies will make you immune to the virus or prevent you from getting infected again.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3993667]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSLWIAIGAADAXBZUBJIWX7L4MEBERURIK2IWMUAALAFWCA3UKWAFAYAAAWVF3VC9FS2XAVZWKFMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/B6DB6949F9C742F04E73A8E138A92597.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683315303&amp;Signature=K7%2BtUXkIQVF1M%2BdU9a%2Bkz7dCVW53%2F3jVLKtbmhzOpQxIQ4xR4cS3ROJkMCo7Ibz10YqsCgw9yrtnLeKMjol80chWksXj%2FsF%2B6LI%2B30DtAnzgyEHekFTkOv3WAC5FRGMetw1ILIxpRnTnKTXYj0dnustXvaOnsWsm1Bv9XoLh9XEkJ6eI8dsy9uWwjiyI4JD76cqQCmn1KjORWEP3in%2Fe42KS%2BR4BuTVKL%2FqSVd%2B%2FG%2B5VuP10cM5VFld9r5gIA%2FiOjv0bvpodis376iLLX%2BOstUiiw3k8nKsDDX8nmY3JjS24dVEYMyY74p8cyE2JSZv%2FECpLU2ffFHFF0hgua9RSTQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-05T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>123</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-aquarium-wants-you-to-video-chat-eels-3994098</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese Aquarium Wants You to Video Chat Eels 3994098]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — A Japanese aquarium is asking you to video call its eels for fear of them forgetting who we are. 

Sumida Aquarium in Tokyo says that social isolation is even affecting its eels. The claim comes after caretakers spotted garden eels burrowing down into the sand as they passed the tank. 

The aquarium believes the new avoidance behavior is because the eels have become unfamiliar with humans since the aquarium closed on March 1st due to the coronavirus. 

While such behavior is natural to the species when frightened, the aquarium is concerned that the burrowing will affect scientists' ability to study them. 

In a press release, they said, 'The disappearance of the Chinese eels made it difficult for the breeding staff to check whether they are doing well, whether they are healthy, are they thin, and are they ill.'

To help the eels feel more at home, the aquarium has launched an 'emergency' three-day event calling on people around the world to video call the eels to get them acclimatized to us again. 

The face-time event began on the 3rd and ends on the 5th. 

This is the first time they have used technology to remind animals that humans exist, therefore they are not sure if it will be a success.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3994098]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNKACXRBB2IWEWCELIAFZ9SGMVBBKUZQK2LWRTZCLBMAEWAMBIIRIWT5KBURXVRJQF4GIV3QB2QA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/E304D069D7EA055211F14B6FCEFF1781.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683401701&amp;Signature=L0Uhs87Hnmh%2Ba7ZJrVy2JVvyBIzGuoGe3dwqs8fpFYE4SBs1%2BdYYEPDoZZpy3adTvWTTKgMeRrAX6EDrKTUcfbFkhnWypRpVMp8ZuF17%2BfUtoF5TxqPWHkEUELzHfjy2p8bb%2FfWcVapRWZ92rPpKJALOHIP0G0FsZH8s5MmkxxFAzGcWTuhufu%2BYM5T1KqgPdPe%2BXLVQ4tUnPYnvKKmTxiQgu%2B9pZ3LQ886ie%2BunI9BQG7tjaZmy5L%2BiEuERT0KIzdExgFZ0dMg5l%2BS5dCWGjZEL3ZTlvazck4XVMD58Y3IuO0UJqDQ0zj%2F%2FY%2FC9W6Cr8u3g0ICjCkrNNr15GrOOWg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>81</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/microplastics-disrupt-hermit-crabs-ability-to-choose-shells-3994009</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Microplastics Disrupt Hermit Crabs' Ability to Choose Shells 3994009]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BELFAST, NORTHERN IRELAND — A study published in the journal Biology Letters has found that exposure to microplastics can disrupt a hermit crab's ability to choose a shell. 

Researchers from Queen's University Belfast and Liverpool John Moores University placed 29 female hermit crabs into a tank containing microplastics. A control group of 35 crabs was placed into a tank with no microplastics. 

After five days the crabs were moved into lower-quality shells and presented with the option to choose a higher-quality shell. Only nine of the crabs that had been exposed to microplastics moved into the new shells, compared to 21 from the control group.

This suggests exposure to microplastics impairs the crabs' cognition, and that microplastics in general can have important effects on an animal's behavior.

Gareth Arnott, co-author of the new research from Queen's University Belfast, told the Guardian he was surprised by the results. We hypothesize that either some aspect of the polyethylene is getting into them to affect their decision making, or else it is an indirect effect that the presence of the plastic in the tank might be influencing their feeding behavior, for example, he said. 3994009]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEBWKCRDLECREB3ELSIRXKDYGIDBVURMKWLFZURLLMEFMARIBALW5BZHK2XRXVRQQ6ZDEVCQBZEA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/6FA4A14A234B1BA8158BF7D9396A1F91.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683401701&amp;Signature=NMlfVwBEOGBGMFpoBkZ2sa028RFJuk%2FQpj5JWMCi4CM9ws9hSq8CIa8wvvYiUs1QUt7Wfkqv8G4isuZyyVY4q07fYVGlHvLRtGF26QBnfCA99%2FhFeYGLrXR7cLfQbUDHEn0UXzChgTAO01tfhx7ZmwTO0JuoHGGy1Ng3YcjkTJNKwactLCGTwemgyOVzYmnxUIPB4y9YQznq3xMdxKdOSGNJPXHOUJ75nU0JzBmlwasLE1rUiXn1WwRUyD17WcDFrW77IO23E3PrPoRbX62kge7VoP2l8Rzh2CSs7Fk%2FasPbZFiFwvhsH7AHgMicIVPpMdHWewRRcFJ3v8qO8%2Bu6dw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>103</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[microplastics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hermit crabs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic in the ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic in the ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastic particles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic affecting marine life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic affecting our environment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic cognition]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic animal behavior]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ environment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-pandemic-could-last-up-to-two-years-study-3993987</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Coronavirus pandemic could last up to two years: study 3993987]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS — A report by the University of Minnesota's Center for Infectious Disease Research and Policy published last Thursday predicts that the coronavirus pandemic could last from 18 to 24 months.

Experts who participated in the study believe the pandemic will not stop until around 60 to 70 percent of the population becomes immune to the virus.

The coronavirus's longer incubation period and high R0, or reproduction number, make it a highly contagious virus. According to a study published in Emerging Infectious Diseases, COVID-19's R0 is a median of 5.7, meaning an infected individual can spread the virus to five to six people.

The study suggests all authorities should prepare for the worst-case scenario or scenario 2, which according to their study is one where the first wave of the spread is followed by a larger wave in the fall or winter of this year.

The researchers posed two other scenarios. Scenario 1 sees small waves of the virus similar in impact occur for about one to two years. In this scenario, the virus slowly stops spreading sometime in 2021.

The third scenario described in the study suggests the first wave we experienced this spring becomes a slow burn — depending on the mitigation strategies imposed in different places.

What about after it is all done? The study says that SARS-CoV-2 will potentially continue to hang around us humans, popping in and out seasonally with a diminished severity over time, just like other viruses do. Let's hope that day comes sooner rather than later. 3993987]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NFXDAFAAFRIVZRLNJAR74XNACVXRT2KWKW5URKBVEWMY32AJDW5BTXKJWWXV35FMSDIVCLAIAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/DA7CF6FF5F1591CA26BA42F7A64B31AD.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683401701&amp;Signature=qf1ir%2F2jNL65%2Fc1qs5437o4AcGhVQu%2BsriY5mtJvDAk1bCUKz513TKKFBo5k50b9bGdQTDRwMqWKu9NSeUkq3UuauINI6EN9S9eDwUACC4RdnkMyHhhE8NkVC1x4dE7shWrHTN%2FhllYUSaeojQxgwEiJuoxNwERJOB6UHo8RBVOlEJOYkByc90Tb7zhK1l14TXOZ%2B8D8FAi0dSIiPevQQh2b1wEDc%2BbtBF2GodhyjvcB0vB4%2FUL5jv3Yo8ecVU%2FCqZSDi9woqmZi0oQ%2BozblFApnqUjDwDeo2jcjqtYLhGywmtYk5vYKfTMt4EQmLR42VgSg4H8uTiTI7%2Fgo0LNC%2BQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-06T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>99</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[coronavirus animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ covid-19 animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SARS-CoV-2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus spread]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus pandemic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ COVID-19]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ COVID-19 virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ COVID-19 pandemic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ novel coronavirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-why-is-the-coronavirus-so-deadly--3994742</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Explainer: Why is the coronavirus so deadly? 3994742]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIPEI — COVID-19 is an airborne disease that spreads in tiny droplets that contain the new coronavirus, known as SARS-CoV-2. When people inhale contaminated droplets, the virus enters into the nose and the throat.

COVID-19 infection usually begins in the nose and throat, because the mucous membranes of these sites contain epithelial cells that are rich in ACE2 cell surface receptors. The virus needs to exploit ACE2 to get into human cells.

The coronavirus's outer coating is covered in spike proteins that give the virus its crown-like appearance. The spike protein possesses receptor binding domains, or RBDs, that the virus uses to pry open receptors before penetrating the cellular membrane.
The ACE2 receptor normally regulates blood pressure. But the coronavirus's downward RBD can bind with this receptor and allow the virus to enter, and then hijack, the host cell.

Once the virus enters the human cell, its coating dissolves and frees viral RNA to hijack the host cell's apparatuses. The cell's endoplasmic reticulum produces viral RNA and proteins, while its Golgi body packages them into whole new viruses.

As the virus multiplies, the infected person may develop early symptoms, such as a sore throat and dry cough, while spreading plentiful amounts of the virus to others.

Other symptoms for the first week of infection include fever; a loss of smell and taste; and muscle aches.

The lungs contain air sacs called alveoli that keep us alive by exchanging carbon dioxide for oxygen.

If the virus moves down the lungs, it attacks the alveoli, which are lined with vulnerable, ACE2 receptor-rich cells.

To fight off infections, white blood cells release cytokines to summon more immune cells. Pneumonic COVID-19 may trigger cytokine storm syndrome, a phenomenon where the body scrambles too many immune cells.

As the virus attacks the lungs, the cytokine storm floods the lungs with white blood cells that destroy both healthy and infected cells.

This fills the air sacs with liquids, mucous and the detritus of dead cells.

Pneumonic COVID-19 disrupts the exchange of oxygen and damages the lungs extensively, which leads to dangerously low oxygen levels that may become fatal.

When the virus gets into the heart, it strikes blood vessel cells that are rich in ACE2 receptors. Clinical studies suggest the viral onslaught causes blood clots that obstruct the artilleries and trigger heart attacks.

Intestinal cells that are responsible for absorbing nutrition called enterocytes also express the RNA for ACE2 and a related enzyme that the virus also exploits, which makes the intestines vulnerable.

A clinical study from the Chinese city of Wuhan found more than a third of COVID-19 patients suffered neurological complications.

According to the neurological study, as many as 35 percent of patients had neurological complications including impaired cognition, stroke and muscle damage. Blood clots that travelled to the brain could be the cause of the strokes. 3994742]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEDWMX3UK5CFEBI7BADRV9LWM5EB7RALA2KA5TIHL5EWCARMAZLAKAZHKFUF5AREF22GMVTQAZHA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/D1E9AAE9C1E73239B3ABFEEF48536009.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683488102&amp;Signature=RdOsUUU1GNSoZsxm2EbfnatOHiwnv8XS4YqgIGkZa6iqEfGAFAU8vRIXLhR2n2%2FdJohIlHXvosl09G7T%2Bw8fWpj%2BQb0DB0J83AUNhVt3JvTBZ9mxx61NoX60cRl%2FTnv7LtmlFle31Q9%2FLTjN%2BW%2FsxTHSSJI9TOVFHwE3CaBBmomYYs46BFfH2rvQY2PM1VtETm6SfsHQo1lii%2B9MidMlxIojVYcJzfEErMcI85WyXdLUH%2F7EJ6277LodJBo5jphyIHBg48WlwbqsDzFimMihDYCAMBSx%2FERTQP2mj93%2B34iccgs4KYiy%2B%2FEpNJOHtBPAsa9HxS5Tymns3avU1QG6yw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-07T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>209</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[COVID-19]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SARS-CoV-2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pneumonia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cytokine storm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cytokine storm syndrome]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ immune system overreaction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heart failure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neurological complications]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ explainer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/newly-discovered-microbe-can-help-stop-malaria-transmission-3994629</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Newly discovered microbe can help stop malaria transmission 3994629]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NAIROBI, KENYA — Researchers in Kenya discovered a microbe that can completely prevent mosquitoes from carrying malaria.

According to the study published in Nature Communications, the microbe could be used to check the spread of malaria around the world.

The research teams from the UK and Kenya found that the malaria-stopping fungal microbe called Microsporidia MB was present in 5 percent of the mosquitoes they sampled.

The fungus grows in the genitalia and digestive system of mosquitoes, and the data suggests it is 100 percent effective in stopping malaria from infecting mosquitoes.

Speaking to the BBC, the authors say they do not as yet know how the fungus stops malaria.

The paper's lead author Jeremy Heren says at least 40 percent of mosquitoes in a region need to be infected with the fungus to curb malaria transmission. 3994629]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5BWPC3WKMCREBIUBSKW7K4UGNJEZRT7KJLF7GZLL5AAKB3SLRJAKBAGKBUFVVILFF6XGAR9ARFB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/BDBBAE6D4B1AE926007A428E0871401E.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683488102&amp;Signature=JaolLkybRjiEg0Gcze7ti1yfQfgf4kKw0GqZZy%2Bll%2BgOxmTB4cxF4RJhEHCo%2FetM1a%2BH%2F40s9UUYaXrDA7uxYoytWMcYh1zTBplqA2lu95QwyTHElNTBgqf%2F6si5yyo6ZRezcS%2B1WEYdJ5Iwjre8uXEwhNZoipcQ1IOObmiGxgj6gRNMql8XgnAABrjBy8zNCeSGWIvnwc8YcCyXXgvdDkYdGClH07wF%2BmHip4ysxumq7j8lwYCbtbsuMIooti%2FvvyF%2B4%2Fc49vJmz16XjG3vOxlLaujdqxQxTp49QjgfdupiZ4%2Bhn9bC2D0fbLWLkelWDNDA9%2FkhRNsmTtQiS3tKTg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-07T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Microsporidia MB]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fungus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microbe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fungal microbe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fungal parasite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquitoes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquito]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malaria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malaria-blocking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kenya]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Africa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/monkey-on-scooter-tries-to-kidnap-kid-in-viral-video-3994599</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Monkey on Scooter Tries to Kidnap Kid in Viral Video 3994599]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SURABAYA, INDONESIA — A monkey riding a tiny motor scooter has been filmed trying to kidnap a toddler. 

According to local outlet, Indonesia Expat, the incident occurred on Saturday in the East Java city of Surabaya and involved a traditional form of street entertainment known as 'masked monkey.'

In the video, the primate rides his tiny bike down a narrow residential street to the tune of gamelan percussion music before slamming on the brakes by a wooden bench where a woman is sitting with a baby and two young children.

The monkey hops off and makes an attempt for the kid, dragging the infant several meters. 

When the monkey brings the abduction to an end, the girl gets up and makes a run for it, fortunately, she only suffered abrasions to her forehead. 

Indonesian's netizens have condemned the handler of the monkey, arguing that it's wrong to enslave it for human entertainment. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3994599]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2KFGXREARAWGVZTLEDR77BCMNIEXFC2LWJW5HZLBSPWEBT3BMIAGV3VAZ7R7ARNQS2XTATLA2NA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/E0D781F7F5101022008023C2EBCA7430.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683488102&amp;Signature=Ry3nXMA3HrbTCK8UocKRdwzd%2F2Qh%2Fkywz13S44h7kjYykxEEAxItWJQUv0rulNL4o7BkLTyAV6W2zL7Zj8gaGat%2FtA35Ufp93V9KhqEimbNL87QAiNvI2BOXEywpA6Oybfjbzzc8YxMjQaY1yj13GwUdF21BHn2PA4cvee2xil0cjXfJ1O2WV3vtmC%2BYzSphMWP15fBhVnSYSXtxjIBgpLeqzuk38%2FeeESVTsFrImFtlqGRxOhGff81R2FhNyjCnBcChYM3gf4e6hZdhFC4yMLJw%2FYv0kkY8w%2BJhWD5%2Fl9ZH2cF4uphs1ndOFOQQZjQZcdF38aZs8gR56i9KzmA2yg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-07T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-kim-jong-un-photos-spark-body-double-theory-3994591</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New Kim Jong-un Photos Spark Body Double Theory 3994591]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA — Kim Jong-un reappeared in dramatic fashion last weekend when he was shown on North Korean media cutting the ribbon on a fertilizer factory, hushing those who said he was ill or even dead. 

However, the photos released by state media from the ribbon-cutting function have given way for a new theory that it's a body double. 

Web sleuths have noted discrepancies in facial, hairline, and dental features when compared with previous appearances.

The International Business Times says that it is a 'well-known fact Kim uses body doubles.'

British tabloid, The Sun even shared a video back in 2017 seemingly showing Kim nattering to two body doubles.

According to IBT, human rights activist Jennifer Zeng was the first to draw attention to the dissimilarities between the two so-called 'versions' of Kim, noting differences in their teeth and ears.

She took to Twitter, questioning, 'Is the Kim Jong-un on May 1st the real one?' Along with a side-by-side comparison of Kim's 'old and new' appearance. 

Former British Member of Parliament Louise Mensch said, 'Don't know, don't care. See no reason to alter my earlier stance. These aren't the same man.' 

Writer and podcaster Akilah Hughes noted that a body double wouldn't be so far-fetched, saying, 'we really believing that's Kim Jong Un when it could absolutely be a dude w plastic surgery?? If I was a murderous dictator I'd have clones.' 


TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3994591]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NACDZEBJJRMWZYBMDFTL43NFJEXE35KVDA5FCTBMARMDAQA5QFPYCUKSVAVVIQFZUGMWZ7KJMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/4F10956CC64359EB4B3375AD332109DE.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683488102&amp;Signature=Jr1rRbVAjN1SO9%2BS8yKqfGuozuDBmK20Q%2FUT58o7wNUhZrlHC8FCS0oyFkxxp1Q%2FUK7rS0hCr%2BynwXEJY5G3hvCMaqhPrZ%2BQ8MEAAd7E5KCjt4DjgSQYfuod2v8Uq5cQuXfha9%2F0so1EXlmAoe3XyDDTpK4UJgzMvFmh9yAFbRaebwmjLaMYxJCtu4rxEBuKvbWXkZVTCqnqaNLkcLBzeRljuc%2BSWHCuHP3sSBM7Vv2rVmf%2FRsk1hgDlRWW1ftYngh7QNdRhEzYJT2RBi%2FjbMYw8%2Fhf2SsB6tHAQuXaur5sZ9KPQP2DdAHkRJHpuvkL%2BBHS92NZx3HzXGoGMhzwrWw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-07T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>130</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/invasive-giant-murder-hornets-just-came-to-the-u-s--3994566</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Invasive Giant Murder Hornets Just Came to the U.S. 3994566]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BLAINE, WASHINGTON — Last December, the Washington State Department of Agriculture confirmed two reports of Asian giant hornets in Blaine, Washington. Two more unconfirmed sightings were reported in Custer, Washington. These killer hornets are now coming out of winter hibernation.

Asian giant hornets can measure between 1.5 to 2 inches, or 3.8 to 25 centimeters,  in length. They have stingers that deliver venom to their victims and mandibles capable of decapitating bees.

According to the WSU Insider, the Asian giant hornet queen wakes from hibernation in April, finds nourishment and then looks for a place to establish a colony that will later go out to bring back food.

The bee population in the United States is most threatened by these hornets from late summer to early fall. While they hunt for food for their next queens, the hornets will decapitate honey bees and eat the bee's larvae and pupae.

Well, you might be thinking, isn't this just nature? The circle of life, so to speak? Nope, not really. First off, we don't know how these hornets made it to the U.S., but they have never been found in the country before, so this new species is an invader and definitely a threat to beekeepers.

Still not feeling like this pertains to you? A threat to bees means a threat to human food production. We need bees in order for many key crops to be pollinated.

According to the United States Department of Agriculture, more than a third of all American crop production requires insects to help pollinate, and the primary pollinator is, you guessed it, honey bee colonies.

So, what can you do? Well, if you live in the States, keep an eye out for these murderous buggers and call local authorities if you are unlucky enough to spot one.

But in your quest to take down the murder hornet invasion, please be aware of their painful, toxin-ridden sting. Oh, and If you're allergic to bees, then definitely stay away because their sting could easily cause a severe anaphylactic shock and even, well, death. 3994566]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLWADRBA5BAPW3EBBJAZ7SAGSIEZRK6KVAF3GIEBVFFABCRBZQREVREABVFTAT7PSZDGBKQAEHA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/9A7C2160D8308096C50B249D4C704970.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683488102&amp;Signature=MCqgltSp10jSKOo1Gkju6VQub%2FRTHC4LegFKZhRHxSUA8qEnjA%2FzJCPWJqI5CUogQWATJFiDIEKdz97QkcgsTHmg7sHhhY1%2FxASyawN56VRtRuDrqabH6PsK41utgL1fdQthImHuliP1esU3sVCes7Id62%2BztbBPRUQWdWu7%2FS5g26I7ey3F2QnYkKpjSRbqteVmVaW%2FY8afp9DNG0xUZ3XX2H2aNrdJ2oSR8Qhh3ihISwgSaYpwgBZNZ5TGExJCCYhHkD%2BCknAXKX%2BYvmmXpcoR%2BjKQ0E7lVViwQAGfBV6icWmEcTkNPzVB5j1aR2IEVFPCmF6z9XfbumC3Zw4JBw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-07T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>163</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[giant asian hornet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant hornet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ murder hornet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ murder hornets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asian hornet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/rivers-may-have-existed-on-mars-for-more-than-100-000-years-3995125</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Rivers may have existed on Mars for more than 100,000 years 3995125]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UTRECHT, THE NETHERLANDS — Scientists believe water may have run in rivers on ancient Mars 3.7 billion years ago, according to a paper published in Nature Communications.

Researchers speculate that the system these rivers formed existed for more than 100,000 years in Mars's geological history.
 
Using data gathered by NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter, scientists surveyed the Hellas Basin and discovered signs on a 200-meter-tall cliff that suggests the region used to support a river system.

Writing in a news release, the team says the extremely high-resolution image from the orbiter's camera allowed them to read the cliff face and see sedimentary rocks that one would find on riverbanks.

According to the researchers, these ancient rivers probably changed their gullies and left behind sandbanks like certain rivers on Earth, such as the Rhine in Germany and rivers in Northern Italy. 3995125]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLFGYABBRAFCVZYLWKW592AGJJEZSK7KZBWRGRDLAGWIBTSKFAFAYCRLWVW7W35FZRGKWI3KVGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/91005DECDF2288885AC0B69C6BD12E03.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683574501&amp;Signature=CTXoGUvq8IvClivlH%2FihE8bpvgAHiC9Fq3YAwqQyIDiWYimxLLrPMaMHH%2B4xJPfa00QK5tegM2bDdU2MP2onpmR3D7Q3CIQJWo3gctbIHnRJ1NbQLkn2qEVHp7Ni9JQGO6E8imoXBtWFX7f6BZRivHU2ixa96K2VZ047rT8DUUgjqZDagN%2FA17F%2Bkm%2B40yVGdHnCW7SO0Fer68fQFszkwfTxfcRJ10Wm2rVOiRRuS%2BNMwCC7GfPugM1L8MX8M6kjai5ILxF07ltv08dbdOcbPCw%2BN1hFZrzvpzU7lSfzPbW3bduNNzh7aPdSG4KxtYdDTbINh2sJS%2B3yZfR%2BPW6OEw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rivers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ river network]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ river system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hellas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Utrecht University]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/5-year-old-in-utah-pulled-over-by-highway-patrol-3995032</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[5-year-old  in Utah pulled over by highway patrol 3995032]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OGDEN, UTAH —  A five-year-old was pulled over by highway patrol while he was on his way to California to buy himself a Lamborghini. 

A five-year-old Utah kid threw, potentially, the most dramatic and, at the same time, impressive tantrum ever. He drove his parents' car onto the highway and planned to drive himself to California. Why? Well, cause that's what you do when your parents don't want to buy you a Lambo. Yep. You heard that right.

According to the Utah Highway Patrol, the story starts when the kid had asked his parents for the thing all 5-year-olds want, a Lamborghini. Welp, let's just say that mom was not too keen on the idea.

So mini-Toretto decided that with or without mom's permission, he would go ahead and fulfill his dream. So, naturally, the kid somehow got in the family car and drove himself onto Interstate 15.

His plan kinda fell through very quickly because soon after he hit the road he was stopped by highway patrol trooper Rick Morgan after he spotted the kiddo zigzagging across the road at 30 miles per hour.

Now imagine watching a driver you stop roll down their window only to find a child sitting in the driver's seat. The kid told the officer he had left home after quarreling with mom and was headed to Cali to get himself a Lambo, he had the money for it too — three dollars to be exact. 

Good news is, no one was hurt in the kid's brave quest for a Lamborghini. Apparently, the little dude was left under the not-so-careful observation of his siblings. Clearly that didn't work. 3995032]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIFKYZHBIDFEBIVBADRZKJFMZAVZU36KEDFVHRHLJNRKBALAEQFPACRLSWWABZLFZRDKVR6B2PB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://fl4e4kle4v6fhmr5ypjtqhz6oc.gcdn.anvato.net/up-image/BB6/AF4/BB6AF4B1A4504BF5B83282CADEC9E6FA.jpg?Expires=1683590400&amp;KeyName=mcpkey1&amp;Signature=tIE5DZ0v7_HCGGyfkyMt76FlbLk</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>113</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-asparagus-reader-predicts-trump-will-be-re-elected-3995005</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Asparagus Reader' Predicts Trump Will Be Re-Elected 3995005]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BATH, U.K. — Jemima Packington is a self-labeled 'asparamancer' who casts asparagus to the ground and makes predictions from the patterns they make.

Among her predictions are Donald Trump will win re-election in November — but will also be re-impeached and 'booted out of office'; a smooth Brexit, more royal babies, and a royal death. 

When 64-year-old Packington appeared on ITV's This Morning, a U.K breakfast show on May 1st, she said the formation of the asparagus for this month forecasts good news on the horizon. 

She said, I'm the world's only asparamancer, and I make predictions using asparagus.'

'You cast asparagus, you don't toss it, and the asparagus create patterns when they are cast on a flat surface.'

'And then from the patterns that are created, I am able to make predictions.'

The world's only asparamancer has correctly predicted Brexit and England's Cricket World Cup win in recent times.

She added, 'The May prediction shows a letter V and a letter E which shows we will have a double celebration during the upcoming bank holiday.'

'The little budlets that you see on the background indicate refreshments of the alcoholic variety, so we are all going to have a jolly good time.'

'Also, the spears coming forward indicate there is really great, good news on the way for us all this month.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3995005]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJIFPXAIBICFKAA9BWJFZ6DYMNIBREC5KVDWRGKWB5EWGARIA6BFEACYAJXW7WAKFMSGPWZ9ARGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/C25C0285AEC13104D011790A6E6AA8F9.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683574501&amp;Signature=fhBs2kksqkylDWmOdOPR8T72BrSudZDHsy23Cm%2FuZkDyaOB%2BlX1UJmYP8djLC472MPjtuWyOMxlx8REB9Nq1bOmWtoOnzLZHNqIVCKhrGyJSsmUDstKgwlaysNJZr9WdONWrG6bt%2FqRxHQ8Xhf4GOdavh%2BJ%2FRC4PUH4JNZe1pkIF%2FdZlK%2B6wHyuRNEGsnTCb35G7v2reIvBeU86ZPf%2BmlQ9QX6Zmkr%2FwbSIaa%2B%2F1PZ6xRq5Yg4keRcY0hvQ5LBlm8IwKgkFAAKqdx3ZKLftmmuZD6EYjFZpa%2F8ROYNNMnC6u5ExBJjv%2Fck%2FOBx8D0%2BsaFTtkPxWc9tX17cajOgTL4Q%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>131</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-uk-s-coronavirus-contact-tracing-app-works-3994953</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How the UK's Coronavirus Contact-Tracing App Works 3994953]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — The United Kingdom is testing a COVID-19 contact-tracing app on the Isle of Wight, the British government announced on May 4. 

According to a press release from the Department of Health and Social Care, the app, which was developed by NHSX, the digital technology unit of the National Health Service, will keep a record of whom the user comes into contact with. 

It will upload this information to a government database to help the NHS study the virus and develop strategies to ease Britain's coronavirus lockdown.

If the user becomes ill, the app will send a notification to everyone they have been in contact with to self-isolate.

The Isle of Wight is a small island in the English Channel with a population of around 140,000 people and a single NHS trust that covers all of the island.

Announcing the move on May 5, health secretary Matt Hancock said the isle's size is ideal to conduct testing under scientifically controlled conditions, ITV reports.

The NHS COVID-19 app will be rolled out for the rest of the nation by the end of the month. 3994953]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIFICRHBIDRPWARKBLRK6L4GMCEXSANAZBRZHAFBSQWPXACAEQFGB3VABUWRBT2QS3GRCAZAIAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/B66D990EEB69F25A7044A3200FC273BF.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683574501&amp;Signature=FQjPorL5v3nktFQZJxum97AGA5hppbIJnbTwT4XY5U%2FwrKKnYy8eqigyOqDm1ONXzDSoBKiZ7MVWhNCf6Fkl3g%2BVFCbKhi05WOF6MWVg4FpQlPAvJ5Z2Sw9tvAhR0LRsEPx5ynG0%2FBbOLYJskCYy%2FOrboAz%2BttSekns0%2BgYudUomzJCZdrPNYIQ86lToX%2F2vSeTEyqjkl16CvlSRz4WzWzOFlv06o%2FXJ2RIeinvPo8svxTePIgWKiuwdhLV5Cf2HnSOI4pUaTMQj1QHNJi6%2BqxzjgXCt9enwLKz%2FeJqT4bW8AFxKOMnVAlgOuVPVAchdeXj8jNGCWo2NXCzZIyGC8A%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>144</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[contact tracing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ COVID-19]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Britain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ privacy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United Kingdom]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SARS-CoV-2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NHS]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contact-tracing app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Isle of Wight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ corona virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus app]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/covidiot-cuts-hole-in-mask-to-breathe-easier-3994947</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Covidiot Cuts Hole in Mask to Breathe Easier 3994947]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LEXINGTON, KENTUCKY — A Kentucky woman was filmed out shopping with a hole cut in her face mask because it made it ' easier to breathe.'

The footage posted on TikTok showed a gas station worker in Lexington totally bemused by the woman as she casually waltzes about the store with a gash down the center of her mask, rendering it useless. 

As the woman approaches the counter, the clerk mockingly questions her, 'where did you get that mask from?'

She replies, 'well, since we have to wear them and it makes it hard to breathe, this makes it a lot easier to breathe.'

The clerk then says, 'cutting it? Yeah, I'll do that too, thanks for the advice.'

The footage, which has received more than 900,000 likes since Friday, comes after Kentucky Governor. Andy Beshear announced that shoppers will be requested to wear masks while in public starting May 11th.

According to the Louisville Courier-Journal, he said, 'While it's gonna seem strange and is probably uncomfortable, I want us to know that this is just another small sacrifice that we can make to make sure that we keep each other safe.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3994947]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIACXZHBJJFMW3HLVDA3KDYMNKSXSK2LVDF7GZHLRGRIDAGB2AAAVTVAV7FXVRPQF2XRATMB6QA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/DE303447AF780D266B98953D765B4F3D.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683574501&amp;Signature=qT5wiDCAuF%2F7%2BSdPnKUWfd50XqUy9S3ILz3g1gPs3bzzHLRmqnwlRZD00psLa3KpuGQFS%2BrA5TdTlliLkbg%2BnG5D0MHNUb5JcUmUSt%2FyxMzjlMMS8B%2FHoJ783B3d2NZ%2FMc%2B8XMF%2FEJlFIZnNLJIZn8HO6uJ969YlsYEyS7yRLQRAxUNUk44bZR9pVc2QgkpONwScSPznuYKtXtVPUxMqb1ME6xPURKeknxyPPfojBwMaeykOGmd760pLQxYOqXzvlGMrwzdn2%2FSYuvtWjmA40bwcqnpIYgZwMacLlR6NZxcm9%2BhFqKecUG6IZE4rHiUwtVtZ%2FZrddXgsgUBpmoWT7Q%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-08T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>99</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-may-have-found-the-black-hole-closest-to-earth-3995520</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists May Have Found the Black Hole Closest to Earth 3995520]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GARCHING, GERMANY — Scientists may have spotted a black hole so close to Earth that its two companion stars are visible to the naked eye, according to a paper in Astronomy and Physics.

Writing in a news release, researchers at the European Southern Observatory say the black hole is 1,000 light-years distant in the system HR 6819 system, which is part of the constellation Telescopium.

According to the paper, the black hole is 1,000 light-years distant in the system HR 6819 system, which is part of the constellation Telescopium.

Scientists say a black hole is usually identified by the accretion disk it forms as it devours a nearby star and the energy that it releases into space.

However, the black hole of HR 6819 exists peacefully with its stellar companions, and astronomers used the orbits of the two stars to infer that an object with four times the solar mass is in the system, which can only be a black hole. 3995520]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNAIYIABWIWZVAYB5ARI944MVAE7RK5AWKRTFKRBVHFPVKYAIQWAVT5A6URRAK7F23DGWA9AEGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/DB1A1D2A01E42AC568B7B5E270E4B377.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683660903&amp;Signature=OTQgnJIs1lXQTajW1Q0Nf5zqe2sVXIUdJ9k4wQohq61mxMXhl47jWnv7jnlTKnKKEAX2tEzaC8GqFUUkHQSt0CCYmpcDN12GExcG9qYDh1A1MMmGErbJYJtVhjkX1nKQ9rxNfpoM2SXmi88m5aL%2BHxYF8dkfePqJGR9q4z0HgT60LRaFGOWEnoF3q%2B3dKPayXKnbsLV5TwpasKPDiredzzFawSwa87EJ2J3bT5WwlVeIUfg4cS7Obme0aw3zuvLaEsC0iDJGn%2B3Yuq8JjlO3zN87Z%2F9iEcY%2BErxuVrSdy6i0EGRP4XcB%2FlNtBqkD2REjA64SfX9yTbIsBVLPnKLyUQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-09T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[black hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hole nearest to Earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hole closest to earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ invisible black hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ HR 6819]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Telescopium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ constellation Telescopium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ European Southern Observatory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/father-and-son-charged-for-murder-of-ahmaud-arbery-3995510</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Father and Son Charged for Murder of Ahmaud Arbery 3995510]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRUNSWICK, GEORGIA — According to The Baltimore Sun, on February 23, Ahmaud Arbery, 25, was running inside the Satilla Shores neighborhood in Brunswick, Georgia when Gregory McMichael, 64, who was standing in his front yard, noticed him.

Gregory believed Arbery looked like a man responsible for several break-ins in the neighborhood so he notified his son, 34-year-old Travis McMichael. They both got into a white pickup truck to go after Arbery. They were carrying a .357 Magnum and a shotgun, respectively.

The father and son then proceeded to chase Arbery, stopping their vehicle in front of the road at which point Arbery ran around the pickup truck.

Video footage believed to be shot by William Bryan, a third individual participating in the pursuit, shows Travis McMichaels holding a shotgun while having a physical altercation with Arbery. Three shots can be heard. Arbery succumbed from his wounds. 3995510]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJLAMCAIAFJRTAI9LAAA3KDWGIDV5URKLWLFZFCXAEGFMBCTAZLF5YKSAE6RZYC5QNZUGBI4AIGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/2D3921D8F23D86E255F7799798A51A51.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683660903&amp;Signature=jUbCYgEAmgVNG8UcW9ytsoJShbYjueWlhdyF5quVxv8IOgZI9f0AEtcq14ZDAFeDDyEvsaavK5j09fhozHngbCbssgsJ9Y5uw%2BUHHe7VN3Rb%2BSvcNUMwV43Vlqgw79cmwVwRcdUiPIvdvFH91RhEirhU6woVJ%2FgFOdj9s8T85W5e0ifZdts2jrvtNM%2FEHt%2FmkHkyVwRl3T%2Ft2vXlFxYhJc%2BYTa8RZw5aertsXlE%2Blm6Td%2BRM63%2BQkI7J6G784CX04nAoJcIX1CEBsLh5t5dOxI0Kvj8q0lXdW2YHWSZYa7lUa8Ln7LKK8PkNrLl%2BfBub05GW2xxRZ2W8Jx2QIJMfbA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-09T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>175</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ahmoud arbery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ahmoud arbery shooting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amour arbery killed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Travis McMichaels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Gregory McMichaels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Georgia Bureau of Investigation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/alabama-cop-body-slams-woman-for-not-wearing-a-mask-3995482</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Alabama Cop Body-Slams Woman for Not Wearing a Mask 3995482]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM, ALABAMA — Inside a Walmart on Tuesday an off-duty police officer was caught on camera body-slamming a woman after an altercation broke out because cops say she wasn't wearing a mask.  

In the video, the officer places the woman in handcuffs as she begins to wriggle away from him; he then grapples the woman, lifts her up, and slams her to the floor face first. 

According to the Birmingham Police Department, a Walmart employee had asked the woman to wear a face mask, but she allegedly grew angry and attracted the attention of the officer.

They also said they're investigating the use of force by the officer, who was, in fact, working a side gig as a security guard for the store. 

The woman has yet to be identified but does face charges for disorderly conduct, resisting arrest, third-degree criminal trespassing, possession of marijuana, and unlawful possession of a controlled substance.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3995482]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZBWCAAEKRCACBKCBSPRR94XMMDSXSIKKJKA5GIHB5HAIWZBAEKRPWKYLR5WZAC5FS6UCWCMARGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/E90C14ADCD7F6E0A69C0A7AC14CB0A0C.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683660903&amp;Signature=nyiTxO%2BPxL4t1jzYamSTa%2FiT1ytCx41cbDb4cC8NF51SOLPoGom%2BfzyrIkPbsJCS2pCr%2FXQcDGbGlFc1H%2FuVHwyheLlE8Nl6wwFPpUVC1HXvGr2ovrdbeV1gHWCVUoFfvpH4nj%2FlRpH8CSK73oPv9WkGOwU9pGdK5Iwvn1g1hdZivxTzvYunlHIZpARVi36fGdtNuHxepiSVbJyLrxY2ODM0gnqUB8bRwWTjZyJS5HOJ%2BWEYzYwoEbEUwHNwqJBcj9ik5IR1JSpjEv54TrE0k3yzNPXn5nNdmcWxiQUTVEd1HWXRPlnfEVcoTgDUEfPbfIEZDEDcdRSHjSpck0yPuw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-09T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>162</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/thieves-steal-97-cars-during-lockdown-in-new-zealand-3995444</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Thieves steal 97 cars during lockdown in New Zealand 3995444]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUCKLAND — A group of thieves cut through a fence of a Jucy Rentals parking lot, stealing 97 vehicles in total. 

According to the BBC, a group of thieves cut through a fence of a Jucy Rentals parking lot in Auckland, New Zealand. They lifted the gate and began taking cars, stealing 97 vehicles in total. 

Jucy Rentals chief executive Tim Alpe told the New Zealand Herald he believed the heist occurred on April 25. The New Zealand Herald reports the thieves stole unbranded Holden Captivas, Mazda 3s, and Suzuki Swifts along with some green and purple branded campervans.

Lockdown regulations have kept New Zealand's streets mostly empty. However, police were still patrolling when they began chasing a car that they believed looked suspicious.

The BBC reports that 85 of the 97 stolen cars have been found and returned to Jucy, and 29 individuals believed to be linked with the heist have been arrested.

A COVID-19 heist may sound smart, what with businesses left mostly unsupervised, but don't you think the police would CERTAINLY notice suspicious activity if you are literally the only human driving a vehicle you just stole on a completely empty street?

And you know what really sucks? Jucy is doing its part in helping the community during these uncertain times. The BBC reports that Jucy was allowing people in need to self-isolate in their campers, and on top of that, they've also pitched in by letting some of their cars be used for food delivery.

Alpe told The New Zealand Herald, 'We're a big operation, but it's just devastating right now, when tourism's just been decimated,' adding, 'To have to go through this as well is just horrific.' 3995444]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRAFMAAGK5BRCCCABNJR5LSHM2JE7UT2A6KWPTACLAFAEDKXAVIRAVZGAJYWAVZMPW3DGAR4AIHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/B739DD8D3191DCF5C033A97D0073736C.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683660903&amp;Signature=hnNJqAvTpAGdiAE0H7VURQIucJP8%2FeHuhxOtxTnpDpZAoyd4QfHC0AbrDMDz6jj9ZRHgq109MWpDvbewtAVz2d7%2F1F77he9BKwKspCIw9z2o9xyaZBfGS9Oo4ol6riBGi4%2BBPaQTZI6cC%2FDpUaAQIC0W6E%2BKYz5IStNbkqYuLVrRBQu4xHAqEbqYDEIXFo8wdMMzMyXeDhKLlczvKKiUz8OXVgpB7Yfv%2BtBSOS8f6fDf0Uxgm4e%2BxLjKTnvPVyJ2%2B88lhNCJyiDi8smtTm0nQhCCfkWgtSpoBmxfjl5JonZUyVBwA0rF%2FsfZ8Irl4phZPdSmvDx%2F2GrlKraQnNn8zw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-09T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>109</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[New Zealand heist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nz heist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus in new zealand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jucy stolen vehicles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jucy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new zealand]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jucy heist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jucy rental heist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  coronavirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ covid-19]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sars-cov-2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kim-s-recent-appearance-what-really-happened--3995343</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kim's Recent Appearance: What Really Happened? 3995343]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  — NK Daily, a South Korean newspaper with informants on the bad side of the border claim that the hermit kingdom's Pyongyang officials scrambled together in a 48-hour panic and mysteriously organized that ribbon-cutting function of the fertilizer factory we saw just to prove he was alive.  

The report also claims that the factory is unfinished and inoperable.

The newspaper's informant said, 'for two days the construction workers fully devoted themselves to preparing for the ceremony. They worked themselves to the bone day and night to create the appearance of a finished factory, coating the outside of the building and fitting it with glass.'

The source claims that in addition, all factory personnel, and even their families were mobilized to plant flower beds and clean the roads within the factory grounds.

Despite this mass mobilization of labor, no one had any idea that it would be their supreme leader, Kim Jong-un that would be opening the factory. 

The insider said, 'nobody onsite expected that the event would involve Kim Jong-un himself.'

'Everyone knows that construction was not complete.'

The factory has also encountered difficulties importing modern machinery and raw materials to produce the phosphatic fertilizer it was built for or being built for. 

The Central Committee of North Korea reportedly issued an order that the factory must have 'at least two' production lines running by October 10th, the anniversary of the founding of North Korea's communist party.

Currently, the majority of the fertilizer used in North Korea comes from their pals in China.

Kim Jong-un's sudden reemergence at the factory after a strange three weeks out may have been an attempt to draw attention to the fruits of North Korea's 'frontal breakthrough' strategy, as well as to rally and inspire increased food production amid the country's food shortages.

However, this doesn't explain why he was away from the public eye for so long.

Mintaro Oba, a former US official who worked on North Korea, told ABC, 'The blunt truth is that we can speculate all we want about where Kim Jong-un was and why he disappeared, but we simply don't know.' 

If he was hiding out to protect himself from the coronavirus, as South Korea said, then that would contradict North Korea's claims of zero coronavirus cases. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3995343]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCAAAKVKNKRAWIRL2KW76DSNEESTST2K5ARTT3YB5FRZVAFBIIRGAZAKR7WVB34QF4XTVZVKVEB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/44B6D08AD418355FA8335BFDF54D1E04.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683660903&amp;Signature=FsELXhOt7lppGGvqXU57DZQiaVnxb9MRBjxRqaSnVrlsU3DwYOqZXTrQ8vxuX5zLPPDMCqUOr87NY6RGOl4sfSgL427hxLeEi5s7YBAnoaGP7ZKOjqyJY1QeOxJqR2zmrzLFy9LNT%2FHRYoraz0cy1R6tSeaFtS%2BPEvPTKZMICe81xz67voRjFvKvkKYZDhX9oBCU1Dh6Dr00kz3lOj6%2Fn5C6WIvmotKt7GMZ%2FJyL%2Bu5LVhF392H8FrNwAunu2Mt8wUxcBmDn%2BJQIChFNqj694FWEyJPUky9B7uGfR%2BO12jVYNmFIqgSA%2FH0GHtSOCX%2FfpQ8uQOrS%2Bm7pm%2BNUMNRNfQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-09T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>143</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/why-the-north-magnetic-pole-is-drifting-toward-siberia-3996444</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Why the North Magnetic Pole is drifting toward Siberia 3996444]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LEEDS, ENGLAND — Scientists now say they may understand why the North Magnetic Pole is moving, according to a new study.

The North Magnetic Pole has been shifting its position from Canada to Siberia, and since the 2000s, the movement has been picking up speed. 

Writing in Nature Geoscience, the scientists say there are jets of molten material in the outer core of the Earth, and alterations to the flow are moving the North Magnetic Pole.

According to the paper, researchers utilized the European Space Agency's Swarm satellites to collect the magnetic data needed for the study.

Citing the authors, BBC reports the molten jet is located much further south than the researchers originally thought in their presentation to the American Geophysical Union two years ago.

The study's lead author is cited as saying that the flow made the Canadian magnetic node weaker in relation to the Siberian node, which causes Russia to win the subterranean tug of war for the Magnetic North Pole. 3996444]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KAPXRFA6PFPWA9LMBF794VMABBKSK2K6KFMUZABSPRMWRMK6CWMVIHAJXW7BIMQRUUCB3MA2QA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/D235CCBF35E27052D47CC95AE1A7308D.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683920102&amp;Signature=XT9MP7nnltbBdkqtdEHVWJRWARWkNoLY%2FsFltOb81smNcxlgjLbpMA%2B%2Behgr0GrVfhXFGk%2Fv30FLPdWAupXAmQdBoXruPm6gdq72T6gJXLmCRZL5vcKSbrjSQeLdANGS93WhOm5q2ktbSptbBCTnJ8deExWE%2FFgK4rzTEuUKkapCov0b%2BfWm4TTMNIXlT22%2BDCNLP%2BJqIFN%2B90k6TLrqUX0YF30lNFsmTryWzR5CZ2%2Bvy2seKT3u1ruz%2B65SxwgDVWlPz2iSrJq875x91egT6mTzegTCOtYgglgoeDq35eOTTfAeke0jt8PZV6ayfzNdxyF6J5c2Y7MwLPy5z%2F6O2A%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>90</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[magnetic north]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north magnetic pole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ magnetic pole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth core]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ outer core]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ World Magnetic Model]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ iron jet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ siberia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ canada]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Leeds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ britain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-longest-immersed-tunnel-will-link-denmark-and-germany-3996393</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's Longest Immersed Tunnel Will Link Denmark and Germany 3996393]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN — Denmark has approved the start of construction for what will become the longest tunnel of its kind, connecting it with Germany.

Work on the Danish side of the world's longest immersed tunnel is scheduled to begin on January 1, 2021, Denmark's Ministry of Transport said in a statement on April 24.

The Femern Belt link will connect the Danish island of Lolland and Puttgarden, a village and ferry harbor on the island of Fehmarn in Northern Germany.

The project is estimated to cost 52.6 billion Danish kroner, or US$7.6 billion, and will include an 18-kilometer electrified double-track railway and four motorway lanes.

When completed it will shorten the journey across the Femern Belt to 10 minutes by car or seven minutes by train, compared to today's 45-minute ferry crossing. 

It is expected to open for traffic in mid-2029, New Europe reports, citing a press conference by Denmark's Minister of Transport Benny Engelbrecht. 3996393]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFIFIDIDAMHRAWKEBNKR3L4YNABV5SZIAFJWRTIFLIHAKBZKKVIFAWKTAWWFXWRLQMSGPW3PKREB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/53E3F83AAE7545C148B159D7CA09DD20.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683920102&amp;Signature=sgbaDbvhNJw9d1FtcF3%2F2LMGMaQpLqb8fIsJ5gvfC68VLIrMvV43TDBhVtksPvc%2BT741kfpNlHPiGbYEKeTQxrlUletoB5BSEA2GNsFNV8p%2BKfcJCzm0LC%2F7cDQxIrOHhyrwoJ4xN3ySfWZeZl5itxodEk0lslTMCGAFU%2FysjfB5HcgWWDEx157rQHR2D32mrU%2BbpR1mJ%2F5KGuCEuCh%2BMZX%2BBDZwfuoaMdieXw8R2Y0QUke9dsjWGbVhrOp2voR%2FrLqY1I3AjTYt%2BH%2B4vThB6nMxQp3s5HAKnBTpjO%2Bznz9Rpfpb%2FiwXrPvYOr2uQoRWzBtmFX%2BZPcQyZ%2F7gkyGQfA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>116</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Femern Belt link]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fehmarn Belt Fixed Link]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's longest immersion tunnel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Femern Belt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Lolland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Puttgarden]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fehrman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Femer Bælt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Femernbelt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Femern Bælt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world's longest tunnels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ engineering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ construction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infrastructure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Baltic Sea]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/care-home-workers-caught-throwing-unacceptable-party--3996354</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Care Home Workers Caught Throwing 'Unacceptable' Party. 3996354]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[OLDHAM, ENGLAND  — A care home unwillingly played host to a party on Friday where the staff were filmed dancing on chairs and doing wheelies on a wheelchair.

The incident took place after the staff had helped at a VE Day celebration for residents and when the video appeared on social media it triggered outrage among some members of the public.

In the video, one member of staff is seen whizzing across the floor on a frame used by frail residents.

The same member of staff is helped by another to do a wheelie in a wheelchair and about a dozen staff are dancing around the room and standing up on chairs.

The care home's manager, Diane Riley said that the staff involved will all be suspended, but their antics prompted some people to call for them to get the sack. 

Riley said, 'There was a party held for the residents to celebrate VE Day which finished at about 8:30 pm.'

'After that staff and others who had come in to volunteer to help with the celebration went into the dining room area. It was closed and no residents were in there - most residents were in bed.'

'The staff were off duty and I think this gathering started at about 9:30 pm. I was not there myself, I had gone home.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3996354]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LRCYIFASNFAWKDB6JAX7LYMRDSRSAQAFIWTG3YAEFWEAAFKELAKYAHA57R7YILFBZDKATLAAHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/8F8F01F156E26FC8E2D0D295D31817A0.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683920102&amp;Signature=nFPRn4zmcH9K0KH%2BVf8BLw5MTNK5oY9PVlCzYV53X0N4PoYbWbCeCudaQxH%2FzRuqciqX2eH1XPKSrIRsrBFQ4Oz9%2FiZpQgpT7rJmHSxmgLrOyY8MXKBOtkIQC2k9cKQmqTZYRBHAH3Jvp%2FnNl2UXxQ44nRHX30lkuM95MyUkxhhmIiqQr55xOt6cEHanO%2Fi2QyhiKk11Xurqh3TVVZb6U3D%2BDeUAyhdcte2lRHdCgxjBLQRJlNo3EBmmsqq4da8pqPVHgBuQaasvdo7sAYfzcKvEvpNnxUpnHn1oX%2FyRsz2B5i4Xu4gkhBKjLmZvoPCopk0sri%2BARWfnBtVAtP8kqg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>116</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-offers-help-to-north-korea-despite-their-claims-of-zero-cases-3996316</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China Offers Help to North Korea Despite Their Claims of Zero Cases 3996316]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — Chinese President Xi Jinping responded to a message that he received from North Korea's Kim Jong-un; and in doing so, may have just outed the country's claims of zero coronavirus cases.

Kim Jong-un said of Xi that he is 'highly appreciating that he is seizing a chance of victory in the war against the unprecedented epidemic.'

Xi said that he too highly appreciated Kim's support during China's outbreak and, 'showed his personal attention to the situation of the pandemic and people's health' in North Korea; a statement that would contradict the narrative Kim Jong-un has been pushing. 

Xi said that more efforts were required to strengthen cooperation in preventing the spread of the virus, adding that China is 'willing to continue to provide assistance within its own capacity for [North Korea] in the fight against Covid-19.'

With Pyongyang being slow to accept public offers of help from the U.S., and with peace talks with Washington stalling, if North Korea accepted, or even looked like they accepted China's help the CPP would surely assert itself as Kim's true ally. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3996316]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IFXC3VAMAAMB3FB5DW5LDRGSKS5RZQABLWXG3YLRHAPAZHKSBWMBRHAWWF3ARKFMTXCBZWKIFA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/E0102009FC2EB94106F9E751364F2B94.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1683920102&amp;Signature=ePAULYGweBavIotADN5DzCtWkaZACHh9u0DtlFZn2Z1BEqyXbyokKji%2FqXxbSc57fYJPEy8baj9x1%2FDnoDD6A7ci99rqpBoCg9VU5h9LTjckGHb8CgLoJUBrgq6YjPvZe9ZWFUFQkaAotI7z6P%2FjchJgyjgHduG2Z0Ey6LDQPAoXv9GNS%2BSOwXeJ83cmzIY6nT%2FiPH%2Ft7AV%2F%2B2Tsk9gcdfHFqCiTtt%2BJJ6TsbGO%2F7r70465ets0XFL1Ljh16slXLAEk57CsdbhKBlvQjaEuYOrJoCAL3lTsnTPVlibIe14JyDnZch0rPt0dL3hu5po9rUjUqyfNQCqCaO7zrlh3bVw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>104</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-survives-after-head-gets-impaled-by-metal-rod-3996798</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man Survives After Head Gets Impaled by Metal Rod 3996798]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JERUSALEM — A man is lucky to be alive after falling from the second floor of a construction site onto a metal rod that pierced his head.

The Jerusalem Post reports Kamel Abdel Rahman, 46, was checking out how the construction of his apartment was going when turned the wrong way and fell to the first floor, headfirst onto a metal rod.

Rahman was found with his head impaled on the rod by family members. He told The Jerusalem Post, I was conscious and I did not feel any pain at all. I do not know how to explain it.

Not only was Rahman not in pain, but imaging from his injury also showed that the rod somehow managed to avoid hitting two major arteries.

After a second surgery that lasted 10 hours trying to fix the mess that the face-impaling left inside Rahman's head, Rahman was released from the hospital a week ago, happy and healthy. 3996798]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AECFMCKUKECRRB3ABJKA7LSBNFJBTE3SKSIFTGCTBRHWGWTZAAJWEA3WKM9ARVAIPWZGEVRWAAAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/2A56BE3B32FC52367C3AC26B2ADB491A.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684006502&amp;Signature=UcF%2FT7BaCBW%2FotHd%2BsNEmw9BauNqBBZobIc35xBw7eh9kJm%2BB4vLBr5UU9dCaN%2FGPTb6eRqkUg61PTO92vp%2Fax5nwRMthfHOmCfy3r%2FAiTPD28wsLpqjgBzGQD80gaU0QgqMQ2TNNZSd7VBkhTfam0oTKweOKufiCubCjxzicfxLXlw2AUCQQM2zIrMviTnfGJcjLJWsvbzFSKkCAOKDINDFUCu55Ao8rs6kWOw9cFFOrxwfOWqytrqpDSP6HIA%2BvzVNzXP7mL8XvV1jT7DglHe%2BgkqRUDTMNkQnIC0BcbmJxMXruyhxqjNrIkIMhVqpKZaIGgXnx3zDtdKw37etmQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-13T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hadassah hospital]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medical miracle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dennis-rodman-hung-out-with-hotties-with-kim-jong-un-3996731</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dennis Rodman Hung Out With 'Hotties' With Kim Jong-un 3996731]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[U.S. — In a new interview on Mike Tyson's Hot Boxin' podcast last Thursday, 48-year-old Dennis Rodman who has acted as an ambassador between North Korea and the States recalled his first visit to the supreme ruler's regime and how they hung out with 'hotties.'  

Dennis said, 'I'm thinking I'm going to do an autograph show or play basketball. I ain't know anything about North Korea, stupid as f**k right?'

The retired NBA player continued: 'When I first met him, I was with the Harlem Globetrotters and I wasn't playing so some of the dignitaries asked me to come with them.' 

Kim Jong-un actually first asked Dennis's former Chicago Bulls teammate Michael Jordan to fly out but the legend himself refused. 

Dennis went on to say, 'We sat there talking about basketball the whole time. The game's over and we go into a room then he says, We'd love you to come back, we enjoy your company. Let's have dinner tonight, a little karaoke, and have some vodka, some hotties and stuff like that.' 

Staying true to his promise, Dennis revealed, 'Next thing I know, we are having dinner and we are drunk as s**t, he starts singing karaoke and I have no clue what the f**k he's talking about.' 

'Everyone starts clapping and then he has this 18-piece women's band come out and these girls are hot but they just played one song. Just one f*****g song. It was the theme from Dallas. He said, that's all we know.'

Dennis also stated that while he's 'good friends' with Jong-un, he 'doesn't get involved' with politics.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3996731]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLFPACSAMCACCIUB5CR36BFGSIB3RCZLVDATHAFBIERKVRGKMJFGV36LR7W5VIKFRTXAWIZASPB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/4D4D59F29CAF2F9A465C37DA991154D8.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684006502&amp;Signature=MXXIikfAGQQVU28Y7awPrIYpBloFBbBLYT1faQbgAWtpJZmZnNLcbZ6mKW9ETEmWiM7pXKfNpnuhXAOHPW6QfywgFdPwLr7ZylWhWNBGcCwQI7RVImYoODCfBam1d3t4k5slGhCHlJS1EvkvRldYqf9jyHIjm2dAE1CsI8OFgbeaLqO2UXifNzTB%2B5YB7u%2FmYlHKUHZAAGRN4iKz10eCdmr5vMB4NVP2z2Fn1mZe17fHCfB4EaYtZK67Q7HWdmmQqRi6wOexSSn%2BHhNIKH38DBtnLzoDg6S3ECS%2BZ1RwLa0Kyp5HnOWoYeMgfB6Jd%2Bxvm5UtaE1zEunm3Y%2BRcImtPg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-13T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>89</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mp-says-oh-f%2A%2A%2Aing-hell-during-commons-video-link-3996680</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[MP Says 'Oh, F***ing Hell' During Commons Video Link 3996680]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Conservative MP for South Derbyshire, Heather Wheeler was speaking during a debate on COVID-19, when she experienced technical difficulties with her video link to the House of Commons. 

Wheeler was then caught setting a different tone, expressing her frustration with the issue, uttering 'oh f***ing hell.'

Deputy Speaker of the House, Nigel Evans, told Ms. Wheeler to 'please carry on', as her comments were blasted through the feed being broadcast to the Commons Chamber.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3996680]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKFACZDAEBRVCIVL6KWR6DXGZBSZEZLKRAAVUCXLBPAPVT6KNBRPYKTKJUR3B37F22DKAI2AJMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/CFAF896E1611F9F94ED8E7F8256D4B8A.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684006502&amp;Signature=nGVLwXVaJboE4tNe419b5NX5QCSXDflZ%2BuHfAbFIcQ%2FISrQRP%2BNuAD8vBzhK7HeAHVm01ScLJZ%2BBh2ouQTajtDSYXOq%2FF%2FFTpAuUGaqlh016W2deU7SWJn9HGCa%2FB2GuJplhyUJ1R8c4UMfipyaO2XAWf8DPQgiPD8e8vrrhZsG4bl15zh3hneGUNtqiCOcii4MY%2BWBB4LHPA2fSDRQkm%2FQENgdK%2B01hbVgLcS19lnclOdhKsyEmzJ2JkskteakerOMgnL2p7yKsi%2FjCY6XAcwNLDfczmt4QKyRjcaHP0SGY5yxSE3npdVG%2FzS4%2BABE1eb%2BOO%2FPM5xQwBZh7qXLysA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-13T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>111</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-dropped-a-giant-rocket-back-to-earth-in-uncontrolled-fall-3997326</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China Dropped a Giant Rocket Back to Earth in Uncontrolled Fall 3997326]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VANDENBERG, CALIFORNIA — A huge piece of a rocket crashed into the Atlantic Ocean at 8:33 a.m. on May 11, according to the U.S. Space Command's 18th Space Control Squadron. The object, the core stage of China's Long March 5B rocket, laned off the coast of Mauritania.

SpaceFlightNow.com reports the core stage of the Chinese rocket was 30 meters long and 5 meters wide. According to CNN, the rocket carried an uncrewed prototype spacecraft to orbit before making an uncontrolled fall to Earth.

The 18-tonne core stage is one of the biggest objects to fall uncontrollably to Earth. Jonathan McDowell at the Harvard-Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics tweeted that the  rocket dashed over Los Angeles and New York City before crashing near West Africa.

McDowell says the core stage had slowed enough that it would have at most destroy a house by the time of impact.

CNN reports the only larger objects to have made uncontrolled falls were Skylab in 1979, Skylab's rocket stage in 1975, Russia's Salyut 7 in 1991, and the space shuttle Columbia in 2003. 3997326]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DWGYIFKVBWEAIVLBKRZ7U3GREBTU34ABLRXGRFLSNAAWTVAWBRPVKTAE6FVAT2QRSDIVZ4B6PB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/797F8C1AD52D2F4D122B215A5337CC05.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684092902&amp;Signature=dNJiwN8eJAXz1bMNE01Wy9PfEhhDA6cypiBrHJTR0PQ5kUqFZdCw9bSutz513VHqSXw3oUBNVc2myvbAHZYLMwnK7yjtPTGSuzEO%2BYId5IR4udX4%2FQW0mzRxl17Mf%2F75JDgAnqTl84F74hUoUvfmp1CG%2BAOR9xPsqWV%2FgsHxd%2BQuARqbLtd4UxsrO3rXDHoPAV%2F9a5UECz%2FYkG186tNKfGNYPde9WtXm4kSaYGGuv%2BmYyK7woJBIcWaSq4Fn1I%2BbyhNqScUicCPKdWmzKlHHfZfgNY3Ihwapnt3UPhzYUMX5I18WqZ%2BzyV9Fyf4hTaldq4Bz%2FM8GYZLXWIlgaVSqsg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>97</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Chinese rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ long march]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ long march 5b]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ core stage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biggest ever pieces of space junk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S. Space Force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Space Force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mauritania]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-chef-spits-and-leaves-cigarette-butt-in-food-3997172</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chinese Chef Spits And Leaves Cigarette Butt in Food 3997172]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[XI'AN, CHINA — A diner watched surveillance footage of a chef spitting into his dish while cooking it for him.

The customer gained access to the video after finding a cigarette butt in a stew he had ordered and then complained about it to the restaurant.

He said he saw the chef 'spitting especially' into the stew but the restaurant worker claimed he was experiencing tightness in the throat and spat on the ground.

Local media reported that the incident took place at around 2 pm on Sunday at the Sufuji Restaurant in Xi'an.

Mr. Zheng, the disgusted diner said he had ordered the stew for his child and sent it back to the kitchen initially due to its poor taste.

Demanding access to kitchen surveillance, he was further shocked to discover that the chef had been cooking without a face mask and then spat in his dish.

The restaurant claimed that the 22-year-old chef, Mr. Wang, had spat on the edge of the wok, not inside.

The restaurant which is located inside a mall said it had ordered the store to shut and 'dealt with the chef seriously.'

Taking to social media, the restaurant said it was very ashamed of the incident.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3997172]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIRAACSANIA7WTCL6PWTLURGVESRRC5A5DFMGRLBREAEV3VAALRGYCRAA7ARWK5Q23XRCA2KEAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/D37475C0010A95887E9CDA0C6F2603D0.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684092902&amp;Signature=mHQLd%2FrhY7KusGZb2EDbPzD2%2BnzLCHDfeetobRutvaoKWTyVCkufuBw7O5CJgHqBeFzDocoQZYunim42xtahnjcMzNyO9gS2eQOEeixOJGIawrvcjrZLeBOGZ1I%2Bu0jwfHTtsm0O8SapaPb9KtLeg6FrF2ogROdmjTR0wZdXkJs4WwzU2zEGOxAEhEjY91n5BEMmq9Lgrc6BT%2BTn4CyketST1udQu6pRnSWaQQ%2F7yqwYwrtzI%2BT0ko5aPnfe7xxgDLDjX9simrOdMpxU5jLtokTIN%2F%2FF4zq%2FYm0fsmg0TDuDnn1s4pKJ5SvV1%2FLN%2BLhFmBUSHnSHfTTqfp3puOMAKQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>90</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-space-force-prepares-to-launch-drone-space-plane-3997141</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. Space Force prepares to launch drone space plane 3997141]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ARLINGTON, VIRGINIA — The U.S. Space Force will launch the X-37B on an Atlas V rocket from Florida's Cape Canaveral Air Force Station on May 16, according to the service's news release.

According to United Launch Alliance, the Atlas V is a two-stage rocket that can be augmented with up to five additional solid-fuel rockets, for a maximum thrust of 10,400 kN.

The robot shuttle is stowed in a capsule that the rocket will carry into space.

According to Space.com, the Space Force's parent service the Air Force has two X-37Bs. The spacecraft has a wingspan of 15 feet, or 4.6 meters, and a length of 29 feet, or 8.8 meters.

Its payload bay is about the size of the bed of a small pickup truck.

The Space Force says the spacecraft will deploy the FalconSat-8, which is a small satellite developed by the Air Force.

The module will for the first time host experiments, including a study on the effects of radiation on various materials and food seeds.

Additionally, the X-37B will carry out an experiment to convert solar power into microwave energy, which could then be transmitted to Earth. 3997141]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASLWIYCXAVCFGBRTLZBAZL2AMMCS3R32LSJRVTALBMAFMCADBAJRGVCTKSYWCWK2QN3GIBKMKFNB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/81DAD21FC57C138E63D138932E0A3AD6.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684092902&amp;Signature=XM5Ub1Ez6z0F5wu7wNSDPIUUIlFbVb4U3TxabDMap%2BRLyRuRxweDd3G29E8QfrKBNhu4KZ22NZwMlGt3aIx9mvTXKPTv00itorqpOzxihwsgjcag2qdYI2TLG3hMXKD1eiOjLveC4DWfYOiLtaeu0wQimRgHhwKFDRUs5xHZFQlkEMjLiC%2F6Dk0AmaVd4a1JOj%2F1b6F3JrT%2BVyu%2F9HH%2B%2BzUIpF%2F%2FPe%2BWxmduRNk0QcIX4en%2BJ5isbTmXl7K%2Bum77QXT5u9duCgm%2FRpk9rmsQU2sgdBDwgiyLFXRwcHj21K8j0mKiaxEBJo4LN%2F%2BSTGkGhQEVicBGd4uYy5Au2wiZ1g%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>74</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[X-37B]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Atlas V]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uncrewed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shuttle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar power]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microwave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United Launch Alliance]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Space Force]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/covidiot-inmates-caught-sniffing-a-mask-3997089</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Covidiot Inmates Caught Sniffing a Mask 3997089]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — Inmates of a California jail have been caught on surveillance video trying to intentionally infect themselves with coronavirus. 

In the video, the inmates from a Los Angeles County jail can be seen sniffing a mask and drinking from the same water bottle.

Sheriff Alex Villanueva told reporters at a news conference that the 'deeply disturbing' behavior resulted in at least 21 inmates testing positive for COVID-19 within a week. 

One of the videos shared by the sheriff on Monday shows an inmate using a hot-water dispenser to fill a plastic bottle and then passing it around as multiple men take swigs from it.

The Sheriff said, 'under normal circumstances, no one would do that anyway, particularly when everyone has the same access to the water and to all the different supplies.'

The biological self-harm was a calculated attempt to raise their body temperatures because it happened moments before the nurse went to check on them. 

in a different unit within the facility, another group of inmates were seen sniffing a mask and sharing hot water from a Styrofoam cup; which the sheriff said was sad to see people 'deliberately try to expose themselves to COVID-19.' 

The incidents took place in mid-April inside the facility's day rooms, a common area where inmates can hang out and make phone calls.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3997089]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADWXYCTKVFWGWRWLNJWZ7L3GRCVTU3SAZCFZGIBBZARKWIKBVIW7W3VLR7R3BRLFATXTBI6AEFA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/7738902AC9C586DFD5A90B8A827AD471.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684092902&amp;Signature=NoiCUbvymiB%2FaxyX7SdJ5h%2F9ytkN9UpyBLEWoABFkGjlseRt22jMF90ndzJjqvJ6WCZeVwmflKfPfFID%2B1qnIGyxeC5G1xtO3BsQn8phsw8XdVDDMxEhg1mRpojf2e7yMUMhGFMLOSaxtjMT0soWcPqFxwC9rz2IeaqVOVjzdl%2B%2FTVdB0LT%2F7h5p53X94IvFtk4hiPx5ejY5hmG25iny9bWJHJsMisdp%2BIHWmnMQKiQBO1K4uZL1ekP6u2oU4NrzPZFJkBaIe4hYIlQXheq7t9Ys%2B4tS1dY5qXW%2FPGFGLdExTGMUJpACJDCc0o%2FA0Oni%2FdDADtefXLWS2WJQdoV9SA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-14T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>95</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/rapper-6ix9ine-has-200k-kid-s-charity-donation-rejected-3997577</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Rapper 6ix9ine Has $200k Kid's Charity Donation Rejected 3997577]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BROOKLYN, NEW YORK — The No Kid Hungry campaign has rejected rapper 6ix9ine's $200,000 donation as he does not align with their values. 

The rapper, who was recently in prison for crimes he carried out as part of a violent gang before making a successful comeback, branded the decision as 'cruel.'

According to the BBC, the Brooklyn rapper had even evaded jail time on previous charges, including child sex offenses with a 13-year-old girl, to which he pleaded guilty to and was ordered to serve a four-year-probation.

In a now-deleted Instagram post, 6ix9ine, or Daniel Hernandez announced he was donating $200,000 to the campaign, which seeks to solve problems of hunger and poverty in the U.S.

The non-profit organization that runs the campaign, 'Share Our Strength' told the BBC it had declined the controversial rapper's offer, saying, 'We are grateful for Mr. Hernandez's generous offer to donate to No Kid Hungry but we have informed his representatives that we have declined this donation.'

'As a child-focused campaign, it is our policy to decline funding from donors whose activities do not align with our mission and values.'

The rappers extensive list of crimes includes racketeering, carrying a firearm, assault with a dangerous weapon, and conspiracy murder charges.

Hernandez responded on Instagram saying that he had 'never seen something so cruel' 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3997577]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KADAPAICKFLAXAR7BBLR59SAGRBV7ST7AWIFTGIKBSPWGAABA5JRGBCYLR6FVBRIQEUXTCKQASNA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/77A9F267B9528346793E3FB1B097D3D5.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684179301&amp;Signature=p%2F0FVklTrBzgldHfDN3OOCbNSOefPdvoP80ITCPcJGXwnAxE6UPbfR1EwUq%2FcBPs0%2BwsiFU2UPQ63oM41znlO5Xt65SLzoD2MdLvg%2B4TjPp90N4boiQdZ8cCnnY%2Fd4I9E1bdsSwI4nDRW0cXrPo%2FX6J9K7oKbwusjiL85OsH1mas6x4%2FnNETdkp7q5Fz6Er0Ecq4urD1l6w0mp%2F%2FxKWYVGarNQWLwQfOOFSCLP6vDiQz49x%2Fka1lkHQ5nF4a4IbZiBs0W4kTf4h3QjBipK0Uw0GNxEKrpC9tULZ8v%2FK5i%2BWn5CSIOnLAhUQZfAT1I%2BSC7N%2B%2Fg%2BuTwxTX%2BaXjHL5pyg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>97</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dwarf-bodybuilder-set-to-be-world-s-shortest-firefighter-3997551</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dwarf Bodybuilder Set to be World's Shortest Firefighter 3997551]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[GREENSBURG, PENNSYLVANIA — Vince Brasco is a 27-year-old bodybuilder and full-time fireman who is set to be crowned the world's shortest firefighter by Guinness World Records. 

Vince, who prefers to be known as a dwarf as opposed to a 'little person', was born with achondroplasia, the most common form of dwarfism, and stands just 4ft 1inchs tall. 

His height, however, has not stopped him from reaching his full potential and more. To prove teenage bullies in highschool wrong, Vince got into weight lifting and after eight years of pumping iron, the once branded 'midget' he's been dubbed the 'Mini Hulk.'

Vince, who works as a full-time firefighter refuses to be defined by his height, saying, 'the bullies made me stronger. I have proved I can do whatever I want with my body.'

'I absolutely love my job and am just as capable as the guys I work with. Because I lift in the gym I can carry the heavy ladders and I can work with the hose.

Vince landed his job at the Greensburg Fire Department in 2007, aged just 15-year-old as a junior firefighter, after three years of rigorous training he earned his stripes as a senior firefighter at the age of 18.

Vince said, 'I have always had a positive attitude, but even still, I have achieved things that were beyond my wildest dreams when I was a teenager. 'I have been ambitious and I want to show other people who is different that you can be whoever you want to be in life.'

Vince has documented his journey to a chiseled body on Instagram and has gained almost 40,000 followers thanks to his inspirational posts all about health and fitness regime. 

And according to Vince, he has received word from Guinness that he will be crowned as the World Record holder for being the world's shortest firefighter in the 2021 edition, to which he said, 'It's a great feeling of course and it will be made official soon.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3997551]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEAAAXZDK6IWCAASLIDAI9L4M2IBKRC6KAAR5HIKBSPRIW3RAEJW5AAEKE6FZWT2QS3UKW3LAZEA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/F77717E9C2F3811E6850020F44A676AA.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684179301&amp;Signature=WPs%2FS%2FcJmDxXLSmxTH%2BYIKYGPm6559DDlNQW3UCPniuJQeZ8Jda4CZfPcoeiKtIwJcY39RDLFZKx%2BlUce%2BNqiu1f3s%2FMlKFkWSA8ryPVKlszHyxavD2BndB0sZM%2BfD%2BuhD0tuE5CBkyI%2BR%2Fg90L9V%2F7DPd6KtBKfLVm7FN6a8aVrnMF36CJ67gIMEN065NPNXVoY6yW0VTwPexC0ZES%2BoiBVWlOmdCx754y%2FCwlZIXQFJ1e3AwT8uFrPwYlNzGqAKBz1hk3paXQ4hia5zTbuvWRnKznv79v6qUUbYN2aPg8Z7OfoZz4EBDJW4UAlpbBWGMKBU3%2FzYZV9DqGzbikfbA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>114</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/archeologists-unearth-remains-of-two-female-mongolian-warriors-3997494</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Archeologists Unearth Remains of Two Female Mongolian Warriors 3997494]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ORKHON, MONGOLIA — Archeologists have found the remains of two women warriors while excavating an elite cemetery at an archaeological site in Orkhon, Mongolia.

Archeologists from California State University, Los Angeles, told Live Science that they found the remains of two women warriors while excavating a cemetery at the Airagiin Gozgor archaeological site in Orkhon, Mongolia.

Specialists examined remains found in 29 burial sites. These include human remains from 16 men, 10 women and three unidentified individuals. Researchers were looking for evidence of the effects of horseback riding, archery and trauma on the body.

Christine Lee from California State University, Los Angeles, lead researcher on the yet-to-be-published study, said the remains of the two warriors showed signs that both practiced horseback riding and archery, just like the remains of the men and male adolescents.

The two women are believed to have been 20 and 50 years old and lived during the Xianbei period, which lasted from 147 to 552 AD. This period was marked by political turmoil. Lee and fellow researcher Yahaira Gonzalez said it is likely they practiced archery and horseback riding because they may have been needed to fight alongside the men.

However, it seems that the two ladies might have not really gone to war. These remains were found in elite graves, and members of the elite may have not fought in battles, Lee said.

That doesn't take away from the fact that, in Lee's own words, 'They were probably pretty badass.' 3997494]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFKDAIAMCAMV3HLEDRKLU3GJLV7F3ZKBIF7TADLAERAVK6KVQWIVAEKE6WXW3ZFS6UCAIWAVAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/D2189B8E44C89E60234651F9CE081C7D.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684179301&amp;Signature=e%2BSKoMUBGZWd%2Bw1klKumFHUbbHdrifUzmWajWJ550y%2BUskL8BsJCHE9poaSUhb75C9z2dAAWcRBd1xPWNOfvckvtVEp3EaF%2BIUSIpMsFStGvNerDzDgTTYp2jUjtgu2ksM0REuy9PiHDBCgxYY7%2B260jbiAfyhNuSd7czug12hgaG0lYMDb%2BSsPFvFrWtWzzVy1xAZggz5s%2Bpfwvt5ShjEi74%2FJBW0QYw6pQ2OFoXj9gnLkIuf90w%2Bi0%2BOWGOcnZXXSwaN6S38ocGh31PAnSUJJErulCKY9qWDwT%2BnyOrurZwE%2B%2Bjs381cN%2Fd6eypD7FssLbCkLxg%2BVRHPrVS%2BMPGw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>113</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[mongolia archeology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Yahaira Gonzalez]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Christine Lee California State University Los Angeles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mulan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ huamulan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hua mulan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ballad of mulan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mongolian warriors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ female mongolian warriors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman mongolian warriors]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/tara-reade-tells-megyn-kelly-how-biden-attacked-her-3997489</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Tara Reade Tells Megyn Kelly How Biden Attacked Her 3997489]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — On May 9, Tara Reade, who is now accusing Joe Biden of assault and worked under Biden's office in 1992, shared her testimony in an interview with Megyn Kelly where she detailed the series of events that lead to the alleged assault. 

Last spring, a total of eight women came forward accusing Joe Biden of inappropriate touching. In late March of this year, one of these women, Tara Reade, decided to come forth and tell her full story in a podcast interview with Katie Halper.

But Reade's testimony goes far beyond 'inappropriate' touching. Reade told Halper that Biden had penetrated her using his fingers.

In an interview with Megyn Kelly published on YouTube on May 9, Tara Reade recalls being sexually harassed during her time as a staff assistant in Biden's Senate office in 1993. She told Megyn that Biden would sometimes put his hand on the back of her neck and stroke it.

When recalling the instance of sexual assault, Reade claims she was asked to hand then-Senator Biden a gym bag in the Russell Senate Office building. She says that this is when Biden pushed hair against a wall and slid his hand under her skirt. Reade states that he then used his fingers to penetrate her.

Reade goes on to say that Biden was whispering vulgar words to her at the same time. Reade says that Biden pulled away when she did not respond to his advances and then pointed his finger at her saying, 'You're nothing to me.'

Reade recalls Biden shaking her by the shoulders and telling her 'You're alright' when he noticed she was unsettled.

This isn't the first time Reade recalls an alleged assault while working for Biden. According to court documents from March 25, 1996, obtained by The San Luis Obispo Tribune, Reade's ex-husband, Theodore Dronen, states that Reade had told him about problems she was having at work 'regarding sexual harassment, in U.S. Senator Joe Biden's office.'

The declaration goes on to say, 'Petitioner told me that she eventually struck a deal with the chief of staff of the Senator's office and left her position.'

On top of that, in an interview with The Intercept, Reade also recalls her mother making an anonymous call to the Larry King Live show where she mentions Reade's situation.

According to The Intercept, someone who heard the Katie Halper podcast found video footage of that call. The Larry King Live episode aired on August 11, 1993. The program was called Washington: The Cruelest City on Earth?. Here's how the call went.

Reade has confirmed to The Intercept that the caller's voice is indeed her mother's and property records also show that her mother was living in San Luis Obispo County.

Joe Biden's campaign has denied these allegations and in an interview on MSNBC's 'Morning Joe', Buden himself says, quote, 'No, it is not true. I'm saying unequivocally it never, never happened.' 3997489]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFKWECTUAIBRAWR9L2KFX9UVMZDV7RZLK5CA3TAFBRHWMARBABDRABCRLWUW7AK9QVRUGCI7KJQA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/3A75017D15119BF1337094D2AC748129.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684179301&amp;Signature=CVHYH3DVzqY5tg%2FknqOnuB7mH2EiGm99%2Bul369IDfD57JxRdLPuM2dLfEyKNnZWC%2ByAHHrDhn8%2FeLEYHcogM4SnCbr%2BhOpJbP8aQ1hkjmCRZc5ze6MjzgEoH0qfVWWHgCCKvK%2BObw2usKxFf0TtnaQ64pZDfZ1isN7npL0hFzQZUIdTL21o86dQfNgGmu8JrFDPIAF89Uj7cR7DlMBpG0QXaNiW9ADsz%2BE%2BAh%2BBien6jiyjAdpGijO1VLWhLFwXyiMN8kddyOBDP5TJusH%2F0n%2BQ7K5IXY83JmPx4aMespplwhfKe2agep%2BgeDjYjMFyT7IB0guvN4kvmfRMFKUUYKg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>191</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Tara Reade]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Joe Biden]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Megyn Kelly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tara Reade Interview]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Tara Reade testimony]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Joe Biden sexual assault]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sexual assault]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sexual assault allegation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ democratic party]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ presidential race]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 2020 presidential race]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/polar-vortex-brings-springtime-snow-to-u-s-east-coast-3998007</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Polar Vortex Brings Springtime Snow to U.S. East Coast 3998007]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — The polar vortex dumped snow and cold Arctic air on parts of the northeast United States and Canada over Mother's Day weekend, the Associated Press reports.

According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, the polar vortex is a band of low pressure Arctic air normally centered around the North Pole. It is located in the middle and upper tropospheres and extends into the stratosphere.

The polar vortex is usually held in place by a current called the jet stream. Disturbances in the jet stream can push frigid, wintry air to parts of Canada and the U.S., while high-pressure systems of warmer air bulge northwards elsewhere. 3998007]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSKAIXRGB2IFIDI9KFIWX7DXGMBSZS36KEAFXGKTLRERRARDA6AF5B3XAJYW5WZPFMRGPCI5AFPA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/135EA486BB028971DDB4E2387D1B16D9.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684265701&amp;Signature=t4E93fQ3FpYBVkL23eWEf24Ul1AWKZA2IPoh4LNpE460Wd42%2BzG%2BZgSLJBa0d%2FNUhnNPw%2FC3Wm30es7kcdcKkWh96B0e9nkgHpZA8DN1zcjkKYrSeK9ieaxRoIMPbWLzpPQP4PxuL96Aew1NOHlmcSPGmDRWg%2BoZH6Uv31ULV2hV9DZ%2BG0rKKvPckJnzMTzohjsyXSJKc8AUAwk5AmNgzFuzb%2BqOVsRg94qz1YeljeBO17KV9fGYXoHwsdmOsD0XGbr1eG6OEY4R1GwJ4pxdia0TAXfcDMQcVjYn7x67gyaiwRHIe9A83PEsz2c%2FdsDFXNSwmsocwRLZXGrTKJUYpg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-16T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Why was it cold on Mother's Day]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Why did it snow in May]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polar vortex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cold weather]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jet stream]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weather]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S.]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ United States]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cold]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extremely cold weather]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/covid-19-tied-to-severe-inflammation-in-children-3997990</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[COVID-19 Tied to Severe Inflammation in Children 3997990]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Nearly 100 children from the United Kingdom developed severe inflammation possibly in connection to the coronavirus, according to the BBC. 

Medical workers sounded the alarm in April after eight children from London fell ill, including a 14-year-old who died.

The BBC reports that most of the eight children did not have respiratory issues, but they did share high fever, red eyes, rash, general pain and swelling, citing doctors at Evelina London Children's Hospital.

Despite the absence of breathing or lung problems, seven of the original eight children were put on ventilators to ease heart and circulatory troubles.

Liz Whittaker at Imperial College London told the BBC doctors believe the mystery inflammatory disease is likely a post-infectious phenomenon related to antibody buildup following a COVID-19 infection. 

Children make up between 1 and 2 percent of coronavirus infections.

The Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health is cited as saying the syndrome is exceptionally rare and that parents in the UK need not confine their children as lockdown measures are eased. 3997990]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFAAIIBZCA7W3DBSPAX9LSNFIEZFC2KADFPU3TBFQRCXZJK2BAAWAGKSXWXWINF5UXPBKLKIFA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/DED771AD09B7BB69ED751F46709E2E34.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684265701&amp;Signature=SkuP%2BARNoGUojtvxnVsXvGdLzXzAu3n0avsjbk7xHPKJ6EhY5PP6kVXptUieglG6iu9okZhou1z9fRhFIWs8Bqf%2FTrdVdWMLltySjcp%2F7%2FP%2F%2BC92soTGT%2BiF3p9KN7ujKOtuDftPsfTF9ZQlyL3MCiil6Ymai%2Fw3vF%2Bj1hHPDKoyUUYiwigSciR6Sc5zk3djfafv0bvAkHf%2BVimdxdOwhwH5dqhBrV5nEr86qKNxE5GwTdteZgJuiC%2Fw44%2By2mtQg1%2FtaDFyfCunin70cSBRAFZIsia43nfUfDujW4toTVwr%2FtO8SqrEV6d%2B1UMzBfMGdzju3vKjcaNts%2FjwOPiDDg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-16T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>85</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[mystery inflammation syndrome]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ severe inflammation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ children]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ COVID-19]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SARS-CoV-2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kawasaki disease shock syndrome]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ London]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Britain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/restaurant-slammed-for-covid-19-surcharge--3997959</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Restaurant slammed for 'COVID-19 Surcharge' 3997959]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WEST PLAINS, MISSOURI — The owners of a Missouri restaurant are pleading with people online to stop abusing their employees after a customer posted a photo of their receipt that showed she was charged a 'COVID 19 surcharge' for a meal.

The disgruntled customer took her frustration to Twitter on May 11 saying, 'Scuse me ... what? A COVID surcharge...?'

The restaurant took to Facebook and explained that the surcharge was applied because of an increase in the price of meat and poultry because of the coronavirus outbreak saying, 'please understand we are not doing this to take advantage of you guys!'

They added, 'We are doing this hoping we can adjust the surcharge weekly rather than just raise all of our prices on our menu due to increased prices from our supplier on meat, poultry, seafood & produce.'

Meat prices in the U.S. have shot up in recent weeks, increasing more than 8% in April.

In response to the backlash, the restaurant said it would take the surcharge off and instead raise their prices across the board. However, it added that it would be offering a 'good promo deal' so customers can 'enjoy our meal with a low cost.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3997959]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZBRMYAELFJFEDIVL6LAVLSBGZCE5RTRA6JFRGIDLMHRCDKSBILFGAC6AJYA3BIJQJZGGB3JAVAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/A8606822A021FDCE39D59C6227A964B5.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684265701&amp;Signature=UUxR82T%2Fr2HxbTXrVnwplZ0cKsxQbQggVgfc1uuAHD7SSYSp1Z0DeOD50hKnhhdy4kfz99yvp1lzRjGOZWXEwq359zL%2FJq5WB0yNLhSgVaH2pQC15fmkHYZU4sH1m3IMa2omJB56lpkcsqVvoABV48Dc92BGhM1rzr9ejrVKpzOq3%2F2iUG%2Bm67NDoZYAtPLrUTkQiUmt5mEG1WYJf6uPm6Brohb6MLYZh8an8BmOw8SpXCZjgVMDr9YdkRrbfqYA4JdwItsmwrxE9BNwc1TFDhN3bFpXEsE40tCzLnmLUKLOx81Gbk0sEKHtiFK0N1VEMtTK%2BoXNhggzdtcKi1TrSw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-16T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>98</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cold-war-nuclear-tests-changed-rainfall-patterns-3997893</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cold War Nuclear Tests Changed Rainfall Patterns 3997893]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SHETLAND ISLANDS, SCOTLAND — According to a study published in Physical Review Letters, the electric charge from radioactivity caused by atomic testing during the Cold War caused a rise in precipitation on the Shetland Islands in Scotland.

During the Cold War, radioactive pollution from American and Soviet Union atomic testing sites in the 1960s spread across the atmosphere.

Specialists from the Reading, Bath and Bristol universities participating in the study used information from bomb tests and records from the United Kingdom's national weather service to determine the long-term effects of bomb radioactivity.

According to data gathered from a research station in Scotland, experts found that on days when radioactivity was increased, clouds were heavier and rain increased by 24 percent. 3997893]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZDAPYIELSJWGDATLBKA5LBFG2KVTET3KJIFTHTXBJPAADILKVLRABABLSWA3VT7FB4DMCKMA5HA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/CF96B5D2B7D7868D51911D170C43358F.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684265701&amp;Signature=tgx8XSaz0YMHpXpS6fIwR91ccRYQ9Rv1B1wpN7aATqL5Wy%2FMeQ%2FjNDc5CGohqpfYy5AlVno1NGFYeBzinJHbnnaH3z6mthZmew3%2Beh0OFdvSblSeLrXAsavPVPcNjnsEW8%2FYjAjRxwIKulSyrlj8rdvS7%2BVlQxFMpNUluFNCzxsFq%2B21AMc%2B9cf2aaQGT3ZMMlEb%2BsxtuMcA1jyK%2BssfaGAQPR4pRi5e6DuoAbYtkWhTrUBUN%2Fut5W3qdek%2BGcjkZchA8WBUvKzngzDl9lHvPJcnz2K87qQPZaK7uLm0aInTZGnzXsdJlZSbIn1iozvWwhY385nb4NU5NKBEXHrEng%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-16T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>88</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Educational]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ graphics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Next Animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Next Media]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ feature]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cold war]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear testing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ physical review letters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nuclear bomb testing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ radioactivity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cold war atomic tests]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ atomic tests]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rainfall]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-brands-himself-a-warrior-and-goes-without-a-mask-3997887</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trump Brands Himself a 'Warrior' and Goes Without a Mask 3997887]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALLENTOWN, PENNSYLVANIA — Donald Trump has proclaimed himself a 'warrior' on his latest visit to a PPE factory where he was yet again pictured without a mask or gloves.

The President addressed workers at the Owens & Minor plant in Allentown, Pennsylvania on Thursday without any protective equipment, despite his aides covering their face and hands.

After branding himself a 'warrior', he said, 'We are all warriors. Everyone in our country is a warrior.'

'We have to because of what happened. It should have never happened. It should have been stopped at the source.'

Trump rejected PPE during the visit, despite two top White House aides testing positive for COVID-19 last week.

The White House has defended Trump's decision not to wear a face-covering by noting that he is tested daily for coronavirus and has tested negative. Officials argue that face-coverings are intended to prevent infected individuals from spreading the virus, so a mask would be immaterial for someone who is not a carrier.

But these criticisms didn't stop him toting his own trumpet, Trump took the chance to brag, albeit vaguely, his own achievements with increasing production, saying, 'Great things are happening with ventilators.'

The president has not worn a mask on camera to date, even as his own White House has directed officials in the West Wing to wear one when social distancing isn't possible. 

And just last week, Trump suddenly remembered he couldn't shake hands so hugged an official on arriving in Phoenix, Arizona, and yet again, wasn't wearing PPE. 

The factory from Thursday has sent millions of N95 masks, surgical gowns, and gloves to hospitals around the country, so, let's just hope it doesn't suddenly shut down with an outbreak of COVID-19. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3997887]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEBRPCZDLFJRKARXLVAAZ6LRMNLSTR33KFKRVGZEL6PFEAAPKJBAGWZBKNVW3WRPQEUGPWA9AMGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/BAA228C032F973B432375A30A8E14CF8.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684265701&amp;Signature=ixQvvsUhsTmv6VDWPdPIGbmmHqIvhXgXDNqH6%2Bwu7KDP97vcCBqLmsUDspsi7rqt7wmEVigjqcFOOHgs3OFjaS%2Bg6ch%2B2ic4tSgwiceh5rHKLOuChf90RpYBwKZScl0l%2Bnof6M9jpLxAApCyLPDnzFiNGynUpB3gMn%2FFW7cxLqdQtVE5FJgtlBuIAykaGy0LGI8DpgFHGEorrUtDcMO2KGTPYGjSRQonzM13Ecrp6g8E7ap7b6jlCMt9IOkUkymuMl91iSOS%2FyVnrwgoXUunLmDKZWqDfQDa%2BOG1lYI3pF6nEkQr23cV8a59AdhfIHshiMWi9dEBm2QWpKEs22kYcQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-16T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>106</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-may-hold-major-military-exercise-in-south-china-sea-3998290</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China May Hold Major Military Exercise in South China Sea 3998290]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — China's People's Liberation Army Navy plans to conduct a large-scale amphibious assault drill off Hainan Island in August, according to the Japan Times.

Citing unnamed Chinese sources, the Japan Times reports the drill will involve landing ships, hovercraft and helicopters, while the carrier Shandong has been deployed in Hainan since December last year. 

The exercise is designed to simulate a navy and marines attack on the Taiwan-held Pratas, a strategically important islet that sits astride China's military egress from Hainan to the Pacific Ocean.

According to Reuters, Taiwan in April announced plans to buy arms from France to upgrade its fleet of six French-made La Fayette-class frigates.

The U.S. Naval Institute reports a U.S. Navy Arleigh Burke-class destroyer made a transit through the Taiwan Strait to warn Beijing's leadership against taking aggressive action in the region.

The Japan Times reports U.S. electronic warfare aircraft may have passed the strait 14 times in April alone.

According to Taiwan's state-run Central News Agency, a Chinese Y-8 aircraft flew into Taiwan's air defense identification zone before being headed off by fighter jets on April 8.

This is the seventh time Chinese military planes flew near Taiwan's airspace this year. 3998290]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVBWPAIHKMGRCDA9LFPWRK2CG2KBVUTSKVDAZTCXBJMFXA39ANAFEBCVAFXRXW39QB2XIATIKRAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/3C1C513A6B257A0653A8B1806BFE4472.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684352101&amp;Signature=FjuhH6WQZdsfFKXyUi1NpDZvilh4DG3ET0VrjLcPMKQbSbO0yVzFAFSGSmuveBROEeAV8SKoKidZMEPTpJFQCpcxTYcuN0Ga3WKXdWQNaycAWdxz%2BL0YD5W%2FH6FZDCMHo9NAokpgVg1Fxfamakn%2F3vhBGuNNSiqh1PTnfJj%2FfEQ8vMHhN5DMarcZi31ME07Z%2FGtOgSZN6vmzQsXsKbwaHjEphGYV3cJBCGcBLcdOSa8XhRquDAkbv4ToCPGOidOUqEmvKj8BWdFOrIcWkU6ZAhNSPbdbSf5D685l4ilKwSiu%2B4v0Mj7l7nWrWSQV81TFTVg4fwl2mq%2B%2B7Z%2B%2BJ2CCRg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-17T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>113</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Chinese military drill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese military exercise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ South China Sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hainan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pratas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Pratas Island]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Shandong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PLA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ PLAN]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S. Navy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destroyer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan Strait]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Taiwan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S.]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ defense]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/astronomers-find-rare-super-earth-in-earth-like-orbit-3998911</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Astronomers Find Rare Super-Earth in Earth-like Orbit 3998911]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHRISTCHURCH, NEW ZEALAND — Astronomers from the University of Canterbury in New Zealand have discovered a new super-Earth orbiting a star located in or near the edge of the Milky Way's galactic bulge, a dense region of stars in the center of our galaxy, according to a press release published by the university on May 11.

This rare super-Earth is 25,000 light-years away. It is one of only a handful among the 4,000 exoplanets to have been detected that is similar to Earth in both size and orbit.

According to their research, which was published on May 7 in The Astronomical Journal, the world is four times the mass of Earth.

It orbits a dim dwarf star that is only 10 percent the mass of our Sun. This star is so small that the researchers could not determine if it is a low-mass star or a kind of failed star called a brown dwarf.

The newly discovered orbits its star at a distance between those of Venus and Earth around our Sun. But because its star's mass is so small, a year on this world lasts 617 days.

To find the planet, the researchers used a method called gravitational microlensing. 

The combined gravity of the planet and its host star caused the light from a more distant background star to be magnified in a particular way. We used telescopes distributed around the world to measure the light-bending effect, University of Canterbury astronomer Antonio Herrera Martin, said in the news release.

These experiments detect around 3,000 microlensing events each year, the majority of which are due to lensing by single stars, the paper's co-author Michael Albrow was quoted as saying in the news release. 

Dr Herrera Martin first noticed that there was an unusual shape to the light output from this event, and undertook months of computational analysis that resulted in the conclusion that this event was due to a star with a low-mass planet. 3998911]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NRMDIFB6IAKWITL2LA7LD4MVBVXST2AFIFTHZCLAFAZDRIAVJAEA3VLSWRRAT2PW2XCBR7ABMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/5F957315B66D5897D5D6755FC8444EF2.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684524901&amp;Signature=kzHnEYESeVXSC1BkKujKeoU5s%2FUEfffFOPlF4zpS3helJ6bKdnc6%2FhtDz0tkTkWtP%2Bv2sXSR0%2BFuLjn75hSNGFau82hjJ1PBxnAh%2FYkykFwfLGGiZlWjk4EAAOIewnGr84yisTXQfhycq4Dar7%2FMcylggBekjXdChlkC9km%2Bu%2FQqIniLcFKXm5sDB04w7jw4kjTip80Pk8pZBNvakiLhelp%2F%2FDGjMEw4t%2BhUmDRaMJZ7JKlYiTBgjfCfEf4AY6XK2%2Bbd2e3FfdrRD0LqFut11hWLZCmyz40NFZSVtbOJlqe5UGq3lqM17CtZGcQfneziIGuFFsbqaQDqe%2F4P%2F2prqQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>86</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Main keyword or keyword phrase you are targeting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ a few variations of your main keyword]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ two to three tags that describe video's overall category]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cop-can-t-stop-smiling-after-18-pals-brake-lockdown-rules-3998809</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cop Can't Stop Smiling After 18 Pals Brake Lockdown Rules 3998809]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM, ENGLAND — Lockdown rules in the U.K. right now are confusing at the best of times. Under the current lockdown restrictions, Boris Johnson has permitted unlimited outdoor exercise, however, social distancing rules must still be followed. 

What this means is that if you exercise outside, you must do so with members of your household, however, some have gotten creative. 

This is the bizarre moment a group of 18 mates pretended to exercise after they were caught breaking lockdown rules by coppers.

The footage, believed to have been recorded in Birmingham was posted by Mr. Craft and it shows the cop crack a smile as the crowd break into star jumps and jumping jacks as he approaches. 

The video went viral with some thinking it was hilarious while others condemned the group for gathering during the lockdown.

One netizen said, 'My heart breaks for those working in the frontline. They sacrifice their lives to save ours and you cannot do the bare minimum of staying home.'

Another added, 'I just hope they're not in a hospital in a few weeks on a respirator thinking to themselves how did I catch COVID-19 and give it to my family?'

A West Midlands Police spokeswoman said, 'We are policing in unprecedented times. Our officers have been asked to implement new laws relating to Covid-19 and restrictions on people's movement.

'The legislation was passed very quickly, with little time for formal training, and given the circumstances officers have done a great job engaging with the public, educating them on the new laws, and enforcing the law where necessary.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3998809]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKFGAIJAACRTWZSL2KA7K4VGREB3RC3KFIF7TZHLMAACDAHL5QWEWCTLSVFAB3ZQN2DECKMKVHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/6A78AC2A166B659E69139949149947BF.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684524901&amp;Signature=xizJZtApGsgSV5X9oPdDbW7Hn0uUs74CUrvFknFjAxCirHliNlJjxI2sczf6y2dvEdijeAZLZDK29OH08nSCkPNVPrVkn36WqXXGPTaHv%2F9ZEvhND1kkMXe8Yu87fZkqAfwMFFlcw04J6E5kpSJE6YkI15uTTTGaOv7g73cH%2FDC3MdlNbioHpVh6DlLJHLMPdBaE%2BjYlN8ZqPkIS2zt8vK4XAxSvmVE%2FNcqfEBi9GGJuDkq6DcFuwWSoKnTOuhiy3w87oRGWRyIUP%2FFOuJKtNtNzQd7v4GiKFjrnfY0DFGfS%2B5PKY7WqyOhy1rqiEHqx1%2FpDbPlxqi5U0M33b207ow%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>113</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-k-school-slammed-for-it-s-crazy-reopening-ideas-3998791</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.K. School Slammed For It's 'Crazy' Reopening Ideas 3998791]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NORTHUMBERLAND, ENGLAND — Holywell Village First School has been slammed for its 'ridiculous' set of ideas of social distancing after it revealed extreme measures in a now-deleted Facebook post.

The school, which will reopen on June 1 said pupils would have to remain inside a hoop marked with an 'X' when they go outside.

Other rules stated that toys, books, and soft furnishings will be removed from classrooms because there are not enough employees to clean them afterward.

Parents also raised concerns about strict rules regarding the use of toilets and children having to 'do their own first aid' if they scrape themselves. The post said children will be given specific time slots 'and will not be allowed to leave the classroom outside of their allocated toilet times.'

It continued with, 'If they fall over or have a toileting accident they will be encouraged to change themselves and clean their scrape or cut. We have sourced PPE which is for use only for staff protection should a child vomit, not for trips, falls, or scrapes. If it is not possible for the child to clean themselves in the event of an accident, the parent will be called to collect them so they can do that at home.'

The school said it did not wish to make such 'drastic' changes but that it was 'doing everything it can' to adhere to government guidance 'to keep staff and children as safe as possible.'

Before it was deleted the post was shared thousands of times. People raised concern that no hot meals would be provided, that parents would be banned from entering the building and that children as young as four will have to learn more independently due to teachers having to keep a two-meter distance.

Speaking to the Metro, one parent said that she felt the blame lay at the government for pushing schools to reopen too soon.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3998791]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKAADCTABLAIVASB6KAT6DWGSJB3R3SKEDW5UAHLWMF3WRIAEKFKVRBKI7AZBIQPRRUEAA2KRGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/843226696470FDD07FAE85A629991183.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684524901&amp;Signature=SLbe6wGQyiZdws%2BFSjXceZ1xBBGBS2EvCszQxnZMUMGPkuhtEWZTDNRr5lVFwBVe8SvqrXUeHqq42%2FKmLd5Ne0gpIkQz7wbJ9R79OIrh2mkPKe578i5D3QD71CHeeLxMMZrEH1sO3CnNMtqMjLFRZ0ddOiYJsVQzGWfGgeHRneEFrv2KNriboYvdkCCEunu%2BXvccp2vkN9j1xbj3yfbvfJJ4ET9g9rGQ65KKCQWtH3B4EKvdJu5aI9sZ%2FE3qWP0fpRlZGcfJMwSbjRymFZhNOA5nueIkdYQwPO61D4lvlmV%2BDDRHWzgRz8kASFEWPi37uTOTPFSfa2LJlZ07oOu5GQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>114</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hokkaido-gypsy-moth-is-detected-for-the-first-time-in-the-u-s--3998756</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hokkaido Gypsy Moth is Detected for the First Time in the U.S. 3998756]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — A recent proclamation issued by the governor of the State of Washington, Jay Inslee, warns about the detection of Hokkaido gypsy moths in areas in Snohomish County, Washington. 

This is the first detection of the species in the U.S., the Washington State Department of Agriculture said in a press release. 

The Hokkaido gypsy moth is native to Russia, according to the National Invasive Species Information Center from the U.S. Department of Agriculture.

Asian gypsy moths measure three and a half inches (about 9 centimeters) long and female moths can lay from 500 to 1,000 eggs, according to the U.S. Customs and Border Protection.

In a press release, the Washington Department of Agriculture said European gypsy moth caterpillars eat more than 500 types of trees, plants, and shrubs.

However, Karla Salp, a spokeswoman for the department, told UPI that Asian gypsy moths pose a greater threat than European gypsy moths because they can consume more species of plants.

If the species establishes itself in Washington it would become a threat to forest ecosystems and could lead to quarantine restrictions and increased homeowner pesticide use, according to Washington's agriculture department. 3998756]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJRICIBA6JACVCFKAARR7D4MNJEZSZLKFIFPFIDLJNA5D3UKJBAABTYKE6WAYC5FZRXTAIVKNNB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/5D262D9B91F0C4B048C2B3FE83A6E6CD.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684524901&amp;Signature=aZj%2By3X7krymQzNwLE9ighrxTAzl5O1DSlBQHYCyqFCjO0i1Wg3SoWxlmRJs4hP8FnNzIIaX%2FJDNvyzVWsjH3jI583RwkpUjlNEQO265bGgljqKy3%2Fvo1zV5ZsySb3FoOSdWbjAy%2FXKhzUSe%2FMGJ%2B4fkl%2FIpOrxhR3bt8VTfVlsMbG9smcfSquUwgA9djq6L1d0rjISaUvjF8n8celWZKgvZjsMdgmcIUfU4W%2Byz0jL8bIxpinUKGhc%2FxvAlthhSy4iaYISzW7BjGI3f6ux8UPH14vWJLmdQ5Hzp4KvOblK93ykzTy%2Br5Ph3Xj677Dv47VN2Fvc7GE60VJGyya6YDg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-19T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>125</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Washington State Department of Agriculture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant asian gypsy moth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant moth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gypsy moth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moth pest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ agriculture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ horticulture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant asian moth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ huge moth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ moth invasion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/children-sick-after-parents-are-allegedly-sold-fake-baby-formula-3999238</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Children sick after parents are allegedly sold fake baby formula 3999238]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HUNAN, CHINA — Chinese authorities in Hunan are currently investigating a baby product shop following reports of five children being diagnosed with rickets after consuming fake milk powder sold by the store.

Several parents of children allergic to regular milk formula in Yongxing County, Hunan Province went to a baby product shop looking for an amino acid-based milk alternative for their babies only to be sold a protein mix, the South China Morning Post reports, citing local media.

One of the parents surnamed Zhu said that staff at the shop told her the product called Bei An Min was an alternative to baby formula, despite its packaging labeling it as a protein drink. Zhu's daughter drank the powdered protein drink for more than two years.

According to a report by thepaper.cn, five toddlers were reported to have lost weight, and developed eczema and a swollen head after drinking the protein beverage.

The paper.cn also reported that some children would slap their heads and all of them were diagnosed with rickets, a condition caused by vitamin D, calcium or phosphate deficiency. 

In an interview with Xi Gua Video, a woman identified as Ms. Chen says that staff told her it was the best-sold product in their store and that all babies allergic to regular formula drank the protein powder.

When Chen pointed out that the product was labeled as a protein supplement, the clerk told her it was 'an abbreviation for milk.' 3999238]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNWXDIHBIHRZAZXB6JAZ7DXMAEV7SAIKWJFVGAABIHR7AIBBEJWGYC5KSUFCVC5FF3XKVCIANQA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/F6FF761AD68657781F30F715413D8E5C.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684611301&amp;Signature=BCAHuces8mCyjLKez1Q64gCkKLtJpxcIaYEh4VjnpYeXXzkpxyI%2B5xLNaH7R32Q1Wxs8tbnWPRaIsf4%2BWL4TReGIbAYGRHA%2FHdl%2BdXJfFzuh1YHtk%2FmNO8Ej9dbm2tNbGk3U9sY2n9rGHLKnKjPvzHdPe%2FitKV3OgFt%2FO1P8TKywwjF5LJUUaORrxO5OKA4hkVU2WXXnRftckr4QitRUg5%2BNALuGdI9TwcB4e%2BIQbAs5eBbtKtk7lZeWxQ7baI2ymZCYAPytu9KI%2Be0o9r16p8xD9c3H%2F0107o6lXudIuSY958Qgc6hdQ75n%2BH4j7cSDUOkmg5nZwK%2FgYCGFJbtVFg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>127</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ milk powder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake milk powder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ milk powder scandal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bei an min powder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bei an min]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rickets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eczema]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/disgusting-woman-filmed-spitting-on-fruit-in-china-3999203</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Disgusting Woman Filmed Spitting on Fruit in China 3999203]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANSHUN, CHINA  — A female vendor was filmed on May 11th, in a now-viral video, sipping water from a bottle and then to mist her waxberries, spat the water from her mouth all over the fruit. 

The clip which was shared to the Chinese platform Weibo has led the farmers market to terminate the woman's contract and stick her on the blacklist for life. 

The video comes after growing international concern over China's open animal markets causing the spread of coronavirus. 

But in a twist, Ms.Yang, the vendor says she has been wronged, as she was in fact spraying water around the berries on the floor to keep the dust down.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3999203]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LMDAPCIJK6JRRBR7LFLWZ943NABSZEAKKFJAZTIDLWNAZBIDAMJRAWTRAE7FVVAPF63XKAKPBZFA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/C0554C5E2F588875C86D91D2FA63E5F3.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684611301&amp;Signature=dycxsh21HcHGeWaQs17wCC9DVO5h3bMouK1gN3NNLkdTw29LA3hRTLqSJWdgVwNQn0v05I0pUsChFZ5TBGT03togdp%2F%2F%2B7LTF8NlP%2FEaWsP2%2FI35XFZ6t4Ov58wDB1YV5A9S5KD54zw%2BQYPkYtqbeXzrEn2tCY133LgC%2FcvpUTx%2FBmwiGbq6ago29qS2JU1CZ83diVdwvtxeicTVOz%2FuJ1KU0UuLeALYTX1oMb9rjQhPA7Cirg15cN5F1o6WbHM0GTCV%2Fy7JZyz9FcjGNbn%2FUKIo8F4E4n20jV%2Fid4B7WlZZhKIep8n9wHNT84Mah68D6tQQXFM55WO3aOqr3ySJiQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>116</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/this-melting-glacier-may-cause-a-1-000-foot-tall-tsunami-in-alaska-3999175</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[This melting glacier may cause a 1,000-foot-tall tsunami in Alaska 3999175]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANCHORAGE, ALASKA — A melting Alaskan glacier may set off a landslide and trigger a tsunami in Prince William Sound, according to a public letter by climate scientists and geologists at institutions including the University of Alaska, the Ohio State University and the University of British Columbia. 

This event could happen as soon as next year and no later than 20 years from now, they say. 

The researchers say the Barry Glacier's retreat inland could send its scarp tumbling down the Barry Arm. A complete failure of the scarp will cause a destructive tsunami to crash down Barry Arm and Harriman Fiord, while partially endangering Port Wells.

If the scarp fails completely, it would raise waves as high as 1,000 feet, which would threaten fishing boats and the hundreds of fishermen and tourists who frequent the region. Even locations far from the Barry Glacier may experience 30-foot tall waves.

According to the letter, climate change is melting Barry Glacier, and the retreating ice has left a swath of the cliff unsupported by its mass. The loose scarp then entered into a slow-motion landslide that is now showing signs of speeding up. 3999175]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMAWMCZBKABAVDZYB6JRK6LXM2LVXFAMABJFTFALBMAFXCIEAMLFEWZBK56ARV39PS2GTBCPAAAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/805B9D36955A25EF0CBE69F6CC25726F.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684611301&amp;Signature=uel43PJGfPq4RuwPgxM6jxYgYTNeQ0jF1YwhPUY46rBetZ%2B2cFPLBd8tJwTDFGMWz5%2B%2Fy5vzVJCaIQImixtCJXPt237F%2Br%2FhforZSdyaWABuhp4aT5ddDSjucWzfOzTVq0EO%2BPj3hGW8P00jIdNh5zYDltUWyV3koTtqHpuq9G%2BOWvQNrNOKZwfjnFB4pA6V99EpVNKYgzimNSmtmOgg7JfZ8IUq0r%2F4cCMrZ1%2Fo4DmfhFhTOgUJhf0%2BuBEgOQZyeFtV%2FcxE8iCX0r9oNebb2vD1cUudVz87lrC3UgVr4p1unJj%2BXGRuOkt%2F5wqdevyqQavwLZPCbDuBZTLdSI2M%2Bw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-20T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Barry Glacier]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ landslide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tsunami]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Prince William Sound]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Alaska]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/super-cyclone-to-make-imminent-landfall-on-india-and-bangladesh-3999769</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Super Cyclone to Make Imminent landfall on India and Bangladesh 3999769]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KOLKATA, INDIA — India and Bangladesh are evacuating millions before the path of Tropical Cyclone Amphan, which is expected to make imminent landfall on the evening of May 20. 

Amphan is the second-ever super cyclone on record to hit the Bay of Bengal. The powerful storm was sustaining an airspeed of 172 km per hour at the time of report.

Citing India's weather department, the BBC reports the storm will bring a 3 to 5-meter surge, and the authorities have called on fishing boats to stay ashore.

The U.S. Pacific Center says up to 33.6 million people in India and 5.3 million people in Bangladesh are exposed to the storm, with capital exposures of up to $273.9 billion.

The cyclone will likely fall on the India-Bangladesh border and the projected path will bring the storm near the Indian city of Kolkata.

More than 14 million people reside in this densely populated urban center. 

Thumbnail credit: FLICKR / VINOTH CHANDAR 3999769]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVBWCAIHKAFRRDRXL2LWZKLVMAEBTE34LRAWRHRFBNQW7WAEAFBRABAAKBVA7WZMPSZXMVZ7KIEB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/91FB8B13C4137A054F5A010F1291B128.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684697701&amp;Signature=uSJxQMPyzt9QFQS1uWhAmWFKnzlTCdZwQpfe%2BMA5HsiwGlUQpmRptaKm9rQTPBlbCoBLR6B9POodvd1vRH2f62DP2i%2FSlDb3kSFPGCrZQsk%2BuVUgUxeQqLAmDO0HkBsuA8UZCtBFHESRpEY5MMAoEkOURXuWgyQ03TPtJeiws0xpw4Ht1nb0fYn0Yc2E7yQzApO8rnRt08AgH9inf0KVtPzl%2FsjiJ55o8R3SWwlUS45BkLMoC4fnYUrbGrLvs%2BVNgmIY9y2xnvSeigPaBlqzOfy1KEv8XF1DQLzRmHPe8%2BHKy5w7YGk0ds65jhMaomCoMj4n1CbabFf9H%2BY2QW8H0g%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[amphan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tropical cyclone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ super cyclone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ storm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kolkata]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ India]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Bangladesh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ natural disaster]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-found-one-of-the-oldest-stars-in-the-entire-cosmos-3999677</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists found one of the oldest stars in the entire cosmos 3999677]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SYDNEY — Astronomers have discovered a red giant 3,500 light-years from Earth that could be one of the oldest stars in the cosmos, according to a paper published in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society.

Writing in a news release, researchers say the very first stars created by the Big Bang are believed to be extinct, but the red giant they spotted in the galactic halo is likely a descendent of those much older stars.

The red giant contains the least amount of iron ever detected, or 1.5 million times lower than that found in the Sun. Since metallic elements are created by ancient stars, an anemic star is likely to be much older than metallic stars.

The first stars were believed to be made of pure hydrogen and helium. When these stars die, they explode into supernovas and create metal elements. This explains why the red dwarf, a direct progeny of the first stars, contains so little iron. 3999677]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIWADTTAIFAPWA9BJKAZ9UVMICVTR32KFPFPTABBVAFRVRFKNDWGWTVKFYFTAAIFMRGRCCIANMB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/EC15F988F0EE2FB98E700FFD493A0332.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684697701&amp;Signature=nEst3318ffgikFMI8SQFPex1vXmCEvgmFq9TQvLkgNvgKLi4AB%2F7C9YnMMN0GwpLYnJo%2F9RxGhcKyQ3GYY20CRZrUqsIVkoxpSFEaBqhhjKEGmXTSMK9gSDuSVo2Zki0G57QM%2FqCV1BHt5tPrFNwRuxCx1LPudccy%2BAn2uRZlhmt3x3oGQ0OgNIYfpGlUrBtCJRuqpaOf4Xl%2FyCqB3TSluYWEApwhdhtBN6RwoqrRHKWcqEH64mk1UzEm2%2F2TCLhXES6vh03FfvW53rFJ7s2hguj3tEAhj%2FsVozgv8BcUAgIy8cFLCsa8TMbO78VvdRDB9RkowgL1Zs46%2BJY%2FJVsmA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[red dwarf]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lowest ever detected iron content]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ metallic stars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ metallic elements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ big bang]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient stars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first stars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ astronomy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Australia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/asteroid-as-large-as-the-golden-gate-bridge-approaching-earth-3999674</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Asteroid as Large as the Golden Gate Bridge Approaching Earth 3999674]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — This year's second-largest potentially hazardous near-Earth object is incoming at speeds of over 11,000 kilometers per second and will zoom past our planet on May 21.

Asteroid 136796, also known as 1997 BQ, is estimated by NASA to be between 640 meters and 1.4 kilometers wide, or roughly the size of the Golden Gate Bridge.

1997 BQ orbits our Sun every 844 days. According to NASA's Asteroid Watch, on May 21 it will pass Earth at a distance of 6.2 million kilometers, slightly closer than this year's largest potentially hazardous near-Earth object, 1998 OR2, which flew past Earth on April 29 at a distance of 6.3 million kilometers.

NASA classifies a near-Earth object — either a comet or an asteroid — as a potentially hazardous object if its orbit brings it within 7.5 million kilometers of Earth's orbit and it is greater than 140 meters in size.

According to NASA's Center for Near-Earth Object Studies, as of April 21, some 22,582 near-Earth objects had been discovered. Of these, 9,085 were 140 meters or larger in size, and 902 were estimated to be larger than one kilometer.

By comparison, the Chicxulub asteroid that wiped out the dinosaurs is estimated to have been 11 to 81 kilometres in diameter. 3999674]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KAMXCVA6PFCDRWKEDWX9BHM2KVTU3SKSIFRTKWBJNAXDZPAEIREW3WABUR3B3ZF64GAVR7AMHB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/110220BA9D21B5D7B7D5C4F8C4046080.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684697701&amp;Signature=OSpycI%2F3rubFfl6AD4E78SinKpctbTRtXAYcqAIAm%2FTOLSSSX10pZE3Cq0Vy01gkQemccEswHvxaOia%2BmTioLOi12SGTBo3jp%2BPg23RBjdOXjMvHimBYRu8FakIhRVkIztM1uQvh%2FaP%2BuYdfR8AQwvo%2B7ea%2Bp8Wg1rpt5AOBqKeZrF%2BW9okaetyTupqWMcNOlz3GMi7aymhejEtEyWrsmgDyIDLuWCiLfyiCsBn%2F7WRrfxvh4%2FZKYouQq5wFhPwGW7ujwMNqRRUNAy64kRM7J64hpqy%2F3Csw2okynbP2EkwFWREQBCjZ%2F4NIZYeSmWEkxMs%2BbkZS69v7YtOjghoXUQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid May 21 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid coming toward earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 136796]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 1997 BQ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ potentially hazardous near-Earth object]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nasa asteroid 21 May 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid May 2020]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/solar-eclipse-to-sweep-across-africa-and-asia-in-june-3999539</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Solar Eclipse to Sweep Across Africa and Asia in June 3999539]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAIPEI — The Moon will cast its shadow over parts of the Eastern Hemisphere from Africa and Eastern Europe to the Pacific in a solar eclipse on June 21, on the same day as the Northern Hemisphere's summer solstice.

According to NASA, the annular phase of this solar eclipse — when only the Sun's outer edges are visible around the Moon in a fiery ring — will cross the Democratic Republic of the Congo, South Sudan, Ethiopia, Eritrea, Yemen, Saudi Arabia, Oman, Pakistan, India, China and Taiwan.

People thousands of kilometers north and south of this area will be able to see varying stages of a partial eclipse. 3999539]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZCFADTVK5FAPBA9BBJW77SFM6KBTFK3KFKFXT3RB6NWZAILL5LW5V3TAJUWAWREQS4GIVA5AJNA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/10A2C5E64E2DEB4E421874DFF7427E53.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684697701&amp;Signature=rHdSRUyhzQrzvi%2FfpJ%2FzERivrrHa5C6vYWrqabR9%2BN%2FyQE9gfErWitCn3zm%2FPVzxJf6htQCLZiga%2F3S2dcBSKCkEmwOE3tdnU69jMQd5INjHbrk%2Bpzz%2FF%2BzaeOclrNVjLfbHnB9%2BIfxxnvF8bKiAwzY190KlRGitQYVuRgJUAW7ZhQLTkw%2BqslYHwEC0w7PuHgRsLOwYVuySRYwcebx9eVeKUzJpYrvOUis88axjqoJ7v6LE06MK4%2BgZSUl3kIOHa5J88lWzy9ctErZdzlhDg8xLy0MZ%2Bx0vII%2B6rnsjLk2RA0pVAI7nYOhtGbiEatsa4Qzz9K3GmJXi7ZIFGqlnBA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>116</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[solar eclipse 2020]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar eclipse video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar eclipse animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ total solar eclipse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how solar eclipse happens]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how eclipse happens]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Politics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Education]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Educational]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ News & Politics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/rabbits-threatened-by-highly-contagious-and-deadly-virus-4000231</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Rabbits threatened by highly contagious and deadly virus 4000231]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MADISON, WISCONSIN — Rabbits are under threat as a deadly hemorrhagic virus spreads across the southwestern United States.

According to a report from the USGS National Wildlife Health Center published on May 7, rabbit hemorrhagic disease virus serotype 2 or RHDV2, a viral disease deadly to rabbits, is spreading across the southwestern United States.

Rabbit hemorrhagic disease virus can infect domestic rabbits and wild rabbits such as hares, jackrabbits and cottontails. 

According to the United States Department of Agriculture, the virus can cause sudden death and nose bleeds caused by internal bleeding. Other symptoms include fever, loss of appetite, swelling and signs of nervousness or irregular breathing.

RHDV2 can survive on a dead animal's carcass for at least three months. It can also spread if an animal or individual comes into contact with an infected animal's droppings or blood.

RHDV2 can also spread through food, water or any other material that has been exposed to the virus. Humans can also spread the virus by carrying it on clothes and shoes. RHDV2 does not affect human health. 4000231]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABLACCTTBSIRMARXL2IA36DVGWLS5RRKKRCFPGZMA5EWICZKBALFCB3TKM9F7VAIQW3UCWA2K2PB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/FC430FDA9654652526D8C6949CBC8DA7.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684784101&amp;Signature=qMQtDfwbwn8pSOFHtZxUClbs1jUSxRuWo%2F7w0xUQaRXcobraF3pkbtOTc3XMsNGceFyjtKX5hFpBzyQ8ARyjGmlmq1fKWUWoRozUT%2FglpMouiIx69T4AvIX%2B%2F5JCaDklxiq6v%2FbXHawVP2qnZ%2F560TJccyQFamTnzLjdKIprIMH8YwXcHqGl6blw5xbxhNcZMmGk3kvn89M%2Fd2gWIjO%2BOynjDYgk8dRUAEtuw3ZfQYH4de6jPw3AmrLsHj2sESMoNJPDDOmTJGyHCyYMOhRdkmrVeGrU0R%2BKO7cO3Z6%2BZG2a4b42QZYYEaFc9t%2F13aZTCKtfnVIAuAM1I77jdHu07Q%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>127</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Rabbit Hemorrhagic Disease Virus Type 2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Rabbit Hemorrhagic Disease Virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rabbit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rabbits]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lagomorph]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RHDV2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-capture-the-formation-of-two-new-planets-4000224</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists Capture the Formation of Two New Planets 4000224]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MAUNAKEA, HAWAII — A group of astronomers has successfully captured an image of the birth of two planets orbiting the star PDS 70, according to a report published in The Astronomical Journal.

The team of researchers used an infrared pyramid wavefront sensor for adaptive optics located at the W. M. Keck Observatory in Hawaii to process images of two protoplanets forming from the circumstellar disk of PDS 70.

Using the infrared sensor, the team implemented a new adaptive optics correction technique to interpret image signals taken from PDS 70 multi-planetary system.

This new infrared sensor measures light distortions caused by the Earth's atmosphere.  Sylvain Cetre, a software engineer at Keck Observatory, told Phys.org that the sensor, dramatically improved our ability to study exoplanets, especially those around low-mass stars where planet formation is actively occurring. 4000224]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVAAACZHLJIAPAKEBMCRI7L3GRAB5FC5LVAA3TAEKNKFCWZHANAFMBABK6YAXVC9PW4UCCI4KWQA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/D529372F0983C41910F2F469B3067D17.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684784101&amp;Signature=nPfryopxMQKsEu8NHU2qoVZaPff69GT6FiE5VJWr0At3Uvg2vneJMvkPBHu8KL5U8maCvJ25VWKuORHhqJz3oPDwtiKA7MXU6DUGRN3qefU9XWNX8ICDF6MbqzCW4FFOcjj1jU%2F3rLqpKa%2FGVbmOryRfr77X5%2Fy7sFfYdFQ%2BNujzlkkk3icRATjHqzJkw9MqomL5xlDkOzEIr3Zdq%2BKTZ00mHCH7Ue%2BZQTJverQMoAVCtEYSzL7M%2FY6A1%2BLhTk0HGR6eiu2%2BfVv%2Fp7pXy44JvRuO2OCr65TGULBczkkhchMmkXg9pX3PylilvU4oD0Rmo69oV4L6Wc96cF50AVZqpg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>80</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[pds 70]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pds 70 system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Keck Observatory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ multi-planetary system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ circumstellar disk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dying-schoolboy-gets-married-with-just-months-left-to-live-4000021</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dying Schoolboy Gets Married With Just Months Left To Live 4000021]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INDIANAPOLIS — A schoolboy has married his girlfriend, after finding out he had just months to live. 

18-year-old Chase Smith married his high school girlfriend, Sadie Mills on the 29th of April after being tragically diagnosed with Ewing's Sarcoma, a cancer of the bones, and told he has just months to live. 

According to a GoFundMe page, set up to support Chase's family, he previously battled the disease in 2014 and 2016, only for it to return this year, with the teenager found to have tumors all over his body.

The now-married couple actually attended rival schools, and first met at an ice cream social in 2018 after a swim meet. Chase cooly asked Sadie for her number a year later, and as they say, love's young dream flourished. 

Sadie was won over by Chase's maturity and dedication to her as they often talked about their plans for the future.

They had wanted to attend university together after finishing school, that was until Chase got the harrowing news he had a mere three to five months to live, with or without treatment.

They brought forward their nuptials after getting their parents' blessing and according to the Indy Star, the ceremony was arranged in just four days and held on Sadie's parent's driveway; there, they shared their first kiss as a married couple in the same spot they'd had their very first kiss just six months previously.

Chase said, 'The most important thing in my world at this point is spending time loving and laughing. Just living life to the fullest and loving every moment.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4000021]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6KFMDTWBZDAEBRTBRARV6JAMZES7EC9KIARZGAMARBRKV3VASCAABC5A6WW3VAKFRUDCBCMAJNB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/880F0AFC1BF9877A2AFCA1482C327A3E.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684784101&amp;Signature=hZmO0OWh7iGtPcSDhyLCOejWqGYI8ivZst07YcTGvhB%2Fgyj6FXgekjg28%2BPUtKdY6eTyjlOKyNiUzsNeQQHco0ErZudwQLOX8DxroH1DohMRAE9js6UpF3VqijAuJBWbhPMFL96%2FY5cp4zifAzaqyfwGmJHAnfEx4bMIkEQYbQHURWwEYQw7CDfjHFueedYms85JoRUJyr2Lx37f%2B29XSL%2FjXHW4jnhIowVl88qAGLrkZyF2LJfLnseW7xJLCU1kOFFhHrFmWFLpflawZDO%2BlBGzmw44Tg2tIwLrwo%2BKMWAQ6%2FvnRIfMclEYjzx8EnSHsL1JYeHD5KCZoaeZOPK5OA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>94</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mississippi-governor-pranked-into-saying-harry-azcrac--4000013</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mississippi Governor Pranked Into Saying 'Harry Azcrac' 4000013]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JACKSON, MISSISSIPPI, U.S. — Mississippi Governor, Tate Reeves was pranked into reciting a fake name while reading the names of high school graduates from his alma mater.

The governor had asked people to submit names of high school seniors so that he could read them on his webcast, in lieu of a traditional ceremony because of the coronavirus. 

On the Facebook live session on Saturday, Reeves began reading from the long list of names from Florence High School when he came to a name that one of his staff afterward assumed was submitted as a prank, one 'Harry Azcrac'.

The 45-year-old Republican governor read it, paused for a moment, and then kept going.

Not to be embarrassed by his gaffe, he took to Twitter to get in on the fun saying, 'Harry's submitter has a bright future as a Simpson's writer!' 

He then added, 'In 10 minutes, we'll be honoring more graduates on Facebook Live. Maybe even Ben — the pride of the Dover family.'

The man of the moment, one Thomas DeMartini, took credit for the prank just a few hours after the governor's faux pas, saying, 'Proud moment: I got Tate Reeves to say the name Harry Azcrac on Facebook live. And yes I've been laughing for about 25 minutes now.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4000013]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIFPXAABIDWIAIRBJJA7LURGVDBKUT6A5BRTUZGK2IRMWTTBMKAGVIAKI6WZVZIQN4DEATIB6QA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/C2AFD2DEF537BE225DD6394CE84974E8.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684784101&amp;Signature=xC5NkxfMX1K6NJPviFv3l9eM3xzmmhEMEJf4%2FzhupAyEC88%2BWQ%2BnKRxHKvm5KBVGHtVDV7boPvUbrnY70VLnYSBI9QckhccMuN8LLqfJoP6JA7yRX92Z%2FsdVOuE5CIWkhdS1epODPm75WEHdfBtGjQn3bFlYmDMcqA0h1S0z3ldDRbB9gtbOMKCxQJ68PxTa8J6o%2FUdYR9RDlVAS3SYrMiFXBRYCvW%2B80IyaiBMhMUsfzt%2FgXpVh8BSpS%2BhgvsQiXVUZULpC77f0%2FkVdY%2FCDiyiR5uikQrvu4Kj80RgHZpfyY45WX1obQ0Ee5hY%2BgwAbaFiFOvlrWyG8B8vcyNwe9A%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>145</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/soccer-team-says-sorry-for-sex-dolls-in-stadium-3999958</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Soccer Team Says Sorry For 'Sex Dolls' in Stadium 3999958]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA — FC Seoul have been accused of using sex dolls in leiu of supporers to fill their stadium. 

The team supposedly believed that they were adding to the idea of cardboard cutouts, previously used by baseball teams in Korea to also help with maintaining an atmosphere within the stadium because of the coronavirus.

On Sunday's 1-0 win over Gwangju FC at the Seoul World Cup Stadium, the dolls were dressed in team gear and even wore face masks.

But sers on Twitter were quick to point out that the mannequins were, in fact, sex dolls, however, the club denies these claims but still issued an apology. 

'We are very sorry about the supporting mannequins that were placed during the game on May 17th. These mannequins may have been made to look and feel like real humans but they are not for sexual use — as confirmed by the manufacturer from the beginning.'

Here's the twist, although the club denies the dolls are for sexual acts, they did admit in their statement that the manufacturer of the mannequins, Dalkom reused some of the parts it previously supplied to another company.

The club's statement didn't directly address criticism of why it chose to work with Dalkom, which does, in fact, manufacture sex dolls, or why nearly all the mannequins at the stadium were female in design.

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 3999958]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KIBWACAALEAAIVI7BMBAT7SANBJBTFKRLSKWZFCRAEHFXYZMBMKFIWC5KI6F5WIMQ26GTBZVKMGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/AF958AF8C6CBEE13D2057B8CF0B6C4B7.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684784101&amp;Signature=xdoh1NH3712xshCYsmXP4NI3aRJKMfxpwQ30MPKI4%2Fy%2FtzBeczJ9RwRG1nIJbIn2FsHF9GuXXgt8dZjWzOerGl5o8JtXjcd%2B%2FlF0dDJg9m7oGyjMRPTuegHXun0WcOJeu%2FnBNatYab3E5Y8L7edDa%2F04tUv6Jv4AVy6icpMCIKp%2BSszI1flZ6VzcRahfSW1Tk9kGkYKlTZZ%2B8ePMaX1fCrfy2El9xZXJQ8tM7Xh3en0Digw1G7oSxTwtDLU5MEgaJlUdg6cW5GSOikDyKu6KtMTAX%2FflwZ9nnEiVQhw1w8iDb80I90fgareTJOJmt361lkvvrCrYhWpYErhVZw5ZYA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>118</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/did-we-find-a-parallel-universe--4000675</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Did We Find A Parallel Universe? 4000675]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HONOLULU, HAWAII — A team of scientists discovered unusual signals caused by high-energy neutrinos. Their cause is unknown. 

A team of scientists discovered unusual signals caused by high-energy neutrinos using a radio detector called the Antarctic Impulsive Transient Antenna, or ANITA, according to a study published in The Astrophysical Journal submitted on January 6.

ANITA floats above the Antarctic, suspended above the continent's ice sheets by a helium balloon. ANITA is designed to detect high-energy neutrinos that hit the Antarctic floor and generate radio light.

According to the study, ANITA detected signals that seemed to be caused by extremely high-energy neutrinos behaving in an abnormal way.

Usually high-energy neutrinos come to Earth from space. However, these detections showed the neutrinos were hitting the antenna at abnormal angles which suggests they had traveled through the planet. This may mean that the detections could either be physics beyond the Standard Model or a systematic error.

This abnormal behavior has led media outlets to speculate on whether or not this is evidence of a parallel universe. However, these speculations have not been confirmed. 

Peter Gorham from the University of Hawaii at Manoa, a principal ANITA researcher, told ScienceAlert, We have encountered a small number of anomalies in our data, and once we have exhausted all of the possible explanations within the Standard Model of physics, only then is it time to consider other ideas that push those boundaries — we are really not there yet, certainly not at the point where parallel universes are necessary! 4000675]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMBRIXTSKSQWKBKDLBJW57JAGSKETSKZKIAWPURDKZBRGVZCKMLREYKXA59AVARFF26UCVAZAFPB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/5F9658B9719D4ACC6E688C1074D6BBD8.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684870501&amp;Signature=FzxCFh9bfF3x4aNa0IWjQI7HazRdW5YRlv5BUjYVA%2BN3cu6RD4ITjO5S4jxj8a4jxEWHRyTlfUAjq8%2BLrvpUnzzd0v%2BGRWM8vgkqZdpLpMcmauhl7EBi2FVQrYML2O%2BZsz3PvZDfMCXh%2Fu%2FyptFNDDnYrhj2EMO55FpmDlK29u3%2BfgeV1dfAuATITAeJcVts2h3LRB1kVqZE6WmzQlYXWlXao8TuD%2F%2FqRUHOc7ntAzMMOQwAWOWf3xXyfa9NnqKLL2xMqXh72LfgSVdlzl6GhcqIdENHABsIX3MHBqqJE8T6FDtzg%2BQ%2FQnhERMyCOwz2yeSnWfGCtTij0ontMQzukw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>197</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Parallel universe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anita]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ANtarctic Impulsive Transient Antenna]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-renames-next-gen-space-telescope-after-nancy-roman-4000666</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA Renames Next-Gen Space Telescope After Nancy Roman 4000666]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[Washington — NASA has renamed its next-generation Wide Field Infrared Survey Telescope after Nancy Roman, the agency's first chief astronomer known as the Mother of Hubble. NASA plans to launch the Roman Space Telescope in the mid-2020s.

The Roman Space Telescope has a silvered primary mirror array that is 2.4-meters wide, about the same size as the Hubble's.

The Roman will include the 300-megapixel Wide Field Instrument, which has a field of view 100 times greater than the Hubble's infrared instrument. One image from the Roman will hold as much detail as 100 Hubble images.

In addition, the new telescope will carry the Coronagraph Instrument, a high-contrast imaging and spectroscopy device.

The Roman will survey the Milky Way with the aim of finding around 2,600 exoplanets. Its primary mission will last five years, with another five in a potential extended mission.

NASA also plans to use the Roman Space Telescope to find clues about dark energy, which could yield the key to understanding the expansion of the cosmos. 4000666]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6KRIYIFAJQWEVKHL2LRVL4RMMBSZRCRKWJWVHABABJFEAAHB2DWEWZHKWVWXWAKQJZXKA3IAVGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/EE89B395B12ABB01A110B7A48D22949C.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684870501&amp;Signature=OjAV6myrGVS9rPIAUhU8aW0H8YnhvPOZEuy%2B3XJ4SQ%2Fz0ot2FrxdzhY4PBY1Nq5DvlDMntU%2FP1h2YXetYwAKEoSZ31DjxupS17XWPcfm51VNI2grQovJeZEwWW95%2B6XyPaT90oPUbb4kDeL0ye2nVqI33taM126fX4hFB3%2Bu0I3evvmvUbc7vllrxeEdLcrWAvGK1vAujbZhVTmIFL%2B6RHkysJC8T4KU0VSNOevZZ%2B6xb6rBBq4Nqf%2B%2BpxrB5MqFGJMd5%2BrgYaFnbJMW0a1GETuaFGDXKtScoFDd%2FyydPie4vYzuTolaa9%2F%2BTFk1rHP8I9YUuxKImrS3DQZrh7K3XA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>94</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Nancy Grace Roman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Nancy Grace Roman Space Telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Roman Space Telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hubble Space Telescope]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hubble]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exoplanets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ successor to the Hubble]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark matter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dark energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space exploration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-made-chimera-mice-with-most-ever-human-cells-4000504</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists Made Chimera Mice with Most-Ever Human Cells 4000504]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — Scientists have engineered mice that have up to 4 percent of their body made of human cells, or the highest amount achieved in human-mice chimeras, according to a study in Science Advances.

To create the chimeras, scientists took human stem cells and chemically suppressed a protein called mTOR for three hours. This forces the cells to revert back to the 'naive' state, which enables them to grow inside mice embryos.

As the embryos matured, researchers found the tissues that would become the heart, liver and bone marrow to contain human cells, which were also found in the blood. Science News reports the technology may help scientists to use chimeras as a source for human organs.

Scientists did not detect any trace of human material in the cells that would develop into mice sperm or egg. This eliminates ethical concerns of chimeras capable of reproduction. 4000504]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6LWMC3WAAGRIB3ALNIA56JBGZAB5STZAJPFTHAMBFJWMATUK5IFAAIDAZ6W7BRQQIUGGA3IKWPB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/D4BC26DAAE8A8EF3F80268AF32513C1D.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684870501&amp;Signature=cv%2BjphLtqtCBF4VlEPl0xjZbSdVFB7aVuFsczVZHKOPugLF7PeXtkdAFbFPs39l%2BuF0RAFjvf6%2FtcJzl8GfCEkGJAcAPOwXSwUghM9C6z1PbpzDyq3jbfcI4dQ2eFbsMiS8AQ8%2BcT%2FuvsuZbv807oAfG1tRYGr9V%2BYYYqfblhGvWLs2DEqtht%2Bpu1ty1fqHG98zkGiAk%2F3nRw78AnsXkwU1VNZlLSdK8suj3a8HoK8truAVI8DsqpfZwzUiv0sdT%2BkPQXdAT6fnSsa65GnnC%2BoV3CbNSoiuQAY9CyAkSHTcfW%2Bulq%2B8amke0XErQNtFntLzzgiydclYIsv9YCLCnAw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[chimeras]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chimera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human-mice chimeras]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human-mice chimera]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stem cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ embryo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ embryo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mTOR]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ human organs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medicine]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/-covidiot-pensioner-stuck-on-beach-on-mobility-scooter-4000480</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA['Covidiot' Pensioner Stuck on Beach on Mobility Scooter 4000480]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LANCASHIRE, ENGLAND — A pensioner has been branded a 'covidiot' after driving her mobility scooter onto a beach and then getting stuck, resulting in what has been labeled a 'major rescue operation.' 

The so-far unnamed woman headed out at around 12.20 pm on Wednesday to soak up the sun at Blackpool's North Beach in Lancashire during one of the hottest days of the year, however, a passerby had to call the emergency services when she became stuck in the sand with her two dogs.  

Racing to the scene within 10 minutes, two response vehicles from the beach patrol attended to the matter and dragged her scooter back onto the promenade with their 4x4.

Witness Russ Holt who was at the incident said, 'I couldn't believe my eyes.' 

'As she was driving onto the sand someone tried to stop her and told her she'd get stuck, but she continued anyway.'

He added, 'Her scooter just sunk into the sand and she couldn't get out.'

'Someone called the emergency services and luckily she was quickly pulled off the beach.'

'I know she didn't intend any harm but she clearly is a bit of a covidiot.'

'It seems stupid to put added pressure on what is a voluntary service - especially during lockdown.'

Lastly, he revealed that 'She was laughing and clearly thought it was funny. I'm just pleased she was okay.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4000480]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIWPDCSAZGAGBRVLWLAIKBCMRABXFC5A2LAXTZGBEDRPBZPANBF5WCSKNXF7VZPQW6GTVA6KREA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/71D7060938BCDCFC86AF056624FD72E0.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684870501&amp;Signature=NWksI1NxKGPqxaxk6CGmQER0vP8VjyAW2eyNYZjazAe4nnIZvx1JZcIJM5%2BiFORjrqDV4AyLZJkZtuyd%2Fu1SP8faBIAVmp9fKgLz46cwQ3TcKQOrcTlLOboq1RFiClwipSTui54zaZHbLKwhMwkaDgczhG0PU9XYLrnLH82Dk4KSv64rnZaO2sCiiEHZgLRGn2nuCxtR1t1BwmZdX%2FCbyrqTjusraV90u18VJHUf8aPSA3Ep6nr6665Vh603jfsuw53sAwiffhjKJNnmgMF4WBM1fe5%2F2IHMUkOJYFe%2F%2F32FN6w5Dtf%2FYtmF7f9MTCSeBt89JmIjBFSRUdI8AM0iOQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>89</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/7-eleven-staff-sprays-customer-in-face-with-hand-sanitizer-4000422</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[7-Eleven Staff Sprays Customer in Face With Hand Sanitizer 4000422]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BANGKOK — A 7-Eleven worker was caught on CCTV accidentally spraying a customer in the face with hand sanitizer. 

In the video, the customer walks in with a mask covering her face and advances to get her temperature checked, which is common practice at stores across Thailand.

The member of staff, who is equipped with a face shield, mask, and thermometer then lifts the device up to the customer's forehead, however, she then swaps out her thermometer for the sanitizer and proceeds to spray then the woman in the face. 

The customer recoils holding her face. The member of staff then guides the woman to the back of the store, presumably to administer medical aid.

The video has since gone viral with shrewd Facebook users in Thailand saying it's likely the store clerk was confused and that it was an accident. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4000422]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDWIDZGKAHRAWRRBWKAZKD4MVABIF35LVAWTUZBKICWCVAAANBW5AZHKFYRRBZPQS6UCB3LASPA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/7D16DF673C62DCE5320EFFCA0889BA89.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1684870501&amp;Signature=Zvl2MZ0W%2F7alRVeiWLzppFcWwJDjJEuFLm%2BSD36Di%2BSoLSNPhgHkf5Uqf%2FnAxNqFb4F36%2BxRH63SocA%2FuSRpW8M9LkqrIVAo7ReEaNGeQug1qDQvB%2BzDsug66OHVKBqqjmqqJ3RtiHfPQkr3IVjtyvDkx9mbXvJTFuVlrFuaKLN%2BrPaOxFQxbhkwCKLSBDgWQVVPvyqd7Q20yk2ZMPv868PdPGM20EWjvq3q8fo5uwKjTEcGBZabPjtHOC2UfXtFNKDEc84NNqloTw7CkN02eF%2BBXWUtGwoePiodONsuMKurOrqVmyuGGWOVgI1hhhTVABgTRtFVHJ%2BsC07yxz3kGA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-23T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>111</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-turn-cargo-containers-into-coronavirus-labs-4001529</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists Turn Cargo Containers Into Coronavirus Labs 4001529]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — Researchers from the U.K. have developed the first-ever shipping container lab for COVID-19 testing that features a mobile, low cost, scalable and open-source design.

The lab units are called CONTAIN, according to a preprint study in BioRxive.

Writing in a news release, the paper's sponsor Open Cell Labs states each automated lab is rated Biosafety Level 2 plus as designed and requires just one staff.

The staff logs the barcoded samples before plating them. Then the plates are handed off to OpenTrons OT-2 liquid handling robots for RNA extraction.

Finally, plates from the OT-2 are put into the QuantStuido5 machine for the quantitative polymerase chain reaction test.

Patients take swab tests via a self-closing service window. Open Cell claims that one lab unit can churn out 2,400 tests per day.

Test results are sent electronically via secured protocols that can be integrated for use by governmental health agencies.

The labs could be scaled up by stacking as many as 39 the units together to form a large-scale coronavirus diagnostic center. 4001529]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAAGXTSKFIWAAZWBJIA37DUGMCSTFC6A6IA3HZGKVBFABZCLIKAAWTSKI6WTAIEPS4XIBTLARGB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/DA40F2DACA4FCA6058198620210E00BC.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685129701&amp;Signature=TE6ZfneP0VuTX%2FZW%2FO0t074rsLwKzUI4KV5kcm1Y4U3Au46BE3I%2FbO0HhMOsc5Y%2FfHbunPhBjpUXuY8shl1T0hTsZCN43514oifnAaN93MtHf0AH9hyEI2JT5oDV1ItE9UhdMnUNJ1sgjuyhKI0GISqqU8Xb6qamRGwwFj8FmzBk7xwU8IMwT5Ldi7JTu0taJLlUmH1w1lb0dbf90ZErvvL%2B28MEqVZ0OFH%2Ft7Eo2XLU%2F3%2BejrZG1XlaceJcXa0O4CzqOT00HNE1hXI7YWa%2FIQnik9FbYiorV3HPn%2FrGztNH79JUumxQRGHnV8ltOZos1gRO6sOKuN%2BIadpBhRBzgQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>104</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Coronavirus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ COVID-19]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SARS-CoV-2]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shipping container labs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ COVID-19 tests]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coronavirus tests]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rapid deployment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ low cost]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ scalable]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mobile modular laboratory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ CONTAIN]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ King's College London]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Open Cell Labs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Britain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.K.]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/rats-are-becoming-aggressive-hunters-in-our-absence-4001406</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Rats Are Becoming Aggressive Hunters in Our Absence 4001406]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTA — In a new advisory from the Centers For Disease Control And Prevention, they say that in our absence rats and rodents have become more aggressive while scavenging for food.

The CDC said on its website that, 'Community-wide closures have led to a decrease in food available to rodents, especially in dense commercial areas.' 

They added that 'some jurisdictions have reported an increase in rodent activity as rodents search for new sources of food.'

The advisory continued with, 'Environmental health and rodent control programs may see an increase in service requests related to rodents and reports of unusual or aggressive rodent behavior.'

So, what can we do to defend ourselves from this potential new threat? The CDC urges residents and restaurant owners to seal up holes where hungry rats could get inside and also to clean up any garbage or debris.

Offering official advice, they said 'Follow established guidelines when cleaning up after rodent infestations to prevent exposure to rodent-borne diseases.' 

Because we're confined to our homes, our lack of littering has even forced some urban rats to turn to rodent cannibalism.

Bobby Corrigan, an urban rodentologist, told NBC News last month, 'They're mammals just like you and I, and so when you're really, really hungry, you're not going to act the same — you're going to act very bad, usually.'

'So these rats are fighting with one another, now the adults are killing the young in the nest and cannibalizing the pups.'

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4001406]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJFKC3XAMDRCWIVLACR59DXNFJVRETZAADR5T3TKVBARVRCAJDWGVAAA6WAZBZNFS3DEVR9KIEA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/6C0EDD73D96EEFA0DCFE4EFC659628E7.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685129701&amp;Signature=TgcI4RG6iVAUByR0XZQRfyEcLaz8iJpxt5f4RZkDB5k18irQk85wsgBg3cMZyLb2RUYxli5pdOJgo650xQWwr%2FNVZ6cOIimiQKaThLat%2B4vn1tqeRYdehn7U%2FbOImKOYme6HZiCqpl44Kiu%2Fh5thU0F%2FR6KMSckvcE%2FaPSSCkU7kKqub7ZgIOdBp3QUZ3IJ9lPoYLDgG%2Be%2B6pWpNp1i%2BHWWn4u0Rd9Kfst9ezizKHEP8%2BaVsl4QTWqWL%2Bbom6UB9tDHXJwXdol2NNI07lFW%2FptBJBZy%2BUDKNO%2FhJgvglKg3ltonhWz46UNpkUOeRo6xIDNMk5jDd4ghv84vw%2BILbwA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>117</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/grieving-dog-refuses-to-leave-his-sister-s-body-4001382</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Grieving Dog Refuses to Leave His Sister's Body 4001382]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KINGSVILLE, TEXAS — A dog named Guardian was found abandoned on the side of a road refusing to leave his sister's body when rescuers arrived to bring them to a shelter and provide aid. 

According to a Facebook post by Kingsville Kleberg Health Department Animal Control & Care Center, the animal control officers received a call last Friday morning about a deceased dog near a rural highway.

When they arrived on the scene, responders encountered what they described as a 'heart-wrenching sight.'

The body of the deceased dog was being protected by another dog, a grieving Catahoula mix that has now been given the fitting name, 'Guardian' by staff at the shelter. 

In the post from Friday, the animal center said, 'This boy wasn't going to let anyone mess with his sister. Our animal control officers had a hard time convincing him everything was going to be alright, and they were there to help him.'

But it's good news for Guardian! The center said, 'He's still a little confused about what happened, but at least he is now in a safe place with fresh cool water and belly full of food.'

And in an update post from the center, they say they now already have an adoption scheduled at 8:00 am on the day he becomes available, this week on May 29th.


TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4001382]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNJWMCZJAICACVR7L6KFT72BMNLVTEAIAEAW3GTRKVDFACZNKZIWEVTTKZ9FAYAFF6ZDMB3IB2NB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/C8AF022308E57B538779461B73B51DD0.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685129701&amp;Signature=BTZCgdtbT8GF4eKH%2FO0Y6n3g6VuNFVHEaF1YOHGTkflDFkpAEXV%2FYRf0Sq5CDQWHmEFiHtbOoCWLtRXTHvkJvpeaBqM8rbGW%2B6UHK5aFFm7qK2lgeQ9hMm4Roly%2BAOXEb5i1gnnSaIIZOYkwkkO57EGAyPTLaNlHid6jJjm24sqtxfekbW7mJSzDu6Mht9fDn4Rw%2FemSG71miK3kxSJkwFK1V54eH%2B8iHUcFTFfFoTmlfvT937OZuNsj6zHVw46jYhsBqsYRwOvjdpdH7%2BXjutOmh1tBRqnYTjd7%2F0dp%2FUZ40PS51HbK8fT8EGneUmkiUXMf53c%2FQlrI21PIECO81w%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>80</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/youtube-automatically-deletes-anti-china-comments-4001935</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[YouTube Automatically Deletes Anti-China Comments 4001935]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA — On Wednesday the 13th of May, Jennifer Zeng, a human rights activist posted a video of someone commenting, 'communist bandit' in the comments section on YouTube, and within 15 seconds, it was gone.

Taiwan News, the outlet who reported on this, then typed the term in Chinese characters in the comments section, but this time on a few different YouTube videos and indeed within 15 seconds or thereabouts, the comment had been automatically deleted from the platform.

They claim that it is not clear why YouTube is automatically censoring this word, they also claim that YouTube has recently started to demonetize content that is critical of Xi Jinping's Communist Party and his handling of the Wuhan virus.

We at TomoNews then conducted our own test, and like Taiwan News, our comments were also deleted.

Watch the video above to learn more. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4001935]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNKRPYZJABJWMCRYKEBAV6L4MZCBXS3ZKFLFXHKYKIEAAC3SBSCWGWKRA6UWVAALFS3GGACQAIFA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/2988087FE5F3AC3339081D9F8F03844D.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685216102&amp;Signature=SYZPaP%2Bl7yJL23I8VuyDB2utRBE6JIWMLpkAjhwIISc16JbR5ZoTULainsxs5vY%2F0MdM3CF2ztDiNSwLFEPF7mJJnogqDgMDDecxWh216najSOszSIzx7tPPHEGnLPC3FpdcS1OVIXDFDS%2FNdTqnxXnWHgvCAC455gX%2BNSqiyoRMctC0pMyoPagZ9WYUrTl5M5qwfR270E7vyMuxXaepo%2FsNMz%2FKbu2z89GPbDXLbfrZPcUfDywb%2FsZrBS2OdfjeJ379de%2F4WlujnPjk0bZQnxDPKhMQmwo0Y1C%2FiAL%2BJIB5sqc6%2Bm9dYOWhmTbXVbEQx8jBqtOemdp%2FP4MMOKrcnQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>358</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cosmic-rays-may-be-the-source%0Aof-biological-handedness--4001887</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cosmic Rays May Be the Source
of Biological 'Handedness' 4001887]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA — Interaction between cosmic rays and early life-forms may be responsible for the fundamental property of chirality, or handedness, in biological molecules, according to a study published in The Astrophysical Journal Letters.

Showers of highly energetic, charged particles from the Sun called cosmic rays are constantly bombarding the Earth. When they hit the Earth's atmosphere, they degrade into cascades of elementary particles.

Many organic molecules such as DNA and RNA can be constructed in left-handed and right-handed versions that are mirror images of each other. In the paper, the researchers propose that the prebiotic soup on ancient Earth produced both left and right-handed versions of these nucleic acids.

Co-authors Noemie Globus, an astrophysicist at New York University, and Roger Blandford, professor of physics and of particle physics and astrophysics at Stanford University, argue that when charged particles from cosmic ray cascades reached the Earth's surface, they affected right-handed and left-handed molecules differently, giving an evolutionary advantage to one chirality. Over time this led to life dominated by a single biological handedness. 4001887]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNFMC3UB5BAEBR7BWJRV92CNFKSTRZMK5BWTTAGKFIRKYRQKIQFMVCSKA7RZBK4QIUXRAA5AFQA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/A40DD6B1ECF812E63BB42345196563F0.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685216102&amp;Signature=sb07XGmp0ZmWne2aGrVb%2BVKgKDBrcQ%2BUZkum6siHqJQBgXQA1V081nPmQAlaL6iY8Y5xfwUvHkEVnBPeXwi4lfYSV7ahKEledNYwSBq0V74vHqO4Nxbb9ZOsVK4QuBKosrskHakV1nXUDbDYH3dOV9CF0KvaCVV6Em7jirGhpnf8i7fddJjuMV%2FqatQHZ7vVLy6pdfeT9N9Cx3Fg9LHI80pVhsUiMhsT7uAbT58XGEwcHsS2KSJHwJenq6BIfZS3suk0kBCfQy43DQcSna36tNQe5IXXmRqUkMTfitxVgEhuljsh8rUfAnn%2FlOABxIe7MkjK09eva9LWWazyPruKLA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>182</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[cosmic rays]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chirality]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ left-handed helix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ right-handed helix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ left-handed molecule]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ right-handed molecule]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biological handedness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DNA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RNA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nucleic acid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ evolution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/this-is-why-it-feels-harder-to-wake-up-on-cold-winter-mornings-4001757</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[This Is Why It Feels Harder to Wake Up on Cold Winter Mornings 4001757]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EVANSTON, ILLINOIS — Research done on fruit flies shows that a special batch of neurons sensitive to outer temperatures suppresses other neurons in charge of morning activeness.

A new study published in the journal Current Biology shows scientists have identified a thermometer-like circuit of neurons that inhibits neurons in a fly's brain that activate alertness, particularly in the mornings.

Neurobiologists from Northwestern University found receptors in the fly's antennas that respond to temperatures below around 25 degrees Celsius, or 77 degrees Fahrenheit.

The main recipients of these neurons are another batch of brain neurons. These neurons are part of a larger circuit of brain cells that are in charge of regulating wakefulness and sleep rhythms.

When the circuit of neurons is activated due to a decrease in external temperatures, certain neurons that are normally activated by morning light are shut down. 4001757]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFIWVCCUARHACARSLSIAV7U4GJJSKE34LVARZTKTAAEACVTUKVJF7ACYKV5RRWK2FS2GAA3MKMGA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/02ED538BA061D3ACBBDCCC747921DE04.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685216102&amp;Signature=EmGFfHbk9OLGiAGXjY8%2Fi6ZQd1mjyQ6fmH3jLSJIUUjeALKOtVlRxtGXhU%2FGUlnZs0gcPcT04KlF9qemYoVgtNvMst7M%2B9eDdsryEm1Z954Zo5mbXNkX2cjraeBBwsx9WvnsZWgfShiaFywZUe6DY8yf3uyfUZQLVAsCi%2Fa9WFR6DB21XB0Y33dZHT41cibzZltITddiY98KlB7ppVsWhgaPJY37UDIs3Lp3zJ5lmV2XKN5M0FINoQMKglysLcNf0KeDFAe5nPoveFvR1S103a4GBuUjsN5eSQ8mBpImBK7KsayC6Mb8ypXYb9e60fTnAhg4kVGqX%2FCZIMt7vwlWXw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-27T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[why is it hard to wake up in the morning]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ why is it hard to wake up in winter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ why am i tired in winter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Drosophila melanogaster]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Drosophila]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Northwestern University]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sleep-wake cycle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fruit flies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-navy-ship-shoots-down-drone-with-laser-weapon-4002458</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[U.S. Navy Ship Shoots Down Drone With Laser Weapon 4002458]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PEARL HARBOR, HAWAII — The U.S. Navy shot down an aerial drone with a solid state laser weapon during a test off Pearl Harbor on May 16, according to the Pacific Fleet.

The exercise marked the first shot fired by the Laser Weapon System Demonstrator at sea.

The amphibious dock Portland was selected as a test platform for the experimental weapon.

Naval documents published by The Drive suggest the laser should include power and cooling units, other subsystems, and integration with the Aegis Combat System. 

According to the U.S. Navy Institute, the LWSD represents advancements in laser director and spectral beam combining technology, which combines multiple beams of different wavelengths into a more powerful laser.

Additionally, the Navy is developing other lasers that will be suitable for the fleet's destroyers that lack the energy output for solid state-type weapons.

These lasers would include hard-kill systems as well as less-than-lethal dazzlers that would dissuade approaching boats and disable surveillance platforms. 4002458]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAAMXRCKWIFCYIYLJJRK7USMJKBVFC3AJKF5U3YKNIRCBRNBEJRAYKUKV6WAAK7FS2XPBAZA5AA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/76D5B66C22DF10D19181877726F5C2C4.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685302501&amp;Signature=MIfXLyOVoRc79P72rjVJlWOEv6t2V8WdAq9E%2Fiwn7c1koWzg8YBN4%2FoVjqJApsiXyRIL9PZ7YZVvQtbNa3fj318Cr%2BBa%2BhosXS7N6HgWNYIEZQy02ai5BSUmyZEA%2B4t1z8IqOO4bf6LjSx0kJ5JtODPP4sLuTto%2F3ZxmM43Tx8xW843xnpcccah%2Bg1GjzPpDh101RR7wKC8C%2FHZsCHS%2F4cL68%2FElRs1oVlLHr%2BQrfzjsrrmCtc536AVsjSPrJQFq8mgJZdsAhdQ8LoRgu8%2BUkH%2F77XOjn6seK0FSoD6bZL1joi1mFRvjaISmqVnSz65%2FtfJKwuphBGZYY6iBHamnLg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-28T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>93</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[laser weapon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ directed energy weapon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high energy laser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solid state laser]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Laser Weapon System Demonstrator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LWSD]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SSL-TM]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  Solid State Laser Technology Maturation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Northrop Grumman]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.S.S. Portland]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/asteroid-that-killed-the-dinosaurs-hit-at-deadliest-possible-angle-4002403</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Asteroid That Killed the Dinosaurs Hit at 'Deadliest Possible' Angle 4002403]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[London — Scientists have determined the angle of impact for the asteroid that contributed to the dinosaurs' extinction 66 million years ago, according to a study in Nature Communications.

Writing on behalf of the researchers, Imperial College London says in a news release that the asteroid had struck at the deadliest possible angle for life on Earth.

Using geological data from the Chicxulub crater in Mexico in a computer model, scientists calculated the space rock's angle of attack at 60 degrees.

The asteroid with its steep impact angle reached sulfur, carbonates and water deep in the Earth.

The vapors and debris were flung into the atmosphere and triggered a nuclear winter that wiped out the dinosaurs.

The researchers found asymmetries between the centers of the mountains inside the crater, the crater's physical center point, and the center of uplifted mantle 30 km beneath the surface. 

Scientists then worked backward to model the asteroid's impact. 4002403]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAWKYCUKRBWPDKCBACRRLDRMRBVRRK5A2IRVFKYAVBAIVCTKVIWCB3XKJWRZAIEQITXTWAVKRAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/20F6ACA7F481F03974A13A4EC1BDED8A.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685302501&amp;Signature=bpLZf7yCAyW5t3FZl0Y0M%2BoElBMchXFflAxpAW8Gv4CICZH3q2L60qHcRxeqGbF%2Fa5GGsSuAXHTYTNCxpuMtqoqSeyDRyfHiEbR%2B2go%2Bc1fFWuyAzeNhUgJwY6hUBsgZm32u8uy4reU3dtu6IgXy5fA%2BJzHjFZZHKv0BEJN70eldqHm34ST%2BKsBnAUTfATReb6ayLA5%2F%2Bcx0C2ylFMoX8oWTnB5j0%2B9FdxslTE1jDv0EvX5t73lZkz%2BKmSd1%2F4ppD%2F7tdrXguCiW5xvBt1xEC0UxiMQrAHdck7nSeLhK7L4ANfLG%2F%2BKQ9nwht4n%2FjWbguTqODihX9EcYvP%2B9JMEmwQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-28T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>71</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Dinosaurs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ extinction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ asteroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deadliest possible angle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ impact angle]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Imperial College London]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chicxulub crater]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mexico]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/update-youtube-automatically-deletes-anti-china-comments-4002280</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[UPDATE: YouTube Automatically Deletes Anti-China Comments 4002280]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CALIFORNIA — Last night, we put out a video that tested the claim that YouTube was automatically deleting anti-China comments, and we proved the claim right, they were, and now, YouTube is claiming that it's all just a big misunderstanding. 

A YouTube spokesperson told TechCrunch that the auto-deletions were a result of an error in their enforcement systems, one that the company is supposedly looking into.

The spokesperson added, 'Users can report suspected issues to troubleshoot errors and help us make product improvements.'

TechCrunch claims that according to YouTube, the situation is an accidental side effect of the platform's comment moderation system, which is in place to filter out hate speech, harassment, and spam. 

However, YouTube did not offer any explanation as to how the terms ended up in the automated system.

The report continues saying that with the vast majority of their workforces out of the office, major tech platforms have leaned more heavily on AI moderation methods in recent months, which results in an all too easy excuse of, less human oversight leads to more mistakes. 

With this investigation supposedly underway, we should then see our comments no longer blocked. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4002280]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJWIDRAAZBAKXKFBJKR7LDRMECSTFAMKZDATGKYASIWGVK6KWDWAVIAKFXRXBT2Q6ZGABZ2ANNB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/EABA5EF5F47EAAC81DA3CAD4538024D7.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685302501&amp;Signature=SaL9m6cYON5M0sG9ISwEv%2BXuAqAEunS2G7saYHCKltyBA9G0vWoUJgcIKfd8sJAEAzMvJ3Wse7dtuxweTZ01HaQrhpeSVuA1vaWVH1vQ3UWlCUcMobCgI%2BWldai5iZnsQfjT89Vw1a%2F7lBTaMZr%2BeGGZP16B6Jw4CmyGSjV%2FxXKp02j0tPPBlyf41%2Bknn4royQF75NNBu%2BnI%2FMSlKqZZq0qC3XK7mJKN%2BeFxZNQ2jM6Ssjd%2FF51ESzA8%2FMsDOMWb0VOUmY8nvIuNCUzcFPuWI%2BWwuSkQjOo0P2APukMnuAfxthXPeT%2BlWnqE5EpNnh2uGP9xEBh0RkgL4uRhclAHdA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-28T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>83</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/viral-wild-karen-takes-a-dark-turn-and-calls-911-4002219</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[VIRAL: Wild 'Karen' Takes a 'Dark Turn' and Calls 911 4002219]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MANHATTAN, NEW YORK — 57-year-old, Christian Cooper who was targeted by a so-called 'Karen' in a now-viral clip, says she took a 'dark turn' and called 911 after he simply asked her to follow the rules. 

Posted to Facebook on the 25th of May, Christian shared his encounter with the woman now identified as Amy Cooper who called police to say she was being threatened by an 'African American' man because she didn't like his insistence that she should leash her dog.

Christian, a former Marvel Comics Editor and graduate from Harvard University in 1984, said that before he started filming he had asked her to refrain from allowing her dog to tear through the plantings in the Ramble and that her dog should be on a leash, even referring to a sign. 

Amy then, before he started filming claimed that the dog runs were closed and that her pup needed his exercise, to which Christian replied, 'All you have to do is take him to the other side of the drive, outside the Ramble, and you can let him run off-leash all you want.'

Thanks to the video gaining millions of views, Amy Cooper has since been fired from her job at Franklin Templeton after her company reviewed the incident, saying in a statement, 'Following our internal review of the incident in Central Park yesterday, we have made the decision to terminate the employee involved, effective immediately. We do not tolerate racism of any kind at Franklin Templeton.'

Adding insult to injury, the Central Park South Civic Association President, Michael Fisher has called on the Mayor to impose a lifetime ban on Amy Cooper ever using the park again. 

He said in a statement, 'This disgusting display of intolerance is unacceptable and should never, ever be accepted in the city's public domain like Central Park.'

And furthering her shame, according to the Abandoned Angels Cocker Spaniel Rescue, she 'voluntarily surrendered' her dog on Monday night. 

TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.

Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!
http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories

You Idiot! - People doing stupid things
http://bit.ly/You-Idiot

Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews
http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews

Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day
http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...

Thanks for watching TomoNews!
Like TomoNews on Facebook ►► http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Twitter ►► @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS
Follow us on Instagram ►► @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus
Subscribe to TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews
Watch more TomoNews ►► http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  

Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com
Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj
Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f

Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter 4002219]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRAAPCRGKWIRCCIYBICWT7LRM5AETR34A6KFXGZABBJRXBAIL5QAGBZHKE9A7AK9F5SDKBRZAFNA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/8964F7B4CC03AA004702162333AD06CC.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685302501&amp;Signature=JcULjVqkDbkXo7e1RrznCKaEg9LLRj5C07S%2FNx3S19kPOhPhx9qFOyw7PhfFMukisVXkrweONRPo27krPrPBHaa3MIi5uWLRK8mOBGDinEa6cdRzkMAEMc5kngK1f3zO3VmfhVA9k5Ern98PnH77Dr0elB7OTHORb5XDHQY8o3%2BuL8AJovXF5LjP1rJci0swbfars6CNb7RQ6YpVuwx3wrx%2BjFtzmJQkSIhfhVMpHfp2cVc8hJ8GiT6YF5otruvKh%2B2U7bE%2BTgAOiN8cR2hmoyjfVlTHRx1nmsaNlEFI1xBFetDzng32kKCQNAuIDaN%2BmbynpJT83TdnOw0GTmM7%2BA%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-28T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>238</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/this-galactic-collision-may-have-formed-our-solar-system-4002208</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[This Galactic Collision May Have Formed Our Solar System 4002208]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PARIS — A new study published in the journal Nature Astronomy using data from Gaia, a space observatory from the European Space Agency, shows the effects of the Sagittarius Dwarf Spheroidal Galaxy on the formation of the Milky Way Galaxy.

Due to gravitational forces, the Sagittarius dwarf galaxy crashes time and time again through the Milky Way's disc. One of these collisions occurred roughly at the same time as the formation of our Sun, around 4.7 billion years ago. It is possible this impact contributed to the Sun's creation.

The team of researchers examined luminosities, distances and colors of stars within 6,500 light-years around the Sun and then compared the information with already available stellar evolution models to understand the effects of the crashes.

Data from Gaia showed three periods of increased star formation. There were peaks 5.7 billion years ago, 1.9 billion years ago and 1 billion years ago. These periods coincide with times where the Sagittarius dwarf galaxy is believed to have crashed through the disc of the Milky Way. 4002208]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIRMAIJASIAVAIRLIAAKL4TGIDBRET3KMCA3UZNKJJWIWADLVLW5ACTKNWRRBK2QFZGTWI7KIAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/E67686566F55DF9833D58BD83A9FA629.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685302501&amp;Signature=IL2Q3Hr86XfPl023y9cADItkaqUnP8r%2FUylqHzGF3mXedIS7ZMCyasIuYpHE9LQ7N6GgieowMUjrrI4G5zdMaXVhkQaZNa4hJxYcnPvtw9gzhmgF4MVu7pERb3jG1PvasTEA7uInSe2Cjq7SV5QUZg9kW44K49YCvLW6odMij%2BOhdLSPvjnvSe1nA6tvl%2Box1XFOSZSvnqaH6Wd5P3ZE1aCVFWUleTmzyA9ssuuTMv5JYcQnE%2FDj%2F%2BScBwkHh07BLJ9ix57AwmNkN5ob2OC%2B1bcYlK7t8IJttoPJ0g%2BYZAVTw5d%2BJPpFBCKDll9%2FI359osBL2xhzzJIVMbS%2BD3alrw%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-28T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>96</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Milky Way Galaxy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Milky Way Galaxy's warp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warp]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ galactic collision]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gaia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sagittarius]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sagittarius Dwarf Spheroidal Galaxy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dwarf galaxy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ European Space Agency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ esa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ozone-depletion-may-have-caused-prehistoric-extinction-event-4002836</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ozone Depletion May Have Caused Prehistoric Extinction Event 4002836]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SOUTHAMPTON, ENGLAND — Ozone depletion may have triggered a mass die-off of ancient fish and plants by ultraviolet ray exposure 358 million years ago, according to a new study in Science Advances.

Science Magazine reports the research team took a perfect six-meter-long mudstone drilled core. Preserved in the sample were spores from land plants that had flourished in the Devonian period, when Greenland was part of the Old Redstone Continent.

According to the study, the fossilized spores showed a transition from healthy, normal spores to malformed and blackened spores. The deformities observed strongly suggest the parent plants suffered DNA damage from high levels of ultraviolet-B rays.

The spores dated to the Late Devonian die-off, the second mass extinction in the period that saw the disappearance of many species, including giant armored sharks. The descendants of the surviving bony fish and sharks would populate today's oceans. 

Importantly, the second-wave extinction wiped out the first four-limbed fish that had ventured onto land. This means another group of five-toed tetrapods became the precursor of land animals. 4002836]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJNRPDRIB6KA7CIYBADRVL2CM2KSXFIIAJPAZGZNKMBAAXRDKRIFEV3VLV5WCAAQQERXMBR2AIHA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://fl4e4kle4v6fhmr5ypjtqhz6oc.gcdn.anvato.net/up-image/0DE/BD1/0DEBD16E04A840E89CA0115B213DFD08.jpg?Expires=1685404800&amp;KeyName=mcpkey1&amp;Signature=842AmcH9UuIDQy6pHz5nuAAEc4Y</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>100</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Devonian period]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mass extinction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ die off]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ozone depletion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spores]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uv]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ultraviolet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ DNA damage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UV-B]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ultraviolet-b]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ age of fishes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armored fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ armored shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tetrapod]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tetrapods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Greenland]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ University of Southampton]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ U.K.]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/deep-oceans-will-get-warmer-%0Aeven-in-the-best-case-scenario-4002770</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Deep Oceans Will Get Warmer,
Even in the Best Case Scenario 4002770]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BRISBANE, AUSTRALIA — Earth's oceans could be experiencing rates of climate change seven times higher than levels today by the second half of the century, even if greenhouse gas emissions drop significantly, according to a report published in Nature Climate Change.

A team of international scientists analyzed present and future models of climate velocity. This is the speed at which marine animals would have to move in order to live in waters with certain temperatures as different ocean layers become warmer.

Scientists then used climate models to estimate climate velocity rates today in three different scenarios: One scenario is where greenhouse gas emissions start falling from now; another is in which emissions would begin to fall in the middle of this century; and the final scenario is one where emissions would continue to rise up to 2100.

However, even in the scenario where emissions would start declining now, climate velocity in the ocean's layer that covers from 200 meters deep up to 1 kilometer down — what is known as the mesopelagic layer — would change from about 6 kilometers per decade to 50 kilometers by mid-century. Conversely, in the same period, climate velocity rate would halve on the ocean's surface level.

Anthony Richardson of the University of Queensland and one of the study's authors told The Guardian, 'This means that marine life in the deep ocean will face escalating threats from ocean warming until the end of the century, no matter what we do now.' 4002770]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFKAPYIDABKFZCIUBRBFZ9DVGVES5UT9KNJRTH3RKVARCA3VANDWEV36AE6F3AT4Q22DCBCLASNA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/F1C9723A143666AE322E9E20DB08E3A4.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685388901&amp;Signature=ckvUDYu5QxYOqE6i%2ByXYTLuvblVFghIFrkVKNlUAsJMjcyNxs3YXPlTdZFOwkOuVVNxTlTxwS81xc97wUzpFeInG3U8%2BAS3bKfotFUYvldoxqWh1C7V%2FmrOQQtJWLER1jkH3EleBLXVPDOmxjgKK%2BeP5FSuZYcbPaeL6z2KLOz48dfM2thY0ZPylDzY3UsMxNrO09KWWwVglrU35dLDlBb5koYZWCNjaaX99PCJ%2BN6z%2F7MlG4Cfvb6d3hDEeaHpNchasGJk52ULE6RBPd6%2Fb9ehWW0ZRJky%2FGK%2BAsCVRTrQNRJJ%2FFboC8YluSuiB6oia8Qve%2FBtci6Mq%2BjyiYP1vYQ%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>139</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change in deep oceans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate shift]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warming oceans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ why are the oceans getting warmer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how warm are the oceans getting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[   TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satire]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/the-new-hong-kong-national-security-law-explained-4003084</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[The New Hong Kong National Security Law, Explained 4003084]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BEIJING — Chinese authorities on May 28 bypassed Hong Kong's legislature to approve a national security law that threatens the foundations of the city's freedoms and autonomy. This new law, which will be implemented upon promulgation by Hong Kong's government, forbids acts of sedition, secession and subversion of China's central government.

This new Beijing-backed security plan raises concerns, particularly for pro-democracy activists, Chinese dissidents and journalists who could fall victim to greater extralegal persecution.

The new law could allow authorities to push back or silence pro-democracy lawmakers in the region. In fact, Reuters reports that on May 28, two pro-democracy lawmakers in Hong Kong were removed from the Legislative Council.

Their removal reportedly happened during a meeting where lawmakers were discussing the first amendment to the new law which would make it a criminal offense to insult the Chinese national anthem.

The announcement of this new law has alarmed Hong Kong's population and sparked a new wave of protests. One of the most obvious concerns is the loss of the 'one country, two systems' status.
However, Chinese authorities deny this. According to a report by state-run press agency Xinhuanet published on May 23, The draft decision of the legislation states clearly that China will 'unswervingly, fully and faithfully' implement the principles of 'one country, two systems,' 'the people of Hong Kong governing Hong Kong' and a high degree of autonomy.

The same article, which is written in a Q&A format, goes on to say that law-abiding Hong Kong residents should not fear this new law and that it targets solely those who attempt to split the country, subvert state power, and organize and carry out terrorist activities, as well as foreign and external forces seeking to interfere in Hong Kong's affairs. 4003084]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIWCD3TAVBAIARTL6KF7KD4MNKSTECSK6LWTGADKFKRPWRKK6CFIAAHKFVWAWIKFS6DIAI2AZHA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://nd-vdo-tomonews.storage.googleapis.com/7921184F8B83AAA5F0CB2A6EA60DA27A.jpg?GoogleAccessId=onemcpadmin@anvato-mcp-apps.iam.gserviceaccount.com&amp;Expires=1685475301&amp;Signature=GgO%2FOhrP%2FQUYN5MjiO96bzzUbkzxdXwBtMWnDLet9kIlZG7%2BC2hOoIjh%2FN2a6x%2FbbFdwkY5bYndKbXNAUKtUQqrBdxkAkkcikBWwE%2Bn%2BpslJEYafd5WAPk7%2F4u0YGpyr5h7fzetNdQZG%2BfKVHamIiAi4NcGNvl3Y41J6YtP7S7amdpw6EVr7gyVB8PA5w5PUtijJJK2FfyB2ZYRlQQv6bUOg%2BWY20NDJf3BFz02gMTzJDe6tdSgFURWCQl%2BO9hcPHptGyYpPYzs4BLTQkCE82O7klRqZ69CikYzTksFZ%2BKKjKWDcB8fZsX8fpoyvwJfUGuTJjaAZNwj50DiZF%2BuQPg%3D%3D</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2020-05-30T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>164</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Hong Kong National Security Law Explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ What is the Hong Kong National Security Law]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hk demonstrations]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hong Kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hong Kong protests]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ security law]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hong kong security law]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beijing security law]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china security law]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  National People's Congress]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Article 23]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Article 23 of the Basic Law]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china national anthem]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hong kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mainland china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NPC Standing Committee]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ TomoNews]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
