<?php xml version="1.0"?>
<urlset xmlns="http://www.sitemaps.org/schemas/sitemap/0.9" xmlns:video="http://www.google.com/schemas/sitemap-video/1.1">
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-twitch-copy-bans-live-streaming-of-female-passengers-3686488</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China's Twitch copy bans live streaming of female passengers 3686488]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[KNOCKOFF LAND — Drivers on China's Uber knockoff Didi have been banned from live streaming female passengers on China's Twitch knockoff Huya.
Apparently there's been some public outcry after two creepy Didi drivers posted videos of their female customers — without their knowledge or consent. Ah, how romantic. 
Drivers are banned from live streaming any interaction with passengers such as prying into their privacy or endangering safety while driving, Huya said on its Weibo account. Weibo is China's knockoff Twitter. 
Looks like some Huya users/Didi drivers were live streaming their in-car conversations with female passengers. 
This comes days after another Didi driver admitted to knocking up a female passenger before he knocked her off. 
Looks like Didi drivers have been convicted of at least a dozen sexual assault cases in the past three-and-a-half years according to Chinese public records, so clearly the actual number is MUCH higher. 3686488]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFNWXDKUAAHRCDIVLMDRZ9UYGEDBXFZILSIFPGALABNACBC7BF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6D6/5FA/6D65FAF9C97918B769F21A41D2BD36FC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-08-31T12:56:27+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Huya]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Huya]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China Didi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Didi]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Chinese Didi drivers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Huya live streaming]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/hot-and-humid-weather-can-prevent-body-from-cooling-off-3686484</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Hot and humid weather can prevent body from cooling off 3686484]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMERICA — With 17 states in the eastern U.S. under heat advisories, the hot temperatures along with the high humidity could be a health concern for some.
According to Popular Science, when temperatures are high and the air is humid, the mechanisms the body has to cool down are not as effective.  

Heat energy moves from warmer to cooler places. When outside temperature is cooler, heat leaves the body. But when outside temperatures are higher, heat can't escape as well. 
In high humidity, the air is full of moisture, so sweat takes longer to evaporate.
As the body tries to cool down, blood is sent to the surface of the skin in order to radiate off heat. This pulls water out of the bloodstream and puts them into the sweat glands.
Because of dehydration, less blood is available to transport oxygen to the brain and other internal organs. Circulation is encumbered as well because the blood has less water.   
 
If those conditions maintain and fluids are not replenished, there is a risk of heat exhaustion. 

If someone appears to be confused, or starts to show other neurological symptoms, that is a sign of heat stroke.  

Young children and older people are at higher risk for heat-related illnesses. 

It's important to stay properly hydrated in hot, humid weather. Wear loose-fitting and lightweight clothing. If possible, avoid direct sunlight. Avoid alcoholic and caffeinated drinks, which are dehydrating. 3686484]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANJRGY3SBBLWGDKDLFJFZ94WMMESKERNAIDR3GALAIHACBZBAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C4A/E93/C4AE93AACD91D6D985B1DBE1507ACC2A.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-08-31T12:50:19+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hot temperature]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heat wave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high humidity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heat exhaustion]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ heat stroke]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/kim-jong-un-wants-to-go-bullet-train-fast-3686008</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un wants to go bullet-train fast 3686008]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA — North Korea is exploring the possibility of a bullet train system, reports Reuters.

Pyongyang is hoping to create a high-speed rail network between its cities and across national borders, according to Reuters.

The news agency reports that a senior North Korean official told the French Senate earlier this year they'd like to cooperate with French companies to build the railway.

According to Reuters, when reporters visited the demolition of the Punggye-ri nuclear test site in June the journey took them 12 hours on North Korea's current railroads. South Korea's high speed rail could have made the journey in just 2 and a half hours.

Reuters reports a project like this could be a potential money-spinner but that nuclear-related sanctions on business with the North could pose a challenge. 3686008]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNJFACRJBECAMARTL5DF79JCMRBSRRK9K5AFMGZDAWPREVRDBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/451/AF5/451AF57314E6B2445A3A13C5BADC1F52.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-08-31T03:23:05+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>52</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ high speed rail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ north]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ korea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ HSR]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Asia trains]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bullet trains]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ transportation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mysterious-ghost-ship-found-off-the-coast-of-yangon-myanmar-3687972</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mysterious 'ghost ship' found off the coast of Yangon, Myanmar 3687972]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MYANMAR — Officials are investigating a ship that was found drifting off the coast of Myanmar, reports Fox News.

The ghost ship was discovered by fishermen about 11 kilometers off the coast off Yangon, Myanmar.

Officials say the empty cargo ship, named Sam Rataulangi PB 1600, was being towed by a tugboat, called Independence, to a ship-breaking factory in Bangladesh.

In a Facebook post, the Yangon police said the ship had an Indonesian flag. 

The vessel was also reported to be more than 177 meters long, according to the Marine Traffic website.

According to AFP, the bad weather caused the cables attached to the ship broke as the ship neared the Yangon River. This is when the crew decided to abandon the ship.

Myanmar Navy officials decided to use coastal radar records to track down the approximate location of the two vessels, Fox News reports.

Officials involved in the case are still investigating further, as the ship's last recorded location was reportedly off the coast of Taiwan before appearing in Myanmar waters. 3687972]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6KFKDKWB5ARZBISLWJFR6DSGMBSRRIIAFIAVFCRKMFACCTWKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/922/841/9228413C2C8C91C25E3FBDE7778113F5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-04T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Myanmar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Yangon police]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cargo ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mystery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ghost ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mystery ghost ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Myanmar coast]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cargo ship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ seas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad weather]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tugboat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coastal radar records]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Sam Rataulangi PB 1600 freighter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vessels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ships]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fishermen]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/china-using-robots-to-teach-robotic-kindergartners-3687822</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[China using robots to teach robotic kindergartners 3687822]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — China has introduced robots into the classroom to teach kindergartners to tell stories and apparently to teach kids problem solving. 
According to the AFP, the Keeko robot is 60-centimeters tall and is equipped with tiny wheels and a large screen for a face. It only costs $1,500. 
The robots have been placed in 600 kindergartens around the country. Looks like the plan is to roll it out throughout China eventually and other Southeast Asians countries that are dumb enough to use it. 
When students answer correct questions or complete some challenge, the robot's eyes turn into heart-shaped eyes. Yeah, that novelty isn't going to wear off in a week's time. 
However one of the principals of a kindergarten where Keeko is on trial said it will be sometime time before robots can completely replace humans in the classroom. 
Maybe they should replace the kindergartners with robots too. Think of how fast they would learn. 3687822]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KZDWVCAELRHATA3ABNIFX6BFGJKB5EZIK6PF3TAFAMGRGCABAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B81/3F1/B813F1B86D2957385793B41399FCE09F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-04T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Keeko]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Keeko robot kindergarten]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China robot teaching kindergartners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ robot teachers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China robot teachers]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/85-miles-of-deep-sea-coral-reef-found-off-atlantic-coast-3687727</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[85 miles of deep-sea coral reef found off Atlantic Coast 3687727]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ATLANTIC COAST — Researchers on board the research vessel (RV) Atlantis have discovered a deep-sea coral reef about 160 miles off the coast of Charleston, South Carolina. 
According to HuffPost, a human-operated submersible named Alvin was deployed from the RV Atlantis, and its cameras discovered enormous cold-water coral populations about 0.5 miles below the ocean surface.
Scientists used Alvin to explore the reef and collect coral samples on Aug. 23 and Aug. 24. 

The team found large amounts of Lophelia pertusa, a branching, whitish coral found in cold waters. 
According to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), L. pertusa can survive in deep-seas by using stinging tentacles to stun its prey and guide food into its stomach.  
The corals found by the Atlantis were located about 16 miles to the northwest of corals found earlier in the summer by the NOAA RV Okeanos Explorer. 

The coral-covered area explored by the Okeanos and the Atlantis run for an estimated 85 miles, layered with massive, rocky piles of dead coral likely accumulated over many thousands of years, according to expedition lead scientist Erik Cordes, reported HuffPost. 3687727]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KFGXCVB5DWTARVBRAWTLSAMJKSXET2ABJW5FKRAZAWEBZEAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D57/9CB/D579CB2F005846CEE187225FAF8C5663.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-04T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ deep-sea coral reef]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ RV Atlantis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Lophelia pertusa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ coral]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/arctic-sea-ice-could-be-impacted-by-the-warm-water-underneath-3687711</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Arctic sea ice could be impacted by the warm water underneath 3687711]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — According to a study published in Science Advances, there is warm water trapped under the surface of the Arctic seas that could significantly melt sea ice in the Arctic.

The researchers used old data from ships and new data from probes installed in the Arctic waters to calculate the heat content.

The warm water beneath the Arctic Sea is accumulating rapidly around 50 meters below the Arctic Ocean.

As the sea ice started to melt, the water was exposed to the sun, and heated up.

The Arctic winds then sent the warmer waters to the north, which is where they are trapped beneath the ice pack at present.

Warm water is typically lighter than cold water, causing it to float. 

According to the CBC, the warm water doesn't float in the Arctic because its saltiness makes it sink. 

Instead, the colder, fresh water sits near the sea ice.

However, the researchers warn the trapped hot water has the potential to come to the surface and impact the ice.

The researchers explain this could happen if the waters become so warm, they stop sinking and begin mixing with the cold, fresh water near the sea ice.

The Arctic is already warning at twice the rate of the global average, this would only exacerbate the dire situation in the polar region. 3687711]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2NRPDTVABJR7DRRBBPRZKLVMSJSXUZLKBLFZTCRB6NFEAABAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DAD/DCD/DADDCD0C18218F3032923AC6872BCD34.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-04T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ The Arctic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic sea ice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic sea ice 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ arctic sea ice melting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm water in the arctic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm water trapped underneath surface in the arctic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm-water time bomb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change the arctic]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dolphin-teaches-tail-walking-trick-to-other-dolphins-in-the-wild-3687646</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dolphin teaches tail-walking trick to other dolphins in the wild 3687646]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA — A team of Australian scientists have observed wild dolphins learning a trick from a dolphin, reports The Independent.

The wild dolphins reportedly learned how to tail-walk from a dolphin who had spent time in a dolphinarium.

Billie, the dolphin, was rescued from a creek and sent to a dolphinarium in Adelaide, Australia.

While she was at the dolphinarium, she learned the tricks of the trade by watching the other dolphins.

To perform the trick, dolphins have to rise vertically out of the water and move across the surface using their tails, by either going forward or backward.

When Billie was released into the wild, she began doing this regularly. This is when the other dolphins also started picking up the trick.

The study found about nine wild dolphins performing the trick in 2011, although the total number of performing dolphins have since diminished.

Dr Luke Rendell, co-author of the study, says this gives us a revealing insight into the potential social role of imitation in dolphin communities. 3687646]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAWCYCXLICW3VR7BJJRZ94XGZABVSAKA6PW7UACKBPWEAADBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/588/E73/588E738C39B9874140FDE478064957C2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-04T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[dolphin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dolphin tricks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tail-walking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dolphinarium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild dolphins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dolphin teaching other dolphin tail-walking tricks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ performing dolphins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tricks of the trade]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/almost-90-elephants-found-dead-near-botswana-wildlife-sanctuary-3688716</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Almost 90 elephants found dead near Botswana wildlife sanctuary 3688716]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOTSWANA — The carcasses of 87 elephants have been found near the Okavango Delta wildlife sanctuary in Botswana.

It appears the animals were killed for their tusks, reports the BBC.

Elephants Without Borders, a conservation nonprofit organization, discovered the dead elephants while conducting an aerial survey.

The report says the poachers tried to hide the massacre by concealing the carcasses with drying bushes.

The organization believes the carcasses were poached as the skulls of the elephants were chopped off, presumably to remove the tusks.

Botswana has the largest elephant population in the world, and in the midst of its anti-poaching unit being disarmed, poachers have begun to breach its borders.

According to data from the Great Elephant Census, a third of the elephants in Africa are estimated to have been killed in the last decade alone.

The organization claims the incident is the largest scale of poaching deaths ever seen in Africa. 3688716]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVCAICZHL6LAAD3ELBIWX7LTMMBEZET7A6KWMTZKKJNWXWKTKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7FC/E0F/7FCE0FAF466CF2B740C367934877B80F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Botswana]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[elephants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant carcasses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wildlife sanctuary]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Africa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poaching]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wild animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tusks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ poaching animals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ivory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant population]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant skulls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drying bushes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hunting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hunting wildlife]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurting wildlife]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant census]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant poaching in Africa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant poaching news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant poaching 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ elephant poaching videos]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ocean-cleanup-aims-to-clean-great-pacific-garbage-patch-by-2040-3688411</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ocean Cleanup aims to clean Great Pacific garbage patch by 2040 3688411]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — The Ocean Cleanup, a nonprofit organization, has launched a beta cleanup system to collect plastic from the oceans, reports Forbes.

According to the organization, there are about 1.8 trillion pieces of plastic on the surface of the Great Pacific Garbage Patch, which is located between Hawaii and California.

The organization has come up with a cleanup system, called System 001,which consists of a 600-meter-long floater and a 3-meter-deep skirt to prevent the plastic in the ocean from flowing over it.

System 001 would also take advantage of natural forces such as the wind, ocean currents and waves to propel the system forward and form a U-shape naturally to concentrate plastic in the center.

The cleanup system is also fitted with solar powered-lights, cameras, sensors, satellite antenna along with anti-collision systems.

A support vessel would come by periodically to take out the plastic gathered by the cleanup system, which would then be recycled and turned into products.

This is just the first fleet; the organization eventually plans to launch 60 more fleets in an year or two.

Some researchers worry the system might be harmful for marine life and could trap sea creatures as well, reports Business Insider.

Meanwhile, others worry plastic parts in the ocean might be deeper underwater than the device can reach, and claim it might be a much more complex task to remove such pollutants. 3688411]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAWXXTXLIEWCCRRLWIAV9JFGEABKF3SA6JW7HRDKMGAADAEAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DEB/BEC/DEBBEC633BA3A7FF5F788EF4B760DA7D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>88</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ocean cleanup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ garbage patch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Great Pacific Garbage Patch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ floater]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic in ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beta cleanup system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic parts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pollutants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ polluted oceans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cleaning up the oceans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ going green]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/sonic-microwaves-maybe-giving-us-embassy-workers-headaches-3688397</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Sonic microwaves maybe giving US embassy workers headaches 3688397]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — Research into brain injuries suffered by U.S. diplomatic staff has been linked to suspected energy attacks on embassy workers in China and Cuba.

The brain can perceive microwaves as sounds in a phenomenon known as the Frey effect. Over time, targeted microwave energy could induce head injury.

A microwave weapon, according to the New York Times, could look like a satellite dish and may be handheld or fixed to a variety of transportation. Citing research, the New York Times reports that U.S. diplomatic staff in Cuba experienced intense high-pitched sounds inside their hotel rooms and homes.
 
University of Pennsylvania brain expert Douglas Smith told CNN the injuries are like like a concussion, but without a concussion as patients had no previous head trauma.

A senior U.S. administration official told CNN authorities suspect the injuries were caused by microwave beams, but added that they have no solid evidence. 3688397]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AACFIDCTL5DAPYKFL6KW7LDVGZAS3FZLABJFPFKTAZEATAZQBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F6E/0DE/F6E0DE3023EEE06FFB9E5402842F115F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-05T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microwave energy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microwave]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science and technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ medical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ear]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how sound travels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ headaches]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ migraine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ USA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Cuba]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science explained]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/guy-meets-girl-on-gta-online-3689374</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Guy meets girl on GTA online 3689374]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS SANTOS — A Reddit user Propain58 said he met his partner, SubtleSwing, while playing golf on GTA online, all by accident.  

How did they hit it off? According to Propain58, she dropped in, hit the ball a few feet and he cracked the joke, Talk about a subtleswing.

Prior to meeting up, Propain58 described how they verified that they were each the real deal. He writes that they were open and spoke with each other and each other's families via chat, Skype and phone. 

Propain58 wrote in the thread, It's a bit safer bet when you can actually see the persons face in video and we were both fortunate that the other was willing to do things to prove we're legitimate people. That said a fair bit relied on trust in the other person and fortunately for us it paid off.

Some users on the Reddit thread don't think the encounter is real. They find it all hard to believe, with some reckoning it's a marketing ploy by GTA creators Rockstar. 3689374]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLFACABAVBAKB3FKBKR3LSCM5BEZRC6KRCFTHKYB6NWZBRHKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/427/6F2/4276F2399CA64CA6C57ACC8D139BF653.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-06T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>105</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gaming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rockstar games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ love story]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ computer games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ entertainment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ playstation 4]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ xbox one]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pc games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gaming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ video games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Reddit stories]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/youtube-lets-jake-paul-make-horrible-videos-for-kids-3689345</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[YouTube lets Jake Paul make horrible videos for kids 3689345]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[YOUTUBE — Jake Paul is one of YouTube most famous stars. The problem is he makes horrible videos targeted at little kids.

According to Paul himself, he makes videos specifically for children age 8 to 16, or 18-ish. 
In his videos, Jake constantly plugs his own merchandise. Sometimes he dedicates nearly half of his extremely long videos to buying his stuff. 
According to the Children Television Act of 1990 passed by congress, children's programming may not include commercials for products related to the program, or featuring characters from the program. 
So basically Paul is breaking the law in many of his videos. 
He also tells his young viewers to pester their parents to buy his merchandise. 
Another problem is Paul makes a lot of content this is sexually-charged or highly disturbing to young children.
How much longer will YouTube let this go on? Probably as long as Paul keeps making them ad dollars. 3689345]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVAFMCIHKMCAIWTHKBKFR9UUGVDEZFZIA6JRVGRKKNMR3C3YKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E51/C18/E51C18F41FE189E6F6905C02680262CE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-06T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jake Paul]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jake Paul youtuber]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jake Paul inappropriate content]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jake Paul inappropriate kid videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Jake Paul baby]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-airport-security-trays-contain-more-germs-than-toilets-3689253</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds airport security trays contain more germs than toilets 3689253]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FINLAND — A study published in the BioMed Central Infectious Diseases journal found that plastic airport security trays carry viruses that could cause respiratory infections.

The researchers involved in the study took swab samples of different plastic trays at the Helsinki Airport three times during flu season in 2016.

Four out of eight security tray samples were found contaminated with rhinovirus or adenovirus, both of which cause cold-like symptoms.

The plastic trays were found to contain the highest frequency of respiratory viruses as the trays were recycled quite often and contained different items such as shoes, laptops among other things.

The study also found the viruses on 10% of the surface area tested such as shop payment terminals, staircase rails, as well as passport-checking counters.

The researchers encouraged people to minimize the spread of viruses by hand-washing and coughing into their sleeves.

The researchers also said the airports should offer hand sanitizers to travelers as well as cleaning and disinfecting the security trays more often.

The scientists involved in the study warned that airports could spread disease and create a potential risk-zone. 3689253]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDWCYCXKRBWCWRYLBPAXKDTGSJEZERMKIBW3HKWKWQAVVAAAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/822/7F4/8227F4808D2C37BB60C69F4137221033.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-06T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Airport]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ security]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ airport security trays]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ security bins]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic trays]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ germs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ respiratory viruses]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spread of disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contagious]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study finds airport security trays contain more virus than toilets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travelling]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/argentina-launches-austerity-measures-as-peso-slides-3689210</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Argentina launches austerity measures as peso slides 3689210]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ARGENTINA — Argentina has announced new austerity measures in a bid to stem its current currency crisis.

This comes ahead of receiving a $50 billion loan from the International Monetary Fund.  

In a televised address, President Mauricio Macri said the country could no longer keep spending more than it earned.

Argentina will slash spending and raise export taxes in order to tackle its budget deficit, The Guardian reports.
The president announced taxes on grain exports and other products and said the nation will abolish about half of the government's ministries. 

The administration did not say which ministries would be closed or merged, the BBC reports.
Argentina is the largest exporter of soy meal and soy oil and is also a major producer of corn, wheat and raw soybeans.

Starting on January 1, those exports will be taxed four pesos for every dollar in value, while processed products will be taxed three pesos for every dollar in value.  

The export taxes will be lifted once the economy has stabilized.  
Argentina's goal is to achieve a budget surplus of 1 percent of GDP by 2020. 3689210]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLWIYIHARDFAWKDLRAA5K4XM2LVXRT7KRDWPGCTKSPR7BRBAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B5B/BF4/B5BBF49FDF206A473DFECC5B63A7E312.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-06T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Argentina]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Argentina peso crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Argentina currency crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Argentina austerity measures]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-offering-750k-prize-for-co2-mars-conversion-tech-3689061</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA offering $750k prize for CO2 Mars conversion tech 3689061]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MISSION CONTROL — NASA is offering $750,000 to anyone that can do their job for them.

The space agency is offering cash-prizes to people who can figure out how to convert C02 into other molecules. Engadget reports. NASA will also try to find applications for tech for here on Earth.

According to Yahoo, participants need to register by January 24, 2019 and apply by February 28. The content's first phase will reward $250,000 to five winning plans, and the next will award $750,000 to those with working and usable technology. 3689061]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A5AFAD3WKMBAEVRYLFPRK6LYMZEBVFAKAJPR5URLA5GWZWTVKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/122/32C/12232C462E2D3B9BE49C6967262E22CD.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-06T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space agency]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ make me laugh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ co2 conversion challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satirical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sci & tech]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space stuff]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space stories]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ comedy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ funny]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ haha]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ make me laugh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA mars animation]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-officials-discover-mystery-leak-in-iss-3690192</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Russian officials discover 'mystery leak' in ISS 3690192]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION — Russian officials have discovered a tiny leak at the International Space Station and believe it may have been caused by a human.

The hole was discovered after Russian ground operators registered a dip in pressure levels in the space station, reports NPR.

This led the crew to discover a hole, about two millimeters in diameter, on the inner wall of a Russian spacecraft attached to the International Space Station.

The crew was then immediately instructed by ground operators to seal the hole with tape. They later used an epoxy-based sealant. This temporarily stopped oxygen from leaking from the cabin.

No one onboard was in danger as a result of the leak.

Originally the authorities suspected the hole could have been caused by a meteorite. 

However, they ruled out the possibility after traces of a drill sliding was discovered along the surface.

According to the Russian News Agency, the Russian officials involved said they will find the person responsible for the accident and find out if it was on purpose or by accident. 3690192]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIWXYCTAZAWMVAYLVCW79BHNEEETSTZKJIF3GRAANPAAAZMKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FA3/79A/FA379A0D4927CB1EE6154B308D229FF5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ International Space Station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ leak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hole in international space station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mystery hole]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mystery leak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mystery leak in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technological error]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drilling marks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drill]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meteorite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oxygen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cabin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sealant]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/how-banned-poison-made-its-way-inside-britain-3690186</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[How BANNED poison made its way inside Britain 3690186]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LONDON — British Prime Minister Theresa May has outlined how two Russian suspects smuggled Novichok poison into the UK as part of an assassination plot.

May told British lawmakers Wednesday how Russian nationals traveled to the UK using the aliases Alexander Petrov and Ruslan Boshirov. Both have been charged in the attempted murders of ex-Russian spy Sergei Skirpal, and two others.

The men managed are believed to have smuggled Novichok inside a perfume bottle, then traveled to the UK where authorities suspected the hatched the assassination plot. 3690186]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KACFPYACKMGWMBA7KBKW79BHGWLS3RT2LSLWRGIDASQWCBRIAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0A7/328/0A7328C29178070C2CFF9434EEDE8EBE.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ britain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ russia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ parliament]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sergei skirpal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemicals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemical]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ travel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Uk and Russia]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/homeless-vet-sues-couple-who-started-400k-gofundme-3690103</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Homeless vet sues couple who started $400K GoFundMe 3690103]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PHILADELPHIA — Last year, a viral GoFundMe campaign started by a New Jersey couple who raised $400,000 for homeless vet Johnny Bobbitt is apparently all gone. 
According to NJ.com, pro-bono lawyers for Bobbitt filed suit against Kate McClure and her boyfriend Mark D'Amico, alleging they were withholding the money raised to get the vet back on his feet.

Bobbitt claims the couple spent the money on lavish trips and extravagant purchases. The couple claims they didn't give all the money to Bobbitt because he would have just blown it on drugs.  

According to the Associated Press, GoFundMe says they are now working with law enforcement to make sure Bobbitt gets all the money that was raised for him. 

Bobbit's lawyer told the Philadelphia Inquirer on Tuesday that he learned the money was all gone in a call with lawyers for Kate McClure and her boyfriend Mark D'Amico. 

McClure and D'Amico started the GoFundMe page for Bobbitt in November 2017 after McClure ran out of gas on I-95 near Philadelphia and Bobbitt gave her his last 20 bucks for gas money. 

A judge has now ordered the couple to appear in court to explain where and how all the money was spent. 3690103]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWKRMDIHAJPAPWZWL6IA574RGEESKET9KEAAVT3XKREFKAKUAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9EE/857/9EE8578FB847D1E245779DA916AA0743.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>77</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GoFundMe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Johnny Bobbitt GoFundMe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ homeless man GoFundMe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ GoFundMe dispute]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kate McClure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mark D'Amico]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/synthetic-bacteria-could-help-cure-rare-diseases-3690088</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Synthetic bacteria could help cure rare diseases 3690088]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MASSACHUSETTS — Researchers have reached an important milestone in synthetic biology by carrying out successful trials on a group of volunteers in order to help treat people who suffer from phenylketonuria.
The genetically engineered probiotic developed by Synlogic could become the first synthetic biology-based medical treatment to be approved by the Food and Drug Administration, according the New York Times. 
People who suffer from phenylketonuria, or PKU, must avoid dietary protein in foods like meat and cheese, because their bodies cannot break down the amino acid phenylalanine, or Phe. 
The study, published on August 13 in Nature Biotechnology, showed that the probiotic can significantly lower Phe levels in both mouse models of PKU and in healthy monkeys, according to The Scientist. 

The treatment is called SYNB1618 and is a modified version of the probiotic Escherichia coli Nissle. 
Researchers say treatment with SYNB1618 is a two-step process. The first step is to get patients' blood Phe under control. The second step is to relax the diet and slowly add natural protein into their diet. 3690088]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LJKFKDZIAMHRKAKEBWKR56BHMEDSZERMK5AR5HRHB5FWCWK6BG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>http://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/83C/BB4/83CBB4D64B3D6DA3A94FEC785EE99D3F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ synthetic biology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ genetically modified bacterium]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ modified probiotic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phenylketonuria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phenylalanine]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/more-syrian-regime-channels-on-youtube-despite-u-s-sanctions-3689983</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[More Syrian regime channels on YouTube despite U.S. sanctions 3689983]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA — Syrian government and state-affiliated channels are still appearing on YouTube.

It's been over two weeks since a TomoNews investigation showed how Syrian President Bashar Al-Assad's official channel was getting advertising from some of the world's biggest brands — including the U.S. President himself.

And yet, despite YouTube terminating the channels we reported about, we've found even more. Why is that a problem?

U.S. sanctions prohibit American companies from providing services to Syria without obtaining a license from the Treasury Department. 3689983]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZARPYKVK2PWPBAWLVAAI9JHMMDVRE36AWPF5GCTB5EF3CRJAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/308/228/308228ACC6A8217FF3E15AA64B42EF70.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>112</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[youtube]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[syria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[youtube advertising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[bashar al assad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[adpocalypse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[refugee crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[programmatic ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[advertisements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[content creators]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[international affairs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[alphabet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/syria-s-mad-syria-ous-about-their-youtube-channels-3689980</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Syria's mad Syria-ous about their YouTube channels 3689980]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA — TomoNews has found yet more channels linked to or affiliated with the Syrian government are on YouTube. 

And this could be a problem for the Alphabet-owned platform. U.S. sanctions prohibit American companies from providing services to Syria without obtaining a license from the Treasury Department.

Several of the channels found are linked to the General Organization Of Radio and TV - Syria, or ORTAS for short. ORTAS is specifically listed on the U.S. Treasury Department's list of Specially Designated Nationals and Blocked Persons.

Now, to be clear, just because we didn't see ads on some of the following channels doesn't mean there are none. It also doesn't mean Syria's getting a cut, but YouTube is. 3689980]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANLWMXTSAAGFAWKDBRCRR9SGGSJEXU33K5BWVUADKBNAXXAQAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EB0/C80/EB0C80D1C48034A789A1B46BB6EA9333.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>226</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[youtube]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[syria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[youtube advertising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[bashar al assad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[adpocalypse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[refugee crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[programmatic ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[advertisements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[content creators]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[international affairs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[alphabet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/syria-s-addounia-tv-should-not-be-on-youtube-but-it-is--3689977</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Syria's Addounia TV should not be on YouTube (but it is) 3689977]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA — Syrian TV channel, Addounia TV is reportedly a privately owned Syrian government mouthpiece. 

A company by the same name is mentioned on the U.S. sanctions list and they're displaying ads. 

Their website: www.addounia.tv has a YouTube link, but it connects to an error page.
The website also connects to a Facebook page. and that page, like many others, has a YouTube section. 

Videos in the YouTube section there shows the same AddouniaTV channel content and has the same YouTube handle. Also the videos on the page's YouTube section take you directly to the AddouniaTV YouTube channel.

And when we used a VPN from the U.S. to watch that channel, we found that some videos like this one were displaying ads on some content.  And why might that be bad?

Previously, in 2011, the EU and Australia sanctioned Addounia TV for inciting violence against Syrian civilians. 3689977]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBJAPAICAWPRXAZYBWIFX7DWMMCB7R3ZAJIR5UZBKAHW3XAFBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/175/ABD/175ABDE79F77D59449EB4C679B012508.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>90</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[addounia tv]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[youtube]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[syria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[youtube advertising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[bashar al assad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[adpocalypse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[refugee crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[programmatic ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[advertisements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[content creators]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[international affairs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[alphabet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/girl-contracts-deadly-infection-after-trying-on-new-shoes-3689749</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Girl contracts deadly infection after trying on new shoes 3689749]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM — A 4-year-old girl is recovering after contracting sepsis from trying on new shoes without socks. 
According to the Sun, Sienna Rasul became really sick the day after trying on a several new shoes with bare feet. 
Doctors think the bacteria may have been in the shoes. Sepsis can develop if bacteria enters the body through an open wound. 

According to the Mayo Clinic, sepsis occurs when chemicals released into the bloodstream to fight infection trigger an inflammatory response throughout the body. 
Physicians believe Sienna may have had a cut or wound on her foot that let the bacteria in.
Little Sienna spent five days on an antibiotic drip in the hospital with her mom by her side. 
Luckily she's out of the woods and has been allowed to go home, but is still being monitored. 3689749]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFEX3TKEEFCV3EKFPAILU4GVEBXU39KBLW3U3TKVHARWTSLE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CA8/5CF/CA85CFA863903C758367051F38EE0F7F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-07T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sepsis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ girl contracts sepsis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new shoes no socks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new shoes bare feet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sepsis infection]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/police-release-sketch-of-suspect-but-something-smells-funny-3690917</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Police release sketch of suspect, but something smells funny 3690917]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PERTH, AUSTRALIA — Something smells fishy about a computer-aided sketch of a suspect shared by Western Australia Police. We can't exactly put our nose on it, but something's snot right.
Officers say a 17-year-old boy was just trying to keep his nose clean while walking through a suburb around 5 p.m. last Friday, when the suspect and his partner in crime robbed him.   
According to the Metro UK, authorities blew the photo out over social media so see if the public could help pick out noseless suspect, but found a bunch boogers instead.  
Two of funniest comments were probably, I hope somebody nose something that can help, and this gem, Surely somebody nose this man. 
Police didn't mention why the sketch was missing a nose, but they may want to think about sinusing up a new sketch artist. 3690917]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJFMXRBAEGFEWTEBSPWX7LTNFJB3ERLAADWVHZHANPRAAAJBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EA7/59D/EA759D622E0A6909D58700A59C026899.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-08T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police sketch]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man no nose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ suspect no nose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police sketch no nose]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ police e-fit no nose]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-why-you-could-have-black-hair-on-your-tongue-3690861</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here's why you could have 'black 'hair on your tongue 3690861]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS, MISSOURI — A 55-year-old woman developed a case of black hairy tongue after taking an antibiotic for an infected wound.
The case was published by Dr. Yasir Hamad, an assistant professor in the Department of Medicine at the Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, in the New England Journal of Medicine on Wednesday, according to CNN. 
The condition refers to when papillae on the tongue grow longer than normal and turn black.

Papillae are normally less than a millimeter long, but can grow to between 12 and 18 millimeters in length in patients suffering from the condition. 
The blackening occurs as the growing papillae trap microscopic food particles that allow bacteria and other microbes to flourish on the tongue. 
Black hairy tongue is an uncommon and harmless side effect of some drugs, but can also be caused by smoking, bad oral hygiene and some medical conditions. 
In this case, the woman was taking minocycline to treat a wound infection from a car accident. Within a week, her tongue turned black, she started feeling nauseous and developed a foul taste in her mouth. 
Four weeks after doctors changed her medication, her tongue turned back to its normal color. 3690861]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNIAMDIJANPAKWIULZDR39D4GVBVZRT4KIDFTFKSKRHRCYCVKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1E2/A36/1E2A363226CC59AD88B856660E36DB13.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-08T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hairy tongue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hair on tongue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ papillae]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hairy tongue symptoms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ black hairy tongue causes]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/icymi-bashar-al-assad-hearts-u-s-social-media-3690701</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[ICYMI, Bashar Al-Assad hearts U.S. social media 3690701]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SILICON VALLEY — U.S. companies are providing services to Syrian President Bashar al-Assad on social media.

As we've said before, U.S. Treasury sanctions, specifically Executive Order 13582 prohibit American companies from providing services to Syria without obtaining a license from the Treasury Department. Do they have a license? We don't know. They may well have. If they don't,  they could be breaking U.S. law.

Bashar al-Assad's propaganda channel was removed from YouTube not long after we reported on it last month. 

Yesterday our further reporting Syrian government and media appearing on the platform garnered no comment from the U.S. government or Google, YouTube's parent company.

The Syrian dictator has accounts on U.S. sites Instagram, Facebook and Twitter. Syria's Permanent Mission for the United Nations links to Assad's Facebook and Twitter accounts — not to mention that now dead YouTube account and that Facebook page, links to the Assad on the Instagram. 3690701]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LIAWXDZIKIARPVATBNKRK9UWMSKS3UT4A5DATHRHAMHAEBADAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/617/54B/61754B760721D3C825AE42052DB5C35B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-08T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>89</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ youtube]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ youtube advertising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bashar al assad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ adpocalypse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ refugee crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ programmatic ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ advertisements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ content creators]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ international affairs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alphabet]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/thousands-of-fish-dead-as-red-tide-plagues-florida-coast-3692488</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[THOUSANDS of fish dead as Red Tide plagues Florida coast 3692488]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TAMPA BAY AREA, FLORIDA — Toxic algae has wiped out droves of south west Florida's marine life.

According to the National Ocean and Atmospheric Administration, red tide algal blooms can produce neurotoxins which are lethal to fish.

A red tide bloom 150 miles long was observed last month in South West Florida. It reportedly reached the Tampa Bay area over the weekend. The algae can also cause hypoxia to fish via oxygen depletion in water. It is deadly to birds, turtles, manatees and dolphins.

Red tide can be harmful to humans if the neurotoxins become airborne, or by eating infected shellfish. Symptoms of infection can include coughing and irritated eyes, although individuals with respiratory conditions may suffer more serious problems. 3692488]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJJACYIAASLFMDKEB5AA39LWM2KB7ET4K2JF3UREAVGAAWK2BB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/078/A63/078A63227CB5F277EC15313AE314CE30.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>53</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ red tide]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ red tide florida]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ red tide florida 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic algae]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ red tide algae]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science explained]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tampa bay]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tampa bay area]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-say-wind-and-solar-farms-could-transform-sahara-3692354</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Researchers say wind and solar farms could transform Sahara 3692354]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Scientists say installing massive wind and solar farms across the Sahara Desert could affect the weather. 

According to a paper published in the journal Science, the wind turbines could help to double the amount of rain in the region.

The researchers say the wind turbines would work to mix warmer air from above and cooler air from below to create a feedback loop which would increase precipitation and vegetation growth.

The large solar panel farms would absorb a larger percentage of the sunlight in the area, leading to cooler temperatures.

The researchers also believe, the energy generated from the wind and solar farms could meet global energy demands.

According to the author of the study, the plan could help agriculture, economic development and social well-being in the Sahara … and other nearby regions. 3692354]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AAAWKACTK5BAXAAXBVCWXLDUGVCSTETRAJIAXHTTAMHWGW3UKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/35E/EE8/35EEE85518B610DEA5B0D5E39B3D6292.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind farms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar farms]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the Sahara desert]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ desert]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ solar panels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wind turbines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weather]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ temperature]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ green the Sahara]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the Sahara desert was once green]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sunlight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ warm air cool air]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vegetation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ agriculture]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ transforming the Sahara]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/snapping-too-many-selfies-might-lead-to-a-wrist-injury-3692332</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Snapping too many selfies might lead to a wrist injury 3692332]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — With social media is taking over people's' lives, here's another thing to worry about — selfie-induced wrist injuries, also known as a selfie wrist.

The news comes after reality show star Kim Kardashian West was ordered to stop taking selfies by her doctor.

According to a study in the Irish Medical Journal, a selfie wrist often occurs when the distal radius is accidently fractured.

The researchers found that people often compromise their sense of space when their trying to take the perfect selfie, leading people to concentrate on their smartphones rather than their surroundings.

In more extreme cases, the injury could lead to trauma and or hospitalization.

In the study, the researchers noted the importance of educating society of the risks associated with taking selfies in order to reduce selfie-related injuries. 3692332]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVAFGYZHKZCFIBARL6IWR9JBMSKSRR34KNIFMTZHAEGFIARDKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/45A/3F3/45A3F3B2FEFF37453F0428A721894561.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Selfie wrist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim kardashian]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ taking a selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ snapping selfies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dangerous]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ doctor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wrist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wrist injury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie-induced wrist injuries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ distal radius]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smartphones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social media]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hospitalization]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ injured wrists]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/parents-warned-selfies-can-increase-head-lice-outbreaks-3692321</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Parents warned selfies can increase head lice outbreaks 3692321]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MURICA — In the United States alone head lice causes around six to 12 million infestations a year in children between the ages of three and 11. 

According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, head lice is primarily spread by direct contact with the hair of an infected person. 

The most common way to get head lice is through head-to-head contact at places like school, home and outdoor sports or camp activities. 
Lice can also be spread when sharing personal care items like combs, brushes, towels and hats. 
According to the CDC, head lice should be treated with a pediculicide, a medication that kills head lice, that has an ovicidal effect meant to kill head lice eggs. 3692321]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEARMXRDK6IWCAKDL5AF7LSGM5DSZEAIAWKFXHZAANQRVBTRBA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/03A/FAB/03AFAB329F2507CFB0255EBC22AE80B7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ head lice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ head lice outbreak]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lice]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lice prevention]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lice treatment]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/us-gov-responds-to-tomo-on-syria-yet-more-youtube-channels-gone-3692230</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[US gov responds to Tomo on Syria, yet more YouTube channels gone 3692230]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[YouTube removed multiple Syria news channels — including some listed on the U.S. Treasury Department sanctions list — following a series of TomoNews reports last week on the Assad regime's use of U.S. social media platforms.  

We reached out to Google, YouTube's parent company, and the U.S. Treasury Department for comment before we published. They didn't come back to us by press time, but on Friday the Treasury did.

Treasury does not comment on investigations or possible enforcement actions, including to confirm whether one exists, a Treasury Department spokesperson told TomoNews in an emailed statement. However, generally speaking, U.S. persons are prohibited from engaging in most transactions involving Syria or the government of Syria unless authorized or exempt.

Google have yet to reply to our request for comment. 3692230]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMARADABK6LRPDI9LMBFXLUUNBIERFZNKMCAXGZAAZFRKAAFKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4D8/EE2/4D8EE22602313B8CCA526704ED6D95A6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-11T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>109</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ youtube]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria sanctions 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  syria news channels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ youtube advertising]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bashar al assad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ adpocalypse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ refugee crisis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ programmatic ads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ advertisements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ content creators]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ international affairs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alphabet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria sanctions 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria sanctions us]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria sanctions summary]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-has-gigantic-61-pound-tumor-removed-from-uterus-3692902</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman has gigantic 61-pound tumor removed from uterus 3692902]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE — A 53-year-old woman had a 61-pound tumor successfully removed from her uterus. 

According to News.com.au, Singaporean doctors removed the giant uterine fibroid, tumors that gradually grow in the uterus if left untreated. 
The massive tumor weighed a whopping 61-pounds and was 25 inches long. The woman also lost 1.8 gallons of blood during the operation. 
According to the case report which was published in the British Medical Journal, the woman had reported trouble breathing when she moved and when she was laying down for about six months. 
Doctors removed her uterus during the procedure and plastic surgeons then reconstructed her abdominal wall, which had been slightly damaged during the removal. 3692902]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2KWMD3VA5AAAAITBWLFR7SCMZBSKE3ZLWJFMHIKK5HAVYIJAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/354/132/3541326F811304B68BAEE3F773F3CE9B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>49</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tumor removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant uterine fibroid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant uterine fibroid removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ successful tumor removal]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mary-and-jesus-given-god-awful-spanish-restoration-3692889</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mary and Jesus given god awful Spanish restoration 3692889]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[RANADORIO, SPAIN — It appears the hand of god has blessed an amatuer painter with the gift of restoration in Spain after she colorfully touched up three 15-Century statues. 
The wooden statues of the Virgin Mary and Jesus, the Virgin and Jesus with St. Anne and St. Peter at a small church in Rañadorio were given quite a divine makeover, The Guardian reports.
Apparently, one of the local residents thought the statues looked a bit drab, so she got permission from the parish priest to have a crack at them over the summer.
Local shopkeeper María Luisa Menéndez told publication El Comercio, I'm not a professional painter, but I've always enjoyed it, and these images really were in need of painting. 
Okay, maybe Menéndez might have gotten a bit carried away, but it's probably historically accurate that the Virgin Mary had turquoise hair. 
Experts aren't sure if the colorful paint can be removed, and the original polychrome paint recovered, the New York Times reports. 3692889]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIWGYCTAMCWGV3CKEBA39DSMZCV5FCZLWLWTGABANPRGYIIBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6B7/2F8/6B72F89AA0B07E2050B1ECBB4F5CF862.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ restoration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ restoration fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spanish restoration fail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mary and jesus restoration]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mary jesus statue restoration botched]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/student-develops-skin-cancer-from-biting-her-nails-3692870</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Student develops skin cancer from biting her nails 3692870]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA —  A woman in Australia had to have her thumb amputated because biting her nails caused her to develop skin cancer, The Sun reported.

Courtney Whithorn, 20, says she developed the bad habit at the age of 16 when she was bullied in high school.

She said she noticed her thumb nail started turning black, but she hid it from family and friends.

She was also self-conscious about it, and chose to use fake nails to hide the condition.

Whithorn finally went to the doctor, which is when she was diagnosed with acral lentiginous subungual melanoma.

That is a malignant melanoma that is a rare form of skin cancer.

Whithorn has now undergone four surgeries to treat the cancer, with the most recent one resulting in the amputation of her thumb. 3692870]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAWMAICKMAA5WAVBABA5K4SMRESISKSAACA5H3RKAAWGDIHAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/74B/C71/74BC71D743049E318B4781E96FBB0030.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>55</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ student]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin cancer nail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thumb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amputated]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ habit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biting nails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acral lentiginous subungual melanoma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malignant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgeries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thumb nail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake nails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thumb nail turning black]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman has thumb amputated after rare skin cancer forms from biting nails]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-researchers-to-develop-elevator-to-space-3692844</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Japanese researchers to develop elevator to space 3692844]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JAPAN — A team of researchers from Shizuoka University plan to develop a miniature space elevator to connect Earth and the International Space Station with a cable.

According to The Mainichi Shumbun, the researchers plan to develop an approximately 10-meter-long high-strength steel cable, with carbon nanotube being considered to be used as the primary material.

They also plan to release a pair of satellites that would connect with the cable, and would measure around 10 centimeters on each side.

The space elevator would be made up of six oval-shaped cars, which would be about 18 meters long and 7.2 meters wide.

A camera would also be attached to the satellites which would record the elevator as it moves in space.

The researchers expect the elevator to travel up to 200 kilometers per hour and carry people as well as cargo shipments into space by 2050.

However, the researchers worry there might be problems such as the elevator colliding with space debris, meteorites or even the transmission of electricity from earth to space. 3692844]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARDRPD3XKWIRACZ7KFLA77JCMEBEXFINK2PWTHZAAIEWCX3XAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DBE/EB8/DBEEB816987FADD2C650695E1A76E0B4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-12T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Japan]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Space elevator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ future]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ future travel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ traveling in space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ outer space]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ International Space Station]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cargo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ carbon nanotube]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cable]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ satellites]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/backward-leg-allows-young-cancer-patient-to-dance-again-3693779</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Backward leg allows young cancer patient to dance again 3693779]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[STONYBROOK, NEW YORK — A young cancer survivor is still able to dance thanks to an innovative surgery. 
Delaney Unger, 12, was diagnosed with osteosarcoma of the left knee in 2016, which would require chemotherapy and amputation of her knee, according to CNN. 
Because of the location of her Unger's cancer, doctors were able to perform a rare procedure called a rotationplasty. 

During a 13 hours surgery in April of 2017, she had her left knee completely amputated. 
Surgeons then took Unger's ankle and foot, rotated them 180 degrees and attached them to the stump of her thigh, according to Newsday. 
This allowed her ankle to function as a knee. 
In October of 2017, Unger received a prosthetic which fits over the backward-oriented foot and extends up the thigh. The prosthesis lets her walk, jump and dance. 3693779]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLWCDIHAMFRZCRXLVDWR7D4NAEB5SAIKBJF5FIABZGRMAZQBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/00B/2A5/00B2A5D8F00B03A1358BB9C775C94B24.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-13T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ osteosarcoma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rotationplasty]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ prosthetic limbs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ knee replacement]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-probiotics-have-little-or-no-effect-inside-the-body-3693625</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds probiotics have little or no effect inside the body 3693625]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ISRAEL — According to a study published in the journal Cell, probiotics were found to have little or no effect inside the body.

The researchers created their own probiotic cocktail by using 11 bacteria such as Lactobacillus and Bifidobacteria to test how well probiotics would colonize a healthy intestine.

Half of the participants were given the 'probiotic cocktail while the other half were given a placebo.

In about half the cases, the probiotic went in and came out the other end, without doing anything for the body.

In the other half, the probiotic stayed for a while before being eventually crowded out by the microbes already in the body.

Dr. Eran Elinav, a researcher involved with the study, told the BBC, in the future probiotics would need to be tailored to the needs of individual patients.

The study was conducted with a small group of participants, and needs further studies to confirm the results. 3693625]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFJFCCRDAZFRXW3HBNIW5LURGJKERSANLRDR3HZHKRHWCDRLKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/506/95F/50695FF03EC51ABC24F6AFA54AB41E16.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-13T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Israel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ probiotics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ yogurts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ good bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gut]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ intestine]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ off-the-shelf probiotic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ probiotic foods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ probiotics and healthy gut bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ probiotics bad]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ probiotics bad for you]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/utah-drops-fish-from-planes-to-restock-lakes-in-remote-areas-3693568</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Utah drops fish from planes to restock lakes in remote areas 3693568]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UTAH — Wildlife officials in Utah have been restocking remote lakes in the mountain by dropping fish from airplanes, reports Live Science.

On Twitter, wildlife officials explained the lakes are being stocked to provide fishing opportunities for the public.

Officials say the fish used are usually only about 3 centimeters to 7 centimeters long and are used to restock more than 200 lakes in the state every year.

Officials claim about 95% of the fish are expected to survive the drop because of their small size.

Previous methods included using milk cans to store the fish and loading it onto animals such as horses to reach remote areas, CNN reports.

However, officials say they have been using this method since 1956 and claims it is less stressful on the fish than the previous method used. 

The previous method of transporting the fish by ground also reportedly took a lot longer than the current method. 3693568]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ARAFGD3XKRER5BAXLRAFT6DVGEBB3RT9K2JW3G3XASMAEDAALG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/287/04C/28704C12BE05FFF6910E76A5688C529C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-13T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Utah]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lakes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wildlife]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fishes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ utah fish stocking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish utah]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish utah lake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish dropped out of planes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aerial fish stocking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fishing opportunities]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ remote lakes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fishing in Utah]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-patent-shows-employees-in-cage-on-top-of-a-robot-3694333</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon patent shows employees in cage on top of a robot 3694333]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Amazon patented a human machine transport system that pairs up humans and machines. 
According to the Seattle Times, illustrations that go with the patent, which was granted by the U.S. Patent and Trademark office in 2016, show a cage-like enclosure around a work space positioned on top of a robotic trolley. 
The company says it does not intend to use the technology, but said it was designed to allow humans to enter robot-only zones in Amazon's automated warehouses to make repairs or retrieve dropped objects. 

Amazon also said the system could be used to cut across an off-limits work space to reach a restroom. 

The reference to the cage transport system appears in a case study of the systems that make up Amazon's Echo ecosystem by Kate Crawford and Vladan Joler published on September 7. 3694333]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAAMYKSKWJFACZSBRBF77SGMFJSXRT4KWKATGZHKWPRECRBAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5EF/95C/5EF95CBAF1B00352DD30B5289AD5E198.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon human transport system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon patent]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon cage like transportation system]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/uncut-visual-novel-adult-game-coming-to-steam-3694310</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Uncut 'visual novel' adult game coming to Steam 3694310]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[THE MATRIX - A Visual novel game on Steam will be uncut when it is released later this week on the Valve platform. 

Fans of raunchware developer Dharker Studios will be excited to know that a certain naughty visual novel has passed has pumped it's way Steam's review process.   

That, according to Ars Technica, is primed for release this Friday.

As the game, it is for Adults Only, so Steam users need to login to view the content. Ars Technica notes, Valve's guidelines says wham bam thank you mam games are not allowed on the site.

According to a description we saw on Google cache the story will follow several women in their early lives as they have to choose what they really love and what path their lives will take. 3694310]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KMAFPCRBKVBRPBKELBKFRKLSMECVRSK9KVAF5UZCBZFAKVAABB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C15/2DC/C152DCAF688DFB5F5F5E150FEBEC9487.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ game on steam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ visual novel]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ valve]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anime]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ steam games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pc gaming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new games]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new game release]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/youtube-channels-claim-to-belong-to-senior-al-qaeda-linked-cleric-3694305</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[YouTube channels claim to belong to senior al-Qaeda-linked cleric 3694305]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SAN BRUNO, CALIFORNIA — Two YouTube channels claiming to belong to an al-Qaeda-linked cleric have been found on the Google-owned platform by TomoNews.

The man featured in both is Abdullah al-Muhaysini. 

According to the New York Times, U.S. government officials suspect he's in high within the ranks of al-Qaeda's Syrian group, the Al Nusra Front. He's accused of funding them, and, has been in Syria for some time fighting against regime forces. The U.S. claims he recruited 3,000 child and teenage soldiers for al-Nusra.

One of YouTube channel claims to be Muhaysini's official YouTube channel. TomoNews couldn't confirm it was the real deal. TomoNews found another channel claiming to be one of his. Again, we don't know if it really belongs to him. 

Worryingly, this second channel contains a Jihadi training video. Looks like it's been viewed by 4,000 people and has been online since October 2016.

Now we didn't see advertising on these channels, however, they're still on YouTube and 
that could be a problem for the Google-owned company. 

Muhaysini was sanctioned by the U.S. under Executive Order 13224 in 2016. This Bush-era law targets terrorists and their supporters. It bans U.S. persons from engaging in transactions and providing services to Muhaysini and several others named connected to the al-Nusra front.

In other words, by this guy being on YouTube, they're technically providing a service to him. 

And unless they're exempt from those sanctions, that's against U.S. law. 

Sanctions have impacted Internet companies for providing services in the past. In 2012, when the New York Times reported that Syrian government websites were being hosted in the U.S., the State Department responded that providing services violated U.S. sanctions.

In fact, the first channel we showed links to now-terminated Vimeo and Wordpress accounts. The Wordpress account says whatever was there violated their Terms of Service.

A YouTube spokesperson told us by email, We terminate accounts that repeatedly violate our Community Guidelines or that violate our Terms of Service and when we are required by law to do so. 

A spokesperson for the Treasury said TomoNews by email,Treasury does not comment on investigations or possible enforcement actions, including to confirm whether one exists. However, generally speaking, U.S. persons are prohibited from engaging in most transactions with sanctioned individuals and entities.

After we emailed both for comment, Muhaysini's channels were terminated. 

Both now display the text, This account has been terminated for violating YouTube's Community Guidelines. 3694305]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KABWVDZCKZHAEWTALSJAX9UUGREBTFZQAIAA3URLAFMFPWRHKA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7C2/375/7C23752ED53BA0D9EF440B0434FAD132.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>176</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ google]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ youtube channels]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ world news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ breaking news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ latest news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ news today]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ syria sanctions]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/student-develops-skin-cancer-from-biting-her-nails-3694270</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Student develops skin cancer from biting her nails 3694270]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA —  A woman in Australia had to have her thumb amputated because of her habit of biting her nails gave her skin cancer, The Sun reports.

Courtney Whithorn, 20, said she developed the bad habit of biting her nails when she was bullied in high school.

She said after awhile her thumb nail started to turn black. 

She decided to hide it from her family and friends, and also used fake nails to hide the condition.

Whithorn said she finally decided to visit the doctor, which is when she was diagnosed with acral lentiginous subungual melanoma. It was a malignant melanoma that is a rare form of skin cancer. 

Whithorn has undergone four surgeries to treat the cancer, with the most recent one resulting in the amputation of her thumb.

So if you have a nail-biting habit, you might want to quit now before it's too late. 3694270]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABKFPC3TAEBRMCZXLRDAR9L3MNIB7ST7AEAWXHRFABPWAWCXAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/566/71E/56671EDA770D6720E124C7B76AD5D84C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-14T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ student]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skin cancer nail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thumb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ amputated]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ habit]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ biting nails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ acral lentiginous subungual melanoma]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ malignant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surgeries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thumb nail]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake nails]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ thumb nail turning black]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-to-fact-check-images-videos-to-combat-fake-news-3695162</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Facebook to fact-check images, videos to combat fake news 3695162]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — According to the Washington Post, Facebook has announced plans to scan photos, videos, and articles uploaded onto the social media site in order to expand its efforts to combat fake news.

The social media giant also listed a few examples of fake images found on the site such as a photoshopped image of a presidential candidate in Mexico and an out of context image of a girl in Syria.

Facebook says it will be using an algorithm in 17 different countries including the U.S.

Facebook will use reverse image searching as well as analyzing metadata to evaluate if videos or photos have been digitally altered.

Once the algorithm identifies an altered image or video, Facebook will send the flagged posts to outside fact-checkers for further review.

The new feature is equipped with machine-learning and was made to help reviewers quickly identify false content. 3695162]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBJAMDACAJJRCBIVLICRI743G2JB5U39KJPWMFKYKSNWPVCYAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5D4/AB0/5D4AB05227A6DA4C8C1DCF165AF9A768.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>64</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ social media]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ combating fake news]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ algorithm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ technology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ reverse image searching]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ analyzing metadata]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ digitally altered images and videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake images]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fake videos]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/officials-urge-vampire-facial-patients-to-get-tested-for-3695039</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Officials urge 'vampire facial' patients to get tested for 3695039]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALBUQUERQUE, NEW MEXICO — Officials in New Mexico are urging patients who have received vampire facials to get tested, reports ABC 7 News.

The news comes after a client of the spa developed an infection, leading to an investigation of the salon.

A vampire facial is a skin care treatment in which a patient's blood is drawn then reapplied to the patient's face.

The procedure gained popularity when socialite, reality television star, and nude-selfie extraordinaire Kim Kardashian instagrammed herself getting it done.

Officials reportedly found the salon had problems with storing, handling and disposing needles.

The health officials suspect one way the infection might have spread is through needle stick-associated transmission, which is a fancy way of saying infected needles.

Health officials are urging anyone who received the procedure at the VIP Spa to get tested for HIV, and Hepatitis B and C.

The beauty procedure is advertised as a way to improve skin health, reduce wrinkles and sun damage,  with apparently the possible side effects of contracting the HIV virus and liver disease. 3695039]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ASJWVDCXAMHRCWRTLVBAI7JGMICSKRKZKEDR3FABKAERMBCXBF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5D2/ED5/5D2ED56D332A73F5001A58CF469FD6EA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ New Mexico]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ facial]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vampire facial]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vampire facial kim kardashian]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kim kardashian]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ HIV virus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ liver disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beauty procedure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hepatitis B]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hepatitis C]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infected needles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ withdrawing blood and applying it on the face]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ customers who received vampire facials urged to get tested]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/translucent-fish-with-no-scales-found-in-pacific-ocean-3695023</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Translucent fish with no scales found in Pacific Ocean 3695023]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM — Three species of translucent fish without scales have been found by a group of scientists in the Pacific Ocean.

According to researchers from Newcastle University, the three fish have temporarily been named pink, blue and purple Atacama snailfish.  
According to USA Today, they were discovered in the Atacama Trench, an 8,000-meter deep trench located off the west coast of South America. 
The fish can handle extreme pressure and are translucent with no scales. 
According to Thomas Linley of Newcastle University, the hardest bones in the fish are located in their inner ear to help them maintain balance and their teeth. 
Without the extreme pressure and cold to support their bodies they are extremely fragile and melt rapidly when brought to the surface, Linley said in a statement. 3695023]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJWGDZBAMDAEATFB5CRR9JHM2KBVF32A6KWXHRAAVARMVIFAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C48/B98/C48B98840A2ED5C119453E0AB09F3815.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ translucent fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ translucent fish no scales]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Atacama Trench]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pink Atacama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ blue Atacama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ purple Atacama]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Atacama snailfish]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mark-zuckerberg-is-fascinated-with-augustus-caesar-3695001</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg is fascinated with Augustus Caesar 3695001]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA — It looks as if Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg has a real big man crush for ancient Roman emperor Augustus Caesar.
You have all these good and bad and complex figures, Zuck said in a New Yorker interview. I think Augustus is one of the most fascinating. Basically, through a really harsh approach, he established two hundred years of world peace.
According to Zuckerberg, Augustus had to make choices, that didn't come for free, and he had to do certain things. 
The Facebook king's Roman interests started in high school. He also named his second daughter August and spent his 2012 honeymoon in Rome. 
The New Yorker interview suggests the Augustus mindset could be why Facebook has pursued growth at all costs. 
This growth strategy also opened up Facebook to outside developers without putting proper safeguards in place to ensure user data was not misused — Cambridge Analytica. 
Looks like growth at all costs actually has quite a few costs, some that Facebook may not be able to afford. 3695001]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AADFGDKTKZDAAVCALMCR7L2HGNIEXRT3A2LW3TAFKVHREVRFAC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/773/3CF/7733CFBC480341ACF46AFAF042BA8C46.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Facebook]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mark Zuckerberg]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Zuckerberg obsessed Augustus Caesar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Augustus Caesar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Zuckerberg Caesar]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/boy-survives-being-impaled-by-skewer-through-face-and-skull-3694812</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Boy survives being impaled by skewer through face and skull 3694812]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HARRISONVILLE, MISSOURI — A 10-year-old boy is still kicking after being impaled by a foot-long meat skewer over the weekend. 
According to the Kansas City Star, Xavier Cunningham fell from a tree house after being attacked by a bunch of yellow jacket wasps on September 8.
He then landed on the metal skewer, which went through his face and penetrated his skull, all the way to the back of his head. 

Xavier was rushed to a local emergency room, then transferred to another hospital, before ending up at the University of Kansas Hospital.  

Surgeons were amazed that the skewer had missed his eye, brain and spinal cord. 

In a nerve-racking hours long surgery, the skewer was successfully removed. Xavier is now recovering in the hospital. 
His family has set up a GoFundMe page called the Missouri Miracle to help cover the medical costs. 3694812]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6NRMCRFBNJRPBR9KACR77JFGRBV5R37AWJRTGZGAEAFKCKTBC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EB8/8C7/EB88C7CB392D0E028CA43AE9870B62B6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ skewer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy survives skewer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ foot-long skewer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy miraculously survives]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ boy survives]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/factory-worker-sustains-fatal-burns-to-body-3694801</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Factory worker sustains fatal burns to body 3694801]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA  — A post from a father mourning the death of his 24-year-old son, who suffered horrific burns at the Guangdong Xinhui Meida Nylon factory where he worked, went viral over Chinese social media a few weeks ago, reports Apple Daily.

The man claims his son was asked to check an extraction tower without any protection when chemical water spurt from the tower, resulting in his son suffering chemical burns on 98.5% of his body. A warning system in place was reportedly faulty at the time.

The father accused the factory for negligence, as they allegedly held meetings for an hour before they decided to send the young man to the hospital.

He also accused the company, in an attempt to save money, of sending his son to a hospital where his injuries were incorrectly treated as if they were burns obtained from exposure to mere hot water.

It wasn't until the family insisted the young man be transferred to another hospital, after days of the treatment not working, did the company apparently admit the injuries were actually chemical burns, and not the result of hot water alone. By then it was too late.

Unfortunately, the 24-year-old passed away after 55 days due to a combination of ailments, including a lung infection and hypernatremia.

And although his father's post went viral, it has since been deleted from Chinese social media. 3694801]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AZBWECTVKMDRPVTELJJWTL4TMSJSISIIA6IFXGIHKRGAGXIGAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/50B/212/50B21260179236AD85BE81B8E87AAF26.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-15T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>85</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatal burns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ factory]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ factory worker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ young factory worker]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ factory accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ factory worker in china]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fatal burns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sustain burns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ injury]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infectious disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ horrific burns]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/eu-article-13-copyright-architect-has-tweeted-copyrighted-content-3696678</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[EU Article 13 copyright architect has tweeted copyrighted content 3696678]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[STRASBOURG — Last week the European Union got one step closer to neutering the Internet.

Article 13 is designed to prevent copyright infringement via automated systems and filters. Critics say it's censorship by other means and that it'll end free speech as we know it.

It's being pushed by German EU lawmaker Axel Voss. The man's official Twitter account has featured some parody in the past.

A series of tweets labelled, Turn of the eras in the digital age, from May 2015 show three satirical images lamenting the Internet.  

In July, BuzzFeed Germany discovered a slew of copyrighted images on his Facebook and Twitter pages. Apparently, the Facebook images were deleted after the website reached out to him for comment.  

According to a Google translation of the article, Voss or his staff didn't really tell the site if he had the right to use them.

We've reached out to Mr Voss with some questions.  

https://twitter.com/AxelVossMdEP/status/601461106742140928
https://twitter.com/AxelVossMdEP/status/605037432833208320
https://twitter.com/AxelVossMdEP/status/602773447207481344
https://twitter.com/AxelVossMdEP/status/861669466161258496 3696678]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRDACCAGKSIAKVTFBJJWZ74XMIEV5ET6K5DWXHCWKRAACARPBB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A0D/D3C/A0DD3C3DB419416273051D2CDB3BA6CA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-18T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>116</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ EU Article 13]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Copyright]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ European Union]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Axel Voss]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Twitter]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ MEP]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Germany]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Copyright Directive]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/diseases-you-could-catch-from-contaminated-flood-waters-3696588</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Diseases you could catch from contaminated flood waters 3696588]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Members of the public are at risk of catching illnesses from the flood water left behind by Hurricane Florence.

Diarrheal diseases such as cryptosporidiosis, E.Coli or giardiasis could be caused by eating or drinking anything that have come into contact with the contaminated flood water, reports Journal-News.

The different diarrheal diseases include symptoms such as diarrhea and nausea.

Rashes and open wounds exposed to flood water also increase the risk of people being infected with tetanus, which is a bacterial infection that could break into the skin.

Another illness people could contract by being in the flooded waters for too long is trench foot. This illness could cause pain, swelling and numbness.

Stagnant flood waters is a gateway for bacteria to enter the body through any open wounds or injuries, ABC News reports.

Officials are encouraging the public to try to avoid exposure to floodwaters, and to keep any open wounds as clean and as dry as possible. 3696588]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFKWGXTUA5BFPBKDLFIA56LYGRDSXF33LSJRTGTWASNRMW35LB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DB0/85D/DB085D6EA8B3FDBD781F2E6DFF0BE441.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-18T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Florence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hurricane Florence 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ illness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flood water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contamination]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flood water contamination]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stagnant flood waters]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ illnesses you could catch from flood water]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptosporidiosis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ E.Coli]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giardiasis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tetanus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ trench foot]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/flashes-of-light-show-how-plants-signal-danger-3696573</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Flashes of light show how plants signal danger 3696573]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MADISON, WISCONSIN — Researchers have found that plants communicate distress by using their own signaling system. 

University of Wisconsin-Madison Professor of Botany Simon Gilroy and his lab have revealed how glutamate activates a wave of calcium that spreads across leaves to warn of danger. 

We know there's this systematic signaling system, and if you wound in one place the rest of the plant triggers its defense responses, says Gilroy, according to the University of Wisconsin. But we didn't know what was behind this system. 
We do know if you wound a leaf, you get an electrical charge, and you get a propagation that moves across the plant, he added. 
The scientists wanted to know what triggered the electric charge, and how it moved throughout the plant. 
Calcium was one possibility, but the researchers needed to be able to see calcium in real time, so special plants were developed the produce a protein that only fluoresces around calcium. 
The team then subjected the plants to caterpillar bites, scissor cuts and crushing wounds and used video to track the responses.
In response to each type of distress, videos show the plants lighting up as calcium spreads from the site of damage to other leaves. 
The signal spread to the other leaves in a few minutes, which was then followed by a spike in defense-related hormones in distant leaves. 

The scientists were then able to pinpoint glutamate as the trigger the sent out the waves of calcium. 3696573]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJNAAYAABBIWCBRVL6LRZ94XMRDSKU35A6KWZHTXB5GAMVIQKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/211/21F/21121F3FE9937426D610113E5A75C274.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-18T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plant distress]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plant systematic signaling system]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glutamate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ calcium in plants]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/eu-s-memes-would-probably-be-removed-under-article-13-3696567</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[EU's memes would probably be removed under Article 13 3696567]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EUROPE — The European Union Commission used memes in tweets over the summer to respond to questions if they were banning them under new copyright rules.

If Article 13 of the EU Copyright Directive was law when they posted these, they could very well have been scrubbed by Twitter. This wants tech companies to filter out copyrighted content from uploads and websites via automation.

That'll largely leave algorithms as the judge and jury of what uploads are copyright infringement and what are not. The EU guarantees freedom of expression, but can a bot tell the difference between a rip off and legit fair use of a work? 3696567]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANNFCCTSBAAAPVA9BBPW5LUUMABSZFIKK2JWMHCWKMARMBICKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0FE/683/0FE683FAA439436CB0E74AC406000CB4.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-18T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>82</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ european union]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ meme]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ copyright]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eu]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ censorship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ copyright directive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ article 13]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ picard]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ picard facepalm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ smurfs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ copyright]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/an-increase-of-spiders-appearing-in-uk-homes-3696479</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[An increase of spiders appearing in UK homes 3696479]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM  — The reason why there is an increase of spiders appearing in people's' home is because it is mating season from September until October, the BBC reports.

Professor Adam Hart, an entomologist who conducted research on the behavior pattern of spiders and how they are affected during different seasons, found that 82% of the spiders seen in houses are male.

He explained female spiders are usually seen in webs formed in garages or window sills while the male spiders generally wander around looking for a dry place to mate.

Professor Hart suggested keeping doors and windows closed and keeping the house clean to deter spiders.

The researcher also said the public should ignore old wives' tales such as using peppermint oil, citrus fruit and even ostrich eggs to prevent the spread of spiders around the house. 3696479]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMAWGXTSKMBFPBIVKBJAX7DXMEBEXE33KJPFVUTWAEAFEBZGLA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7F5/9FA/7F59FA8C7812E4F25290830CE37D69D5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-18T19:35:03+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spider]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ home]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UK]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spider season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spiders UK]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to get rid of spiders]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ increase of spiders in UK homes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mating season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ male spiders]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ female spiders]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ influx of spiders]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/storms-florence-and-mangkhut-both-deadly-in-different-ways-3697315</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Storms Florence and Mangkhut both deadly in different ways 3697315]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[US/PHILIPPINES — Two powerful storms have been causing destruction on opposite sides of the earth, one in the southeastern coast of China and one in the east coast of the U.S., but both have been wreaking havoc in different ways.

Typhoon Mangkhut had winds of 165 miles per hour, compared to Hurricane Florence which only had winds of 90 miles per hour when it hit North Carolina's coast, according to the weather channel.

However, Hurricane Florence was deadly in terms of the amount of rain it produced,  causing water damage.

Typhoon Mangkhut formed farther south in the western Pacific where water is warmer, which gave the typhoon the perfect environment to intensify.

In comparison, Hurricane Florence formed near Africa, and was out of the tropics by the time it made landfall, which caused the hurricane to be weakened by the dry air in the region.

Experts say that both are storms of the same type, but those that occur in the Pacific west of the International Date Line are called typhoons instead of hurricanes.

They also expect Typhoon Mangkhut to be the deadlier storm, as it has already caused death and destruction in the Philippines, and is now heading for China's southeastern coast. 3697315]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFLAIAKUBWJRXBZRLNPRK9DWGREBRU3ZK6PW3FIAAFNAKVRGAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E66/22C/E6622CE9C97004E0F6BC8BCFEC935FD6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane florence 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane florence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon mangkhut]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon in philippines 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon mangkhut hong kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[typhoon mangkhut in hong kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon hong kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  typhoon mangkhut philippines]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon vs hurricane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon china 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wreak havoc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ different ways]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destruction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  deadly]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/mt-gox-payouts-could-trigger-bitcoin-market-crash-3697306</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Mt. Gox payouts could trigger Bitcoin market crash 3697306]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[TOKYO — Experts are warning of a possible market crash as a now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange is set to finally payout its creditors.

Fortune reports that in 2014, 850,000 bitcoins then valued at $473 million were stolen from Japan-based exchange Mt. Gox, in one of the biggest digital heists in cryptocurrency history.

Mt. Gox has since filed for bankruptcy, but is now set to finally payout 160,000 bitcoins at current valuations to its customers.

A former Mt. Gox trader who spearheaded the investigation into the exchange's bankruptcy told the Telegraph that it's likely those who get their coins back will want to immediately sell them off, potentially causing supply to outstrip demand.

And with the value of bitcoin already plunging in recent months, there are fears that the flood of payouts could lead to a price drop that would ultimately crash the market.

Mt. Gox customers who lost money in the heist can file their payout claims until October 22, after which coin distribution is expected to begin. 3697306]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEDFPCADLVAAEATELSKR3KJHGMAS7STSA6PAVFIFANQR7BKWAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A2E/731/A2E731705FC0F0646F86D539F42C5D1B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin crash]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mt gox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin exchange]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cryptocurrency exchange]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin heist]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin hack]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mt gox payout]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin value]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bitcoin price drop]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-video-challenge-makes-kids-think-they-re-invisible-3697252</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New video challenge makes kids think they're invisible 3697252]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — A new viral video challenge is sweeping across the States where older siblings trick their brothers or sisters into thinking they're invisible.
According to Scroll, looks as if people are taking their cue from magician Justin Willman as his Netflix show Magic for Humans. 
On the show, Willman tricks a stranger into thinking he's invisible by getting all the people around him to already be in on the joke. 
Now the joke is being played on unsuspecting little brothers and sisters with pretty hilarious results — depending on who you ask. 

So if you feel like being a d-bag to your younger siblings all you need is a phone, a blanket and some time on your hands. 3697252]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNLRICZJBSJRCBZ7BSLR39JGMFJVRSC9AVCFPHAAK5EFEVZDKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/98C/330/98C330F30E334944C3239E3983CFD4F0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>56</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ invisible challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral video challenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ invisible]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ #invisiblechallenge]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/here-are-some-of-the-scariest-videos-of-typhoon-mangkhut-3697192</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Here are some of the scariest videos of Typhoon Mangkhut 3697192]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HONG KONG — A lot of shocking footage was filmed during the storm that wreaked havoc across Hong Kong over the past few days, here are some of the most jaw-dropping moments caught on camera. 3697192]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/LNNFVCRJAEGRAAATBSIWZ7UXNFJSTECZLWKWVUAKBZGAKAZMKH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8A8/8C1/8A88C1A35D20DE04202A0D3D396AC1E5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Hong Kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon mangkhut]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon mangkhut hong kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[typhoon mangkhut in hong kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon hong kong]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[wreak havoc]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ destruction]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ videos of typhoon mangkhut]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoon mangkhut videos]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/chemicals-in-cosmetics-may-harm-female-hormones-3697098</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Chemicals in cosmetics may harm female hormones 3697098]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FAIRFAX COUNTY, VIRGINIA — A new study has found that chemicals in skincare products can negatively affect women's hormones.

The study showed that beauty products may even contribute to infertility or breast cancer.

 A new study has found that chemicals in skincare products can negatively affect women's hormones, and may even lead to infertility or breast cancer.

According to the George Mason University study published in the journal Environment International, beauty products often contain environmental products such as parabens, which are antimicrobial preservatives, or benzophenones, which serve as UV filters.

Researchers collected over 500 samples from 143 women aged 18 to 44 who had no chronic health conditions and didn't use birth control.

Analysis of the samples indicate that those with the chemicals present in their system produced abnormal amounts of the reproductive hormones estrogen and progesterone, reports the Independent.

Too much estrogen has been linked to fibroids and irregular periods, but too little prevents eggs from maturing. Excessive progesterone, meanwhile, is associated with breast cancer and unusual vaginal bleeding. 3697098]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K2NWVYZEAAGWKWZSKEDF57SGGMDB7RK5KVCA5FAKAREAMBCZBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E92/346/E923469C44A0640E43539235FCB92EC9.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>78</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ beauty products]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chemicals]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hormones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ female hormones]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paraben]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ benzophenone]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ estrogen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cosmetics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ personal care]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ UV filters]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bpa-free-plastics-found-to-be-as-harmful-as-regular-plastic-3697082</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[BPA-free plastics found to be as harmful as regular plastic 3697082]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — A new study published in Current Biology determined BPA-free plastic products aren't necessarily safer.

Twenty years ago, when the researchers conducted the experiment for the first time, BPA was found to give rise to chromosomally abnormal embryos in mice, leading the researchers to believe the same could be happening to humans.

BPA was found to interfere with the endocrine system in the body which regulates everything from fertility to brain development.

In this new study, researchers used BPS, a bisphenol which is used to replace BPA, and found the mice in the study all began to develop reproductive problems even though they were kept in BPA-free cages — similar to their previous study.

BPA was found to affect the developing brain, heart, lungs, as well as other organs in the body.

The researchers are warning the public about the dangers of different types of plastics used in consumer products as they could ultimately affect the body.

A researcher involved in the study said plastic containers should never be put into the microwave or dishwasher because this causes the chemicals in the container to leak. 3697082]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBLWADRCBRDRIVZWLZDFT74XM5BBIEC9KRAWTTKWA5ERIAAAAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D0E/708/D0E7081E869DC5149CC57DF1010174DB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BPA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BPS]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BPA free plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[BPA plastic dangers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BPS]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  is BPA-free plastic safe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ harmful to health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic is harmful to health]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ harmful]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dangers of plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ regular plastic]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/fortnite-is-causing-a-whole-mess-of-divorces-3697054</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Fortnite is causing a whole mess of divorces 3697054]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM — It looks like the massively popular game Fortnite is causing a spike in divorces.  
According to Divorce Online, the online game has been named in over 200 divorce cases in the U.K. alone, CNN reports.
According to the site, that's around 5 percent of the 4,665 divorces filed since the start of the year. 
But the thing is, Fortnite is widely popular all over the world, so the number of divorces caused by the game could actually be much higher. 
In June, the WHO listed gaming addiction in general as a potentially harmful tech-related behavior. 3697054]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIRPCKTBJIAGWKEKBLW59UYNEBBTRZQAWIWVURCAVGFCCADBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C23/878/C238783BE16A67273EBED352FD8CE0DC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fortnite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fortnite video game]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fortnite divorces]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Fortnite causing divorces]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ divorces]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-left-with-painful-boils-after-catching-rare-disease-from-pet-cat-3697004</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man left with painful boils after catching rare disease from pet cat 3697004]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS — A Missouri man suffered giant boils on his neck after contracting a rare, infectious disease from his feline friend.

The 68-year-old had gone to the doctor after a weeklong fever followed by two months of painful swelling on his right of neck and face, according to The New England Journal of Medicine.

The man's cat died two days before his symptoms began, supposedly from feline leukemia, though no laboratory testing confirmed this.

Doctors now suspect a misdiagnosis, saying it may have instead been infected with toxic Francisella tularensis bacteria, which was likely transmitted to the man via bites or scratches while he was administering medication.

The man later tested positive for tularensis and was diagnosed with glandular tularemia, for which he was put on antibiotics for four weeks.

The painful swelling improved in just five days, and was completely gone in three weeks.

Tularemia is more commonly known as rabbit fever, since rabbits, hares, and rodents are especially susceptible. Pets typically contract the disease when they consume infected prey. 3697004]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIAAYCTBNLWMWZSB6IAX7LUMMBS3RZLK2KAVTKWAAHRAVIGKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8FC/F55/8FCF55EFFD5F5B72F965230184D28BA8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-19T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tularemia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tularensis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant boils]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ swelling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rare diseases]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ francisella]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rabbit fever]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tularensis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ animal disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cat infection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ infectious diseases]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ life threatening diseases]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/climate-change-is-making-hurricanes-way-worse-3697968</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Climate change is making hurricanes way worse 3697968]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON — Global warming is affecting hurricanes by making them wetter with more energy that intensify faster. 
According to the Associated Press, storm surges are more dangerous because of rising sea levels, with storms moving more slowly, thus increased levels of precipitation. 
The Associated Press spoke with 17 meteorologists and researchers who study climate change, hurricanes or both.
Dean of the environment school at the University of Michigan Jonathan Overpeck said, Florence is yet another poster child for the human-supercharged storms that are becoming more common and destructive as the planet warms.

Several months after Hurricane Harvey, studies found climate change significantly increased the chances for Harvey's record rain falls. 

Scientists say that for every degree the air warms, it can hold almost 4 percent more water and feeds more energy into the storm. 
University of Exeter climate scientist Peter Stott said the warmer air and water also make storms more intense or stronger. 
National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration climate scientist Jim Kossin and Overpeck also mentioned that studies have shown storms intensifying more rapidly than before. 3697968]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNKRCCIBAFKRCDCCBIAWTKBGG2KE5SILK2JWZUCYKAHAGAIBBH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/444/3E9/4443E948892C8D47D5AF9FBB3349920B.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricanes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ typhoons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hurricane intensity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ storm surge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ storm intensity]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/live-worm-pulled-out-of-man-s-brain-in-china-3697954</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Live worm pulled out of man's brain in China 3697954]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[CHINA — Doctors in China discovered something unwelcome in a man's brain after he had an undercooked meal, reports The South China Morning Post.

Apparently the man, identified as Mr. Liu, loved to eat grilled food, and was in good health until recent months when he suddenly started having epileptic fits.

He went to the doctor and took a blood test, which is when they found out a tapeworm had taken up residence in his brain.

Obviously the next step was to pull the thing out, which they did, all 10 centimeters of it, which is when they found out it was alive.

Apparently the worm was springy and white and could swim.

The doctors said the worm might have made its way into Mr. Liu's system after he ate undercooked or contaminated food.

They also explained that the possibility of a worm reaching the brain and staying there is higher than finding its way to other organs, as the brain receives almost a quarter of body's blood supply.

The doctors said once the worm is in the brain, there is a chance it could reproduce and further damage brain function, causing problems such as nausea, epilepsy and the bleeding from the blood vessels.

Well, that's why you should be very careful of what you put in your mouth. 3697954]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFIWEXZDAVDFGAZWLNIR77D4MZEBRSIMK2KRZTILKMHFEXZFAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0A1/05F/0A105F346309B067106A360E3D1E93A6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ China]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ epileptic seizure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ grilled foods]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tapeworm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tapeworm in human]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tapeworm in brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ worm in brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ worm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ live worm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ undercooked meat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ contaminated food]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ doctors pull out live worm from man's brain]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/household-disinfectants-could-be-linked-to-child-obesity-3697946</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Household disinfectants could be linked to child obesity 3697946]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALBERTA, CANADA — Commonly used household disinfectants and multi-surface cleaners could be making children overweight by affecting their gut bacteria, according to a study published on Monday in the Canadian Medical Association Journal.  

Infants living in households where antimicrobial disinfectants were used at least once a week were twice as likely to have elevated levels of the bacteria Lachnospiraceae at ages 3 to 4 months than children whose homes did not use disinfectants frequently, according to CNN. 

According to Anita Kozyrskyj, lead author of the study, higher levels of Lachnospiraceae in animal studies have been associated with higher body fat and insulin resistance. 

Researchers collected stool samples from 757 infants and analyzed their body mass index, BMI, at older ages in addition to parental use of disinfectant products.
Scientists found that around 80 percent of Canadian households use disinfectant products at least once a week.  

While the team found an increase in Lachnospiraceae with increased antimicrobial disinfectants, they did not find the same association in disinfectants without the bacteria-killing ingredients or eco-friendly cleaners. 
These results suggest that gut microbiota were the culprit in the association between disinfectant use and the overweight, said Kozyrskyj, according to CNN. 
Though the results show connection between disinfectants and the gut microbiome, that does not imply causation. 

According to Kozyrskyj, further studies need to be carried out to establish a causal relationship. 3697946]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAWEC3UKVDAGBCELWJRZ9BFGZCBVE3ZLWPRVGADAZAR7DRNKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EBB/F39/EBBF3932017D57E4DE1AAF4CE2EE42A0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>76</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ childhood obesity]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ child obesity disinfectants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ household disinfectants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ multi-purpose cleaners]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ disinfectants]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/trying-to-hold-in-your-fart-%0Abad-idea--3697942</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Trying to hold in your fart? 
Bad idea. 3697942]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES — We all know that ominous rumbling followed by a very urgent need to pass gas.

But do you ever wonder what happens when you do?

Whether you find it weird, gross, or funny, farting is a perfectly normal bodily function. On average, we fart anywhere from 5 to 15 times a day, according to the UK's National Health Service.

But say you're on that date and are holding one in. Then what? Apart from the obvious discomfort, the pent-up gas can get reabsorbed into circulation and emerge out of your mouth as gross fart breath, reports a study published in Digestive Diseases and Sciences.

Hold it in too long and the intestinal gas could build up to a point where it just shoots out of you in a massive, uncontrollable fart.

So next time you feel the urge, it's best to just let er rip. 3697942]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KAAWGDZCKVDRPVKEBBIWZ7SFNACS5ETRAAAA5GIDBZEA5DAGKB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/841/954/841954F1CCB89CBF5F2E5434AFD8A4BA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ farting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ gas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ passing gas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fart breath]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ how to hold in a fart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ holding in a fart]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ flatulence]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ intestinal gas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stinky]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stinky fart]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/ghostly-sound-of-children-singing-nursery-rhymes-blamed-on-spiders-3697906</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Ghostly sound of children singing nursery rhymes blamed on spiders 3697906]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[IPSWICH, UNITED KINGDOM — A family in the English village of Ipswich lived in constant terror after being tormented by the sounds of ghostly singing.

The Ipswich Star reports that almost every night for nearly a year, a mom and her two kids were awakened by the disembodied voice of a little girl singing It's Raining, It's Pouring.

When the singing didn't stop, the woman reached out to the local town council. They found it difficult to believe, but nevertheless asked her to contact them the next time it happens.

So when the singing started up again around midnight on September 12, she called the council, and together they traced the eerie music to an industrial building- being played through a loudspeaker.

Turns out the creepy nursery rhyme was an alarm meant to stop thieves and trespassers, and was only supposed to be heard on the property.

It was triggered by an over-sensitive motion sensor, and was constantly being set off by itsy-bitsy spiders crawling across the lens.

The site has since apologized for the disturbance and adjusted the volume, which means the poor woman and her kids can finally get a good night's rest. 3697906]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5AFXAIFKRHRTVAYB6LF57LXGMDBVRC4KVCAXT3YARHAGCKTBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/775/979/775979C1F42C08DB85885A242D3B6AE2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>79</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ghostly singing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ horror movie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ghost of ipswich]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spiders]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nursery rhyme alarm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ creepy singing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ creepy nursery rhyme]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ipswich]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ motion detector]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/half-of-world-s-sea-turtles-have-already-consumed-plastic-study-3697698</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Half of world's sea turtles have already consumed plastic: Study 3697698]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA —   Researchers found that ingesting just one piece of plastic could increase the chance of a sea turtle to die by 22 percent, according to a study published in the Scientific Reports.

The researchers found younger turtles have a higher risk of dying from plastic than adult turtles as they tend to float with the ocean currents where most of the small lightweight plastic lies.

Adult turtles in comparison tend to be choosier with what they eat, choosing instead to eat sea grass and crustaceans.

The researchers explained a even a thin, flimsy piece of plastic could block the intestine, resulting in blockage in the long run. While harder pieces of plastic could cause internal injuries, which could ultimately lead to death.

The study also found that about half of the sea turtles on Earth have already consumed plastic.

Dr. Hardesty, one of the authors of the study, said we should rethink our relationship with plastic and work to reduce the turtles' exposure to plastic. 3697698]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSJAGAIGA2LRTWCDLWIRT6DRMWLVZS3ZKWLWMGZHAVGAKDRJBG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D95/A28/D95A2854845795C26F955CA53AD5E6F7.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-20T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Australia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[plastic pollution in the ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic sea pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ turtles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oceans]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea turtles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ plastic killing sea turtles]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/texas-county-mayor-shoots-gator-seeks-revenge-for-mini-horse-3698726</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Texas county mayor shoots gator, seeks revenge for mini-horse 3698726]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LIVINGSTON,TEXAS — The mayor of Livingston, Texas decided to take matters into her own hands and shot dead an alligator she believed ate her miniature horse, reports The Houston Chronicle.

Judy B. Cochran believes the 12-foot-long, 580-pound alligator could have eaten her miniature horse several years ago as it was much larger than other alligators in the area.

She used a dead racoon as a bait for the alligator, caught it and hooked it up.

After that, Cochran fired a single shot straight into the gator's head.

The grandmother did receive some negative comments for killing the gator, but she believed it would have become a nuisance to another person if she didn't handle it.

She promised the alligator wouldn't go to waste as parts of it would be prepared into meat for food, and boots to wear.

Apparently, Cochran isn't the first in her family to kill an alligator. Her grandson apparently killed an even bigger alligator when he was just 5 years old. 3698726]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSNWMCRGBACRPXIYLWIF7LSGGEBBZFZNKJJWPTAHKAARAWALAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B9/5E2/3B95E200D44A2AE7F77983A876A608CC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alligator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ miniature horse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alligator shot dead]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alligator shot in texas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ grandma kills alligator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[grandma gator in texas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ revenge]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alligator bait]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mayor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ texas]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/microplastics-could-be-entering-food-chain-through-mosquitoes-3698499</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Microplastics could be entering food chain through mosquitoes 3698499]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[READING, UNITED KINGDOM — Microplastics could be entering the food chain through mosquitoes, researchers have discovered.

This, in turn, threatens birds and other creatures that consume the flying insects.

Scientists from the University of Reading fed microplastics to mosquito larvae, and discovered the plastics remained inside the insects after they became adults. The study was published in the journal Biology Letters on Wednesday.

Researchers used Culex pipiens mosquitoes because of their prevalence around many global habitats. The team found the larvae consumed fluorescent microplastic particles that were 0.0002 centimeters in size.  
According to The Guardian, as the larvae matured into the pupa stage and then into adult mosquitoes, many of the particles were transferred as well. 
This means that creatures that eat the mosquitoes — such as birds, bats and spiders — are also ingesting the plastics. 
The lead author of the study, Amanda Callaghan, a biological scientist at Reading told the AFP, although the research was carried out in a lab, it was highly possible this process was also occurring in the wild.  
It's a very major problem and those plastics already in the environment are going to be with us for a very, very long time, Callaghan said. 3698499]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A6IWGXTWAIAFPCZWLJKF794SGFIBKF3SKZBWXURGB5FRCBANLH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E73/E87/E73E87067B070F8BFCED9859D5847BFC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastics pollution]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microbeads]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ microplastics mosquitoes]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mosquito larvae microplastics]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-find-sharks-meeting-in-the-middle-of-the-pacific-ocean-3698435</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Researchers find sharks meeting in the middle of the Pacific Ocean 3698435]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[UNDER THE SEA — Scientists have conducted research as to why the great white sharks gather in the Pacific Ocean during winter and spring.

According to the Monterey Bay Aquarium Research Institute, researchers added tags to 20 sharks to track their movement in the ocean.

The sharks were found leaving California waters in December to head for the middle of the ocean between Hawaii and California, an area the scientists considered to be an oceanic desert.

Scientists then used a research vessel called Falkor to explore the area, and found the oceanic desert was actually an oasis, as there was an abundance of jellyfish, phytoplankton, squid and fish, leading the researchers to refer to the area as the White Shark Cafe.

Marine life in the region were found swimming up and down the water column, in what is known as the midwater range.

The scientists believe the sharks were feasting on the tiny marine life in the area, however they aren't completely sure as there is a possibility the sharks were also mating in the region. 3698435]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KVARPCZHKJKAMC3FLMCRZKJCNADVRRRLKSKWPHREASQRCBCSBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E90/E86/E90E8660CEA6E2CBCBA4F981E79572A1.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Great White Shark]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[great white shark eating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sharks]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark gathering]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ scientists]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mid-Pacific Ocean]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark videos]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shark movements]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ marine life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ jellyfish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ phytoplankton]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ squid]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fish]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ White Shark Cafe]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ White Shark Cafe video]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ White Shark Cafe research]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/daily-aspirin-may-be-useless-harmful-for-older-healthy-adults-3698396</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Daily aspirin may be useless, harmful for older healthy adults 3698396]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS, MINNESOTA — Taking a daily low-dose aspirin may have no benefit, or might actually be harmful to healthy, older adults, according to a new study. 
The study followed more than 19,000 people ages 65 and older in the United States and Australia for an average of 4.7 years, according to NPR. The results were published in the New England Journal of Medicine on Sunday. 

Participants were given 100 milligrams of aspirin daily or a placebo. 

According to NBC News, at the end of the trial period, 90.3 percent of the aspirin-treated patients were still alive, compared with 90.5 percent of those given placebos. 
The rates of physical disability and dementia were similar in both groups, while the rates of coronary heart disease, heart attacks and strokes were also similar. 
We found there was no discernible benefit of aspirin on prolonging independent, healthy life for the elderly, said Anne Murray, a geriatrician and epidemiologist at Hennepin Healthcare in Minneapolis, who helped lead the study, according to NPR. 

The study found a significant risk of internal gastric bleeding in the aspirin-treated group, as well as a slight increase in cancer deaths within the same group. 3698396]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AEAACXTUKNJFPCRWBNIWTKJHMMCBTUZMAACFTHILANNR3WT5AD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/36B/738/36B738E4D40E81EEF883BD91EEBCBFEC.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-21T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>73</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aspirin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ low-dose aspirin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aspirin harmful healthy older people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aspirin no benefit elderly]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/women-develop-breast-cancer-from-donated-organ-in-rare-case-3699603</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Women develop breast cancer from donated organ in rare case 3699603]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AMSTERDAM — In an extremely rare case, four patients developed cancer after receiving organs from the same donor, with three succumbing to the disease.

When doctors harvested the kidneys, lungs, heart, and liver of a 53-year-old organ donor, she had no known medical conditions, and no malignancy was detected, according to a case report published in the American Journal of Transplantation.

Breast cancer cells were later found in the lung, left kidney, and liver recipients, with DNA analysis showing they came from the donor. The tree died after the cancer metastasized.

A fourth organ recipient survived following removal of the donated right kidney, stopping immunosuppression drugs, and chemotherapy.

The study suggests the donor has micro-metastases, which are groups of cancer cells that spread from their site of origin, but are too small to be detected.

Organ donations are not allowed for anyone with an active malignancy, as cancer transmission can occur during transplantation.

This rare medical occurrence, however, is believed to be the first case of breast cancer being transferred. 3699603]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KJIRCDAAA6NAKAZ7LFKAZLU4GEAS7RALK2KFXTZKAZFATACUAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.storage.googleapis.com/up-image/801/4DB/8014DB0DE46C401994739E42E8E03A47.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[breast cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[donated organ]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[organ donation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[organ transplant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[transplants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[transplant risk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rare medical case]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[transplantation immunology]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[transplants]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[transplant risk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[rare medical case]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[transplantation immunology]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-develop-functional-sodium-battery-to-replace-lithium-3699562</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists develop functional sodium battery to replace lithium 3699562]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WEST LAFAYETTE, INDIANA — Scientists have found a way to successfully synthesize sodium as a viable replacement for lithium-ion in batteries.

As the rare lithium used in most batteries is fast becoming scarce, scientists are looking into sodium, which is more abundant, and can service large power facilities at a lower cost, according to a Purdue University report.

The problem with sodium is that it explodes when exposed to water. Sodium ions in a battery also tend to stick to the anode, building up into a solid electrolyte interface that can grow too large and hamper charging ability.

To make sodium functional, Purdue University scientists used ultrasonic dispersion to melt it into a purple liquid. Once cooled into a powder, it is suspended in hexane for even particle distribution.

A few drops of the suspension liquid on cathode or anode electrodes allows a sodium-ion battery to function with more stability, and at a higher capacity.

According to Purdue assistant professor of chemical engineering Vilas Pol, adding in the sodium requires only minimal modifications to the battery production process, making it both promising and practical. 3699562]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IFMDZFAZGRMWIULMDWZLSHMZEV7F39AZAFPFCRKSPFZWTVAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F97/058/F97058EF9DE4D19BD91CF2FC63092FD3.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ batteries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sodium battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sodium ion battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lithium battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lithium ion battery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sodium powder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cheap batteries]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ purdue university]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-may-open-3-000-cashier-less-go-stores-by-2021-3699262</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Amazon may open 3,000 cashier-less Go stores by 2021 3699262]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[SEATTLE — Amazon is planning on saying goodbye to supermarket workers after reports that it plans to open 3,000 Amazon Go stores by 2021.
According to Bloomberg, this would be a major move into brick-and-mortar for the online retail juggernaut. 
The move would target grocery stores like Krogers, convenience stores like CVS and 7-Eleven, and big-box retailers like Target and Walmart. 
According to Bloomberg, shoppers use a smartphone app to get into the store. After scanning their phone at a turnstile, they can grab whatever garbage they want and walk out without stopping at a register. 
Sensors and computer-vision technology track what shoppers select and bill them automatically. Say goodbye to checkout lines — and human workers. 
Amazon is still experimenting with what it wants to offer at the Go locations such as a convenience store that sells ready-to-go meals with some groceries, or something like a fast food joint. 3699262]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KSKWPDZGAMGAMARVBSJRX7DTMRDVTS32A6KFVTALABPAXATVAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B8/731/3B873104C82231DC0E9A96E0E95CB089.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Go]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Go cashier-less]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon Go convenience stores]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Amazon brick-and-mortar]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/1-000-foot-long-spider-webs-in-greece-are-just-a-massive-orgy-3699254</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[1,000-foot-long spider webs in Greece are just a massive orgy 3699254]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AITOLIKO, GREECE — The beautifully picturesque beaches of Aitoliko have been covered in a whole lot of spider loving recently. 

In a video posted to YouTube by Giannis Giannakopoulos, networks of spider webs stretching a 1,000-feet-long are shown covering shrubs and beach palms. 
According to Newsit.gr, who asked biology expert Maria Chatzaki, the massive webs of love happen every summer. 
According to Live Science, spiders commonly known as stretch spiders for their long, ovular bodies, have an affinity for the water and are great web builders. 
The massive web networks are great for catching insects and nesting. 
The warm temperatures and high humidity of the Greek coasts create the perfect mating conditions for the spiders. 3699254]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLWGXAHAEEFCVIXKBKRI94XMEDBXR36A6IRVUALAMAW7VZGAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E65/1E5/E651E5A02A1D0713343C69DB09BCECD2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spider web]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stretch spider webs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ aitoliko greece spider webs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spider webs cover beaches]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/first-day-of-autumn-to-arrive-this-saturday-marking-the-fall-equinox-3699077</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[First day of autumn to arrive this Saturday, marking the fall equinox 3699077]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[WORLD — This year's fall equinox takes place on Saturday, September 22, 9:54 p.m. Eastern time, marking the end of summer, according to the weather channel.

The autumn equinox, also known as the September equinox, occurs when the sun crosses the earth's equator from the Northern Hemisphere into the Southern Hemisphere.

During the winter, Earth's Northern Hemisphere tilts away from the sun, and during the summer it tilts toward the sun. The shift in Earth's tilt is what causes the change in  seasons.

During the equinox, day and night will be balanced to about 12 hours around the world.

The Autumn equinox usually takes places on September 22, 23 or 24 in the Northern Hemisphere.

After this, the days will start to get shorter while the nights get longer as it enters the winter season.

The term equinox comes from two latin words meaning equal and night.

This occasion is celebrated in different parts in the world, with some cultures the event by spending time with loved ones. 3699077]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABIFPDKTAZGAIVIVBBIRRK44MMCS7RIKAZAFRU3SABPR3AIFKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E95/88B/E9588B4C0BBCCFDA613AEDF6D32591B5.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-22T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fall equinox 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ fall equinox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ equinox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ autumn equinox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ autumn equinox 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ end of summer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ summer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ autumn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first day of autumn]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ first day of fall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Earth's tilt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Northern hemisphere]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Southern hemisphere]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ september equinox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ all about fall equinox]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ all about autumn equinox]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-s-cliff-selfie-leads-to-fatal-fall-3701027</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman's cliff selfie leads to fatal fall 3701027]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[MUNISING, MICHIGAN — A California woman met her untimely demise after trying to take the perfect snapshot on a picturesque cliff.

The Marquette Mining Journal reports that 32-year-old Sunnyvale resident Tu Thanh Nguyen was hiking solo in Michigan's Pictured Rocks National Lakeshore when she stopped for a photo op near a cliff along the North Country trail.

While taking a selfie, Nguyen got too close to the edge and fell 200-feet off the cliff- straight into Lake Superior.

Two kayakers witnessed the nasty plunge and rushed to her aid. They retrieved her from the water and brought her back to shore, but the poor woman didn't make it.

The National Park Service has deemed the incident an accident, and have already notified Nguyen's family. 3701027]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFJAGAIDANIA7V3FBVBAR9URM2JVREZNK6LRZGCYBZDRTA3VAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/961/C85/961C850A83A3996778DD14EFCEB8FA8F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>45</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cliff selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tragic selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman falls off cliff]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ hiking selfie]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lake superior]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  pictured rocks national lakeshore]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-deciphers-mating-calls-of-giant-pandas-3700858</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study deciphers mating calls of giant pandas 3700858]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Pandas are able to identify one another by their calls, according to a study published in the Scientific Reports.

Pandas have a more than a dozen distinct vocal sounds they make but when it is time for mating season, there is a distinct sound that both male and female giant pandas use, a husky, rapid vibrato known as a bleat.

The bleat helps to alert other pandas if there is a mate available in the area. It also contains information such as the size and identity of the panda.

Pandas have a short mating season as the female pandas only ovulate once a year and are able to conceive for only a few days in an year, according to the New York Times.

The researchers recorded the bleats of giant pandas and tested how well the sound would travel through dense bamboo thickets.

However, the researchers found that the bleat works best if a potential mate is less than 10 meters away.

The study could help conservationists trying to encourage pandas to breed as their population continues to dwindle. 3700858]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLWKXZBAZDFKARUKFPF7KBHGJLSISK6KNIFRGZAKFIRAYIGBE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D8E/1A8/D8E1A8F4D0B80B69BCE83712D87621DB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>62</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant pandas]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mating calls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bleat]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pandas mating calls]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda mating season]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bamboo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ forest]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pandas identify one another by bleats]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ male and female pandas mating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda mating sounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda vocal sounds]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ panda video]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/20-pound-ovarian-cyst-removed-from-woman-s-stomach-3700837</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[20-pound ovarian cyst removed from woman's stomach 3700837]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROBERTSON COUNTY, TENNESSEE — A woman in Tennessee had a huge 20 pound ovarian cyst removed from her stomach, according to reports from WVLT-TV.

Ashley Walden first visited the doctor five years ago after experiencing abdominal pain. The doctor diagnosed her with a benign ovarian cyst, but her the pain eventually got worse and she started gaining weight. 

Walden ended up looking like she was six months pregnant and said she could barely walk.

She ended up in the emergency room. The doctors conducted a series of tests and found that the cyst had hit a growth spurt.

The doctors finally removed the giant cyst and found it went from her liver down to her bladder.

Walden says she regrets not getting surgery done earlier and said it isn't worth putting off your health.

She says her plans now involve hanging out with her kids. 3700837]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AABRAYCTKJJWEAAWLAAFR9DXMVCBVRK7KVDWVGKYB2JWKYIKAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1BD/EEA/1BDEEA2BFB2C8436BF56D0E7B335121D.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-25T19:35:02+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>51</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyst]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ovarian cyst]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ovarian cyst removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 20-pound cyst in stomach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman has 20-pound cyst removed]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ abdomen]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stomach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyst removal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cyst growth spurt]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant cyst]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant cyst stomach]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant cyst removal]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-addicted-to-drinking-her-own-piss-3701472</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Woman addicted to drinking her own piss 3701472]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — A woman named Carried from Colorado Springs featured on TLC's Strange Addictions likes to drink a something that would gross most other people out.

Her own wee wee. 
Carrie was featured on the program several years ago, and at the time had been drinking her own Number 1 for four years. If she's still at it, that mean she's been doing this for a decade.
She apparently downs 80 ounces of her own Country Time Lemonade every day — sometimes by the glass, sometimes through her nose with a Neti pot. 
According to Fox News, one doctor said Carrie suffers from a type of Pica disorder where people enjoy eating inorganic things like dirt or wood. 

Carrie uses her own pee pee as eye drops, to brush her chompers and on her skin. 
During the show she said she drinks almost all the tinkle that leaks out of her body. 3701472]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNKRGCRBABMAEVCCB5AAI6JCGJIBXUZMA2JRVGIHASKRGDKUKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3D1/C4F/3D1C4FF4EF828FCE9870E8775B17F7D6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drinking]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman addicted]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ woman drinks own]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ strange habits]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/anorexic-woman-is-so-thin-she-can-play-living-corpse-in-horror-film-3701382</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Anorexic woman is so thin she can play living corpse in horror film 3701382]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BARNAUL, RUSSIA — In trying to get a woman with an eating disorder back on the right track, one Russian doctor didn't mince words and went straight from zero to savage.

News.com.au reports that Kristina Karyagina suffers from severe anorexia. She's eaten only small pieces of fruit since high school, and has become dangerously underweight as a result.

The 26-year-old is so skeletal she weighs only 17 kilograms — the same weight as a 4-year-old child.

Her plight got public attention after reality TV star Maria Kokhno started an online campaign to raise money to fly her to a specialist for treatment.

Kokhno had previously battled with the disease, and arranged for Karyagina to see the same no-nonsense doctor who helped her get better.

In one appointment, he brutally asked the girl if she ever considered playing a living corpse in a horror movie- an approach which may be working, since she's started to eat more than just tiny bits of fruit.

It's but one milestone on a long road to recovery, but both Karyagina's mom and Kokho are hopeful that she will make it through. 3701382]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIWGYZHAREFPARTLSLWR9JHMZBSZUT6KBJAXUAGARDAPB32KE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3B4/DF8/3B4DF816DE5F9CE7106B1FD9B3E77D7F.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>67</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anorexic]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ living corpse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anorexia]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ eating disorder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anorexia nervosa]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mental illness]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ anorexic woman]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/spacex-changes-design-for-bfr-spaceship-for-mars-3701311</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[SpaceX changes design for BFR spaceship for Mars 3701311]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — SpaceX's Mars-colonizing Big Falcon Rocket spaceflight system has undergone a redesign.

It will consist of two parts, a spaceship and a rocket booster, standing 118 meters tall at launch, 11 percent taller than their previous design, reports NBC News.

Instead of placing six Raptor engines onto the spaceship, SpaceX now plans to add seven Raptor engines to power the BFR spaceship.

The spaceship will also now include two movable fins near its nose and two larger fins near its tail. 

SpaceX's founder and CEO Elon Musk says this will help the vehicle maneuver its way to safe landings.

The previous design didn't include any front fins.

He also explained the vehicle will land like a skydive rather than an airplane, landing vertically after slowing its descent.

Musk said he believes this design might be better than the previous one. He also added it looks beautiful. 3701311]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KFNWXXADBZAFAVI7BMAW5LD3GMDERSKSLRBR3TZCBZAATBRCKF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0A8/3B0/0A83B05216EBA46DEB4510D94C3773E2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ SpaceX bfr]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spacex mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spaceship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spacecraft]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Mars-colonizing Big Falcon Rocket]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ BFR spaceship]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bfr mars mission]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bfr mars animation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spacecraft to mars]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vertical landing spacex]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ vertical landing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ space race]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ exploring space]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-propose-massive-wall-to-save-ice-sheets-from-collapse-3701302</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists propose massive wall to save ice sheets from collapse 3701302]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA — Scientists have proposed a crazy plan to build a wall around the Antarctic ice sheets in a bid to slow their collapse.

As the planet heats up due to global warming, the world's ice sheets are rapidly melting and causing sea levels to rise at an alarming rate.

To prevent this global catastrophe, scientists proposed constructing artificial undersea mounds to catch the ice as it flows forward, thereby allowing it to reground, according to new research published in The Cryosphere.

A second idea aims to address the threat of warm water currents, which have been known to thin ice shelves.

According to the research, building a long, continuous wall or sill across the front of the glacier will block warm water from seeping under the ice shelf.

The study authors found that smaller structures would have a 30% success rate, and that larger walls may be even more effective.

However, some scientists warn that such geoengineering is simply a band-aid for the real problem, and offers no real solution to reversing global warming. 3701302]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KEBRPCIDK2PACCRRBIBF5L2AMAASVST7AJPA3UZEARCRGVIFKD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/29E/026/29E0263CC8932CD6FE0E7A6152200651.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Antarctica]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice sheets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ collapsing ice sheets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ melting ice sheets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice sheet collapse]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Antarctic ice sheets]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artificial wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ giant wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ massive wall]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sea level rise]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ global warming]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/keto-low-carb-diets-could-be-bad-for-you-in-the-long-run-3701169</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Keto, low-carb diets could be bad for you in the long run 3701169]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[BOSTON — Popular low-carb diets like keto may be all the rage these days, but new studies have found that they may not be good for you in the long run.

Business Insider reports that the ketogenic diet is a high-fat, low carb plan where healthy fats make up 80% of a person's daily calories, and protein 20%. Only 50 grams of carbohydrates are allowed a day, compared to the USDA recommendation of 225 to 325 grams.

The idea is to go into a state of ketosis, in which the body burns fat instead of carbohydrates for energy.

But while a ketogenic diet helps reduce sugar and processed food intake, according to a study of overweight men published in the American Journal of Clinical Nutrition, it doesn't necessarily burn more body fat.

Dieters tend to eliminate healthier carbohydrates like bananas, legumes, or oats, and with them nutrients like magnesium, calcium, and potassium. Some of the findings suggest going low-carb could lead to glucose intolerance or even diabetes, though more research is needed to confirm this.

Research that looked at eating patterns of U.S. adults found that those who ate a moderate amount of carbs were more likely to live longer than high or low carb eaters.

A third study that surveyed Europeans' eating habits revealed that those who ate fewer fresh vegetables, fruits, and nuts are more likely to develop deadly cancers.

Diets sure are tricky. But it seems there's no big secret to eating healthy except for what we've been told time and time again: more greens, less meat, and no junk! 3701169]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWNWGYAHBZEFIAIWLBPWX6JFGVABTSK2KIAWMHAHK2JFEBAABE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D8B/7A8/D8B7A8272913460732EB2508BEFAD2BB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-26T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>100</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ keto diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ketogenic diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ low carb diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ low carb]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ consequences of keto diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ healthy diet]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ healthy eating]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weight loss]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-first-floating-dairy-farm-set-to-open-in-netherlands-3702158</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[World's first floating dairy farm set to open in Netherlands 3702158]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ROTTERDAM, NETHERLANDS — The world's first fully-functional floating dairy farm is set to begin operations in the Netherlands. 

According to Business Insider, the three-level, 89-by-89 foot complex will be floating in the water in Rotterdam. 
The floating dairy will have 40 cows and can produce around 211 gallons of milk daily. 
The bottom level of the facility will house the processing and packaging machinery, with the cows and milking robots on the second level, while the third floor will grow clover and grass for the cows to eat.  
According to Minke van Wingerden, co-leader of the project, who spoke with Business Insider, the farm will try to recycle as much as possible. Cows will be fed leftover food waste from the city. The cows' manure will be processed and sold as fertilizer. 
She also said the floating farm can be made to be hurricane-resistant. 
Van Wingerden said Beladon is currently in talks with another Dutch city for a second farm. She said they are also interested in opening farms in Singapore and China. 3702158]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DFMYAFKEAWZDCHLSPA3LSGGEBS3U3SAWJR5GTRKRBAAARGLD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5E7/1D3/5E71D3FC42A8EAB2C64A32FC48697054.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>69</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ floating dairy farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ floating farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Beladon]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Beladon floating dairy farm]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Beladon floating farm]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-finds-humans-are-causing-earth-to-wobble-more-as-it-spins-3701903</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[NASA finds humans are causing Earth to wobble more as it spins 3701903]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[EARTH  — There are three reasons why our planet wobbles: glacial rebound, melting of ice and mantle convection, according to a study published in the journal Earth and Planetary Science Letters.

Earth's shape and weight distribution isn't perfectly even, due to the mountains and glaciers on Earth's surface. Large glaciers, such as Antarctica or the Arctic, compress the earth which causes the sides of the planet to bulge outward.

As the glaciers start to melt, the land would gradually start to regain its original shape. This process is referred to as glacial rebound and was found to only be responsible for about 3.5 centimeters of axis wobble each year.

Scientists used to believe glacial rebound was the main reason why Earth would wobble.

NASA found the melting of the ice, fueled by the release of greenhouse gases, accounted for one third of Earth's wobble.

Mantle convection also affects the planet's spin as molten rock rises and falls and can redistribute Earth's mass.

NASA says the planet's wobble will continue to increase as the combination of these three factors continue to affect Earth.

However, they added the wobble isn't large enough to impact ecosystems...for now. 3701903]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6LWXCZFAAGAXAISKEDRKKDYGEDSKUT2LSJWVTABARCFGYZHAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4A6/B52/4A6B523BD4F856A18310E1B76C0447F6.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>72</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ NASA]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Earth]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth's wobble]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth wobble 2018]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the earth is wobbling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ earth's spin]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glacial rebound]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ice melting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ mantle convection]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ factors affecting earth's wobble]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/france-cleaning-up-tire-sea-sanctuary-3701867</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[France cleaning up tire sea sanctuary 3701867]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FRANCE — France has begun removing 25,000 car tires it dumped into the Mediterranean in the 1980s off the French coast.

The move comes after officials failed to restore marine life and instead began polluting the water. 
According to the AFP, beginning last week, divers and a specially rigged boat have begun hauling out hundreds of old rubber tires about 500 meters from the coastline between Cannes and Antibes. 
The original idea was to have the tires serve as a sanctuary for marine life and as a foundation for coral to grow. 
According to Denis Genovese, head of an association of local fisherman, talking to the AFP, sedentary creatures did not use them, while grouper fish, conger eels and sea bream swim around them. 
A University of Nice study in 2005 discovered that the tires were leaching toxic chemicals, including heavy metals, into the water.

Another concern now is that after 40 years, the tires will break down into smaller pieces putting nearby seagrass meadows at risk. 
In 2015, 2,500 tires were removed to show that the clean up could be done safely. 
Around 10,000 tires are scheduled to be removed over the next few weeks, with the remaining 12,500 set to be pulled in the second quarter of 2019. 

The tires will be sent to recycling centers where they will be broken down into smaller pieces to be used in construction. 3701867]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2LFGDTVAECA5VZWBNIAKLUTGECB5RTRLWIWZFKYAMBWPDIFAG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4C5/D32/4C5D3255B5586B026568D513042F3C1C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>70</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ France tire sea sanctuary]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ France tire sea]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tire sea sanctuary cleanup]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tire sanctuary]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/viral-photo-shows-baby-crawling-across-lakewood-road-3701809</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Viral photo shows baby crawling across Lakewood road 3701809]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[LAKEWOOD, NEW JERSEY — The internet went ballistic over the weekend after a baby was photographed crawling across a New Jersey street.

The Lakewood Patch reports that Cory Cannon had been driving through Lakewood Saturday night when he spotted what he thought was a toy in the middle of the road.

It wasn't until it moved that he realized it was a real-life baby crawling across the street on all fours.

He immediately stopped his truck to block traffic, and snapped the now-controversial photo as proof before picking up the baby and calling the cops.

A neighbor later came out and took the baby back to his parents, who only then realized their kid wasn't in the house. They say the whole incident was an accident, and that the tiny tot might have crawled out through an open door left open by an older sibling.

Authorities are currently investigating what happened with the help of the New Jersey Department of Child Protection and Permanency.

Still, there's no reassuring angry netizens, and the viral shot has since sparked a flurry of comments about bad parenting.

Even Cannon is getting flak for snapping a photo before rescuing the baby, which he claims was only meant to protect himself as a black man in America.

Had he picked the little dude up and drove to the police station, another driver might assume kidnapping and call it in — and we all know how that pans out. 3701809]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6IRCAIFA2LACWZSKBPAR7BAMIDB3RTZLWPA5UCYK2KAKC3SLC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4FF/1C1/4FF1C14071888673EFB2ECE28C7C7037.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>66</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lakewood baby case]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby on road]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby crossing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby crawling on road]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad parenting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ viral photo]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby crossing road]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ baby's day out]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/new-kind-of-therapy-could-help-those-with-paralysis-walk-again-3701803</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[New kind of therapy could help those with paralysis walk again 3701803]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Researchers have tested a new technique using electrical stimulation on the spinal cords of paralyzed patients to help them walk again.

A device called the epidural stimulator was implanted over a portion of the lower spinal cord, according a study published in the New England Journal of Medicine.

The device itself does not move the legs for the person, however it enables the neurons and nerves to be stimulated and receive signals the brain used to send before the patients became paralyzed.

The device has the ability to be turned on and off by a touch of a button.

The patients were also required to undergo intensive physical therapy along with electrical stimulation, and were taught how to train their bodies and minds on how to move again.

A participant of the study says the stimulator helped restore functions of the body such as bladder control and regaining muscle mass.
 
A researcher told The Washington Post, the study shows that the brain has the capability of relearning to walk in the right conditions.

The study was conducted with 14 paralyzed patients, with only three being able to regain the ability the walk. 3701803]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNLWIAABAABRADAYLMART944NEDERS33AFKRTFALKVCRMAAGAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/21C/653/21C6535AA7013C862F58EB836A138090.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-27T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spinal cord]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ therapy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ spinal cord stimulation]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paralysis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paralyzed people]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paralyzed people walking again]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ research]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ neuron]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nerves]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ epidural stimulator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ stimulator]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ paralyzed people walking again]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ physical therapy]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ relearning to walk]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ relearning to walk after injury]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/cuddly-puppies-causing-drug-resistant-illnesses-3702842</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Cuddly puppies causing drug-resistant illnesses 3702842]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA — The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention says puppies are to blame for spreading a drug-resistant bacterial infection to more than 100 people across the country.  
According to CNN, the CDC says puppies have caused more than that one-hundred people to become ill in at least 18 states from campylobacter bacteria.
It's a common bacteria that causes diarrhea, stomach pains and fever. 

The main problem is that it is normally resistant to antibiotics. 
According to the CDC, puppies from six pet store chains between January 2017 and February 2018 were responsible for the outbreak. 
No deaths have been reported, but at least 26 people were hospitalized. Samples from all patients showed that the bacteria was resistant to all forms of antibiotics. 
Without treatment, patients normally recover from a campylobacter bacterial infection in around five days. 
According to the CDC, 95 percent of the patients say they had come into direct contact with a pet store puppy.    

The CDC reminded the public to wash and sanitize hands before and after handling new animals. 3702842]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWLWIYAHBVHWKCCDLFKAKLD4NADSVFKSLSIWXHAHBZCWAAADAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/501/894/5018947668FA55F503EF07D41FE1D0DB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ drug-resistant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antibiotic resistant]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ campylobacter bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ puppy campylobacter bacteria]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ puppies]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cute puppy]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/husband-gets-tongue-bitten-off-by-pregnant-wife-for-being-ugly-3702452</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Husband gets tongue bitten off by pregnant wife for being ugly 3702452]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI — A poor chap in India nearly lost his tongue after frustration with his not-so-good looks prompted his pregnant wife to bite it off.

The Times of India reports that according to the police, the two 22-year-olds weren't exactly compatible, and fought regularly. Locals say the woman also thought her husband was ugly, which only made things worse.

Reports say the couple had only just patched up after an argument when the wife kissed him, and then deliberately bit off nearly half of his tongue.

The man has since undergone surgery, but doctors can't say if he'll ever be able to talk again.

His pregnant wife was later detained after her father-in-law reported the incident to the police.

She already confessed to committing the bizarre act. But as to whether it was pregnancy hormones, long-simmering hatred, or just the crazies that pushed her to do it is anyone's guess. 3702452]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AMCAGYKSL2MFIBIXLMBAT6JBGJLSRET5AJKRXTICKSIRCWTVAH?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/882/753/882753FA2862077E5CD8DAAA8D7D51F0.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ugly husband]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ugly]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bite tongue]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tongue bitten off]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tongue bite]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ pregnant wife]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ married life]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bad marriage]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/400-year-old-shipwreck-discovered-off-portugal-s-coast-3702446</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[400-year-old shipwreck discovered off Portugal's coast 3702446]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[PORTUGAL — Researchers are hailing the discovery of a 400-year-old ship as one of the most significant finds of this decade.

A team of archaeologists have discovered an ancient shipwreck off the coast of Cascais, Portugal earlier this month, reports The Guardian.

The ship was believed to be returning from a trip to India and was carrying different relics from the late 16th or early 17th century when it sank.

The wreckage was discovered 12 meters beneath the surface of the water, covering an area 100 meters long and 50 meters wide.

The director of the project said the wreckage was discovered by divers using geophysical survey equipment.

Peppercorns, cowrie shells and nine bronze cannons were found at the site as well as 
fragments of Chinese porcelain dating back to the 16th and 17th century.

The mayor of Cascais said the discovery is extraordinary and helps us learn more about history. 

Officials plan to examine the artifacts and believe there is still more to be discovered at the site. 3702446]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KRCFKYIGLZHFIBKHL2KW79D3NEBS3STRAJLWVGICB2KWIB3WAF?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/02E/03A/02E03A58D6DC320C6EDEBB1217290FEA.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Portugal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shipwreck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ shipwreck found off coast of Portugal]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 400-year-old shipwreck]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ wreckage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ artifacts]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ relics]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ ancient discovery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cowrie shells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ peppercorns]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bronze cannons]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ chinese porcelain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ discovering a shipwreck]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-with-brain-tumor-receives-3d-printed-titanium-skull-plate-3702375</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Dog with brain tumor receives 3D-printed titanium skull plate 3702375]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ONTARIO, CANADA — Doctors in Canada used 3D-printing technology to replace a dog's skull with titanium following major cancer surgery.

According to an article released by the University of Guelph, a 9-year-old dachshund named Patches had a large tumor growing into her skull, pushing dangerously close to her brain and eye socket.

Using an innovative new approach, University of Guelph researchers used rapid prototyping to print out a 3D model of Patches' head and tumor.

This enabled veterinary surgeons to do a test run of the tumor removal, and create a custom fitted titanium plate to replace the parts of the skull that would be lost.

Because of the technique, what would have been a lengthy surgery took only four hours, with Patches waking up just 30 minutes after the procedure.

The procedure is believed to be the first of its kind in North America, and marks an advancement in veterinary medicine that researchers say can also be useful in human medicine. 3702375]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K5DAADIFLSNRICKHLFJWR7LVM6KBTSC5K2PF5FAEKSKAEWIPKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8E6/700/8E67002F5EF037F9434936713FC864CB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-28T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>59</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ 3D printing]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cancer surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dog tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tumor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ tumor surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rapid prototyping]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ dachshund]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ veterinary surgery]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-antibiotics-could-be-used-to-treat-appendicitis-3703464</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds antibiotics could be used to treat appendicitis 3703464]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[FINLAND — There is an alternative to patients with appendicitis who don't want to get surgery, according to a study published in the Journal of the American Medical Association.

In the past, appendicitis was considered a medical emergency, with surgeons removing the appendix immediately as they feared there was a possibility it would burst.

However, the researchers found that nearly two-thirds of patients with appendicitis don't have to fear their appendix would burst and can choose to take antibiotics instead.

Only 7 percent of patients who received antibiotics were found to have some kind of complications, with the authors saying the success rate for the antibiotic treatment was almost 64 percent.

However, 36 percent of the patients eventually needed surgery to remove their appendix.

The author of the study says antibiotics instead of surgery is a feasible, viable and a safe option for those who have an uncomplicated appendix, meaning they don't need to worry about their appendix bursting.

In an editorial accompanying the study, the deputy editor of the journal said the treatment has a high chance of success, but that the public could also choose to get surgery if don't want to worry about appendicitis coming back again. 3703464]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/AFIAADTUA6LAEVATLSIRVKDVMIDSZST4K2PAVU3SA5DRVBTYAA?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/55C/A71/55CA7187C5ADBE97569F63EF404103E8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>405</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ appendix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ uncomplicated appendix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ complicated appendix]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ appendicitis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ appendicitis surgery]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ antibiotics for appendicitis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ appendicitis antibiotics used]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ avoiding surgery for appendicitis]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ appendix bursting]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ removing appendix]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-misses-his-flight-decides-to-chase-plane-down-tarmac-3703437</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man misses his flight, decides to chase plane down tarmac 3703437]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[DUBLIN, IRELAND — Irish po po busted a man at the Dublin airport on Thursday for breaking onto the tarmac and trying to chase down a plane after missing his flight.
According to the BBC, 23-year-old Patrick Kehoe and a woman missed a Ryanair flight to Amsterdam. 
According to a statement from an airport spokesman, they were engaging with Ryanair staff at the gate and the male passenger was becoming agitated, BBC reported. 

Kehoe then started banging on the window to try to get the aircraft to wait — hold up — that didn't work? 
That's when Kehoe took matters into his own hands by breaking through a locked door and rushing onto the tarmac — with his suitcase under his arm — so he could chase the plane down himself. 
Everything was going according to plan until Ryanair workers stepped in and retrained Kehoe. Airport police showed up after that and introduced Kehoe to some pavement and handcuffs.

Kehoe was charged with criminal damage to a door lock and granted bail. He was released on his own bond and is scheduled to appear in court again on November 8. 3703437]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KNJAGAIBAWKR3WAUBRDWX94XMBJE7RALABKF3HAFKEEAVBTYKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/70E/1E2/70E1E22D7DF2E0E57CE446C8B2F6C3B8.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>65</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ misses flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man misses flight]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man chases plane]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man chases plane down tarmac]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man misses Ryanair flight]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/introducing-the-brett-kavanaugh-calendar-app-3703336</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Introducing the Brett Kavanaugh Calendar app 3703336]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA['MURICA —  Are one of those people who is always forgetting or missing important dates or appointments?

Or are you someone who painstakingly plans your activities down on a calendar and then also retroactively goes back and amends said calendar to reflect actual events? 

Well, as the confirmation hearings for Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh continue to captivate the nation, lots of names have been dragged through the mud — but none can be more egregious than the sullying of meticulous calendar keepers. 
What's wrong with a little — or a lot — of organization in your life? That's why developers at Tomo have developed an AI-enhanced, state-of-the-art Kavanaugh Calendar app. 
Big party at so and so's next week? We got you covered. Is today arms or legs day at Planet Fitness? We got you covered. Did I whip out my junk last night? You should cover that up. 
With the Kavanaugh Calendar app, you can plan out your sexual assaults months in advance or amend them on the fly. It's also great for victims too. 
The app has just been released on Apple App Store and Google Play Store. Get yours today — and never miss anything again. 3703336]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWIFMCAHA5AAIARRB5CWTLBGMRAV5RC2KFJW5TIGKSJAKCRBKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1C2/167/1C21679B90375D7336F48AEC46F5798E.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>75</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Brett Kavanaugh]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Brett Kavanaugh calendar]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Kavanaugh Calendar app]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Supreme Court]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Supreme Court nominee]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/man-hacks-off-own-arm-to-save-own-life-after-sausage-accident-3703328</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Man hacks off own arm to save own life after sausage accident 3703328]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[JAMESTOWN, NORTH DAKOTA — A North Dakota man amazingly cut off his own arm to save his life after it became stuck in an electric meat mixer. 
According to KFGO, Myron Schlafman was making sausage in his garage on Aug. 17.
According to AP, he went to remove a chunk of meat from the machine, when he accidentally stepped on the power pedal, pulling his left arm into the machine. 
Myron said the bone was severed but that his hand remained attached by some skin, nerves and tissue. 
Talking to KFGO, Schlafman said, when my arm went in there, that must have been instant shock. I just looked and knew I was in big trouble. When I cut off my arm, I could feel my nerves jumping. If I would have hesitated, I would have stood right there and bled to death.
Schlafman also credited two responding officers for saving his life by quickly applying a tourniquet. 
The 69-year-old Vietnam veteran was then transported to the hospital, were he spent nine days and underwent three surgeries. 

After his arm heals, Myron will be fitted with a prosthetic. 3703328]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/A2IRCAKVA2LR3ATFBSKFZL2AMNJBZFIMAFJR3TKTKFKRGBIDAB?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/22A/559/22A55983DBE7CEA820A080CFEAE99E4C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>68</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ man making sausage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sausage making accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ sausage accident]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cut off]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/study-finds-increase-of-bee-deaths-may-be-linked-to-weed-killer-3703136</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Study finds increase of bee deaths may be linked to weed killer 3703136]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS — Monsanto is being accused of killing off bees around the world, reports NPR.

Bees are being exposed to glyphosate, an ingredient in weed killer, according to a new study published in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences

Scientists painted the bees' backs with colored dots to track them, and found that  glyphosate significantly decreased the amount of healthy gut bacteria in honey bees.

This could increase the chance of bees receiving infections or even dying because of harmful bacteria.

They believe glyphosate may be contributing to colony collapse disorder, a phenomenon when bee colonies are wiped out.

Scientists encouraged the public to avoid spraying using weed killers that contain glyphosate when they are spraying their flowers.

The researchers involved say better guidelines are needed to regulate use of glyphosate in order to protect bees.

In a statement, Monsanto denied the accusations and claims no large-scale study has ever found a link between glyphosate and honey bee health issues. 3703136]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ANIAGY3SA6KWGCZ9LNPWX9SAMEAV5S3RA5BWRUZCA2JAXBAEKC?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5D0/074/5D007434598BDFCFFA7B05E053BCFFFB.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>60</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ honey bees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bees dying]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bees dying at alarming rate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ glyphosate]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ weed killer]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ colony collapse disorder]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[  colony collapse disorder bees]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee death]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bee death linked to weed killer]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/school-bus-driver-fired-for-letting-young-kids-drive-the-bus-3703123</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[School bus driver fired for letting young kids drive the bus 3703123]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[VALPARAISO,INDIANA — A bus driver in Indiana was caught on camera letting young students drive her bus during her afternoon route, according to a report from NBC News.

Apparently 27-year-old Joandrea McAtee would allow her young students to take turns driving her bus for short distances after the school day ended.

The three students, ages 11, 13 and 17 each took turns steering the wheel. McAtee is seen helping them steer the wheel too.

Well, someone was smart enough to record the incident which is a parent came forward to report it.

McAtee was immediately fired from her job as a school bus driver and taken into custody.

McAtee was charged with neglect of a dependent, a level six felony, reports The Times of Northwest Indiana.

Who ever thought letting kids drive a school bus would be a good idea? 3703123]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/K6JFEDIFAVCACAZXLEARX6D4MBKETSCZKNLFXGAGKFKRGBRDAE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/56B/A5B/56BA5B0E410AFFD02708F8EA8B6C2EA2.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>57</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Indiana]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ school bus driver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bus driver]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bus driver gets fired for letting kids drive]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kids driving bus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kids driving school bus]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ young students driving]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kids take turn driving]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ kids taking the wheel]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-may-be-close-to-finding-a-cure-for-alzheimer-s-disease-3703112</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Scientists may be close to finding a cure for Alzheimer's disease 3703112]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[USA — Scientists have found a way to target toxic particles that destroys healthy brain cells and leads to illnesses such as Alzheimer's disease, according to a new study published in the journal PNAS.

Alzheimer's disease causes the brain to shrink dramatically over time, which leads to memory loss, personality changes along with other symptoms.

Researchers have identified the toxic particles, small clumps of protein known as oligomers, as the most likely cause of dementia.

Proteins in the brain are usually responsible for vital cell processes, however when they form clumps and start to build up, they start killing healthy nerve cells instead.

Researchers involved developed small molecules which would target oligomers and work to slow down the formation of these toxic particles.

The study claims their method was the first to directly target the toxic oligomers.

Alzheimer's disease affects millions of people worldwide and the team hopes the study would lead to the development of new drugs to treat the disease in a few years. 3703112]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KBIRADZCA2LAGW3HLFKA76DUGRBBVST9KNIR3HIBKZERPV3RAD?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/838/C39/838C391EDB518001284257FCB34DFD44.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>58</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Study]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ science]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's disease]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's cure]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ cure for alzheimer's]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ oligomers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic oligomers]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ toxic particles]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's treatment]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's drugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ new alzheimer's drugs]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ nerve cells]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ brain shrinkage]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ alzheimer's brain]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/bachelor-vietnam-contestants-ditch-dude-for-each-other-3703057</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Bachelor Vietnam contestants ditch dude for each other 3703057]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[HANOI, VIETNAM — In a twist absolutely no one was expecting, two contestants on the Vietnam version of the Bachelor ditched the titular lead and left to be together.

If you need a refresher, The Bachelor is a reality dating show that has women compete for the affections of one supposedly swoon-worthy male.

The rose ceremony is basically elimination night, where the man gives a rose to whoever he wants to keep on.

But in possibly the wildest moment in show history, one woman confessed that she'd fallen in love not with the bachelor, but with a fellow contestant, and begged to leave together.

Even more shocking is that she actually agreed, and went to return her rose. The emotional scene ended with both women walking away.

Sadly, that love story ended pretty quickly. In yet another plot twist, Next Shark revealed that straightness prevailed and the bachelor managed to convince his runaway lady to come back and win his love.

Female relationships springing from the Bachelor isn't entirely new. The Australia edition previously saw two women start dating after the show ended, though they've since broken up. However, it might be the first time a pair of ladies struck up a romance while still doing the program. 3703057]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/ABJWGC3TARCRPBZTKBKARKLSGNJE7SK7A6PF5HZLKEDRCVTSKE?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9EC/02C/9EC02C45C7BFE1D737299906843D5D0C.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>61</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bachelor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ bachelor vietnam]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ the bachelor]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ rose ceremony]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ LGBT]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ lesbian]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ surprise love story]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
  <url>
    <loc>http://us.tomonews.com/methane-gas-found-leaking-from-alaskan-lake-3703040</loc>
    <video:video>
      <video:title><![CDATA[Methane gas found leaking from Alaskan lake 3703040]]></video:title>
      <video:description><![CDATA[ALASKA — Researchers have discovered a lake in Alaska that is bubbling due to methane emissions. 

Due to increasing temperatures from global warming, ground that used to be permafrost in the Arctic is now thawing and releasing trapped greenhouse gases into the air, thereby accelerating climate change. 
According to the Washington Post, Katey Walter Anthony, an associate professor at the University of Alaska Fairbanks, Esieh Lake is bubbling because of methane gas.  

The gases are geological in origin. The researchers say there are fossil fuels buried close to the bottom of the lake, and in combination with the melting of the permafrost, represent a source of greenhouse gases. 
The lake emits around two tons of methane gas daily — the equivalent of methane emissions from 6,000 dairy cows. 

Scientists will need to do further research to see if this phenomenon is occurring in other Arctic lakes. 3703040]]></video:description>
      <video:content_loc>http://api.nm.anvato.net/v2/media/KWJWMXRHARAFMACDL2KFR72BGEEERU3RAWKW7HRAASKFAWRMKG?fmt=mp4</video:content_loc>
      <video:thumbnail_loc>https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A4A/A06/A4AA060B5E0D22D06F32B13F9882E187.jpg</video:thumbnail_loc>
      <video:publication_date>2018-09-29T19:35:01+00:00</video:publication_date>
      <video:duration>63</video:duration>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[TomoNews]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Satire]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Esieh Lake]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Esieh Lake bubbling]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ Esieh Lake methane emissions]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ greenhouse gases]]></video:tag>
      <video:tag><![CDATA[ climate change]]></video:tag>
    </video:video>
  </url>
</urlset>
