<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3970157</guid>
      <title>Russian police seize custom batmobile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW <br/> Police in Moscow have confiscated a batmobile replica over concerns that its not up to road safety standards.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the vehicle was a fully functional replica of the batmobile seen in the ridiculously bad 2016 film Batman V Superman: Dawn of Justice.  <br/><br/>A statement from Russia's Ministry of Internal Affairs says the custom batmobile was spotted in central Moscow and subsequently seized by police because it wasn't manufactured within factory conditions, and therefore not roadworthy.<br/><br/>Officials say the vehicle's dimensions "exceeded applicable norms."<br/><br/>The owner, a 32-year-old from Moscow, is now being investigated on three different charges: the batmobile's lack of documentation, its excessive weight and size, and the irregular features that aren't allowed on road-driven vehicles.<br/><br/>There's no indication that the owner is trying to be a crime-fighting vigilante ala Batman, so maybe he's just a massive fan with a lot of cash to spare.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-police-seize-custom-batmobile-3970157</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/02/3970157/3970157_D246245CE3504CEE948CC5A74EC77DAC_200302_3970157_Russian_police_seize_custom_batmobile_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 02:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970561</guid>
      <title>Woman goes blind after having her eyeballs tattooed black</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WARSAW, POLAND  <br/> Aleksandra Sadowska, a 25-year-old from Wroclaw, Poland and devoted follower of famous rapper 'Popek' decided to copy him by getting the whites of her eyes dyed black.<br/><br/>After the eye-watering procedure, she began complaining of sharp pain in her eyeballs, according to her, the tattooist said it was normal and could be treated with painkillers.<br/><br/>Despite taking the advice, Aleksandra has since tragically lost the sight in her right eye and been warned the irreparable damage will soon claim the vision in her left eye too.<br/><br/>During an investigation, it emerged the tattooist from Warsaw, known as 'Piotr A' made a number of serious errors, including using ink made for use on skin, which should never come into contact with the eyes.<br/><br/>The tattooist, who still runs his salon where he carries out mainly ear piercings, has now been charged, four years after Aleksandra's ordeal began. If sentenced, he could face three years in prison for unintentionally severely disabling the woman.<br/><br/>How did he plea? Not guilty.<br/><br/>Incredibly, however, she's not letting it defeat her, saying, "I will not lock myself in the basement and get depressed. I have sadness behind me but I live on."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-goes-blind-after-having-her-eyeballs-tattooed-black-3970561</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/03/3970561/3970561_1445161CEA694A38AAC8A172BA17C94E_200303_3970561_Woman_goes_blind_after_having_her_eyeballs_tatto_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 01:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971457</guid>
      <title>How airlines are sanitizing planes amid the coronavirus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> As the novel coronavirus spreads globally, major airlines are taking preventative measures to ensure their airplanes are as clean as possible.<br/><br/>Southwest Airlines told CNN Travel that their airlines' cleaning procedure includes disinfecting all hard surfaces inside the cabin as well as cleaning all seats and the carpet amid the outbreak of Covid-19.<br/><br/>An American Airlines spokesperson told the broadcasting network that airplane lavatories and floors are being thoroughly cleaned while all visible trash on seat pockets is removed before every flight.<br/><br/>A Qantas Airways spokesperson explained that their cabins, seats, galleys and washrooms are being cleaned and disinfected. <br/><br/>The spokesperson also noted that their planes use HEPA filters as part of their air-conditioning systems. The airline says the filters "provide much cleaner air than other public spaces" such as trains or shopping centers.<br/><br/>Delta Air Lines says it is using a technique called fogging, which involves spraying an EPA-registered disinfectant on all trans-Pacific flights landing in the U.S. The airline says it plans to expand fogging to more inbound international flights.<br/><br/>Cathay Pacific is replacing all seat covers and disinfecting all surfaces and carpets as well as sterilizing water equipment and replacing air filters, CNN reports. <br/><br/>The airline has also stopped providing hot towels, pillows, blankets, magazines and duty-free service on all flights to and from China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-airlines-are-sanitizing-planes-amid-the-coronavirus-outbreak-3971457</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/05/3971457/3971457_C94FA76C0DD14B0D82528363ECEDAC23_200305_3971457_How_airlines_are_sanitizing_planes_amid_the_coro_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 03:09:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971940</guid>
      <title>Inflatable latex pants for dudes may be the next big fashion trend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> If you're one of those people who has been waiting for the concept of truck nuts to be translated into high fashion, your day has finally arrived.<br/>According to VT,  for his London College of Fashion graduate collection, menswear designer Harikrishnan came up with the idea to make men's inflatable latex pants.<br/>The amazing pants were strutting their stuff out on the catwalk earlier this month. <br/>The extremely bulbous pants are made up of 30 separate latex panels; either solid white or in strips of red and green. <br/>In a recent interview with Dezeen, he said he got the idea, "when I was playing with my dog and I started thinking about how exaggerated objects must look like from such a low angle. The thought of him seeing me as a giant figure or not seeing my head at all was intriguing, so I decided to reimagine the people around me through the game of distortion."<br/>He also added, "In fashion, I see the same images and similar proportions everywhere. I want to create visual imagery that's as far away as possible from neutrality, to make people question the relevance of the proportions we see every day."<br/><br/>They still kind of look like truck nuts in pant form.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/inflatable-latex-pants-for-dudes-may-be-the-next-big-fashion-trend-3971940</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/06/3971940/3971940_F7EC54743BFC4A2288E891C83C7B3FFD_200306_3971940_Inflatable_latex_pants_for_dudes_may_be_the_next_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 02:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3972991</guid>
      <title>Airlines are wasting thousands of gallons of fuel on 'ghost flights'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EUROPE <br/> Airlines are wasting thousands of gallons of jet fuel flying EMPTY airplanes amid China's latest gift to the world because of some fantastic European rule saying operators can lose their flight slots if they're not flying. <br/>Business Insider reports that people around the world are saying no thanks to air travel as the China Sniffles-19 has spread like wildfire around the globe <br/>According to Business Insider, European nanny rules demand that airlines flying out of Europe must continue to run 80 percent of their assigned slots or risk losing them to competitors. <br/>The Times of London reports that this has led to some airlines flying completely empty  "ghost flights" to and from Europe.<br/>Clearly, destroying the environment for business is probably the best way to go. And luckily jet fuel grows on trees, so we'll always have more to burn. <br/>According to the failing New York Times, the airline industry has been one of the harder hit industries among the recent Co-China-19 madness with some estimates saying worldwide revenue to fall $63 billion to $113 billion for the year. <br/>Our thoughts and prayers go out to airlines across the world during these trying times. Stay strong guys.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/airlines-are-wasting-thousands-of-gallons-of-fuel-on-ghost-flights--3972991</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/09/3972991/3972991_4D5D4B419E68415E9901E1291BDDB051_200309_3972991_Airlines_are_wasting_thousands_of_gallons_of_fue_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 01:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973462</guid>
      <title>Soccer legend Ronaldinho in jail for using fake passport</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ASUNCION, PARAGUAY <br/> Brazilian soccer legend Ronaldinho has been labeled, "stupid" by his lawyer after being banged up for using a fake passport.<br/><br/>His bizarre and brazen comment came during an interview with a Brazilian newspaper, saying "the courts have not taken into account the fact that Ronaldinho didn't know he was committing a crime, because he didn't understand he had been given false documents. He is stupid."<br/><br/>The 39-year-old Samba star and tiki-taka legend, along with his brother Roberto were hauled to court after being arrested at the Sheraton Hotel in Asuncion on Friday.<br/><br/>While Ronaldinho's lawyer appeals a decision not to allow the star to be placed in house arrest, the first photos of him in prison appeared on social media still sporting his trademark grin.<br/><br/>And Blas Vera, the head of the Paraguayan jail, told Reuters, "In broad terms, he is doing very well. I see he is in good spirits, just like you see him on television, always smiling."<br/><br/>The footy star known for his tricks on the pitch, along with his brother, are claiming they're the ones who were tricked. His lawyer has said Ronaldinho had been given his Paraguayan passport as a "gift" by a businessman, assumed it was an "honorary-type" document of no real value and gave it to an official without thinking when he reached Paraguay because it was the "first thing he got out of his bag."<br/><br/>This Brazilian businessman who is alleged to have handed over the passports and two women believed to be the rightful owners of the travel documents are now also in custody.<br/><br/>Interestingly, Ronaldinho did actually have his Brazilian passport confiscated after he was convicted alongside his brother of building an illegal fishing platform on a lake in a conservation area, but Paraguayan prosecutors confirmed earlier this week that it had been returned to him<br/><br/>So why didn't he use his own passport when entering Paraguay? Twinned with his lawyer's comments about it being the "first thing" he laid his hands on, this situation is being greeted with a mixture of ridicule and disbelief.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/soccer-legend-ronaldinho-in-jail-for-using-fake-passport-3973462</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/10/3973462/3973462_851038C297EB430DA44EF8E4D1B30822_200310_3973462_Soccer_legend_Ronaldinho_in_jail_for_using_fake__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 05:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973521</guid>
      <title>Great Barrier Reef may soon face dangerous bleaching period</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOWNSVILLE, AUSTRALIA <br/> Hot weather over the coming weeks could see the Great Barrier Reef enter a period of dangerous coral bleaching, reports Vice.com.<br/><br/>Citing international marine experts, Phys.org reports that Australia's Great Barrier Reef might soon face another period of severe coral bleaching if the warmer than average March weather continues to heat the reef. The last time that happened large swathes of corals were wiped out.<br/>For scale, the GBR is around the same size as Japan. Vice reports that between 2016 and 2017 half of all corals died in Australia's Great Barrier Reef following a series of heatwaves.  According to National Geographic, 30 percent died in 2016, and a further 20 percent perished in 2017 due to heat stress.<br/><br/>The coming weeks will be a "critical time" for the reef, explained David Wachenfield, Chief Scientist at the Great Barrier Reef Marine Park Authority (GBRMPA), in a weekly update on the reef's health posted to GBPRMPA YouTube channel.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/great-barrier-reef-may-soon-face-dangerous-bleaching-period-3973521</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/10/3973521/3973521_98D51184C8084A3F9BFD0C95B9B9B96E_200310_3973521_Great_Barrier_Reef_may_soon_face_dangerous_bleac_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 07:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973838</guid>
      <title>POLICE CHASE: Man can't stop because "bird in the back"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SURREY, U.K. <br/>  A businessman who fled police in his Rolls-Royce claimed he could not stop because a woman was performing a sex act on him.<br/><br/>57-year-old Businessman Maurice 'Fred' Sines, who owns a string of lucrative caravan parks, took police on a pursuit back in May 2018, from a PGA golf tournament through the exclusive Wentworth Estate. <br/><br/>Guildford Crown Court heard that there had been complaints about his behavior earlier in the day and police had arrived at the tournament to see him leaving.<br/><br/>The Daily Mail report that the police began to pursue him when they spotted his car driving erratically. During the pursuit, his $500,000 Phantom drove on the wrong side of the road, went the wrong way around a roundabout, hit speeds of 96kmph in a 40kmph, and narrowly avoided a head-on crash.<br/><br/>The pursuit came to an end when officers experienced problems with their radios, shortly after, they found his car abandoned nearby. <br/><br/>When officers finally caught up with him he confessed he was in the car but it was being driven by a chauffeur who he had ordered not to stop because he had "a bird in the back", and claimed he didn't want to be caught because he had recently gotten back with his wife.<br/><br/>However, CCTV showed that Sines was actually in the car alone; the story was fabricated, he had refused to stop because he was driving while banned.<br/><br/>Yesterday on the 10th of March at Guildford Crown Court, Sines was not only handed a suspended sentence but also slapped with a two-year driving ban, a three-month tagged curfew, ordered to pay a $6,500 penalty and $5,400 in court costs.<br/><br/>He said, "I saw a police car and I panicked. I regret what I've done."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/police-chase-man-can-t-stop-because-bird-in-the-back--3973838</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/11/3973838/3973838_D07691413F4941C69C97F20D6482388E_200311_3973838_POLICE_CHASE__Man_can_t_stop_because__bird_in_th_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973900</guid>
      <title>Comet annihilated ancient human village, research suggests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ABU HURERYA, SYRIA <br/> Impact from a comet around 12,800 years ago is believed to have wiped out a human settlement, according to new research published in Scientific Reports.  <br/><br/>The study suggests that meltglass samples found at the Abu Hureyra site in Syria could be evidence that a comet destroyed the area.  <br/><br/>The high-energy and intense heat needed to create the molten glass material could only have resulted from a cosmic impact, suggests study author and University of California Santa Barbara, Geology Professor James Kennet. He says those sorts of temperatures could melt a car in less than 60 seconds.<br/><br/>The findings back a theory known as the Younger Dryas impact hypothesis. This suggests that debris from a disintegrating comet entering Earth's atmosphere struck areas in the Americas, the Middle East and Europe some 12,800 years ago.<br/><br/>Kennet says that the settlement at Abu Hureyra would have been "abruptly destroyed" by such an event.<br/><br/>Thumbnail image via University of California, Santa Barbara.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/comet-annihilated-ancient-human-village-research-suggests-3973900</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/11/3973900/3973900_BFB53C15EDC94F858CE86522108D5A80_200311_3973900_Comet_annihilated_ancient_human_village__researc_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 07:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974043</guid>
      <title>How the coronavirus spread in the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE  <br/>  The spread of the Wuhan coronavirus has medical authorities around the world scrambling to develop efficient ways to detect and contain the pandemic.<br/><br/>Health officials in U.S. have learned that despite doing "everything right" the virus is so contagious that it has managed to go under the radar. This is how the virus entered and spread in U.S.<br/><br/>According to Bloomberg, Patient Zero arrived at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport from Wuhan, China on January 15. During his time there he took public transportation at the airport.<br/><br/>On January 19, he checked himself into a clinic after experiencing a fever and cough. He was admitted, tested for the virus and sent home to self-quarantine. Results of the test came back positive the next day and Patient Zero was then admitted into a special biocontainment ward at Providence Regional Medical Center in Everett, Washington. This unit was originally developed for the Ebola virus. By February 21, Patient Zero had fully recovered. <br/><br/>However, an infected individual or individuals went undetected. Health experts researching the spread in Seattle believe that it was in the four-day window of time from January 15 to 19 that Patient Zero may have infected more people. <br/><br/>Marc Lipsitch, an epidemiology professor at the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health, told Bloomberg that according to his estimates, for every dozen cases American officials caught, 20 to 25 went undetected. <br/><br/>The lack of efficient testing kits and testing criteria also exacerbated the spread of the novel coronavirus. Early testing kits from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention were working well. However, by mid-February, testing results were coming back inconclusive due to manufacturing issues.<br/><br/>Faulty testing criteria also affected early and efficient detection. Early on, only patients with mild symptoms who had come in contact with a potentially infected person or had traveled to Wuhan themselves. This means that individuals who did not fit these criteria who carried the coronavirus were not tested.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-coronavirus-spread-in-the-u-s--3974043</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/11/3974043/3974043_0C21C84118834FFA82D400DF168EA308_200311_3974043_How_the_coronavirus_spread_in_the_U_S__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 12:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974215</guid>
      <title>Churches removing healing holy water amid Wuhan virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOLY LAND <br/> Oh lord<br/>Catholic churches around the world are getting rid of communal holy water and shutting down holy sites amid the recent China-Cough-19 panda-demic. <br/>According to God Daily Dot, the pools of the shrine of Our Lady of Lourdes in France have been closed to the public. The spot is popular for believers who think bathing in the "healing waters" cure sickness<br/>god, that's ironic.<br/>HuffPost reports that Catholic churches in the U.S. are draining holy water fonts. The fonts are used for Catholics to bless themselves as they enter church.   <br/>These are just some of the measures being taken by bishops in Miami, Seattle and Chicago to slow the spread of the Wuhan virus. <br/>According to HuffPost, some bishops are also banning the distribution of consecrated wine through a common cup. <br/>Some bishops have also begun to remind priests and deacons that they can switch up how the host, aka sacramental bread, is offered to churchgoers. <br/>According to HuffPo, priests and lay ministers are being reminded to wash their hands like they have OCD before and after mass, and have hand sanitizer for those distributing Communion. <br/>Don't worry guys...you have God on your side. That is, unless he's down with the Wuhan too.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/churches-removing-healing-holy-water-amid-wuhan-virus-outbreak-3974215</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/12/3974215/3974215_15412FE6045D45369B75C1F603FD1626_200312_3974215_Churches_removing_healing_holy_water_amid_Wuhan__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 04:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975782</guid>
      <title>Dude breaks out of prison using makeshift dummy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SUDBURY, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> A violent UK prisoner is back behind bars after fleeing prison using a makeshift dummy, Birmingham Live reports.<br/><br/>Prisoner Luke Harvey inmate managed to dupe his guards with the dummy one Friday night last August. He was doing 12 years for armed robbery but was due for release this year.<br/><br/>Birmingham Live reports that prisoner Harvey then scaled a 3m fence at Sudbury prison. On the other side his girlfriend, Hannah Smith, was waiting for him in a getaway car. <br/><br/>The two are then said to have gone to Skegness for the weekend.<br/><br/>Harvey told Hannah he was due back at prison on Monday. But, Derbyshire Live reports that he went on the lam for six days by himself before getting a ride from Hannah to Birmingham. And that's when the law caught up with them.<br/><br/>Harvey was sentenced in 2014 to 12 years but would've been released this year. He got another 10 months added to his sentence. Meanwhile, Hannah, a mother of one, got six months and community service. According to Derbyshire live, the two are no longer an item.<br/><br/>WIKIMEDIA COMMONS / DMITRIJ M<br/>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Skegness,_UK_-_panoramio_(17).jpg]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dude-breaks-out-of-prison-using-makeshift-dummy-3975782</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/16/3975782/3975782_815E27B9EE29455FB3161393665FCBA1_200316_3975782_Dude_breaks_out_of_prison_using_makeshift_dummy_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 08:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976575</guid>
      <title>Girl licks toilet seat in Coronavirus Challenge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> Accused 'clout-chaser' and two time Dr. Phil guest, Ava Louise has caused outrage after attempting to start #CoronavirusChallenge by licking a toilet seat.<br/><br/>In the video, which was originally shared to TikTok, the 22-year-old aspiring influencer from Miami is seen licking a toilet seat, allegedly while in a plane bathroom. <br/><br/>Despite people calling for her arrest, she claims that she Cloroxed the toilet for 40 minutes before licking it.<br/><br/>Unfortunately, her so-called "really good" friend followed in tow and filmed himself licking a door handle.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/girl-licks-toilet-seat-in-coronavirus-challenge-3976575</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976575/3976575_094FADEA97854C32B8AAA9957933F1C5_200318_3976575_Girl_licks_toilet_seat_in_Coronavirus_Challenge_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 05:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976674</guid>
      <title>Israel fighting coronavirus with cell phone data</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JERUSALEM <br/> Israel plans to combat the coronavirus outbreak via the cyber-monitoring of its citizens, according to Reuters. <br/><br/>The New York Times reports the country will monitor cell phones to track people with COVID-19 and those who have come into close contact with them. The Israeli government will comb through the geolocation data gathered from the country's telecommunications providers to pinpoint those affected.<br/><br/>This will then be used to track the history of the infected person's movements and to identify potentially infected individuals. Once identified, those suspected of catching the virus will receive a message telling them to self isolate immediately.<br/><br/>According to the Thomson Reuters Foundation, there are 324 cases of the virus in Israel, 41 in Palestine and none in the Gaza Strip.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/israel-fighting-coronavirus-with-cell-phone-data-3976674</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976674/3976674_2EA4A754539B40C0A01D02DEAB39EB99_200318_3976674_Israel_fighting_coronavirus_with_cell_phone_data_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 09:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977424</guid>
      <title>Woman's grim method for staying healthy not backed by Doctors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AYLESBURY, BUCKINGHAMSHIRE, U.K. <br/> Health blogger, Tracy Kiss is encouraging people to consume semen in a bid to stay healthy during the Coronavirus pandemic.  <br/><br/>She claims she ingests her boyfriend's product every day, either "directly" or in a smoothie. <br/><br/>The personal trainer has also been applying his semen on her skin for the past three years, which she dubs "nature's multivitamin." The blogger believes it's overflowing with vitamin C, calcium and magnesium.<br/><br/>The mum-of-two from Aylesbury, Buckinghamshire, said, "the purity of it is just wonderful. It's nature's multivitamin, and it's there, it's natural, it's free. It's everything you need in one daily dose."<br/><br/>She also added, "there were times when my family didn't want to give me a kiss on the cheek."<br/><br/>Dr. Sarah Javis said she was, "extremely worried" when she heard this as she says, "the idea of drinking semen doesn't have the slightest nugget of science behind it and is frankly, extremely worrying."<br/><br/>But Tracy stands by it, in fact, she used to use her best friend's 'product' as a face mask to treat her rosacea, that was, of course, until she met her boyfriend.<br/><br/>Dr. Sarah Jarvis wants people to know that this is a myth, along with all the other "nonsense" out there regarding home remedies to keep you sanitized. She says, "there are clear ways you can protect yourself and they are the messages we are giving out constantly" i.e. wash your hands. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-s-grim-method-for-staying-healthy-not-backed-by-doctors-3977424</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/20/3977424/3977424_B5B434F244254C1C82589639576BDF3D_200320_3977424_Woman_s_grim_method_for_staying_healthy_not_back_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 23:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978492</guid>
      <title>Ronaldinho celebrates his 40th with a prison BBQ</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ASUNCION, PARAGUAY <br/> Despite Ronaldinho being told he faces spending six months behind bars, the tiki-taka legend is celebrating his 40th with a huge BBQ in his Paraguayan jail along with a slice of modest cake. <br/><br/>It comes after he helped some inmates win a 16kg pig with five goals in a prison football tournament.<br/><br/>According to Paraguayan newspaper Hoy, the Ballon d'Or winner was convinced to join in as he watched the match unfold while talking to a prison guard.<br/><br/>The star unsurprisingly showcased his class, scoring five and getting six assists. <br/><br/>Locked up but certainly not forgotten, Ronaldinho also received birthday messages from fellow Brazil 2002 World Cup winners, Ronaldo and Roberto Carlos.<br/><br/>43-year-old, Ronaldo posted a photo of himself with Ronaldinho with the caption, "Congratulations, may you overcome this difficult stage of your life with the same joy as always!"<br/><br/>46-year-old Carlos said, "Best wishes friend." <br/><br/>Surprisingly, the cherished star has so far been snubbed by former club Barcelona, as they used their social media channels to send best wishes out to current stars Antoine Griezmann and Jordi Alba, who were also born on March 21.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ronaldinho-celebrates-his-40th-with-a-prison-bbq-3978492</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/23/3978492/3978492_D222F02BBEBA44AF9477E419EED0A5D1_200323_3978492_Ronaldinho_celebrates_his_40th_with_a_prison_BBQ_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 05:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978435</guid>
      <title>Quarantined citizen disguised as T-Rex stopped by Police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MURCIA, SPAIN <br/> Spanish police were prompted to post a video online, along with a statement to remind citizens to stay indoors after an unidentified citizen was caught roaming the streets disguised in a T-Rex costume. <br/><br/>It comes after Spain's Prime Minister, Pedro S&#225;nchez imposed a 15-day state of emergency that has restricted free movement besides essential trips. <br/><br/>And while walking pets is still allowed, the police did note on social media that dinosaurs are not included under this exemption. <br/><br/>Officers did not provide details of why the resident was sporting a dinosaur outfit, or who they were. However, many commenters suggested that it may have been the unidentified person's attempt to shield themselves from the virus.<br/><br/>Murcia Police also wrote, "remember that you can go outside during the ESSENTIAL TIME so that our pet meets his needs and do not forget to collect their droppings.<br/><br/>"Do not use your pet as an excuse to break the rules."<br/><br/>The tweets offer some light-hearted relief in the country, which has so far seen nearly 18,000 cases and 831 deaths.<br/><br/>The metrics suggest that Spain is currently the fourth worst-hit nation in the world after China, Iran, and Italy.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/quarantined-citizen-disguised-as-t-rex-stopped-by-police-3978435</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/23/3978435/3978435_C34C50D65297444B8A9BC23E82F2FE39_200323_3978435_Quarantined_citizen_disguised_as_T_Rex_stopped_b_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 02:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978828</guid>
      <title>Air pollution and CO2 levels plummet amid pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> As the world battle's with China's latest gift to humanity, levels of pollutants in the air over many cities have dropped as the Xi Jinping Virus affects work and travel. <br/>BBC reports that researchers in New York say carbon monoxide primarily from cars has been reduced by almost 50 percent compared to last year. Carbon dioxide emissions have also taken a sharp dive. <br/>As economies around the world are feeling the effects of the Pooh Virus, emissions of a whole bunch of nasty gases that come with energy and transportation have dramatically been reduced. <br/>According to scientists, C02 emissions are at their highest in May due to decomposing leaves, the levels recorded could be the lowest we've seen since the global subprime mortgage crisis over a decade ago. <br/>Columbia University researchers said that in the Big Apple alone, traffic levels were down 35 percent compared to a year ago. The enormous levels of carbon monoxide spewed out from cars and trucks fell around 50 percent for a few days last week. <br/>According to the Beebs, they also found a 5-10 percent drop in CO2 over New York and a big drop in methane too. <br/>Similar drops in pollutants were also found in China and Italy. <br/>Unfortunately, once the world gets over this China Cough-19 thing, most countries are going to focus on getting their economies going again at all costs, regardless of the impact on the environment. Fantastic.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/air-pollution-and-co2-levels-plummet-amid-pandemic-3978828</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/24/3978828/3978828_3EAF900070E7444193875D2549A28706_200324_3978828_Air_pollution_and_CO2_levels_plummet_amid_pandem_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 02:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978992</guid>
      <title>Image shows Sphinx built to align with equinoxes: ex-Egyptian official</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EGYPT <br/> A former Egyptian antiquities minister has claimed that a recent image is evidence that the Sphinx was built to align with the equinox.<br/><br/>According to Zahi Hawas, former Minister of Antiquities, the image is evidence of an astronimical and religious connection between the sphinx and the spring and autumn equinoxes. These are cosmic events when day and night and equal in length. Hawas' assertion goes against modern archaeological thinking.<br/><br/>Research from 2018 suggests that its construction also may relate to the autumn equinox. According to Newsweek, the Great Pyramid of Giza almost fits with the four cardinal directions.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/image-shows-sphinx-built-to-align-with-equinoxes-ex-egyptian-official-3978992</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/24/3978992/3978992_FF46929E66D249BA8AF80C524E8505CE_200324_3978992_Image_shows_Sphinx_built_to_align_with_equinoxes_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 08:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979288</guid>
      <title>Vicar catches fire during home sermon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PLYMOUTH, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Things got a little hot under the dog collar when a vicar conducted a virtual sermon and accidentally set himself on fire. <br/><br/>The Church of England recently requested all public worship to be suspended until further notice because of the Coronavirus.  <br/><br/>Reverend Stephen Beach from Saint Budeaux Church in Plymouth, decided to invite his flock to a virtual Sunday service, broadcasted live from his home last weekend.  <br/><br/>To create the ambiance of his at-home sermon the vicar lit five candles and placed them in a cross-shaped candle holder in the near background of the video. <br/><br/>But as he spoke from the book of truth to his audience through the camera, he sat a tad too close to one of the naked flames.<br/><br/>And in typical British fashion, he deemed himself on fire with, "Oh dear, I've just caught on fire. Oh, my word."<br/><br/>The video was shared by the vicar's niece on Twitter and since the video went viral, the priest's niece has reassured the internet that her uncle is unharmed, except for a new hole in his favorite sweater.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/vicar-catches-fire-during-home-sermon-3979288</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/25/3979288/3979288_A649877AF9C34DD1964F586E76CA47E1_200325_3979288_Vicar_catches_fire_during_home_sermon_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979257</guid>
      <title>Frenchman runs marathon on balcony because of virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOULOUSE, FRANCE <br/> A man in France stuck at home because of the Xi Jinping Sniffles-19 decided it wasn't going to stop him from running a marathon, so he decided to run in on his balcony. <br/>According to the Associated Press, Elisha Nochomovitz ran 26.2 miles on his 23-foot-long balcony. <br/>According to the AP, he saw it as a physical and mental challenge, and he also shared the images online as a way "to extend my support to the entire medical personnel who are doing an exceptional job." <br/>He ran the balcony marathon from his apartment in Balma, a suburb in Toulouse.<br/><br/>It took him six hours and 48 minutes to finish the one man race. He also made himself a bit nauseous in the process, and also worried he would piss off his neighbors with all the noise. <br/>Apparently, Nochomovitz had been training for a marathon and wanted to see if he could run in whatever condition. <br/>He told AP he lost track of how many laps he did, but luckily his pedometer kept track for him. <br/>So, how's it going to take before someone tries a triathlon on his or her balcony?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/frenchman-runs-marathon-on-balcony-because-of-virus-3979257</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/25/3979257/3979257_B1475E25BF334E6C933665BAA47763CE_200325_3979257_Frenchman_runs_marathon_on_balcony_because_of_vi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 02:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979767</guid>
      <title>U.K radio host flabbergasted after stupid Coronavirus comments</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> One elderly woman from the U.K called in to a local radio station to say, "If we get it, we don't actually care", so long as she could go to the beach. <br/><br/>The radio host was flabbergasted after the caller's naive comments, before promptly cutting her off. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-k-radio-host-flabbergasted-after-stupid-coronavirus-comments-3979767</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/26/3979767/3979767_1C73061478CE44899D59A53EE223D383_200326_3979767_U_K_radio_host_flabbergasted_after_stupid_Corona_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 05:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3980176</guid>
      <title>Spanish police serenade quarantined citizens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MAJORCA, SPAIN <br/> Spanish police took to the streets to entertain quarantined citizens. <br/><br/>Footage shared on Twitter shows two police cars winding down a deserted street in Majorca with their sirens on as quarantined residents applaud.<br/><br/>As the officers exit their vehicles, one officer can be seen leading the line-up; he then starts playing guitar and singing through an MJ style headset. Residents can be heard joining in as the other officers clap and dance around in circles.<br/><br/>As quickly as the song started, the officers applauded themselves, jumped back into their vehicles and were, presumably, on their way to another show.<br/><br/>Local media reports that the officers played from 3 p.m. to 7 p.m. spreading the joy and lifting the spirits of an otherwise grief-stricken nation. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/spanish-police-serenade-quarantined-citizens-3980176</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/27/3980176/3980176_7E7F4E7C4BFE4749A763E4D73D8A525C_200327_3980176_Spanish_police_serenade_quarantined_citizens_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 04:25:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981109</guid>
      <title>COVID-19 new symptoms: loss of sense of smell and taste</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> Anosmia, the loss of smell; hyposmia, a reduced sense of smell; and dysgeusia, the distortion of the sense of taste could all be linked to COVID-19. <br/><br/>According to a report from the American Academy of Otolaryngology-Head and Neck Surgery, anosmia, the loss of smell; hyposmia, a reduced sense of smell; and dysgeusia, the distortion of the sense of taste, should be added to the list of symptoms caused by the COVID-19 virus.<br/><br/>In a newsletter on the topic, Claire Hopkins, President of the British Rhinological Society, and Nirmal Kumar, President of ENT UK, reported that more than two in three confirmed cases of coronavirus in Germany have anosmia.<br/><br/>Similarly, in South Korea, 30 percent of patients who tested positive for the virus had anosmia as their main symptom.<br/><br/>The report also mentions anecdotal evidence that a patient can be generally asymptomatic, only presenting anosmia, and still test positive for COVID-19. <br/><br/>However, patients with just anosmia are often not tested or asked to self-isolate as this symptom is not yet recognized as a sign of coronavirus.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/covid-19-new-symptoms-loss-of-sense-of-smell-and-taste-3981109</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/30/3981109/3981109_1CC2A66B6F1D48619CEF8BDF2E7C5046_200330_3981109_COVID_19_new_symptoms__loss_of_sense_of_smell_an_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 01:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981259</guid>
      <title>Neanderthals ate seafood, new research suggests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRUTA DA FIGUEIRA BRAVA, PORTUGAL <br/> Research published in the journal Science has found that Neanderthals living on the coast of Portugal ate a variety of seafood.<br/><br/>This is contrary to the thinking that humans were unique in their ability to hunt for marine life<br/><br/>Citing the research, the BBC reports that Neanderthals were found to have eaten sharks, dolphins, mussels, crabs, eels, sea bream, seals and some sea birds. Food from marine resources is thought to have made up half of the Neanderthal diet. The rest is said to consist of ancient cattle, horse, deer, goat and tortoise.<br/><br/>It is believed that humans developed their creativity and cognition from eating the brain-enhancing fats of marine life.<br/><br/>Research from earlier this year found evidence that suggested Neanderthals living in a cave in Italy used to dive for shellfish. It is thought that they used the shellfish not only for food, but for making tools as well.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/neanderthals-ate-seafood-new-research-suggests-3981259</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/30/3981259/3981259_9FACD93982FB4677AB5471198014780E_200330_3981259_Neanderthals_ate_seafood__new_research_suggests_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 08:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981202</guid>
      <title>British PM tells Brits, "we will do this together"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> British Prime Minister, Boris Johnson has spoken in his first self-isolation video today since announcing he has Coronavirus; he took to Twitter to boost morale, expressing his gratitude to the nation and hero National Health Service workers on the frontline.<br/><br/>Mr. Johnson said, "our policy remains unchanged, that is to delay the spread of the disease so as to reduce the pressure on the NHS, reduce the demand on the NHS at that critical peak moment and that's how we aim to save many thousands of lives."<br/><br/>"I want to thank everybody who has been complying with our instructions to stay at home."<br/><br/>In a rallying cry, he passionately stated, "We are going to do it. We are going to do it together."<br/><br/>"I think one thing Coronavirus crisis has proved is that there is such a thing as society, so thank you to all of you and remember, stay at home.<br/><br/>"Protect our NHS and save lives."<br/><br/>Mr. Johnson also praised the army of over 750,000 Coronavirus volunteers who have enlisted to assist the National Health workers in a move of public togetherness not seen since the Blitz. <br/><br/>He also revealed 20,000 former National Health Service staff have returned to their posts to join the fight against the deadly disease.<br/><br/>His comments come as case numbers in the U.K are at 19,522 and with the death toll currently standing at 1,228.<br/><br/>To ensure national effort amid the crisis, the Prime Minister penned a letter now being sent out to British households this week, saying, "It's important for me to level with you, we know things will get worse before they get better."<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/british-pm-tells-brits--we-will-do-this-together--3981202</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/30/3981202/3981202_4487E3BBF7D7401597152DEEC0DC2034_200330_3981202_British_PM_tells_Brits___we_will_do_this_togethe_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 06:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981582</guid>
      <title>King of Thailand 'isolates' with 20 women in German hotel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GARMISCH-PARTENKIRCHEN, GERMANY <br/> Thailand's controversial King Maha Vajiralongkorn, also known as Rama X reportedly booked out an entire 4-star hotel, after the resort received "special permission" from the district council. <br/><br/>The local district council says that "the guests are a single, homogeneous group of people with no fluctuation."<br/><br/>German tabloid, Bild reports that the 67-year-old King's entourage included a "harem" of 20 concubines and numerous servants.<br/><br/>119 members of his original entourage had been reportedly sent back to Thailand over fears they had contracted the Coronavirus. <br/><br/>News of his luxurious self-isolation was met with anger by tens of thousands of Thai people who risked breaking the country's laws by criticizing him online.<br/><br/>Under said laws, anyone who insults or criticizes the monarchy could be imprisoned for up to 15 years.<br/><br/>The Independent says that a Thai hashtag which translated to "Why do we need a king?" appeared 1.2 million times on Twitter within 24 hours after an activist claimed the King was traveling on holiday in Germany while the outbreak continued to spread across Thailand.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/king-of-thailand-isolates-with-20-women-in-german-hotel-3981582</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/31/3981582/3981582_BA153B298BF34FE5B519561FA970E7C6_200331_3981582_King_of_Thailand__isolates__with_20_women_in_Ger_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 05:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
