<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 18:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3943792</guid>
      <title>Sriracha hot sauce recalled over fears of  'exploding' bottles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA/NEW ZEALAND <br/>The BBC reports that bottles of Sriracha hot sauce have been recalled in Australia and New Zealand over fears they might go kaboom.<br/><br/>According to Food Standards Australia New Zealand, lactic acid build-up is causing certain bottles to bloat and continue to ferment. That means if you try and open one, it could very well blow up in your face.<br/><br/>According to the website, customers should watch out for bloated 17 and 28-ounce bottles with a March 2021 expiration date and take them back for a full refund. <br/><br/>Seems Sriracha's been exploding everywhere lately. The BBC reports that just last month, Irish officials have had to impose a recall on similar grounds.<br/><br/>Hipster Tabasco also made headlines in the outback last October, after 400 kilos of speed were found hidden inside the imported sauce bottles.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sriracha-hot-sauce-recalled-over-fears-of--exploding-bottles-3943792</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EEA/4AC/EEA4AC950F5437E8D1E0C6C5932ED004.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943792/3943792_3118F5EBBD7A4C01BB2577B07B4CBDBF_200102_3943792_Sriracha_hot_sauce_recalled_over_fears_of___expl_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 04:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944246</guid>
      <title>U.S. sends paratroopers to Kuwait after Baghdad embassy riot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Washington <br/> The U.S. Army's 82nd Airborne Division is deploying paratroopers to Kuwait, after Iran-affiliated rioters swarmed the U.S. embassy in Baghdad.<br/><br/>U.S. Secretary of Defense Mark Esper said in a written statement on Tuesday that Air Force C-17s were already flying in 750 paratroopers of the division's Immediate Response Force.<br/><br/>The Military Times reports that the 750 paratroopers will be joined by an additional 4,000 U.S. soldiers from the division's IRF in the following week.<br/><br/>The 82 Airborne Division said in a statement that the 1st Brigade Combat Team is currently assigned to the IRF role.<br/> <br/>According to Fox News, the alert sequence for the Division Ready Brigade is to have one rifle battalion ready in 18 hours, another rifle battalion in 36 hours and a third in 54 hours.<br/><br/>The alert brigade should be ready to deploy for operations within a 96-hour alert window. <br/><br/>Fox reports that the aircraft carrier USS Harry S. Truman has been in the Gulf of Oman with its carrier strike group, armed with F-18 fighters and Tomahawk cruise missiles.<br/><br/>Citing the Pentagon, Fox reports that there are 60,000 US troops in the Middle East, including the 14,000 reinforcements added since May in response to Iran's rising threat.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-sends-paratroopers-to-kuwait-after-baghdad-embassy-riot-3944246</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C6C/DA2/C6CDA2737A7656B7903CB85C98606F28.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944246/3944246_6F41EC4436564385B09B49A127EE1FAF_200103_3944246_U_S__sends_paratroopers_to_Kuwait_after_Baghdad__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 03:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944400</guid>
      <title>Protesters storm on U.S. embassy in Baghdad</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAGHDAD, IRAQ <br/> The U.S. embassy in Iraq was hit with attacks during violent protests, an action which has been condemned by President Donald Trump. He has since called on Iraq to use its forces to protect the embassy.<br/><br/>According to CBS News, an estimated 6000 protesters, including Iraqi Shiite militiamen gathered outside the American embassy in Baghdad on Tuesday during a hostile protest. Several dozen managed to break into the compound and were heard shouting, 'down, down, USA!', whilst they smashed a main door and set fire to a reception area.<br/><br/>Protesters also threw stones over the walls, pulled down security cameras, stormed empty guard posts and were seen hanging yellow flags belonging to the Kataeb Hezbollah militia on the walls of the embassy. U.S. soldiers watched from the roof and used a loudspeaker to urge the crowd to stay away.<br/><br/>Videos posted to social media captured smoke funneling out from one guard checkpoint on the perimeter of the compound. Iraqi special forces responded by firing tear gas to try and disperse the protesters. <br/><br/>According to the New York Times, the demonstration was in retaliation to U.S. airstrikes that killed 25 Iran-backed Kataeb Hezbollah, an Iraqi Shia paramilitary group just two days earlier. <br/><br/>The Pentagon, however, says their airstrikes were in retaliation to an attack consisting of more than 30 rockets on an Iraqi military base near Kirkuk, northern Iraq. The attack killed an American defense contractor and injured four U.S. service members.<br/><br/>A U.S. defense official told CBS News that the military is sending reinforcements to the embassy from units already within the country, adding, "there are no plans to evacuate Embassy Baghdad."<br/><br/>President Trump accused Iran of "orchestrating" the break-in, adding that "they will be held fully responsible."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/protesters-storm-on-u-s-embassy-in-baghdad-3944400</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F7A/5BF/F7A5BF28DB053547A315296351415CDF.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944400/3944400_095D842F89BD437C9FFA329A43DA1886_200103_3944400_Protesters_storm_on_U_S__embassy_in_Baghdad_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 07:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945795</guid>
      <title>Brit man gets 5-inch dragon horn removed from back</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LIVERPOOL, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> If you ever thought it was a good idea to ignore whatever that thing is that's growing on your skin, don't <br/> or else you could end up dragon horned like this guy. <br/><br/>According to the British Medical Journal, doctors were surprised to discover a 5-inch long "dragon horn" growing out of a 50-year-old man's back.<br/><br/>But no, he wasn't turning into a scaly fire-breather. In reality, the "dragon horn" was a cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma, a fairly common type of skin cancer. <br/><br/>What's unusual is how massive it got <br/> which is what happens when you neglect that cancerous skin lesion for 3 whole years!<br/><br/>SCC cases are usually seen in older people with light skin with a weak immune system and lots of sun exposure.<br/><br/>In this case, the patient was a low-risk manual laborer, who wasn't immunosuppressed and had no significant sun exposure or family history of skin cancer.  And unlike most folks battling skin cancer, there wasn't anything abnormal with his lymph nodes either. <br/><br/>To treat the man, doctors had to surgically remove the horn along with a good chunk of healthy skin to make sure no cancer got left behind. They then took a skin graft from his thigh to patch up the deep wound.<br/><br/>What's mind-boggling is that healthcare in the UK is free. So everyone who has to deal with America's crappy system probably wants to know why the dude didn't just go to a doctor? Treatment would've been a lot less gnarly.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/brit-man-gets-5-inch-dragon-horn-removed-from-back-3945795</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945795/3945795_1915512C42164D85A88E366D158666DE_200106_3945795_Brit_man_gets_5_inch_dragon_horn_removed_from_ba_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946057</guid>
      <title>How a U.S. drone strike killed Iran's Quds Force commander</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAGHDAD, IRAQ <br/> General Qassim Soleimani, head of Iran's expeditionary Quds Force, was killed early Friday by a U.S. drone that fired missiles into his convoy near Baghdad International Airport. <br/><br/>The U.S. military has confirmed that it carried out the attack. <br/><br/>The Times of Israel reports that a MQ-9 Reaper drone fired four missiles into two cars and destroyed the vehicles on the airport's access road.<br/><br/>Citing local media sources, the paper reports that the blast tore Soleimani apart and the general was later identified by the ring he wore on his hand.<br/><br/>The strike killed Soleimani, his son-in-law and five Iranian Revolutionary Guards members.<br/><br/>According to the New York Times, several Tehran-backed Iraqi militia leaders in the convoy were also killed.<br/><br/>The Times of Israel reported 10 fatalities for the airstrike.<br/><br/>The Washington Examiner reports that the MQ-9 drone was favored for its quiet propellers and loitering capabilities.<br/><br/>Citing debris analysis by independent observers, Forbes reports that the missiles utilized could be the JAGM, a missile type that adds advanced sensors to the Hellfire missile.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-a-u-s-drone-strike-killed-iran-s-quds-force-commander-3946057</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3946057/3946057_E1B26C9277404D03B529A8BD2A04CB8C_200107_3946057_How_a_U_S__drone_strike_killed_Iran_s_Quds_Force_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 08:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946758</guid>
      <title>Ukrainian Airlines plane crashes in Tehran, killing all aboard</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN <br/> A Ukrainian passenger plane crashed in Iran shortly after takeoff on Wednesday, allegedly due to technical issues.<br/><br/>According to FlightRadar24, Ukraine International Airlines Flight 752 took off from Tehran's Imam Khomeini airport at 6:12 a.m. on Wednesday. It was bound for Kiev.<br/><br/>Al Jazeera reports that the Boeing 737-800 jet had been carrying 176 passengers and crew members.<br/><br/>According to Iranian State TV, the aircraft is suspected to have experienced mechanical issues, and stopped sending flight data just minutes after takeoff.<br/><br/>The plane crashed in a field in between the cities of Parand and Shariar. All 176 passengers on board were killed.<br/><br/>An Iranian emergency official told state TV that emergency crews were trying to collect the bodies, which lay among shattered parts of the aircraft.<br/><br/>The Associated Press reports that according to a civil aviation spokesman, an investigation team has also been dispatched to the crash site.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ukrainian-airlines-plane-crashes-in-tehran-killing-all-aboard-3946758</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946758/3946758_8D0FE5FCB71F40E18476067FE2F5EC50_200108_3946758_Ukrainian_Airlines_plane_crashes_in_Tehran__kill_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 14:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947121</guid>
      <title>Misleading images of Aussie fires make their way to social media</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY <br/> As Australia's fires burn at an unprecedented rate, social media activists have been quick to share maps and images of the wildfires <br/> though not all of them are accurate.<br/><br/>One example is of a map that was widely shared on social media as it seemed to show the live extent of the spread of fires across Australia. In reality, it was a visualization created by artist Anthony Hearsey which showed where fires were detected across Australia from December 2019 to January 2020.<br/><br/>In response to the criticism, Hearsey admitted in an Instagram post that the scale was a bit exaggerated and said that some of the fires depicted may not be burning anymore but said it was "generally" true as he had obtained data about the fires from NASA's website.<br/><br/>Another misleading map claimed to show all the wildfires burning across the country and used data from an Australian government website called MyFireWatch. It was later discovered that the map was inaccurate as the data gathered included any heat source including gas flares and refinery furnaces.<br/><br/>Social media users have also been spreading old photographs or fake images to show the extent of destruction caused by the fires, Australia's SBS News reports. <br/><br/>One photograph shows a family hiding under a pier with the atmosphere turned orange in color due to the flames. The image was taken in 2013, not during the recent wildfire outbreak.  <br/><br/>Another photo shows a girl holding a koala and wearing what seems to be an oxygen mask while a forest in the backdrop is caught in flames. A Twitter user pointed out that the image could easily have been photoshopped to show the girl holding the koala with the fires burning in the background.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/misleading-images-of-aussie-fires-make-their-way-to-social-media-3947121</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947121/3947121_65B24283ACE046BDB9E53BB1433F41CF_200109_3947121_Misleading_images_of_Aussie_fires_make_their_way_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 10:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946976</guid>
      <title>What we now know about Ghosn's daring escape from Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> On December 29, former Nissan, Renault boss Carlos Ghosn, who was under house arrest facing charges of diverting millions in company funds for his personal use, walked out of his house in Tokyo wearing a hat and a surgical mask in plain view of security cameras.<br/><br/>Bloomberg reports that police surveillance was lax during the holidays and that Ghosn's lawyers had filed a legal complaint that prevented Nissan's hired agents from following him.<br/><br/>Ghosn claims he would not have received a fair trial in Japan, where 99 percent of those accused of a crime are convicted.<br/><br/>Citing Japan's NTV, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn boarded a bullet train in Tokyo and arrived at Osaka at about 4:30 pm. <br/><br/>He then called a cab to a hotel near Kansai International Airport.<br/><br/>Citing sources familiar with the matter, Bloomberg reports that Ghosn apparently evaded security by hiding in a case that was too big to be scanned by the airport's X-ray machines.<br/><br/>Earlier, Ghosn's alleged accomplices had flown in on a Bombardier Global Express Jet with the case. Ghosn would use both in his escape.<br/><br/>According to Bloomberg, Ghosn was aided by U.S. contractor and ex-Special Forces veteran Michael Taylor in his flight.<br/><br/>At 11 p.m., the Bombardier Global Express took off and headed for Istanbul with Ghosn on board.<br/><br/>Bloomberg reports that Ghosn's alleged rescuers carefully plotted the flight to avoid countries with extradition treaties with Japan such as South Korea and instead flew through Russian airspace.<br/><br/>Russia was viewed as more friendly territory as Ghosn is credited with saving the ailing automaker AvtoVAZ, which he brought in to the Renault-Nissan Alliance's fold.<br/><br/>The jet landed at Istanbul's Ataturk Airport at around 5:00 a.m.<br/><br/>After that, Ghosn would again secrete himself as cargo in the box before boarding a smaller Bombardier that would take him to Beirut.<br/><br/>In addition to Brazlian and Lebanese passports, Ghosn has two French passports. One was taken by the Japanese authorities and another kept by his lawyer as a condition of his bail but stored in a flimsy box that could be broken easily with a tool. <br/><br/>However Reuters reports the French government denies Ghosn used the nation's passport.<br/><br/>Citing a Lebanese judiciary official, Reuters reports that Lebanon has received a request to extradite Ghosn from Japan, not Interpol.<br/><br/>Bloomberg reports that Ghosn entered Lebanon legally, where extradition of citizens is denied as a matter of policy.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/what-we-now-know-about-ghosn-s-daring-escape-from-japan-3946976</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3946976/3946976_F228312BAED24490A2F92505B3733B0B_200109_3946976_What_we_now_know_about_Ghosn_s_daring_escape_fro_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 06:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947734</guid>
      <title>Iran may have shot down the Ukrainian commercial jet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN <br/> The BBC reports that Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau says intelligence shows that Iran had shot down the Ukrainian passenger plane with a missile, possibly in error.<br/><br/>According to CNN, U.K. Prime Minister Boris Johnson states that British intelligence has reached the same conclusion.<br/><br/>CNN reports that the plane had crashed shortly after it took off from Tehran airport on Wednesday.<br/><br/>The Boeing 737 was carrying 176 passengers and aircrew, all killed in the crash.<br/><br/>On Thursday, CNN aired a video it obtained that apparently shows a missile striking an object over Tehran's skies at the time of the commercial jet's crash.<br/><br/>CNN states that it cannot independently verify the video.<br/><br/>Citing U.S. officials, CBS News reports that a satellite detected infrared blips of two missile launches, then another of an explosion. The network states that officials were confident the plane was shot down by a missile.<br/><br/>Newsweek quotes three US and Iraqi officials as saying they believe a Russian-made Tor M1 surface to air missile had struck the plane.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/iran-may-have-shot-down-the-ukrainian-commercial-jet-3947734</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947734/3947734_6F8E64EF62B54958A1CB87B448CB183A_200110_3947734_Iran_may_have_shot_down_the_Ukrainian_commercial_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 13:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948637</guid>
      <title>Supermarket offers cheap TVs on accident, kicks out shoppers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONTPELLIER, FRANCE <br/> French supermarket G&#233;ant Casino accidentally advertised TVs that cost over $440 for only $35. <br/>According to the BBC, this caused a whole bunch of shoppers to rush over and grab a TV, or two<br/>or five. <br/>The Beebs says the mix-up occurred because the televisions were tagged at 30.99 euros instead of 399 euros. <br/>Unfortunately for shoppers, the store refused to sell the TVs at the bargain basement price, but the people weren't having it. <br/>The customers then blocked the checkout area demanding that they be allowed their flatscreens. <br/>So G&#233;ant did the reasonable thing and called the police. BBC reports that dozens of police officers had to be sent to help clear the store out.   <br/>Images and video posted to social media show angry customers with a mountain load of TVs refusing to leave the store empty handed. <br/>The police were finally successful in getting everyone out, although it did take over an hour after the store's closing time. <br/>The BBC reports that French retailers are required to sell items at the listed price under the consumer code, however exceptions are allowed for obvious mistakes.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/supermarket-offers-cheap-tvs-on-accident-kicks-out-shoppers-3948637</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948637/3948637_504FAA6054174731B591BC19EAD9F537_200113_3948637_Supermarket_offers_cheap_TVs_on_accident__kicks__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 02:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948780</guid>
      <title>Iran admits downing Ukranian aircraft, but calls it an accident</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN <br/> Iran has admitted to accidently shooting down a Ukranian airplane on January 8, killing all 176 passengers and crew members onboard.<br/><br/>According to the Guardian, Ukraine International Airlines flight PS752 took off from Tehran's Imam Khomeini International Airport at 6:12 a.m., and reached roughly 8,000 feet in altitude before the plane exploded and came crashing down at 6:18 a.m. The flight was en route to Kiev, Ukraine.<br/><br/>Iran had previously denied shooting down the plane for three days, before issuing a statement on Iranian state TV in which the country took responsibility for the incident, reports BBC News. The country said the plane was hit due to "human error" and said the flight was hit by a missile unintentionally.<br/><br/>An Iranian Revolutionary Guard airspace commander said that the plane was downed by a short-range missile that exploded beside the aircraft, though he did not specify which missile system was used during the incident.<br/><br/>Images shared on social media appears to show the remains of a missile believed to be from Iran's Tor-M1 system near the site of the plane crash.<br/><br/>Iran said its military was at its "highest level of readiness" due to heightened tensions with the U.S.The incident occurred just hours after Iran carried out missile strikes on two Iraqi air bases housing U.S. soldiers.<br/><br/>Iran's military apologized and said that they would work to upgrade their systems to prevent these types of mistakes in the future.<br/><br/>Iranian citizens have since taken to the streets condemning their government and even chanting for their Supreme Leader Ayatollah Khamenei to step down in the aftermath of the downing of the Ukranian jet, CNN reports. Demonstrators say they want those responsible for the mishap to be prosecuted.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/iran-admits-downing-ukranian-aircraft-but-calls-it-an-accident-3948780</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948780/3948780_360B191B5FDA4A1683E6A03E9BB4980F_200113_3948780_Iran_admits_downing_Ukranian_aircraft__but_calls_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 07:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949118</guid>
      <title>Tortoise's 'libido' saves his species</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA CRUZ ISLAND, CALIFORNIA <br/> A 100-year-old tortoise named, 'Diego' has been credited with saving his species after he was enlisted to help boost species numbers as part of a conservation program. <br/><br/>Set up in 1965 the program has produced more than 2,000 giant tortoises and this time around, Diego is said to have fathered 800 offspring. <br/><br/>Diego was requested from California's San Diego Zoo, however, the Galapagos National Park believes that he was originally from there and was taken during a scientific expedition 80 years ago.<br/><br/>He will be released back to Ecuador's Galapagos Islands, located in the Pacific Ocean for a well-deserved retirement where he will join a 1,800 strong tortoise population, with park rangers there crediting him with fathering 40% of them.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tortoise-s-libido-saves-his-species-3949118</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949118/3949118_B94B56D721EC4D209E6F304E2D2FF89A_200114_3949118_Tortoise_s__libido__saves_his_species_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 02:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949343</guid>
      <title>How Iran accidentally killed 176 people on Flight PS 752</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN <br/> Iran's military on Saturday admitted that its air defense system had shot down Ukraine's Flight 752 by mistake.<br/><br/>Citing Iranian official statements, the New York Times said the passenger jet had been misidentified as a U.S. cruise missile.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports that the Tor is a mobile system carrying eight missiles, that can be operated without input from other air defense infrastructure.<br/><br/>Citing defense analyst Steven Zaloga, Bloomberg reports that the missile's guidance system is unable to distinguish cruise missiles from military aircraft or civilian airplanes.<br/><br/>Citing FlightRadar24, Bloomberg reports that the Boeing 737 made a slight right turn two minutes after its takeoff from Tehran International Airport, which was normal.<br/><br/>The plane was clearly transmitting its identity and position until it climbed to about 7,900 feet of altitude, presumably because it was hit by missile fire."<br/><br/>The plane plunged into a field in between the cities of Parand and Shariar. All 176 passengers and crew were killed.<br/><br/>Due to the Tor's indiscriminate guidance system, most nations do not operate the weapon without connecting it into a command structure.<br/><br/>Bloomberg reports that according to Zaloga, SA-15 operators were not supposed to fire without authorization.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-iran-accidentally-killed-176-people-on-flight-ps-752-3949343</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949343/3949343_B6D435F9383243209E49625242050F72_200114_3949343_How_Iran_accidentally_killed_176_people_on_Fligh_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949414</guid>
      <title>Carrots and sweet potatoes airdropped to hungry animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW SOUTH WALES <br/> As Australia continues to struggle with bushfires, brush-tailed rock-wallabies are getting a helping hand via air.  <br/>According to Global News, the New South Wales government is airdropping thousands of kilograms of carrots and sweet potatoes to starving animals in a mission called "Operation Wallaby."  <br/><br/>In a statement released on Sunday by NSW environment minister Matt Kean, "initial fire assessments indicate the habitat of several important brush-tailed rock-wallaby populations was burnt in the recent bushfires. The wallabies typically survive the fire itself, but are then left stranded with limited natural food as the fire takes out the vegetation around their rocky habitat." <br/><br/>He continued, "the wallabies were already under stress from the ongoing drought, making survival challenging for the wallabies without assistance."<br/>Global News reports that the aerial food deliveries are expected to help endangered species like wallabies amid larger wildlife recovery efforts across the country in the aftermath of bushfires. <br/><br/>According to a government media release, nearly 2,000 kilograms of veggies were dropped to 11 different rock-wallaby colonies. <br/>The drops will continue, and will be accompanied by feral predator control as the little critters recover.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/carrots-and-sweet-potatoes-airdropped-to-hungry-animals-3949414</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949414/3949414_BE9A4C7194D54645B33B81FED3BC475B_200114_3949414_Carrots_and_sweet_potatoes_airdropped_to_hungry__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949556</guid>
      <title>Woman gets caught lying about why she's late to work</title>
      <description><![CDATA[In an epic photoshop fail, a woman was caught lying to her boss about why she was late to work.<br/><br/>In an attempt to get a day off, the unnamed woman sent an image of a punctured tire with a nail in it to her boss and apologized for not being able to make it in.<br/><br/>However, on zooming into the image it's clear that the image has been photoshopped.<br/><br/>The boss shared the epic fail with her coworker, Sydney Whitson who shared it via Twitter in a post that has since gone viral with over 45,000 retweets and counting. <br/><br/>In an unsurprising twist, if you google 'nail in tire', it's the first image that comes up.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-gets-caught-lying-about-why-she-s-late-to-work-3949556</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949556/3949556_5AFFB030697E4EB39849B37290AED9CF_200115_3949556_Woman_gets_caught_lying_about_why_she_s_late_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 23:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949941</guid>
      <title>British tourist dies falling off Australian cliff taking selfie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY <br/> A British woman is sadly no longer around after taking a plunge off a cliff in Australia<br/>while trying to selfie. <br/><br/>News Corp Australia reports that 21-year-old Madalyn Davis was at Diamond Bay Reserve on Sunday with some friends.  <br/>According to reports, Davis had been at a party in a rich suburb east of Sydney, when they decided to watch the sunrise from the cliffs, which also happen to be a popular selfie spot. <br/>According to Marine Rescue New South Wales, Davis and her friends split up when they got to the cliffs. <br/>BBC reports that signs are placed to warn people to stay away from the cliff edge and the local mayor said the height of the fences in the area had been increased. <br/>It appears that Davis was attempting to take a selfie when she somehow fell off and was fatally injured. <br/>When everyone regrouped, Davis was nowhere to be found, so they called rescue services. Emergency crews responded to the scene around 6:30 a.m. local time. <br/>Her body was located and retrieved from the water about four hours later.   <br/>According to her social media accounts, Davis was an eyelash beautician and had recently been to Thailand and Bali before making her way Down Under.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/british-tourist-dies-falling-off-australian-cliff-taking-selfie-3949941</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949941/3949941_CC29B381F753448D84907FD3F942DC27_200115_3949941_British_tourist_dies_falling_off_Australian_clif_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950372</guid>
      <title>Domino's wants to open more than 800 shops in Italy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ITALY <br/> Pizza giant Domino's is clearly overestimating the world's love for crappy American pizza with its latest announcement that it will open 880 locations in Italy. <br/>That's right folks. According to the New York Daily News, Domino's for some reason thinks that it can get a piece of the pie in the land where actual pizza was invented. <br/>According to the CEO of Domino's Italy Alessandro Lazzaroni, the new stores would join the 16,000 other locations the pizza juggernaut has in 85 other countries. <br/>Lazzaroni said the new locations would center on north and central Italy and focus on home delivery as their selling point. <br/><br/>Domino's for some reason actually thinks it can become the biggest food delivery outlet in the country.  <br/><br/>Domino's apparently already has 29 stores in Italy, mostly around Rome, Milan and Turin. <br/>The announcement sparked hilarious reactions online with some making comparing the move to "selling ice to Eskimos" or "bringing sand to the beach."<br/>Perhaps Taco Bell should think about a move to Mexico? Or maybe Panda Express should think about a hard China push? <br/>Don't listen to the haters Domino's. You guys will crush it in Italy. With pizza products like hot dog stuffed crust, how could you possibly go wrong?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/domino-s-wants-to-open-more-than-800-shops-in-italy-3950372</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950372/3950372_4DD8E7A1A16E40C58259788892F40086_200116_3950372_Domino_s_wants_to_open_more_than_800_shops_in_It_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950582</guid>
      <title>Indian restaurant found to have moldy food and a bug in mayo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUTHIN, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> An Indian restaurant in Ruthin, Wales was found to be home to moldy lamb chops, moldy cheese, moldy red peppers and a tub of mayonnaise with an insect inside. The restaurant, which had been inspected before, tried to fool its customers by flipping its zero-rating hygiene sticker upside down, to give the impression it had a top mark of five.  <br/><br/>Magistrates were told by Julia Longworth, prosecuting for the local council that, "significant improvement was required."<br/><br/>The owner of the restaurant, 41-year-old Mohammed Chowdhury was fined a total of &#163;1,260. He admitted to seven offenses of failing to comply with food hygiene regulations and his chef, now unemployed, Hanna Ali pleaded guilty to five food hygiene offenses and was also fined. <br/><br/>Court chairwoman Ann Dickinson said, "We found the photographs of the kitchen quite shocking."<br/><br/>In the owner's defense, the court heard that Mr. Chowdhury hadn't spent enough time at the restaurant to make the necessary improvements from previous inspections because he also worked at Manchester airport.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/indian-restaurant-found-to-have-moldy-food-and-a-bug-in-mayo-3950582</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950582/3950582_2A95E66D080A4076BEAF9F18FD2C0404_200117_3950582_Indian_restaurant_found_to_have_moldy_food_and_a_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 00:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3951759</guid>
      <title>Missing 3-year-old girl found with her trusty dog by her side</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PILBARA, AUSTRALIA  <br/> It's good news down under after a three-year-old girl was found safe and sound after going missing in Western Australia's flood-hit Pilbara region.<br/><br/>On Wednesday at around 2:30 p.m, three-year-old Matilda, accompanied by her pet Jack Russell, wandered off from her home in Noreena Downs Homestead, an area that has recently been flooded with heavy rain.<br/><br/>The Western Australia Police Force said the floods lead to a number of creeks surrounding the property to be full of water. <br/><br/>After the water level receded a bit, Matilda was able to make her way across one of these creeks. However, when it started to rain again, the creek quickly filled, thus trapping her and her dog.<br/><br/>Around 4 p.m the alarm was raised that Matilda was missing. Police said they were throwing every resource they had to locate her.<br/><br/>Three helicopters searched from the skies, whilst mounted police teamed with State Emergency Service searched from the ground. <br/><br/>Matilda, with her faithful dog at her side, was alone for nearly 24 hours without shelter before being spotted wandering around 3.5km south of the homestead. She was rescued and happily reunited with her family.<br/><br/>Pilbara's police superintendent, Kim Massam praised the girl's dog who, "stayed with her that whole time."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/missing-3-year-old-girl-found-with-her-trusty-dog-by-her-side-3951759</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3951759/3951759_4239969A602D43D1975C1658846F6527_200120_3951759_Missing_3_year_old_girl_found_with_her_trusty_do_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3951850</guid>
      <title>Burger King offers Prince Harry a job</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BURGER KINGDOM <br/> As Prince Harry and Meghan Markle prepare to step back as senior members of the British royal family, future employment will most definitely be an issue. <br/>Thank the Queen, okay, more like the king in this case, Burger King to be exact. <br/>According to Fox News, Burger King Argentina kicked things off by offering Harry and Meghan a spot in their royal family as the couple say they want to be financially independent of the monarchy. <br/><br/>Amid all the Megxit madness, the fast food chain with royal roots decided to weigh in with an ad reading, "If you're looking for a job, we have a new crown for you." <br/>"We have a proposition for you: do as thousands of people and take your first steps in the world of work with us," it goes on to say. "You know that the crown will suit you perfectly." <br/>"Also, after so many years of living as dukes, it is time for you to start eating like kings." <br/>The message ends with a link to apply for a j<br/>o<br/>b at B.K.<br/>Burger King U.S.A., then followed Argentina's lead with a tweet a few days later saying, "you always have a job in our kingdom."<br/><br/>And then another a few days later to Harry with the message, "this royal family offers part-time positions."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/burger-king-offers-prince-harry-a-job-3951850</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3951850/3951850_4BF17D88F6CD49E3AB505EBF59DF4C76_200120_3951850_Burger_King_offers_Prince_Harry_a_job_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 04:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952076</guid>
      <title>France is deploying its sole aircraft carrier to fight ISIS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS  <br/> France is deploying its sole aircraft carrier Charles de Gaulle to the Middle East.<br/><br/>Citing President Emmanuel Macron's speech to the military, Reuters reports that the carrier and its battle group will support counterterrorism operations from January to April.<br/><br/>According to Naval Technology, Charles de Gaulle is a 261.5 m long nuclear powered carrier with a displacement of 38,000 tonnes.<br/><br/>The de Gaulle's air group includes up to 40 Rafale M fighters, E-2C early warning aircraft, and various helicopters, including the Dauphin PEDRO.<br/><br/>The carrier's deck load is supplemented by an internal hanger equipped with two lifts for aircraft.<br/><br/>The ship is also armed with the Aster and Mistral air to air missiles and 20mm guns for close range defense.<br/><br/>Citing Macron, Reuters reports that after its deployment in the Middle East, the carrier will proceed to the Atlantic Ocean and the North Sea.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/france-is-deploying-its-sole-aircraft-carrier-to-fight-isis-3952076</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952076/3952076_672F6E175CA742D38E753E8E02E2746E_200120_3952076_France_is_deploying_its_sole_aircraft_carrier_to_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952314</guid>
      <title>ISIS preacher dubbed "Jabba the Jihadi" captured in Iraq</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSUL, IRAQ <br/> An overweight ISIS zealot dubbed "Jabba the Jihadi" was caught by an Iraqi SWAT team in Mosul last week, but as his name suggests, the known gang leader was too large to get into a police car, so instead, they loaded him onto a flatbed truck.<br/><br/>That's according to the military newspaper, Stars and Stripes who say the man, Abu Abdul Bari, a known preacher of provocative speeches, ordered the execution of scholars and clerics who refused to pledge allegiance to ISIS when it occupied the area.<br/><br/>In July 2014, 'Jabba' also ordered the destruction of a mosque believed to be built on the burial place of Jonah, the biblical prophet who once had a renowned encounter with a whale.<br/><br/>Maajid Nawaz, founder of the London-based counter-extremist organization Quilliam, took to Facebook to say that the images held a significant "psychological blow" to ISIS as gluttony is frowned upon by jihadists, yet this, "walrus was their top religious cleric."<br/><br/>British anti-ISIS activist, Macer Gifford who fought with a U.S. backed Kurdish militia in Syria, applauded the arrest in a Twitter post, saying,  "Good luck hanging him in Iraq." <br/><br/>He added, "he literally looks like the world's biggest chicken."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/isis-preacher-dubbed-jabba-the-jihadi-captured-in-iraq-3952314</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952314/3952314_2FCC89C416E744ECB38CA0DE3BC5008C_200121_3952314_ISIS_preacher_dubbed__Jabba_the_Jihadi__captured_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 23:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953708</guid>
      <title>Man buys stolen bike so he can return it to the owner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> 26-year-old Ste Burke bought an expensive stolen bicycle just so he could return it to the original owner.<br/><br/>Speaking to Metro.co.uk, Ste said that he was outside his house getting his gym bag from the back of his car when he was approached by three men carrying the bike; he said he spotted a lock around the back wheel and knew it was stolen. <br/><br/>According to Ste, they tried to sell the &#163;1350 bike for &#163;100; he instead offered &#163;80 which they happily accepted. <br/><br/>He said, "as soon as they left I put it on Twitter because I knew it wouldn't have been stolen far away as it was locked."<br/><br/>A few hours later a man carrying paperwork, receipts and the key for the lock met Ste. He told him that his home was "recently burgled" and that he'd pay him back the &#163;80. <br/><br/>Ste respectfully declined and insisted he didn't do it for a reward.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-buys-stolen-bike-so-he-can-return-it-to-the-owner-3953708</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953708/3953708_DFCD27EF414340889440F5DCDB6B9776_200123_3953708_Man_buys_stolen_bike_so_he_can_return_it_to_the__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 09:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954258</guid>
      <title>A Harry day in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANADA <br/> Now with Prince Harry and Meghan Markle taking a step back from the spotlight, how will they adjust to life in Canada, eh?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-harry-day-in-canada-3954258</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954258/3954258_C8171755559540098204A31195F8B581_200124_3954258_A_Harry_day_in_Canada_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 10:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954151</guid>
      <title>Personal trainer says he's too muscley for parking spaces</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> A personal trainer, known as the 'Greek Stallion' claims he has "no option" but to use designated parent and child parking spaces because he's too muscular.<br/><br/>Chris Goodwin, who claims he's a "muscle-model champion" and "a beast" says he always picks the wider parking spaces to permit his 20-stone frame to get out of his car; saying "I'll just go and park in the same parent-and-child bay, even if I'm on my own &#8211; I always do it." <br/><br/>Adding, "I don't give a c**p what people think of me. I'll do what I want. I can't fit out of my car &#8211; I'm too big."<br/><br/>According to Metro.co.uk, Chris was filmed trying to get out of his car in a normal spot, where he claimed, "I'm stuck! I'm actually stuck!"<br/><br/>He added, "I don't think it is selfish, I really don't."<br/><br/>"People take it way over the top because you're parking in a bloody parent-and-child bay. They want to bloody fight you like Mike Tyson would."<br/><br/>"I still think anybody should be able to park there and that's not being selfish. I think I should have my own bay saying, 'The Greek Stallion's Bay.'"]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/personal-trainer-says-he-s-too-muscley-for-parking-spaces-3954151</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954151/3954151_A7502337EA514A6BAEB64EE44BFBCD59_200124_3954151_Personal_trainer_says_he_s_too_muscley_for_parki_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 07:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955893</guid>
      <title>Woman dies during cake-eating contest on Australia Day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HERVEY BAY, AUSTRALIA <br/> A woman inhaling cakes during a contest commemorating Australia Day is unfortunately no longer around after eating it.  <br/>According to the New York Daily News, the idea was to cram as many small cakes known as lamingtons<br/>traditional sponge cake covered in coconut-dusted chocolate<br/>down as possible in an allotted time. <br/>News.com.au reports that the unidentified 60-year-old woman was among a whole bunch of contestants at the Beach House Hotel in Hervey Bay, Queensland on Sunday, January 26. <br/>Local news showed cell phone video of rows and rows of people ramming down pies and lamingtons as fast as humanly possible. Glasses of agua are next to each person to help wash down the desserts. <br/>According to witnesses, the woman was inhaling the cakes at breakneck speed around 2 p.m. <br/>That's when some people in attendance said she looked like she choked on some cake, which caused her to have a seizure. <br/>According to News.com.au, pub workers immediately jumped in and started giving the woman CPR. Paramedics arrived shortly after and took over. This went on for about 30 minutes. <br/>She was then taken to the hospital where she was later pronounced not living.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-dies-during-cake-eating-contest-on-australia-day-3955893</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/29/3955893/3955893_BED78C2A9CDC4BD693F3CFE67A732E9A_200129_3955893_Woman_dies_during_cake_eating_contest_on_Austral_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 11:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956066</guid>
      <title>Rescued turtle found pooping out a ton of plastic particles</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUENOS AIRES, ARGENTINA <br/> A green sea turtle was rescued off the coast of Buenos Aires after it was entangled in a fishing net at the end of last month, according to the Mundo Marino Foundation, an Argentinian conservation organization. <br/><br/>Researchers took X-rays of the turtle's belly and found that its digestive tract was clogged up with a bunch of plastic trash such as nylon bags and netting.<br/><br/>The turtle was promptly treated with medication to get everything flowing smoothly again. It then spent the next month pooping out over 13 grams of plastic waste. <br/><br/>The organization said in a statement that this is the equivalent of 26 plastic straws or 2.5 credit cards.<br/><br/>Researchers said the turtle is healthy now and has been feasting on greens such as lettuce and seaweed instead of abandoned plastic waste.<br/><br/>The Argentinian organization explained that they previously found two other green turtles with plastic in their digestive tracts.<br/><br/>One of the turtles was found dead with plastic waste in its belly while the other was taken in by the organization after which it dumped out a fragment of a plastic bag.<br/><br/>The green turtle has been listed as an endangered species on the International Union for Conservation of Nature Red List, mainly due to the threat of plastic pollution and habitat degradation.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/rescued-turtle-found-pooping-out-a-ton-of-plastic-particles-3956066</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956066/3956066_DE9ADF62355E42F5BA3A0686DC741862_200130_3956066_Rescued_turtle_found_pooping_out_a_ton_of_plasti_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 02:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956300</guid>
      <title>French firefighters set themselves on fire in protest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS <br/> A violent clash between police and firefighters broke out in the streets of Paris on Tuesday, during a protest over working conditions and pay. <br/><br/>French police attempted to control the situation by firing water cannons and tear gas at the firemen, some of which had even set fire to themselves.<br/><br/>The Fire brigade unions want a pay raise of 25% and argued that their work is made increasingly difficult due to staff cuts and attacks against them.<br/><br/>Paris police said firefighters who tried to break down or scale fencing near the Nation area of the city were dispersed by water cannon.<br/><br/>France24 explains how firefighters have demonstrated before, back in October one protester in the southern city of Dijon was seriously hit in the eye and has not recovered his vision.<br/><br/>Videos showing baton-wielding officers struggling against the forces of protesting firefighters made their way online.<br/><br/>The news outlet, Metro claims France has seen widespread labor unrest since December, with unions mobilizing against President Emmanuel Macron's plans to reform the pension system.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/french-firefighters-set-themselves-on-fire-in-protest-3956300</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956300/3956300_E00BA04285CD4003B7451668F293A8C9_200130_3956300_French_firefighters_set_themselves_on_fire_in_pr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 10:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956247</guid>
      <title>China demands apology from Danish paper over virus cartoon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK <br/> As China continues to struggle containing the massive outbreak of the Wuhan coronavirus, luckily it's still finding time to get its feelings hurt and wasting time asking for apologies. <br/>Reuters reports that the Chinese embassy in Denmark has DEMANDED an apology from newspaper Jyllands-Posten after it published a cartoon of the Chinese flag with its five yellow stars replaced with coronavirus particles instead<br/>NAILED IT.<br/>In a statement, the embassy said the paper and Danish artist Niels Bo Bojesen should apologize to the Chinese people for publishing the image, captioned "Coronavirus" in their Monday paper edition. <br/>The statement whined that "without any sympathy and empathy, it has crossed the bottom line of civilized society and the ethical boundary of free speech and offends human conscience."<br/>What exactly does China know about the ethical boundaries of free speech? <br/>Anyways, editor-in-chief Jacob Nybroe said the paper had not intended to make fun of the grave situation in China, but refused to apologize. <br/>Nybroe told Danish media that, "we cannot apologize for something that we don't believe is wrong." <br/>And to be honest...shouldn't the WORLD be one asking for an apology from China for giving us this latest coronavirus epidemic?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-demands-apology-from-danish-paper-over-virus-cartoon-3956247</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956247/3956247_67ACCA3D6B3643FC96EC9E1F36EF7E1C_200130_3956247_China_demands_apology_from_Danish_paper_over_vir_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 08:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956708</guid>
      <title>Pentagon says 50 soldiers were injured after Iranian missile strike</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRAQ <br/> The Pentagon now says that 50 U.S. troops stationed in Iraq have been diagnosed with traumatic brain injury after an Iranian missile strike earlier this month.<br/><br/>The agency previously said that 34 troops had been injured in the Iranian attacks.<br/><br/>In an earlier statement, the Department of Defense explained that Iran launched more than a dozen ballistic missiles that targeted U.S. military and coalition forces in Iraq on January 7.<br/><br/>The attack was an act of retaliation against the U.S. after the killing of Qassem Soleimani, an Iranian Revolution Guard general.<br/><br/>Thirty-one of the soldiers were treated in Iraq and have since returned to duty, Reuters reports, citing a statement. Eighteen troops have been sent to Germany for further treatment while one was sent to Kuwait and has since returned to duty.<br/><br/>According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, symptoms of traumatic brain injury include headaches, dizziness, nausea, and sensitivity to noise or light.<br/><br/>The Trump administration has been criticized for taking so long to reveal the extent of casualties caused by the Iranian missile attack, reports BBC News. <br/><br/>U.S. President Donald Trump had initially said that no U.S. soldier had been injured right after the attack before raising the number of casualties to 34 and now 50.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/pentagon-says-50-soldiers-were-injured-after-iranian-missile-strike-3956708</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956708/3956708_E22778C17085487AA9D01E0C4CEFC3D2_200131_3956708_Pentagon_says_50_soldiers_were_injured_after_Ira_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 07:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
