<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:11:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>4004998</guid>
      <title>Armed Men Demand Dog in Bizare Home Invasion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PRINCE GEORGE, CANADA <br/> Police are bemused over a home invasion incident that involved two suspects who weren't looking to grab pearls or wads of cash, but a dog. <br/><br/><br/><br/>Citing authorities, a report from CBC News says a call came in on the evening of May 29 that two men brandishing what appeared to be guns entered a Prince George home and demanded the occupants hand over a dog.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The occupants refused and the intruders quickly fled after officers arrived at the scene of the crime. <br/><br/><br/><br/>Police say they arrested two suspects shortly after the incident, which they believe was calculated. Prince George RCMP said in a news release that 'The two individuals entered the residence and demanded the occupant hand over the dog. It's not clear what led up to the point of the home invasion or whether there's a relationship or squabble over it.'<br/><br/><br/><br/>They also added that the suspects and one of the adult male victims were known to each other and that fortunately no one, including the dog, was physically injured; Police are not releasing the breed or any details about the sought-after pup.<br/><br/><br/><br/>23-year-old Shayn Robert Bulmer and 23-year-old Dylon Sadillo McLemore were both charged with break and enter, possession of a weapon, and two counts of assault with a weapon. <br/><br/><br/><br/>According to the report, officers found a rifle, a BB gun that was made to look like an assault rifle, and that body armor was left behind at a residence when the suspects fled from police out the back door. <br/><br/><br/><br/>The RCMP said the suspects are being held in custody pending a court appearance on Tuesday, and that more charges may be considered.<br/><br/><br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/><br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/><br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/><br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/><br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/><br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/><br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/><br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/><br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/><br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/><br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/><br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/><br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/><br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/armed-men-demand-dog-in-bizare-home-invasion-4004998</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4004998/4004998_1952DC155DA14BA7969B21869ED4182D_200603_4004998_Armed_Men_Demand_Dog_in_Bizzare_Home_Invasion_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005428</guid>
      <title>Man Smashes Car Window to Rescue Trapped Dog</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SWANSEA, WALES <br/> A video has emerged of a man smashing his way into a car to rescue a dog at a supermarket car park on a scorching hot day. <br/><br/>The clip was captured by 29-year-old Zoey Thronton, who was shopping at a Tesco in Swansea last Sunday; she claimed that the suffering dog was inside on its own for 'at least 30 minutes.'<br/><br/>According to Wales Online, Zoey noticed a woman looking concerned and went over to see if everything was okay, saying, 'we went over to see if everything was alright and it turns out that the dog was inside, it was really hot.'<br/><br/>'The window was open a little bit but we were there for at least half an hour before any action was taken.'<br/><br/>'It's long enough for a dog to overheat in a car.'<br/><br/>She even alerted the surrounding shops to send out a message over the tannoy system to try and locate the neglectful owners before their window was smashed, however, to no avail. <br/><br/>Out of nowhere, a man jumps into action and smashes the window and jumps through the car to rescue the dog. <br/><br/>Zoey stated that the dog was panting heavily and that the police, who received a call at 2.30 pm had arrived even before the owners got back. South Wales Police have, like so many, warned that dogs can die in hot cars.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-smashes-car-window-to-rescue-trapped-dog-4005428</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/04/4005428/4005428_5C0F9B65BE9E4E5080DCAB63782623F7_200604_4005428_Man_Smashes_Car_Window_to_Rescue_Trapped_Dog_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 10:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006545</guid>
      <title>Mum Dies After Drinking Two Liters of Coke Per Day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INVERCARGILL, NEW ZEALAND <br/> A mum of three died after drinking nearly two liters of Coke, plus energy drinks, per day. <br/><br/>34-year-old Amy Louise Thorpe from Invercargill, New Zealand was also 15 weeks pregnant when she was found unresponsive and face down on her bed on December 4 in 2018. She suffered an epileptic seizure and died.<br/><br/>According to findings released by coroner David Robinson, her excessive divulgence on caffeinated fizzy drinks may have been the reason why. <br/><br/>The inquest heard that Thorpe would guzzle down two liters of Coke and between 500ml to one liter of energy drinks per day. <br/><br/>Thorpe, who had a history of epilepsy and other conditions, found that her pregnancy increased her seizure frequency to about once a week.<br/><br/>According to the New Zealand Herald, Thorpe was seen by neurologist Graeme Hammond-Tooke in November 2018, who reported the epilepsy diagnosis was uncertain but treated her on the basis of that diagnosis. He encouraged her to try another antiepileptic medication, however, she was reluctant to change her drugs or undergo further tests. <br/><br/>And just weeks later, she was found unconscious and face down on her bed with her torso leaning over the bedside cabinet. Paramedics desperately tried to revive her but sadly they were unable to save her life.<br/><br/>Her partner, who was unnamed in the report, described her as being 'addicted' to caffeinated drinks.<br/><br/>When the coroner sought advice from Thorpes' Neurologist about the significance of caffeine in this case, the associated professor reported that studies suggested drinking caffeine increased seizure susceptibility while in some cases, chronic use of caffeine may protect against seizures.<br/><br/>Dr. Hammond Tooke said, 'In the case of Ms. Thorpe, I think it is possible that excessive caffeine contributed to poor seizure control.'<br/><br/>In 2010, there was another incident of a woman dying from a coke overdose from the very same city in New Zealand. The woman, Natasha Harris drank up to eight liters of Coke a day for several years before her death.<br/><br/>At the time, Coca-Cola said that it could not be proven that drinking large quantities of the drink contributed to her death.<br/><br/>A company spokesperson said that they were disappointed that the coroner had chosen to focus on the combination of excessive consumption of Coca-Cola and other health and lifestyle factors as the probable cause of her death.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mum-dies-after-drinking-two-liters-of-coke-per-day-4006545</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006545/4006545_D6777C6AEF5A4C3981863E74F9EC8616_200608_4006545_Mum_Dies_After_Drinking_Two_Liters_of_Coke_Per_D_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 23:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007292</guid>
      <title>WHO finally recommends wearing masks in public places</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> The World Health Organization on June 5 changed its guidance on wearing masks to curb the transmission of the COVID-19 disease, recommending governments encourage everyone to wear masks in public places.<br/><br/>The WHO said evidence from studies in recent weeks showed masks could serve as "a barrier for potentially infectious droplets."<br/><br/>The organization had previously said there was not enough evidence to say that healthy people should wear masks.<br/><br/>The WHO now recommends wearing masks in public settings such as stores, at work, social or mass gatherings, and in closed settings such as schools or places of worship.<br/><br/>The global body also recommends wearing masks in cramped conditions such as slums and refugee camps, and on public transport.<br/><br/>To prevent critical resources from being diverted from healthcare workers, the WHO recommends that members of the general public wear fabric or "non-medical" masks.<br/><br/>These masks should have at least three layers <br/> an absorbent inner layer, a filter, and an outer layer that does not easily absorb water.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/who-finally-recommends-wearing-masks-in-public-places-4007292</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007292/4007292_5CA7FF5850C441789D6688FAD59DAD62_200610_4007292_WHO_finally_recommends_wearing_masks_in_public_p_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 04:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007648</guid>
      <title>Meanwhile in Russia: Mom Pregnant With Step-Son's Baby</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KRASNODAR KRAI, RUSSIA <br/> 35-year-old Russian influencer, Marina Balmasheva from the western region of Krasnodar Krai, was married to husband 45-year-old Alexey, for 13 years before they got divorced. After their marriage ended, she started a relationship with Alexey's son, 20-year-old Vladimir.  <br/><br/>Why did they get divorced? Her ex told a Russian talk show that he discovered the relationship when he heard the pair having sex.<br/><br/>Saying, 'I could not fall asleep one night when I heard them having sex. Then I understood that Marina was cheating on me with my son.'<br/><br/>And just last month, to make matters worse, she recently posted a throwback picture essentially bringing further attention to their previous relationship, making it all the more weird. <br/><br/>Now Marina has revealed that she is expecting a baby with Vladimir.<br/><br/>In an Instagram video, Marina handed her hunk the positive pregnancy test and embraced him. The couple also announced their plans to marry since finding out about the pregnancy.<br/><br/>The influencer with more than 400,000 followers shared the news on Instagram where she wrote, 'I'm tired of hiding. Everything is possible in this world. We are four weeks and yes, that is why we decided to get married.'<br/><br/>Of course, she opened herself up to criticism with one person rightly pointing out, 'What shocks me most is that this boy grew up before her very eyes.'<br/><br/>So, is she worried about her new man potentially running off with a younger model? No, says Marina, 'I understand that in some time he may meet another younger woman and leave me but I think &#8211; no. He will grow into a brave real man.'<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/meanwhile-in-russia-mom-pregnant-with-step-son-s-baby-4007648</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/11/4007648/4007648_54F891F9E6DD44B9A30971243B461C54_200611_4007648_Meanwhile_in_Russia__Mom_Pregnant_With_Step_Son__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 04:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010153</guid>
      <title>China-India Himalayan Border Clash Turns Deadly</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI <br/> Indian and Chinese border defense troops had a deadly encounter last Monday that left at least 20 Indian soldiers, including a colonel, dead, according to the Times of India.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports a dozen Indian soldiers remain missing. They are thought to have been captured by Chinese forces.<br/><br/>The clash occurred in the Galwan Valley region of eastern Ladakh. Details of the encounter are unclear. However, the Guardian reports that the altercation seems to have happened when Indian border troops unexpectedly met Chinese troops while patrolling.<br/><br/>China and India have had decades-long disputes over the Line of Actual Control which separates the two countries. The two countries fought a war over the region in 1962 and have since continued to have frequent conflicts in the area.<br/><br/>And what does China have to say about this deadly incident? Well, according to China's Global Times, it was the Indian troops who provoked the attack by crossing the Line of Actual Control.<br/><br/>The jingoistic state-run outlet also claims that the clash was "intentionally staged" as an effort to take over Chinese territory and deflect attention from India's management of the COVID-19 epidemic.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-india-himalayan-border-clash-turns-deadly-4010153</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010153/4010153_4312AD552E654C039F1965BC02D6CB31_200618_4010153_China_India_Himalayan_Border_Clash_Turns_Deadly_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 01:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010248</guid>
      <title>'Rough Sex Gone Wrong' Defense to be Outlawed in the U.K.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> In a move that will make the sexually aggressive think twice, the U.K is set to ban the so-called, 'rough sex gone wrong' defense. <br/><br/>Never heard of it? Well, according to the BBC, as it stands, if someone kills another person during sexual activity they could face the lesser charge to murder, manslaughter. To murder someone, there needs to be the intent to kill or to cause them grievous bodily harm.<br/><br/>However, campaigners of 'We Can't Consent To This' have been pushing for the defense of 'rough sex gone wrong' to be outlawed and that they want an expectation that murder charges are brought against those suspected of killing a person during sexual activities.<br/><br/>How common is it? Well, the campaign group collated 60 examples of women who were killed during so-called 'sex games gone wrong' in the U.K., since 1972.<br/><br/>Interestingly, the group claims that 45% of these 'rough sex gone wrong' cases actually ended in a 'lesser charge of manslaughter, a lighter sentence or,' get this&#8230; 'the death not being investigated as a crime at all.'<br/><br/>In a move to outlaw the excuse used by lawyers, a justice minister has told MPs that it was 'unconscionable' that the defense can be used in court to justify or excuse the death of a woman 'simply because she consented.'<br/><br/>Speaking to MPs at the Commons' Public Bill Committee, MP Jess Phillips said, 'The law should be clear to all - you cannot consent to serious injury or death, but the case law is not up to the task.'<br/><br/>She said when a woman is dead 'she can't speak for herself' but any man charged with killing a woman or a current or former partner could 'simply say she wanted it.'<br/><br/>The Domestic Abuse Bill for England and Wales is due to become law later this year.<br/><br/>The 'We Can't Consent to This' campaign group said what had happened in Parliament 'was genuinely a big step forward', and that, 'We should know within weeks what their proposals are and if they've gone far enough.'<br/><br/>Chiming in, British PM Boris Johnson has said, 'We are committed to ensuring that the law is made clear and that defense is inexcusable.'<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-rough-sex-gone-wrong-defense-to-be-outlawed-in-the-u-k--4010248</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010248/4010248_D1735D928BBF41E7A02962C4CD60A232_200618_4010248__Rough_Sex_Gone_Wrong__Defense_to_be_Outlawed_in_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 06:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
