<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 18:11:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3931166</guid>
      <title>Dog nearly burns the house down after turning on microwave</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ESSEX, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> A dog in England inadvertently started a house fire after he turned on the microwave.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the husky had been left alone inside a house in Essex when he switched on the appliance, which was on a kitchen counter.<br/><br/>This wouldn't be a problem if there was nothing in it, but a packet of bread rolls just happened to be inside, and they began to burn and start a small fire. <br/><br/>The homeowner wasn't home at the time, but got alerted to the blaze by an app on his phone.<br/><br/>Checking the live feed from a camera inside the house, he saw smoke coming from the kitchen and quickly called fire services.<br/><br/>Firefighters got to the house and found the kitchen filled with smoke, but contained the fire so it didn't spread to the rest of the house.<br/><br/>Essex Fire Services says the dog wasn't hurt, and that his human got very lucky. Just imagine how serious it would have been if the blaze wasn't caught in time!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-nearly-burns-the-house-down-after-turning-on-microwave-3931166</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5FA/359/5FA359A58533CEAB01955625E30ADFCB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3931166/3931166_5F8C2DAF87B34D86B54900D560108B8B_191205_3931166_Dog_nearly_burns_the_house_down_after_turning_on_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 15:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931302</guid>
      <title>Polar bear spray painted with graffiti in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHUKOTKA, RUSSIA <br/> Video shared on social media of a polar bear spray-painted with graffiti is causing outrage after experts say it poses an extra threat to an already endangered animal.<br/><br/>World Wildlife Fund employee Sergey Kavry told the BBC that the video was shared on a WhatsApp group for indigenous people in Russia's Chukotka region, but that he didn't know where exactly it was filmed.<br/><br/>The polar bear had been spray painted on one side with "T-34", the name of a Soviet-era tank. It could take weeks to wash off, and would seriously screw up the animal's ability to camouflage while hunting. <br/><br/>After Kavry posted the video to Facebook on December 1, it went on to spark outrage among experts and en.<br/><br/>Anatoly Kochnev, a scientist at the Institute of Biological Problems of the North, says the bear was probably sedated or at the very least immobile when the letters were painted. <br/><br/>So either it was done for science, or as a sick joke.<br/><br/>Kochnev says polar bears have been foraging closer to residential areas due to the lack of food, so it's possible the locals may have stepped up to stop them.<br/><br/>Local Russian media claims though, that it was an expedition of scientists in Novaya Zemlya that marked the bear after it scavenged through rubbish bins of a human settlement, to see if it would return.<br/><br/>Either way, poor bear.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/polar-bear-spray-painted-with-graffiti-in-russia-3931302</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/828/333/828333CD1B6AF83B2627F1C32840FD6A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931302/3931302_1B2B02ABDC664719B2AA4DF2C2081B17_191206_3931302_Polar_bear_spray_painted_with_graffiti_in_Russia_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 02:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934493</guid>
      <title>Man with mosquito-killing farts hired to create insect repellant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAMPALA, UGANDA <br/> Who needs bug spray when you can just toot to make the mosquitoes go away?<br/><br/>A Ugandan man called Joe Rwamirama is claiming he lets out farts that can kill mosquitoes.<br/><br/>The toxic toots are supposedly lethal only to bugs, not people. Best not to take chances though.<br/><br/>The 48-year-old told the Talk of Naija that he doesn't eat anything special, bathes daily and doesn't stink. But for some reason, the mosquitoes can't stand to even lay a foot on him.<br/><br/>Must be nice to not know what a mosquito bite feels like.<br/><br/>His unusual attribute is pretty famous in his village, where he says no one has ever gotten malaria. Why? Because his gas is so potent and far reaching, it apparently knocks out flying insects over a six-mile radius. <br/><br/>What?! Larger than the Hiroshima bomb fallout?!<br/><br/>Joe further claims he's been signed on by two companies who want to study his intestinal gas and harness its bug-repelling properties. He won't say which companies, though, only that they're paying him 'millions' according to the Daily Mirror.<br/><br/>We're a little skeptical, but who knows, we could be seeing bug spray bottles with Joe's face on them in the not too distant future.<br/><br/>Toot on, Joe, toot on.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-with-mosquito-killing-farts-hired-to-create-insect-repellant-3934493</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/60E/041/60E0419DFD5B3BD9B1BB70A1B523EDE3.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934493/3934493_B0165E46B85F441FA36EF33666BE449D_191213_3934493_Man_with_mosquito_killing_farts_hired_to_create__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 17:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934556</guid>
      <title>Mystery as 'hundreds' of birds found dead in the road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANGLESEY, U.K. <br/> Hundreds of starlings have been found lifeless on a lane in Anglesey, North Wales. <br/><br/>The 200 plus birds were spotted by Hannah Stevens on Tuesday afternoon when she was on her way to an appointment; she saw the flock flying in the sky, however, about an hour later she found the birds dead in the road with blood on their bodies. <br/><br/>She got on the phone and called her partner, Dafydd Edwards.<br/><br/>41-year-old Edwards told Sky News that when his partner first saw the birds, "they took off to the fields<br/>and she thought, 'Oh, that was a large number of birds', and then on her way back she found them all dead in the road."<br/><br/>Mr. Edwards said, "It was very distressing<br/>my gut instinct is that they have been poisoned, but we don't know." <br/><br/>His partner, Ms. Stevens reported seeing the birds eating something in the road.<br/><br/>The couple has since contacted the police and the Animal and Plant Health Agency who they say are looking into the incident. <br/><br/>RSPB Wales told Sky News: "We are concerned with what we have seen."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mystery-as-hundreds-of-birds-found-dead-in-the-road-3934556</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D22/C00/D22C00A9645A18D2E2F0956B1FF17FB6.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934556/3934556_F101116D95334C60814E4D4B24882C50_191213_3934556_Mystery_as__hundreds__of_birds_found_dead_in_the_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 01:46:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935005</guid>
      <title>Bald eagle seconds away from becoming dinner for octopus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER ISLAND, CANADA <br/> A bald eagle who almost became the main course for a hungry octopus off the coast of Vancouver Island will luckily live to fly another day after the intervention of some Canadian salmon fishermen. <br/>According to CNN, the group was on the way back to their float house when they heard screeching and splashing sounds last Monday.<br/>According to salmon farmer John Ilett, the guys found "a full-sized eagle submerged in the water with a big giant octopus in the water trying to drag it down."<br/>The fishermen had a front row seat to mother nature for about five minutes as they went back and forth on whether or not they should intervene. <br/>Ilett said, "we weren't sure if we should interfere because it is mother nature, survival of the fittest. But it was heart wrenching <br/> to see this octopus was trying to drown this eagle."<br/><br/>The salmon fishermen maneuvered their boat closer, so Ilett could reach out with a pole. <br/>He was able to use the pole to latch onto the octopus and give it a bit of a tug, which then caused it to release its death grip on the eagle. <br/>The eagle then hightailed it over to the shore as quickly as possible, while the octopus disappeared back down into the water.  <br/>The men didn't see how the eagle got all wrapped up, but Ilett guesses our feathery friend tried to grab the octopus out of the water, but then became prey himself. <br/><br/>Guess that's what you call biting off more than you can chew.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/bald-eagle-seconds-away-from-becoming-dinner-for-octopus-3935005</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/42D/D89/42DD890B6E68504B19B61F7767BA8F93.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3935005/3935005_F1EAA3DAC8BC46DA91E1BBCA4FBC8BE7_191213_3935005_Bald_eagle_seconds_away_from_becoming_dinner_for_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936278</guid>
      <title>Russian girls go gaga over bizarre wavy lip trend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUSSIA <br/> Talk about next-level lip contouring.<br/><br/>The New York Post reports that ladies in Russia are going gaga over devil or octopus lips <br/> a bizarre new beauty trend where the lip line is wavy or scalloped. Essentially, it's the lip filler's edgier cousin.<br/><br/>No one's entirely sure when, where, and WHY it started, but Russian plastic surgeon Emelian Braude claims we have him to thank for it. Thanks but no thanks, Doc.<br/><br/>As with most weird trends, opinions on the devil lip range from "What fresh hell did you rise out of??!" to "Ohmygod take my money!" A lot of folks don't believe it's a real thing that exists either, claiming that it's nothing but a Photoshop job.<br/><br/>To settle the score, Dazed Digital consulted dental surgeon and facial aesthetician Dr. Krystyna Wilczy&#324;ski, who says they're unnatural, and can't be legit.<br/><br/>She claims that to achieve this, you'd have to be injecting filler inappropriately, and basically letting it block the blood vessels around the lips, which is definitely not safe.<br/><br/>Thing is, the images going around the interwebs is so convincing some ladies might actually go out to get fillers to achieve the look.<br/><br/>Beauty influencer Nilam Holmes warns that that kind of lip job isn't easily reversible, and is going to distort the lip border. When it wears off, it won't do so evenly, so best be prepared for frilly octopus puckers for years to come. <br/><br/>If this wavy devil lip is really your jam, maybe try hacking it through makeup instead of messing up your pouters.<br/><br/>Just get yourself a drag queen and learn to paint face the non-permanent way.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-girls-go-gaga-over-bizarre-wavy-lip-trend-3936278</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BEF/E0D/BEFE0DEAABA0D746EBB534D71C89F43D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936278/3936278_B8BE9764965944DEA52AA1C260457986_191216_3936278_Russian_girls_go_gaga_over_bizarre_wavy_lip_tren_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 15:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936212</guid>
      <title>Muscular kangaroo is harassing people and tearing up gardens</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA <br/> A six-foot and ripped kangaroo has been wreaking havoc Down Under, attacking three people in recent months.<br/>According to LadBible, the kangaroo from Queensland has already had run ins with a tourist from New Zealand, the wife of a bar owner and an elderly woman. <br/><br/>According to Stuff, the unnamed Kiwi was in town for a wedding when he got up close and personal with the towering kangaroo. <br/>The massive marsupial put its paws on the man's shoulders and was about to kick him, before it was scared off.  <br/><br/>The next unlucky victim was the wife of bar owner Shane Toy, who was outside of the pub when she was attacked by the kangaroo a few months ago.   <br/>Luckily, a customer armed with a bar stool came to his wife's rescue. They all then locked themselves in the pub until the kangaroo bounced. <br/>Then last week, according to 7 News, a 72-year-old woman was out walking her dog when she got jumped<br/>literally.   <br/>Apparently, the roo snuck up from behind and shoved the woman down to the ground and scratched up her shoulders, legs and torso.  <br/>But like a true soldier, the woman declined an offer by paramedics to be transported to the hospital. <br/>The local police have since been notified and are now tracking the kangaroo.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/muscular-kangaroo-is-harassing-people-and-tearing-up-gardens-3936212</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8AA/DF4/8AADF477BFBB6D9868F27EDB6216E4E9.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936212/3936212_F80CB7BB9D1F48B5ACE8A148F765D315_191216_3936212_Muscular_kangaroo_is_harassing_people_and_tearin_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937576</guid>
      <title>Dog keeps eating everything in site, including his own muzzle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEDDINGTON, U.K. <br/> A cute little puppy from the other side of the pond really likes to chew on things, so much so that he's already had four trips to the surgeons to have foreign objects removed from his stomach. <br/>According to the Metro, Dexter quite enjoys chewing on things that he probably shouldn't be chomping on like fishnet tights, chocolate and duct tape. <br/>His owners Andrew and Teri Gumpert from Teddington have already had to take the 18-month-old doggo to the vet more than seven times already because of his unusual eating habits. <br/>Other things that have strangely found their way into Dexter's tummy include a tennis ball, wood chippings, a hair scrunchie, a plastic bag and one of his play toys. <br/>So the Gumperts decided to get Dexter a muzzle. Problem solved. Well<br/>maybe not. He ate that too. <br/>It appears that Dexter enlisted the help of another dog in the household to help him loosen the muzzle a bit first. Then it was down the old hatch. <br/>Owner Andrew said, "we hope it's just a playful puppy thing and he'll eventually grow out of it as at the moment we can't take our eyes off him for a minute." <br/><br/>Where's the dog whisperer when you need him?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-keeps-eating-everything-in-site-including-his-own-muzzle-3937576</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/476/370/4763703DED0546C797EA712BE891D341.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937576/3937576_46CBC8F03B244B3C830C774616300CFA_191219_3937576_Dog_keeps_eating_everything_in_site__including_h_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 05:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937469</guid>
      <title>Car blows up after driver used 'excessive' aerosol</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HALIFAX, YORKSHIRE, U.K <br/> A car in Halifax exploded after the driver used "excessive" aerosol before sparking up. <br/><br/>The so-far unnamed motorist was caught in traffic around three in the afternoon on Saturday.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the blast blew out the windscreen and windows and also buckled the doors; it was so forceful it caused damage to windows at nearby businesses.<br/><br/>Police said the incident "could've been worse" and fortunately the man escaped with only minor injuries.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/car-blows-up-after-driver-used-excessive-aerosol-3937469</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/248/37C/24837C6730C3A04BC29DB5CED0D1D84A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937469/3937469_1A08B89712E74E8EB4222167A7916990_191219_3937469_Car_blows_up_after_driver_used__excessive__aeros_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 01:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937460</guid>
      <title>$66 million in jewelry stolen from F1 heiress Tamara Ecclestone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> Some Ocean's Eleven-esque robbers reportedly jacked around $66 million in jewelry from F1 heiress Tamara Ecclestone. <br/>Reuters reports that a spokesman said the daughter of ex Formula 1 boss Bernie Ecclestone was left "shaken and angry" after the Pink Panther prowlers evaded both the 24-hour security teams that patrol the street known as "Billionaire Row" and Tamara's own internal crack squad security. <br/><br/>The Sun reports that Ecclestone had just left her 57-room mansion with her hubbie and 5-year-old daughter to go on Christmas holiday when three men got in by climbing over the back fence and going through the garden. <br/><br/>They then carried out a 50-minute Thomas Crown Affair, clearing out every single piece of jewelry from hidden bedroom safes.  <br/>According to the Sun, rings, earrings and a Cartier bangle worth $105,000 were all taken in the heist. <br/>The Italian Job was then interrupted by one of Tamara's security guards.<br/>The thieves then Fast & Furious-ed it out of there and were long gone by the time cops showed up with some dogs.  <br/>Police say no arrests have been made yet, but that it was on the hunt for the three suspects.<br/>Our thoughts and prayers are with Tamara at this difficult time as one can only imagine the pain and anguish she must feel over all her bling bling that went bye bye. <br/>Naturally a GoFundMe campaign has been started to help Tamara get back on her feet.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-66-million-in-jewelry-stolen-from-f1-heiress-tamara-ecclestone-3937460</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FE8/555/FE855544FB0B008A143C18310DB254FB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937460/3937460_D5A10DDC67774C3F910531AC32D53C80_191219_3937460__66_million_in_jewelry_stolen_from_F1_heiress_Ta_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 01:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940511</guid>
      <title>Belgium's upgraded APCs can only be driven by small people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS <br/> It looks like the Belgian army's latest tank upgrade forgot to take into account that people would need to fit inside them. <br/><br/>According to the BBC, drivers or gunners of the new and maybe not-so-improved Pandur must be shorter than 5'7'' to fit in the armored vehicle. <br/>This is great because Belgium is one of the tallest countries in the world.<br/><br/>The upgrade program for the Pandurs has a budget of $34 million, but all is well since the Belgium Ministry of Defense says it only spent $1.9 million of it so far.<br/><br/>Citing Belgium's broadcaster VRT, the BBC reports that Belgium bought the Pandurs from Austria in 1966.<br/><br/>Belgium has been trying to modernize the aging Pandurs for military operations, including a planned deployment to Mali in 2021.<br/><br/>The Brussels Times reports the upgrades included extra armor, air conditioning and raised floors to protect troops from IEDs.<br/><br/>The upgrades might have made the Pandur safer, but apparently, you have to be Tom Cruise size to actually drive them.<br/><br/>Citing VRT, the BBC says the upgrades make steering and braking a "nuisance, and that the tall floor makes it hard to get in or out of the Pandur."<br/><br/>That is a very bad thing for when your ride is on fire.<br/><br/>According to BBC, Admiral Yves Dupont told the local press that the upgrades weren't finished. <br/><br/>He also said it's not unusual for armor crew to be restricted to being 5'7" tall, which is technically true if you are in a Russian antique.<br/><br/>However, Belgium's MP Wouter de Vriendt isn't buying any of this and tweeted that the Pandur upgrade was a "fiasco" and that the Pandur "could not be used."<br/><br/>In the meantime...Belgium is now looking for a few good men<br/>short ones though.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/belgium-s-upgraded-apcs-can-only-be-driven-by-small-people-3940511</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/47F/A11/47FA11628B2F5769AA66922B41D6BE25.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940511/3940511_BA41E7BFE3AA471489B4BE7579F7F70E_191225_3940511_Belgium_s_upgraded_APCs_can_only_be_driven_by_sm_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 15:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940511</guid>
      <title>Belgium's upgraded APCs can only be driven by small people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BRUSSELS <br/> It looks like the Belgian army's latest tank upgrade forgot to take into account that people would need to fit inside them. <br/><br/><br/><br/>According to the BBC, drivers or gunners of the new and maybe not-so-improved Pandur must be shorter than 5'7'' to fit in the armored vehicle. <br/><br/>This is great because Belgium is one of the tallest countries in the world.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The upgrade program for the Pandurs has a budget of $34 million, but all is well since the Belgium Ministry of Defense says it only spent $1.9 million of it so far.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Citing Belgium's broadcaster VRT, the BBC reports that Belgium bought the Pandurs from Austria in 1966.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Belgium has been trying to modernize the aging Pandurs for military operations, including a planned deployment to Mali in 2021.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The Brussels Times reports the upgrades included extra armor, air conditioning and raised floors to protect troops from IEDs.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The upgrades might have made the Pandur safer, but apparently, you have to be Tom Cruise size to actually drive them.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Citing VRT, the BBC says the upgrades make steering and braking a "nuisance, and that the tall floor makes it hard to get in or out of the Pandur."<br/><br/><br/><br/>That is a very bad thing for when your ride is on fire.<br/><br/><br/><br/>According to BBC, Admiral Yves Dupont told the local press that the upgrades weren't finished. <br/><br/><br/><br/>He also said it's not unusual for armor crew to be restricted to being 5'7" tall, which is technically true if you are in a Russian antique.<br/><br/><br/><br/>However, Belgium's MP Wouter de Vriendt isn't buying any of this and tweeted that the Pandur upgrade was a "fiasco" and that the Pandur "could not be used."<br/><br/><br/><br/>In the meantime...Belgium is now looking for a few good men<br/>short ones though.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/belgium-s-upgraded-apcs-can-only-be-driven-by-small-people-3940511</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/47F/A11/47FA11628B2F5769AA66922B41D6BE25.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940511/3940511_BA41E7BFE3AA471489B4BE7579F7F70E_191225_3940511_Belgium_s_upgraded_APCs_can_only_be_driven_by_sm_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942553</guid>
      <title>New leaked OPCW documents reveal Douma inconsistencies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DOUMA, SYRIA <br/> Wikileaks has posted several documents that further exposes the coverup within the OPCW of what really happened during the alleged Douma gas attacks.<br/><br/>On the night of April 7, 2018, Syrian military helicopters allegedly dropped chlorine bombs on the town of Douma, killing dozens of civilians.<br/><br/>The Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons sent a fact-finding mission to investigate two sites where gas cylinders were found: a rooftop balcony and a bedroom. <br/><br/>According to the official OPCW report, the rooftop bomb first struck a corner of the balcony wall.<br/><br/>This initial impact decreased the cylinder's velocity and changed its trajectory, causing it to hit the concrete floor hard enough to make a hole and fracture the valve, but without sufficient energy to fall through.<br/><br/>At the bedroom location, the official report maintains that the chlorine-filled cylinder fell parallel to the roof of a building and crashed through the concrete."<br/><br/>"It fell through and briefly impacted the floor, then continued forward on an altered trajectory that landed it on the bed. The harness and valve remained intact, and its contents were not discharged.<br/><br/>In a newly-leaked memo on Wikileaks, a scientist who was part of the Douma fact-finding mission told OPCW Director-General Fernando Arias that over 20 inspectors have expressed concern over inconsistencies in the official findings.<br/><br/>The memo's author claims that  except for one FFM member who was a paramedic, all others on the ground in Douma were excluded in the production of the final report.<br/><br/>Instead, OPCW gathered a separate "core" group that operated from "Country X", believed to be Turkey, to create said report.<br/><br/>Wikileaks had also released the first draft of the report, in which investigators say they were unable to explain "the relatively moderate damage to the cylinder...compared to the destruction caused to the rebar-reinforced concrete roof."<br/><br/>Blood and other samples taken from alleged victims who fled to Turkey found no trace of any nerve agent &#8211; a finding left out in the final report. No trace was detected in surrounding buildings or vegetation in Douma, either.<br/><br/>Another crucial finding involves the symptoms of the victims in the alleged chemical attack as being inconsistent with exposure to chlorine-containing choking or blood agents like chlorine gas, phosgene, or cyanogen chloride.<br/><br/>These directly contradict the final report, which states the investigation found "reasonable grounds that the use of a toxic chemical as a weapon took place."<br/><br/>In a report on CounterPunch, OPCW whistleblower 'Alex' said chlorinated organic chemicals are present in the natural environment, so to serve as an indicator of a chemical attack, chlorine levels should be significantly higher than what is already present.<br/><br/>In an email exchange with FFM leader Sami Barrek from July 2018, an investigator raised concern that the final report mentioned the presence of chlorinated organic chemicals at the scene, but excluded the fact that only very low levels were recovered.<br/><br/>Earlier in May, a leaked OPCW engineering assessment by ballistics expert Ian Henderson had found that the characteristics of the cylinders and surrounding scene were inconsistent with being dropped from an aircraft. It concluded that there is a higher probability they were manually placed at the two sites.<br/><br/>In CounterPunch, Alex mention an incident that could explain why the OPCW was ignoring so many dissenting voices.<br/><br/>In July 2018,  Alex claims the OPCW was visited by US officials from an unknown US agency, who told them emphatically that "the Syrian regime had conducted a gas attack, and that the two cylinders found on the roof and upper floor of the building contained 170 kilograms of chlorine.<br/><br/>The Americans, along with the British and the French, had launched retaliatory airstrikes against Syria for the chemical attack on Douma.<br/><br/>If it turns out that the attack was in fact a false flag operation masterminded by the rebels, it would be a massive blow to the narrative already established by the Western powers.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-leaked-opcw-documents-reveal-douma-inconsistencies-3942553</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A20/4FA/A204FAE3C335FC3B4DA85AA3D185ECEB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942553/3942553_6BC39F27271749A3AAC436507877A3F4_191230_3942553_New_leaked_OPCW_documents_reveal_Douma_inconsist_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 12:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942593</guid>
      <title>Super thirsty koala grabs a drink from cyclist's water bottle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA <br/> A woman out biking with her friends was shocked when an extremely parched koala walked up and drank from her water bottle. <br/><br/>According to 7 News, Anna Heusler was biking with a group of cyclists toward Adelaide last Friday when the thirsty little fella hailed them down. <br/>It approached the riders, so Heusler started giving it water. That's when her furry new friend climbed up onto her bike so it was easier to have a sip<br/>okay, more like a massive gulp. <br/>In a series of several Instagram posts, Heusler said the koala was suffering from severe thirst due to recent the heatwave and fires.   <br/>Heusler told 7 News that it wasn't unusual to see koalas while biking, but seeing one approach them like that was surprising. <br/>Talking to the station, she said, "we've seen literally hundreds of koalas over the years, we have never seen a koala do this."<br/>Unfortunately, they didn't have more water to give the little guy. They eventually put the furry fellow back into some nearby trees. <br/>Australia's koalas have been seriously struggling after massive bushfires in the region this year have destroyed habitats, leaving them without food or water.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/super-thirsty-koala-grabs-a-drink-from-cyclist-s-water-bottle-3942593</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0CF/860/0CF860FCD0892D118351D8670A7EC6BF.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942593/3942593_0753B6238F154D67B153389A16A748CC_191230_3942593_Super_thirsty_koala_grabs_a_drink_from_cyclist_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 13:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
