<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 18:11:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3957678</guid>
      <title>World's first cheese-themed hotel opens in London</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMDEN, LONDON <br/> Can you brie-lieve it! <br/><br/>The world's first 'cheese-themed' hotel has opened in London, with cheese-themed wallpaper, artwork, bedding, and even cheese-scented soap.<br/><br/>The Cheese Suite in Camden will be open until the 6th of February; the room is a part of a promotion by restaurant chain Caf&#233; Rouge to celebrate its new 'cheesy menu'.<br/><br/>Guests will also have access to a 'cheese hotline', at the push of a button you'll be provided with 'melted cheesy goodness' straight from Caf&#233; Rouge.<br/><br/>Stays are limited to one night and are free, guests are selected at random but are encouraged to donate to the restaurant chain's charity, the Prince's Trust.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-first-cheese-themed-hotel-opens-in-london-3957678</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957678/3957678_01F1BB1A00384BE99980F265226FFEAC_200203_3957678_World_s_first_cheese_themed_hotel_opens_in_Londo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 23:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958216</guid>
      <title>Greece plans to build sea barrier to keep migrants out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LESBOS, GREECE <br/> Greece wants to put up a sea barrier to stop boatloads of refugees and asylum-seekers from reaching its islands.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, migrants fleeing persecution and violence in countries like Afghanistan and Syria often try to reach Europe by travelling through Turkey to Greece.<br/><br/>Migrant camps on several Greek islands are now overcrowded, but plans to create new ones have only angered residents, who took to the streets to protest them.<br/><br/>With arrivals proving hard to manage, Greece is planning to install a floating barrier near the island of Lesbos on the Aegean Sea.<br/><br/>According to the Guardian, the 2.7-kilometer long netted barrier will rise from pylons 50 meters above water, and will be equipped with flashing lights.<br/>Greece's defense ministry said the budget for the project is 500,000 euros, which includes around four years of maintenance costs.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that such barriers rising above sea level will make it difficult for small boats to pass, and may present a problem for propeller-driven vessels.<br/><br/>Greek authorities believe a sea barrier will be able to curb flows in a similar manner to the barbed-wire fence built in Evros, along the northern land border with Turkey, in 2012.<br/><br/>Amnesty International, meanwhile, criticized Greece's plan, warning that it would only add to the dangers refugees are already facing in their quest for safety.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/greece-plans-to-build-sea-barrier-to-keep-migrants-out-3958216</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958216/3958216_1B6F6DEBDB574F5FA36D2D84192E0583_200204_3958216_Greece_plans_to_build_sea_barrier_to_keep_migran_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 03:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958725</guid>
      <title>Four passengers collapse on Ryanair 'flight from hell'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUDAPEST / EDINBURGH <br/> What was supposed to be an uneventful 3-hour plane ride to Edinburgh turned hellish after passengers started collapsing mid-flight.<br/><br/>Passenger Shaun Pinkerton told the Scottish Sun that the fire alarm on the plane was going off during boarding, but the Ryanair flight still took off as planned. <br/><br/>An hour into the January 31 trip, a 17-year-old girl collapsed in the cabin, and had to receive CPR. A second passenger also fainted, followed by Pinkerton, and then a fourth and final person.<br/><br/>Cabin crew had to perform CPR and bust out huge oxygen tanks for the fallen passengers.<br/><br/>Pinkerton himself needed an oxygen mask, and claimed he went into shock and started shaking.<br/><br/>The 27-year-old says passengers feared there was something wrong with the plane &#8211; that there wasn't enough oxygen. He blames the airline for the "flight from hell" and is demanding compensation. <br/><br/>But in a statement to the Independent, Edinburgh Airport denies any fault with the aircraft, and confirmed that cabin crew called ahead to request medical assistance upon landing.<br/><br/>The plane touched down in Edinburgh normally and was met by medics, who provided treatment for the four victims of the fainting spells.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/four-passengers-collapse-on-ryanair-flight-from-hell--3958725</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958725/3958725_186B87A3F91244C28095B3B8C2CEA052_200205_3958725_Four_passengers_collapse_on_Ryanair__flight_from_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959186</guid>
      <title>An Air Canada Boeing 767 has close call in Madrid</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRID <br/> On Monday, Air Canda's Toronto-bound Flight 837 had to request an emergency landing almost immediately after taking off from the Barajas International Airport in Madrid.<br/><br/>The Associated Press reports that the Boeing 767 had a ruptured tire and that one engine had failed.<br/><br/>Citing a Spanish civil aviation official, AP reports that the landing gear did not fold up properly and a piece of it may have been ingested by the engine, causing damage.<br/><br/>According to the Spanish edition of The Local, the Spanish air force scrambled an F-18 to escort the Boeing and help assess the damage.<br/><br/>AP reports that the commercial jet circled over Madrid for nearly four hours to burn off fuel until it was light enough to attempt a landing.<br/><br/>Shortly after 7:10 p.m., the Boeing 767 made a safe landing back in Barajas with no injuries to the 128 passengers and eight crew on board.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/an-air-canada-boeing-767-has-close-call-in-madrid-3959186</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959186/3959186_A73D430096A24D069D407FD9354C6BAB_200206_3959186_An_Air_Canada_Boeing_767_has_close_call_in_Madri_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 02:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959511</guid>
      <title>Boeing breaks apart after skidding off runway, killing three people</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISTANBUL <br/> The crashed airplane, a Pegasus Airlines Boeing 737-800 on Flight 2193 from Izmir to Istanbul, arrived at the Sabiha Gokcen[e] airport at 6:19 p.m. on Wednesday.<br/><br/>The plane was carrying 177 passengers and six crew.<br/><br/>According to International Flight Network, weather conditions were poor with heavy rains and a powerful tailwind that may have caused the plane to touch down too late.<br/><br/>The Boeing overshot the runway and had trouble slowing down on the rain slicked surface.<br/><br/>Flight data indicates that the Boeing's last recorded speed was dangerously fast at 117 km per hour.<br/><br/>Speaking at a news conference, Istanbul Governor Ali Yerlikaya said the plane was dragged 50 meters before falling down a 30-meter slope, the New York Times reports.<br/><br/>The jet broke into three pieces and social media footage apparently shows passengers fleeing the wreckage after the crash.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports that three people were killed and 157 were hospitalized.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/boeing-breaks-apart-after-skidding-off-runway-killing-three-people-3959511</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959511/3959511_8E773F25C8E84C88B7D1E50650CF3026_200206_3959511_Boeing_breaks_apart_after_skidding_off_runway__k_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961845</guid>
      <title>Queen sends disgraced Andrew to meet with Chinese Ambassador</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> Britain's Queen Elizabeth sent her son, Prince Andrew to offer her condolences to the Chinese government for those affected in the latest crisis.<br/><br/>Prince Andrew made headlines last year for a disastrous BBC interview that saw him fail to defend himself against allegations of sexual assault; the Prince also couldn't explaion his relationship with Jeffrey Epstein which led Andrew to announced he was stepping back from public duties.<br/><br/>The meeting was met with mockery and shock, with one netizen calling out the Queen's decision, "You know this is a veiled insult, right?"]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/queen-sends-disgraced-andrew-to-meet-with-chinese-ambassador-3961845</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3961845/3961845_6CC75FCDAE04426A99DDB967E004EF60_200212_3961845_Queen_sends_disgraced_Andrew_to_meet_with_Chines_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 00:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962808</guid>
      <title>Woman jailed for trying to open plane door mid-flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHELMSFORD, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> A lady who tried to open a plane door mid-flight is set to spend the next two years in the slammer.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that last June 22, Chloe Haines had been drunk as a skunk on both alcohol and medication while travelling with her wheelchair-bound nan aboard a Jet2 flight to Dalaman, Turkey.<br/><br/>Prosecutors say she lunged at a door handle on the emergency exit door, bellowing "I want to die!" and "I'm going to kill you all!" as cabin crew and passengers tried to restrain her. <br/><br/>She was kicking and punching, and even scratched up a cabin crew member named Charley Coombe.<br/><br/>Haines' antics sparked a hijack alert, which then prompted two Royal Air Force fighter jets to scramble up there and intercept the plane, guiding it back to Stansted for an emergency landing.<br/><br/>She later claimed she had blacked out and didn't really remember anything after downing her unholy cocktail.<br/><br/>Haines pleaded guilty to two charges: endangering the safety of a passenger plane and assault by beating.<br/><br/>Jet2 has also banned her for life after her little air rage incident cost them &#163;86,000.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-jailed-for-trying-to-open-plane-door-mid-flight-3962808</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962808/3962808_6B998C8D63594BF988C509553700E487_200213_3962808_Woman_jailed_for_trying_to_open_plane_door_mid_f_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 15:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964038</guid>
      <title>Vessel with Iranian-made weapons onboard seized in Arabian Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARABIAN SEA <br/> The U.S. has seized yet another vessel containing Iranian-made weapons that was apparently bound for Houthi forces in Yemen.<br/><br/>The USS Normandy was conducting maritime security operations when it stopped a stateless dhow in the Arabian Sea on Sunday, February 9, according to a statement from the U.S. Central Command.<br/><br/>Sailors from the missile cruiser boarded the vessel in accordance with international law.<br/><br/>They found and seized weapons onboard including 150 Dehlavieh anti-tank missiles, three surface-to-air missiles, thermal imaging weapon scopes, and components used for unmanned aerial and surface vessels.<br/><br/>In a statement, the U.S. Central Command explained that these weapons were deemed to be of Iranian origin. <br/><br/>These were seized as they were determined to be for Houthi fighters in Yemen, which would violate a UN Security Council Resolution. The resolution prohibits the sale, supply and or transfer of weapons to these fighters.<br/><br/>The weapons are now in U.S. custody waiting for final disposition.<br/><br/>The statement, which was released on Thursday, also noted that the seized weapons were "identical" to weapons seized by the USS Forrest Sherman in the Arabian Sea in November.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/vessel-with-iranian-made-weapons-onboard-seized-in-arabian-sea-3964038</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964038/3964038_6F657B571F4C4DA5A5B33FE697C263B3_200217_3964038_Vessel_with_Iranian_made_weapons_onboard_seized__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964939</guid>
      <title>Tourist takes risky shot on the edge of Rio cliff</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIO DE JANEIRO <br/> How far would you go for the perfect Instagram shot?<br/><br/>A video taken last November 2019 in Brazil is giving people the heebie jeebies after it showed a female tourist posing on the edge of a cliff &#8211; perilously close to a 3,000-foot drop.<br/><br/>The nerve-wracking display was taken atop Rio de Janeiro's Pedra de Gavea mountain, which the unnamed woman had to take a demanding two-and-a-half-hour hike to get to.<br/><br/>She managed to get to the top of what the Brazilian Tourist Board calls the world's largest coastline monolith, which is a victory in and of itself. But you know what they say &#8211; photo or it didn't happen.<br/><br/>The woman did one better by having herself filmed as she shuffled her bum closer to the edge of the rock. The dude taking the video gets her to move forward even more, and the foolishly fearless lady complies, before posing with both arms raised. <br/><br/>It's a cool shot for sure, but one wrong move and off the cliff you go. Fortunately, and shockingly, the woman didn't fall off, and came away from the whole experience completely unscathed.<br/><br/>The internet reacted as it does, criticizing the lady for risking her life and the lives of people on the ground below, who could've been seriously hurt had she fallen.<br/><br/>But it's not like she's the first one to do this. Search Pedra de Gavea on social media and you'll see a whole lotta folks risking life and limb to do exactly what this woman did.<br/><br/>That's just how the cookie crumbles in this Instagram-obsessed world.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tourist-takes-risky-shot-on-the-edge-of-rio-cliff-3964939</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3964939/3964939_0BB7B064055B48E5BCB212CA0CC1E79B_200219_3964939_Tourist_takes_risky_shot_on_the_edge_of_Rio_clif_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 02:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965456</guid>
      <title>Russian lieutenant proposes to girlfriend with 16-tank display</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW <br/> A platoon commander in Russia decided to propose to his girlfriend in a most unusual way &#8211; with the help of military tanks. <br/><br/>According to RT, Lieutenant Denis Kazantsev got permission from his commanders to carry out his big proposal at the Alabino testing grounds southwest of Moscow.<br/><br/>On the morning of February 13, 16 T-72B2 tanks rolled onto the range and proceeded to maneuver around until they lined up in a heart formation.<br/><br/>23-year-old Kazantsev can be seen leading girlfriend Alexandra Kopytova to the middle of the heart, making sure to keep her eyes all covered. Lover Boy then gets down on one knee and pops the question while holding out some flowers and a shiny ring.<br/><br/>Unsurprisingly, Kopytova said yes. It'd be awkward if she said no, because as it turns out, she and Kazantsev have already been married for a year.<br/><br/>He told Metro News that his first proposal was in December 2017. But seeing as how they lived in different cities then, it probably wasn't THAT romantic and needed a round 2.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-lieutenant-proposes-to-girlfriend-with-16-tank-display-3965456</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965456/3965456_ECFF854FF33D429BA76568BB115B50AC_200220_3965456_Russian_lieutenant_proposes_to_girlfriend_with_1_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 02:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965944</guid>
      <title>Queen blocks Harry and Meghan using brand 'royal'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM / CANADA  <br/> The Duke and Duchess of Sussex, Harry, and Meghan have been told they won't be allowed to use the 'Sussex Royal' label after quitting the royals.<br/><br/>Harry and Meghan spent tens of thousands of pounds building a website that was based on the brand which started from their Instagram account which boasts 11.2 million followers.<br/><br/>The couple has also registered 'Sussex Royal' as a trademark internationally on items including clothing, stationery, books, and teaching materials.<br/><br/>However, The Queen has claimed that the two should no longer be using the term 'royal' if they no longer carry out royal duties. <br/><br/>A royal source has since stated that the future use of the term 'royal' by the abdicated couple "needed to be reviewed."<br/><br/>Harry and Meghan first used the 'Sussex Royal' name when they created their own household with the intention of being financially independent; however, now they may now have to re-name their website and start again from scratch.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/queen-blocks-harry-and-meghan-using-brand-royal--3965944</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965944/3965944_5E3A3017BF90474B9B3FFBB8827C2B0D_200221_3965944_Queen_blocks_Harry_and_Meghan_using_brand__royal_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965937</guid>
      <title>Plane passengers spotted traveling in full-body plastic suits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY <br/> With the C thing infecting people all across the world, folks these days have taken to sporting protective gear to keep it at bay. <br/><br/>For most, that means donning a face mask, maybe even gloves if you're a bit more paranoid. But these two people took it up several notches when they decided to get on a plane while in a mask, latex gloves, AND fully covered in plastic.<br/><br/>Who needs a hazmat suit, amirite?<br/><br/>Twitter user Alyssa423 had spotted the pair on her flight, which according to the Dailymail, was going from Sydney to Hamilton island. She shared a video clip of the duo on the platform, which has since racked over 90,000 views.<br/><br/>Twitter users had mixed reactions to the full-body plastic suit: some were impressed at the lengths to which the pair were willing to go and could totally relate. But a lot of folks thought it was a dumb idea, since not only was it a suffocation hazard, but such extra precautionary measures may not be all that effective anyway.<br/><br/>But hey, whatever gives you peace of mind.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/plane-passengers-spotted-traveling-in-full-body-plastic-suits-3965937</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965937/3965937_EC6C31C2AD034CB080A5249607602271_200221_3965937_Plane_passengers_spotted_traveling_in_full_body__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966460</guid>
      <title>Far-right extremist kills 9 in Germany shisha bar shootings</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANAU, GERMANY<br/> A gunman in Germany opened fire on two shisha bars in what police suspect is a racially-motivated attack.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that around 10 p.m. Wednesday, a 43-year-old man began shooting inside the Midnight shisha bar in the city center of Hanau in Germany. He then fled by car to the Kesselstadt neighborhood about 2.5 kilometers away, and continued his attack at another shisha bar, called Arena Bar and Cafe. <br/><br/>According to CNN, nine people were killed in the attacks, with both German and Turkish nationals being among the victims. Six others suffered injuries.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that following the shootings, police carried out an hours-long manhunt that lasted through the night.<br/><br/>According to the Guardian, special police force officers stormed the suspect's home at 5 a.m. local time and found the suspect dead along with another body. Police say the gunman, later identified as Tobias Rathjen. had shot his 72-year-old mother and then himself.<br/><br/>The Bild newspaper reported that the suspect left a letter of confession, in which he expressed "extreme right wing views. He also put up a video explaining his motives, but it has since been taken down from social media sites.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/far-right-extremist-kills-9-in-germany-shisha-bar-shootings-3966460</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/22/3966460/3966460_8C9D551656274DE0B53FB0432BC2686C_200222_3966460_Far_right_extremist_kills_9_in_Germany_shisha_ba_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967205</guid>
      <title>Australian train runs off rail and kills two on a troubled track</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WALLAN, AUSTRALIA <br/> An Australian XPT train travelling from Sidney to Melbourne derailed on Thursday, February 20, resulting in the deaths of the train driver and co-driver. Citing Australian officials, the BBC reports that 153 passengers were on board at the time.<br/><br/>Australia's ABC reports the rail firm found track faults in the days before the accident. Citing passengers, BBC reports the driver had announced that he would try make up for earlier delays. At 7:50 p.m., the train derailed near Wallan, a township about 45 km from Melbourne.<br/><br/>Citing Victoria Police, ABC reports the impact killed the train driver, a 54-year-old Australian Capital Territory man, and the pilot, a 49 year old Castlemaine woman. The crash turned the engine and the first carriage on their sides.<br/><br/>Footage and images of the aftermath show that the engine and four passenger carriages left the rails. ABC reports that 12 passengers were hospitalized, including 11 with minor injuries and one person who suffered upper torso wounds.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/australian-train-runs-off-rail-and-kills-two-on-a-troubled-track-3967205</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967205/3967205_3A04AC7E1E254B998EE02B6A8A5D9F69_200224_3967205_Australian_train_runs_off_rail_and_kills_two_on__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 06:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967643</guid>
      <title>Russian mom set to marry her stepson after divorcing his dad</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUSSIA <br/> A 35-year-old popular Russian blogger is gearing up to marry her 20-year-old stepson after her 10-year marriage to his father ended in divorce.<br/><br/>On her Instagram page which boasts 406,000 followers, Marina Balmasheva said, "You never know how life will turn out and when you will meet a person who makes you smile. I know that some will judge us, others will support us, but we are happy and wish you to be as well."<br/><br/>Marina said she is very happy with her stepson, Vladimir and that he is helping to raise three of his five siblings. <br/><br/>She went on to say that the couple will have more children and that wedding bells are on the horizon, however, no date has been reported.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-mom-set-to-marry-her-stepson-after-divorcing-his-dad-3967643</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967643/3967643_D6243C15FB4C471D9CB4F8B2D47E3266_200225_3967643_Russian_mom_set_to_marry_her_stepson_after_divor_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 05:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968088</guid>
      <title>Surfer punches shark in the eye and tells it to "F*** off!"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PAUANUI, NEW ZEALAND <br/> A 60-year-old surfer fought off a Great White shark by punching it in the eye repeatedly after it took hold of his arm and clamped down on his surfboard. <br/><br/>Aucklander, Nick Minogue says he was "quite a long way out" at Pauanui Beach, and at around 11:30 am his elbow, forearm and then board were all attacked by what experts believe to be a three meter-long Great White. <br/><br/>Minogue instantly remembered that sharks hate being punched in the eyes and nose; he shouted, "f**k off!" and went to strike it, but missed.<br/><br/>He said, "then I pulled my fist back and shouted 'f**k off!' again and got it right smack bang in the eye. It's quite a big eye, about three knuckles across."<br/><br/>According to Minogue the shark disengaged its teeth from his board and swam off. <br/><br/>Desperate to get out of the water, Minogue said it was only him and a German surfing at the time. After Minogue started screaming, both he and the German started paddling back to shore as fast as they could with Minogue adding, "The German guy was kind of screaming the whole way which probably made me paddle even faster."<br/><br/>Fleeing the open water, Minogue was "bumped" into again by what he says was probably a Great White; he sat up on his board and punched that one too. <br/><br/>With his fingers intact and one small puncture wound to his arm, Nick Monuge is looking ahead to a surfing trip later next week.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/surfer-punches-shark-in-the-eye-and-tells-it-to-f%2A%2A%2A-off--3968088</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968088/3968088_F89A018A621C4A6AB37D4D6E4129A179_200226_3968088_Surfer_punches_shark_in_the_eye_and_tells_it_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 03:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968058</guid>
      <title>WHO warns COVID-19 could become a pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> The World Health Organization has warned that the world should prepare for a potential coronavirus pandemic.<br/><br/>Outbreaks of COVID-19 have emerged in South Korea, Italy, and Iran, causing concern and prompting the WHO to say countries should be in 'a phase of preparedness' for a possible pandemic.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that a pandemic occurs when an infectious disease easily spreads from person to person across many parts of the world.<br/><br/>Thus far, the outbreak has been centered in China, where the virus originated. Over 77,000 people have been infected, and 2,600 have died.<br/><br/>South Korea currently has 830 confirmed cases &#8211; the largest number outside China. Eight have died, and 7,700 troops are now quarantined after at least 13 in the military were found to be infected.<br/><br/>Most of the country's cases are in Daegu, where clusters have been linked to a hospital and a secretive religious group.<br/><br/>The largest number of cases in Europe &#8211; at least 229 &#8211; are in Italy. To contain the outbreak, authorities have locked down several towns in the Lombardy and Veneto regions.<br/><br/>Iran also has 61 confirmed cases, the majority of which is in the holy city of Qom.<br/>According to the BBC, cases have also been reported in Iraq, Afghanistan, Kuwait, Oman, and Bahrain, all of which involve people who came from Iran.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/who-warns-covid-19-could-become-a-pandemic-3968058</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968058/3968058_D16B7DD0CE324C5B8EDBF82139830F8A_200226_3968058_WHO_warns_COVID_19_could_become_a_pandemic_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 02:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3969075</guid>
      <title>Eyeball tattoo leaves alt-model blind for 3 weeks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTRALIA <br/> 24-year-old alt-model, Amber Luke has spent more than $25,000 on modifying her body, and she recently revealed that she went blind for three weeks after inking her eyes late last year.<br/><br/>Dubbed 'Blue-Eyes White Dragon' by friends, Amber claims, "I can't even begin to describe to you what the feeling was like, the best thing I can give you is once the eyeball was penetrated with the ink, it felt like the tattoo artist grabbed 10 shards of glass and rubbed it in my eye."<br/><br/>Amber, who developed an addiction to tattoos at the age of 16, said, "unfortunately, my artist went too deep into my eyeball <br/> If your eyeball procedure's done correctly, you're not supposed to go blind at all. I was blind for three weeks. That was pretty brutal."<br/><br/>Amber, who has had her tongue split, a silicone implant in her eye, a boob job, cheek and lip fillers and pointed implants placed in her ears says the eye tattoo was totally "worth it." <br/><br/>She said every morning she wakes up, looks at her eyeballs and is happy because blue is her favorite color. <br/><br/>Before you judge, Amber has one request, "We should all try and take a step back and wonder how creative and passionate that person must be to express themselves like that <br/> instead of shunning someone, look at their beauty &#8211; I mean come on, it's 2020."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/eyeball-tattoo-leaves-alt-model-blind-for-3-weeks-3969075</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/28/3969075/3969075_04D24940B1BB4DB7872839350319B931_200228_3969075_Eyeball_tattoo_leaves_alt_model_blind_for_3_week_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 02:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
