<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 18:11:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3915995</guid>
      <title>Russian pilot lets female passenger fly the plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE UNQUALIFIED SKIES <br/> Unbelievable footage showing a female passenger at the controls of a plane during a scheduled flight has really taken off in good old Mother Russia. <br/>According to the Siberian Times, video appearing to show a woman flying the aircraft from the co-pilot's seat was sent to a Russian news website.  <br/>In the video, the pilot's voice can be heard giving instructions to Maverick, who is thought to be in her late 20s with zero flying credentials. <br/><br/>Russian reports say the incident occurred on a Russian airlines IrAero flight aboard an Antonov-24 from Yakutsk to Batagay. <br/>The flight occurred on August 31, but the video has only recently emerged. <br/>Investigators will probably spend decades piecing together how this footage made its way public. <br/>It is most likely unrelated to the pictures and video of the flight on Anna's IG with the captions "This is unbelievably cool" and "Thank you!"<br/>Strangely the account has mysteriously been deleted. <br/>According to Russian news, the pilot involved in the Hot Shots incident is Kirill S. <br/>IrAero airlines told Russian media that it is now investigating. A spokesman for the company said, "there are doubts that these materials have anything to do with our airline's activities in providing passengers transportation."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-pilot-lets-female-passenger-fly-the-plane-3915995</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4A9/B6F/4A9B6FEA0706BAFCDC265D56048F5F2D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3915995/3915995_E9B46C0EA48E4E8CA780D3FA78F27FE9_191104_3915995_Russian_pilot_lets_female_passenger_fly_the_plan_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 10:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917583</guid>
      <title>Driverless Tesla drives itself through Vancouver parking lot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VANCOUVER <br/> A Tesla Model 3 was spotted driving on the wrong side of the road with no one behind the wheel in Vancouver on Monday. <br/>According to Richmond News, a woman filmed the zombie white Tesla slowly moving through a parking lot in a Richmond shopping center at around 2 p.m. <br/>Apparently the Model 3 had been activated using the "Smart Summon" function, which allows owners to call their vehicles to their location, or a location of their choosing, within a 200-foot radius using the Tesla mobile app. <br/><br/>Reports say the rogue Tesla entered the parking lot on the wrong side of an intersection and then continued for about 50 yards on the wrong side of the road.   <br/>The woman who captured the footage said at one point a mall security guard came out and started chasing the empty Tesla down, before a man, thought to be the owner's friend, came out to explain it was being "summoned." <br/>Another clip from inside the parking structure shows the Tesla stopped with the owner standing by the trunk. <br/><br/>After putting some stuff in, he is then seen driving away. <br/>The shopping center told the Richmond News they are aware of the incident and have notified the authorities.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/driverless-tesla-drives-itself-through-vancouver-parking-lot-3917583</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B7B/03D/B7B03D5698D628B59BB1D4BA43EEACC1.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917583/3917583_6AB9C3EB0BD04BB7AAAA16DC3270FAD6_191107_3917583_Driverless_Tesla_drives_itself_through_Vancouver_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 11:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917417</guid>
      <title>1.3 Million pound house is making people 'ill'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PINNER, MIDDLESEX, U.K <br/> One home in the U.K, is making headlines for its strange decor.  <br/><br/>The home in Pinner, Middlesex has been making headlines for its' unusual interior after it was listed on Rightmove, a U.K real estate company for a cool 1.3 million pounds which is about 1.7 million dollars.<br/><br/>The detached five-bedroom "family haven" has puzzled would-be buyers and netizens with its strange - and large collection of plug sockets and recessed lighting.<br/><br/>Every wall appears to be absolutely covered in sockets. Sockets that're piled on top of one another and don't even lineup. <br/><br/>The strange thing is, no one knows why, not even the homeowner. <br/><br/>Speaking to The Sun Online, 45-year-old tech boss and homeowner, Devang Gandhi said the property was already like that when he bought it six years ago. <br/><br/>"The sockets are very handy because you don't have to pull the cables."<br/><br/>"Wherever you want to stick in the plug, you can stick it in for the TV, DVDs, stereos."<br/><br/>"You have separate plugs for everything rather than having wires everywhere."<br/><br/>"It's very nice."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/1-3-million-pound-house-is-making-people-ill--3917417</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/639/B25/639B252655CBA9D26D0A13657728DE8B.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917417/3917417_FD6637D9968849FFA613793A93F9066C_191107_3917417_1_3_Million_pound_house_is_making_people__ill__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 06:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917876</guid>
      <title>British tourist eaten by shark while on vacation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REUNION ISLAND, FRANCE <br/> An unnamed tourist from the UK was vacationing with his wife in Reunion Island when tragedy struck.<br/><br/>The man and his wife were spending a week-long vacation on the island when the 44-year-old decided to go on a swim by himself on November 2, the Herald Scotland reports. <br/><br/>His wife reported the man as missing when he didn't return from his swim. Authorities then launched a full search including a helicopter and boats.<br/><br/>Even divers were called to look around the coral reef in the area, while sniffer dogs were patrolling the island.<br/><br/>Eventually scientists examined five fish caught around Reunion Island and found a severed hand with a wedding ring inside one of the shark's stomach.<br/><br/>The man himself has yet to be found. According to the report, the man may have drowned and his corpse could have attracted the shark to chomp down on his hand.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/british-tourist-eaten-by-shark-while-on-vacation-3917876</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/15E/32B/15E32B1F13F2D810E1066A08E6223828.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3917876/3917876_600C6774589E40B1976ADDF062793383_191108_3917876_British_tourist_eaten_by_shark_while_on_vacation_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 03:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919502</guid>
      <title>Man shoots neighbor in the chest with crossbow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST LOTHIAN, SCOTLAND <br/> A Scottish man was shot in the chest with an arrow after a feud with a crazed neighbor.<br/><br/>The High Court in Glasgow was told Raph Muir got into an argument with Shaun Reynolds over "anti-social behavior," the Daily Record reports.<br/><br/>Muir then grabbed two crossbows he kept at home and aimed one of them at Reynolds' chest. The 31-year-old was heard screaming at Reynolds saying, "I'm not leaving here until you are dead."<br/><br/>Reynolds ended up with an arrow stuck in his chest, which he pulled out.<br/><br/>The 46-year-old only sustained one "superficial" wound on his chest.<br/><br/>Scottish firearms police officers arrived at the scene and ordered Muir to lie on the ground and then arrested him. While searching his home, the police found three crossbows, a chainsaw, a baseball bat and a knife.<br/><br/>According to the Daily Record, the Muir later told the police that he wanted to "murder people" who bothered him while he was at home.<br/><br/>The crossbow attacker pled guilty to attempted murder at the High Court in Glasgow. He now faces a lengthy jail term and is due to be sentenced next month.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-shoots-neighbor-in-the-chest-with-crossbow-3919502</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/142/CF4/142CF421FDB42B18121E418C3FF6E7FB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/11/3919502/3919502_A7C824CC5DE547D5B3F6959A6D2BF65F_191111_3919502_Man_shoots_neighbor_in_the_chest_with_crossbow_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 12:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3921532</guid>
      <title>Russian airline passenger used a body double for his fat cat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW <br/> A Russian cat owner is now short a few hundred thousand air miles for sneaking his fat cat aboard a flight using a hairbrained scheme involving a cat double. <br/>He should have gotten away with it too, but for some unexplained reason, his air carrier Aeroflot found out. <br/><br/>It was most likely entirely unrelated to the man's Facebook post about the entire thing. <br/>BBC reports that 34-year-old Mikhail Galin was flying from the Latvian capital of Riga to Vladivostok, which had a stopover in Moscow. <br/><br/>Traveling with Mikhail was his furry feline friend Viktor. <br/><br/>Everything was going along PURR-fectly, until Aeroflot staff refused to let Mikhail take Viktor into the passenger cabin for the second leg of his flight because of weight restrictions. <br/>Aeroflot rules state pets weighing more than 17 pounds have to be shoved in the luggage hold. Viktor was tipping the scales at 22 pounds.   <br/><br/>So what did Galin do? He delayed his flight so he could find a skinnier cat double to pass the airline's weigh in. <br/>He returned the next day with the Viktor-lite version the next day and got past the check-in desk. <br/><br/>Mikhail then gave back the smaller cat to its owner at the airport before getting on the plane with Viktor for his flight to Vladivostok. <br/>After his Facebook post about the entire ordeal went viral, Aeroflot took notice and decided to strip Galin of all his air miles.<br/>The cat was contacted for comment, however by the time of publication TomoNews wasn't yet able to find out whether Viktor's miles are still good.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-airline-passenger-used-a-body-double-for-his-fat-cat-3921532</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE3/3C6/EE33C6D3FEAD1CDC3C42CDA2FFEF7CF7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921532/3921532_E867FC2F5F944F488105368F2835271D_191115_3921532_Russian_airline_passenger_used_a_body_double_for_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 11:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3921528</guid>
      <title>Giraffe hit by van dies and falls on jeep, killing Swiss tourist</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KRUGER NATIONAL PARK, SOUTH AFRICA <br/> A South African safari took a tragic turn on Sunday when a giraffe was hit by a tourist van, which then fell onto another passing jeep in Kruger National Park. <br/>CNN reports that a taxi van carrying 13 tourists was driving through the park when a giraffe suddenly stepped out onto the road.  <br/>After being struck by the taxi, the giraffe then fell on a rental safari vehicle carrying two occupants traveling in the opposite direction. The rental was driven by a Swiss national.  <br/><br/>The collision unfortunately killed the giraffe and left the driver seriously injured. He later succumbed to his injuries at the hospital.  <br/><br/>The passenger of the rental vehicle and two other tourists from the taxi van also suffered minor injuries. <br/>A press release from the South African National Parks urged the public "to always be watchful of all kinds of species while driving on the roads in the Park."<br/><br/>The statement also added, "these animals have a right of way." <br/>According to CNN, giraffes stand from 14 to 19 feet tall and can weigh as much as 2,800 pounds. Both vehicles involved in the crash sustained serious damage. <br/>Park officials are now investigating the incident.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/giraffe-hit-by-van-dies-and-falls-on-jeep-killing-swiss-tourist-3921528</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/154/3D5/1543D5CBEFBEC3EF4535AAD702DB3C29.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921528/3921528_1ED156E82BC84E908273526E52E4973D_191115_3921528_Giraffe_hit_by_van_dies_and_falls_on_jeep__killi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 11:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3922838</guid>
      <title>Italian council floods right after rejecting climate measures</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VENICE, ITALY <br/> The Veneto regional council flooded for the first time ever last Tuesday  just after it happened to reject measures to address climate change. <br/>CNN reports Venice was a bit on the wet side last week after being slammed with the worst flooding in more than half a century. <br/>According to a Facebook post by Democratic Party councilor Andrea Zanoni, the council chamber in Ferro Fini Palace began to look like Waterworld around 10 p.m. local time, as councilors were debating the 2020 regional budget. <br/>In the post, Zanoni said the rejected amendments included measures to fund renewable energy, replace diesel buses with greener ones, scrap polluting stoves and reduce plastics impact. <br/>Regional council spokesman confirmed with the most trusted name in news that the council was flooder after discussing the amendments of the 2020 budget without watering it down with specific details. <br/>According to the council's website, meetings were moved to Treviso last Thursday and Friday because of the flooding.    <br/><br/>Venice Mayor Luigi Brugnaro said last week the historic flooding was a direct result of climate change, and you know, he's probably right.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/italian-council-floods-right-after-rejecting-climate-measures-3922838</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B8E/C6A/B8EC6A6E843B2959215679E6FEA9EC93.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922838/3922838_720852379827473397BD31E1372881D7_191118_3922838_Italian_council_floods_right_after_rejecting_cli_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 12:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923528</guid>
      <title>Trapped hoarder rescued
after massive junk cave-in</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANLEY VALE, AUSTRALIA <br/> An unnamed elderly hoarder living in Canley Vale near Sydney was trapped for about sixteen hours after her stockpile fell on her.<br/><br/>Australia's Nine News reports that the stash included eighties fashion mags and food from the 1990s.<br/><br/>Neighbors told 9 News that the woman and her husband have been hoarding for as long as they can remember. Apparently, the mess got so bad that her husband started sleeping in the car.<br/><br/>The woman's solitary bliss was rudely interrupted when a treasure trove of goodies collapsed on her Sunday evening. After she failed to respond to his regular check-up call the next morning, her husband called in the emergency services.<br/><br/>Nine News reports that neighbors saw rescuers break into the house via a side window.<br/><br/>The woman was saved, but apparently the situation was so bad that special equipment and training designed for earthquake rescue were used to dig her out of nearly a tonne of debris.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/trapped-hoarder-rescued%0Aafter-massive-junk-cave-in-3923528</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6B2/CDA/6B2CDAAD48178A9730BDD54E51107D23.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/20/3923528/3923528_654B90C8DCC94E758C7F82E9EA2B6803_191120_3923528_Trapped_hoarder_rescued_after_massive_junk_cave__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 01:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924028</guid>
      <title>Two men boiled alive after their car falls into sinkhole in Russia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENZA, RUSSIA <br/> A sinkhole opened up in a Russian parking lot, swallowing up one car. <br/>Metro reported that the freak accident occurred at a parking lot in Penza. <br/><br/>According to local media, another vehicle had driven over the same parking spot minutes before, but noticed steam coming from the ground, so quickly hightailed it out of there. <br/>That's when the two men driving in a Lada Largus pulled up and parked in the spot. <br/>After the guys stopped the car, the asphalt collapsed right under them.  <br/>The men died "almost instantly" after being sprayed by 167 degrees Fahrenheit water inside the sinkhole. <br/>Local media suggested that a hot water pipe had burst under the parking lot, causing the sinkhole. <br/>In Russia, hot water is piped to buildings underground during the crazy cold winters.  <br/>The two men have not been publicly identified. The accident is now being investigated by authorities.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/two-men-boiled-alive-after-their-car-falls-into-sinkhole-in-russia-3924028</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/897/79B/89779B15B6AE2D0E03914C91D816B57F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/21/3924028/3924028_C38D05CB70C64F66B33F6EFCBA631A9E_191121_3924028_Two_men_boiled_alive_after_their_car_falls_into__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924566</guid>
      <title>Family lugs uncle's corpse to
insurance company to prove death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KWADUKUZA, SOUTH AFRICA <br/> According to South Africa's News 24, the KwaZulu-Natal family took the drastic measure to get their roughly US$2,000 payout after video of the incident went viral, thus shaming insurance company Old Mutual.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/family-lugs-uncle-s-corpse-to%0Ainsurance-company-to-prove-death-3924566</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/77C/88C/77C88C7C34515E66C0F87DA9263655F6.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924566/3924566_45EA1D1890FE498D912FA68EE27C9A29_191122_3924566_Family_lugs_uncle_s_corpse_to_insurance_company__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 03:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926104</guid>
      <title>Woman caught stealing 8 pairs of jeans by wearing them</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VENEZUELA <br/> A shoplifter in South America tried to pull a Joey Tribbiani by wearing the clothes she was planning to steal all at once.<br/><br/>According to The Sun, the incident is believed to have occurred at a store in Venezuela, and involved an unidentified woman and her bizarre plan.<br/><br/>No one knows how she did it, but the crafty lady put on pair after pair after pair of denim jeans <br/> on top of the pair she already had on! <br/><br/>How she even managed to walk, let alone move with that much denim on is another mystery. But she did it, and got as far as the exit before security noticed what was up.<br/><br/>In a video that has since gone viral, Miss Skillz is seen inside a bathroom, peeling each jean layer one by one. <br/><br/>The man filming her counts each one while trying really hard not to laugh. He eventually getting a grand total of eight. <br/><br/>It's unclear if the lady was arrested for charged for any crime, but now that she's famous online, here's hoping she'll think twice next time before shoplifting.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-caught-stealing-8-pairs-of-jeans-by-wearing-them-3926104</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/570/479/57047982DCFE9E29AD3BB44865B3FA35.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926104/3926104_01CE2EA755C249DF941ED280A7AEAAA4_191125_3926104_Woman_caught_stealing_8_pairs_of_jeans_by_wearin_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 09:58:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926179</guid>
      <title>Hero gym teacher wrecks rifle-wielding shooter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VELIKA PLANA / SERBIA <br/> Physical education teacher Slavoljub Stojadinovic has been hailed a hero after stopping a crazed gunman at his high school.<br/><br/>Serbia's Beta News Agency reports that Stojandinovic was coaching at the gym when a student told him that his help was urgently needed because of trouble in the philosophy class."<br/><br/>The daily Blic reports that the trouble turned out to be a gun toting maniac pumping bullets into the ceiling and trying to take hostages."<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the Ministry of Education later said the gunman had an automatic rifle."<br/><br/>Stojadinovic told Beta News that the gunman fired twice at his head and missed. <br/><br/>The PE teacher disarmed the alleged gunman and kept him subdued until law enforcement arrived.<br/><br/>[CUT 4] <br/>The BBC reports that the gunman was the only person injured in the incident.<br/><br/>Stojadinovic told Beta News that although he had been wearing bandages on his hand, the wound was not a result of his struggle with the gunman.<br/><br/>[VIDEO 1]<br/>According to the BBC Serbia, the police later recovered explosive material in the gunman's bag.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hero-gym-teacher-wrecks-rifle-wielding-shooter-3926179</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/715/615/71561550E38C887A8B1E12137AA20127.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926179/3926179_B076EE75C48E47B38CD651AFF3FAF4B5_191125_3926179_Hero_gym_teacher_wrecks_rifle_wielding_shooter_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926168</guid>
      <title>A third of Africa's tropical plants could go extinct: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AFRICA <br/> A new study from the journal Science Advances suggests that roughly 7,000, or 33 percent, of African plant species risk extinction.<br/><br/>The researchers focused on two International Union for Conservation of Nature Red List criteria, related to habitat decline and future population reduction, and developed an algorithm to assess more than 20,000 plant species' risk of going extinct.<br/><br/>Based on the assessment, four African regions <br/> Ethiopia, west Africa, central Tanzania and the southern Democratic Republic of the Congo <br/> in particular were found to be the most vulnerable, with more than 40 percent of local flora potentially being threatened with extinction.<br/><br/>Species at risk include local trees, herbs, lianas and shrubs.<br/><br/>The study also pointed to ecoregions concentrated in West Africa that include large numbers of threatened species, specifically the Inner Niger Delta savanna, Sahelian Acacia savanna, Guinean mangroves, western Guinean lowland forest and Guinean montane forests.<br/><br/>Researchers said these plant species are threatened by deforestation, climate change and population growth.<br/><br/>In addition, scientists found another third of flora species in the region that is likely rare and could potentially risk extinction in the near future.<br/><br/>Co-author of the study, Gilles Dauby, from the French National Research Institute for Sustainable Development told the Guardian that these species could likely be threatened if human pressure increases in tropical Africa.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-third-of-africa-s-tropical-plants-could-go-extinct-study-3926168</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2AC/AD7/2ACAD7F090354CD882A7DC99751D4DA1.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926168/3926168_0FBB952F4FCE402BB4A4A2D42E41DA4B_191125_3926168_A_third_of_Africa_s_tropical_plants_could_go_ext_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926650</guid>
      <title>Rabbits are being sucked into plane engines in Ireland</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBLIN <br/> Rabbits are being sucked up into plane engines as they taxi down runways at Ireland's Dublin Airport. <br/>The Irish Post reported 11 rascally rabbits have been "ingested" by engines in 2019, while 44 hares have been rescued and relocated away from the airport. <br/>Apparently, bunnies and high-performance plane engines don't pair well together and pose a greater risk than bird strikes. <br/>According to the Irish Post, chopped-up rabbit gunks up the propellers and engine bits a lot more than birds. <br/>The rabbit pieces attract more scavenging birds to the runways which then increases the likelihood of a bird strike. <br/>Airport workers have been using flare guns and netting to keep the bunnies from bouncing into harm's way. <br/>According to the report, the rabbits that are caught are released back into the wild by under the supervision of the National Parks and Wildlife Services.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/rabbits-are-being-sucked-into-plane-engines-in-ireland-3926650</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/106/648/106648B2883A36E7F4CDA57DFA3B285F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926650/3926650_5EACD891CAD949CEBE0059438A105ACB_191126_3926650_Rabbits_are_being_sucked_into_plane_engines_in_I_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927488</guid>
      <title>13 French soldiers perish in helicopter collision</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAMAKO, MALI <br/> A helicopter collision in Mali has taken the lives of 13 French soldiers in France's worst military loss in four decades.<br/><br/>On Monday evening, a French Tiger attack helicopter was reinforcing troops on the ground chasing after militants in Mali when the helicopter collided with a Cougar military transport helicopter around 7:40 p.m. local time.<br/><br/>The incident occurred near the Mali's border at Burkina Faso and Niger.<br/><br/>The two aircraft crashed near each other, killing all 13 French soldiers on board, including an officer and six commandos, according to the BBC. <br/><br/>An investigation has been launched to discover the cause of the collision, the heaviest single French military loss since a 1983 attack in Beirut killed 58 paratroopers.<br/><br/>In a tweet, French President Emmanuel Macron expressed "deep sadness" and called the soldiers "heroes."<br/><br/>French lawmakers observed a minute of silence for the fallen soldiers on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/13-french-soldiers-perish-in-helicopter-collision-3927488</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/543/DDC/543DDCC9245FAD1E275500FAE46FA59E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927488/3927488_6DAF40D8D73142EFB61746CF570232F7_191128_3927488_13_French_soldiers_perish_in_helicopter_collisio_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 02:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927828</guid>
      <title>Cows rocking VR goggles in Russia to help with milk production</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOSCOW <br/> A dairy farm near Mos-COW has finally come up with a use for VR headsets<br/>putting them on cows. <br/>According to Interesting Engineering, RusMoloko dairy farm in Russia looks a bit on the futuristic side with dairy cows running<br/>okay, maybe not running<br/>walking around with fitted VR goggles. <br/>The goggles have been specifically designed for dairy cows to see if technology can help trick the animals into relaxing in order to produce more milk.   <br/>So do the cows just watch MOOOO-vies all day? Sadly, no. <br/><br/>The headsets show a red-focused color scheme, which copies the shades of summer and is supposed to make the cow think it's standing in a field. <br/>According to Moscow's agriculture ministry, designers created a unique VR summer field based on several studies showing cows are better at perceiving shades of red than blue or green. <br/><br/>Russian officials claim the initial testing of the VR goggles have gone well. Apparently the cows won't shut up about them. <br/>A spokesperson for the agriculture ministry said, "during the first test, experts recorded a decrease in anxiety and an increase in the overall emotional mood of the herd." <br/>Now we just need to see if this leads to more milk, either way, quite a MOOO-ving story.  <br/><br/>In the meantime, expect Google and Facebook to think of ways to start showing these cows ultra annoying personalized ads.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cows-rocking-vr-goggles-in-russia-to-help-with-milk-production-3927828</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3BC/1F2/3BC1F23FA585FDD9295E4207DB5CCCF5.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927828/3927828_DDAA74ED7F1749CFAC58044FB2B4141C_191128_3927828_Cows_rocking_VR_goggles_in_Russia_to_help_with_m_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 12:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
