<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 18:11:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3992817</guid>
      <title>Locust plague threatening food security in East Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EAST AFRICA <br/> East African countries could be facing a food crisis as waves of locusts have hit crops in the region since the end of 2019, according to a report by the Globe and Mail. A third wave of the insects is expected to hatch and spread in June and July.<br/><br/>Just one locust can travel 150 kilometers in 24 hours and is capable of eating its own weight in crops each day.<br/><br/>A small swarm of locusts, which would be around 40 to 80 million, can cover about a square kilometer and eat the same amount of food consumed by 35,000 humans in a day.<br/><br/>On top of crops being impacted by the waves of locust plagues, Stephanie Hanson, senior vice-president of One Acre Fund, told the Center for Strategic and International Studies that farmers' incomes have also been affected due to restrictions put in place during the pandemic, which limit their capacity to sell food in local markets.<br/><br/>The pandemic has also made it difficult for farmers to get rid of the locusts. Hanson noted that pilots in Kenya who fly pesticide aircraft are required to land at local airports before the national curfew is lifted.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/locust-plague-threatening-food-security-in-east-africa-3992817</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/01/3992817/3992817_4A678713027B465B83F41DF184349FB5_200501_3992817_Locust_plague_threatening_food_security_in_East__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 02:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3993667</guid>
      <title>Madonna Claims she is Immune to the Coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LISBON, PORTUGAL <br/> The 61-year-old 'Like a Virgin' singer says she wants to breathe in 'COVID-19 air' because she has the antibodies to protect her from contracting the disease.<br/><br/>The singer said on Thursday in an Instagram video, 'I took a test the other day and I found out that I have the antibodies, so tomorrow, I'm just going to go on a long drive in a car, roll down the windows and I'm going to breathe in the Covid-19 air.'<br/><br/>She added, 'I hope the sun is shining. I have not been wanting to write lately but that does not mean I'm not thinking, thinking about what I want to write or want to say.'<br/><br/>The 80's icon known for decades of tabloid attention-seeking, appears to be claiming that following a test, it has proven that her immune system has already seen the coronavirus without symptoms. <br/><br/>In a previous navel-gazing video that is part of what she's dubbing her 'Quarantine Diaries', the pop star branded the coronavirus 'the great equalizer' whilst perching nude in a milky bathtub filled with rose petals. <br/><br/>She said that the pandemic doesn't care if you are rich or poor.<br/><br/>She said, 'That's the thing about COVID-19. It doesn't care about how rich you are, how famous you are, how funny you are, how smart you are, where you live, how old you are, what amazing stories you can tell.'<br/><br/>Madonna then attended a birthday party on Saturday, and in a video clip, at least eight people are seen gathered in close proximity despite social distancing rules.<br/><br/>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention or 'CDC' says it is still unclear whether antibodies will make you immune to the virus or prevent you from getting infected again.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/madonna-claims-she-is-immune-to-the-coronavirus-3993667</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/04/3993667/3993667_DDCD7DBD2AD8469CAE443DC284198537_200504_3993667_Madonna_Claims_she_is_Immune_to_the_Coronavirus_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 03:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3995005</guid>
      <title>'Asparagus Reader' Predicts Trump Will Be Re-Elected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BATH, U.K. <br/> Jemima Packington is a self-labeled 'asparamancer' who casts asparagus to the ground and makes predictions from the patterns they make.<br/><br/>Among her predictions are Donald Trump will win re-election in November <br/> but will also be re-impeached and 'booted out of office'; a smooth Brexit, more royal babies, and a royal death. <br/><br/>When 64-year-old Packington appeared on ITV's This Morning, a U.K breakfast show on May 1st, she said the formation of the asparagus for this month forecasts good news on the horizon. <br/><br/>She said, "I'm the world's only asparamancer, and I make predictions using asparagus.'<br/><br/>'You cast asparagus, you don't toss it, and the asparagus create patterns when they are cast on a flat surface.'<br/><br/>'And then from the patterns that are created, I am able to make predictions.'<br/><br/>The world's only asparamancer has correctly predicted Brexit and England's Cricket World Cup win in recent times.<br/><br/>She added, 'The May prediction shows a letter V and a letter E which shows we will have a double celebration during the upcoming bank holiday.'<br/><br/>'The little budlets that you see on the background indicate refreshments of the alcoholic variety, so we are all going to have a jolly good time.'<br/><br/>'Also, the spears coming forward indicate there is really great, good news on the way for us all this month.'<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-asparagus-reader-predicts-trump-will-be-re-elected-3995005</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/07/3995005/3995005_CEE2DD8CCD6F4D4394F23E872E2431BF_200507_3995005__Asparagus_Reader__Predicts_Trump_Will_Be_Re_Ele_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 06:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994953</guid>
      <title>How the UK's Coronavirus Contact-Tracing App Works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> The United Kingdom is testing a COVID-19 contact-tracing app on the Isle of Wight, the British government announced on May 4. <br/><br/>According to a press release from the Department of Health and Social Care, the app, which was developed by NHSX, the digital technology unit of the National Health Service, will keep a record of whom the user comes into contact with. <br/><br/>It will upload this information to a government database to help the NHS study the virus and develop strategies to ease Britain's coronavirus lockdown.<br/><br/>If the user becomes ill, the app will send a notification to everyone they have been in contact with to self-isolate.<br/><br/>The Isle of Wight is a small island in the English Channel with a population of around 140,000 people and a single NHS trust that covers all of the island.<br/><br/>Announcing the move on May 5, health secretary Matt Hancock said the isle's size is ideal to conduct testing under "scientifically controlled conditions," ITV reports.<br/><br/>The NHS COVID-19 app will be rolled out for the rest of the nation by the end of the month.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-uk-s-coronavirus-contact-tracing-app-works-3994953</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/07/3994953/3994953_35192A892E4C4DB8BE7E3F1221105DE0_200507_3994953_How_the_UK_s_Coronavirus_Contact_Tracing_App_Wor_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 03:52:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3995444</guid>
      <title>Thieves steal 97 cars during lockdown in New Zealand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUCKLAND <br/> A group of thieves cut through a fence of a Jucy Rentals parking lot, stealing 97 vehicles in total. <br/><br/>According to the BBC, a group of thieves cut through a fence of a Jucy Rentals parking lot in Auckland, New Zealand. They lifted the gate and began taking cars, stealing 97 vehicles in total. <br/><br/>Jucy Rentals chief executive Tim Alpe told the New Zealand Herald he believed the heist occurred on April 25. The New Zealand Herald reports the thieves stole unbranded Holden Captivas, Mazda 3s, and Suzuki Swifts along with some green and purple branded campervans.<br/><br/>Lockdown regulations have kept New Zealand's streets mostly empty. However, police were still patrolling when they began chasing a car that they believed looked suspicious.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that 85 of the 97 stolen cars have been found and returned to Jucy, and 29 individuals believed to be linked with the heist have been arrested.<br/><br/>A COVID-19 heist may sound smart, what with businesses left mostly unsupervised, but don't you think the police would CERTAINLY notice suspicious activity if you are literally the only human driving a vehicle you just stole on a completely empty street?<br/><br/>And you know what really sucks? Jucy is doing its part in helping the community during these uncertain times. The BBC reports that Jucy was allowing people in need to self-isolate in their campers, and on top of that, they've also pitched in by letting some of their cars be used for food delivery.<br/><br/>Alpe told The New Zealand Herald, 'We're a big operation, but it's just devastating right now, when tourism's just been decimated,' adding, 'To have to go through this as well is just horrific.']]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/thieves-steal-97-cars-during-lockdown-in-new-zealand-3995444</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/08/3995444/3995444_7277C003151145D5A37C7AEA1B2C47E9_200508_3995444_Thieves_steal_97_cars_during_lockdown_in_New_Zea_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 07:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3996354</guid>
      <title>Care Home Workers Caught Throwing 'Unacceptable' Party.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OLDHAM, ENGLAND  <br/> A care home unwillingly played host to a party on Friday where the staff were filmed dancing on chairs and doing wheelies on a wheelchair.<br/><br/>The incident took place after the staff had helped at a VE Day celebration for residents and when the video appeared on social media it triggered outrage among some members of the public.<br/><br/>In the video, one member of staff is seen whizzing across the floor on a frame used by frail residents.<br/><br/>The same member of staff is helped by another to do a wheelie in a wheelchair and about a dozen staff are dancing around the room and standing up on chairs.<br/><br/>The care home's manager, Diane Riley said that the staff involved will all be suspended, but their antics prompted some people to call for them to get the sack. <br/><br/>Riley said, 'There was a party held for the residents to celebrate VE Day which finished at about 8:30 pm.'<br/><br/>'After that staff and others who had come in to volunteer to help with the celebration went into the dining room area. It was closed and no residents were in there - most residents were in bed.'<br/><br/>'The staff were off duty and I think this gathering started at about 9:30 pm. I was not there myself, I had gone home.'<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/care-home-workers-caught-throwing-unacceptable-party--3996354</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/11/3996354/3996354_6CADBA1270594236A66C4F749AD586CE_200511_3996354_Care_Home_Workers_Caught_Throwing__Unacceptable__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 05:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3996680</guid>
      <title>MP Says 'Oh, F***ing Hell' During Commons Video Link</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> Conservative MP for South Derbyshire, Heather Wheeler was speaking during a debate on COVID-19, when she experienced technical difficulties with her video link to the House of Commons. <br/><br/>Wheeler was then caught setting a different tone, expressing her frustration with the issue, uttering 'oh f***ing hell.'<br/><br/>Deputy Speaker of the House, Nigel Evans, told Ms. Wheeler to 'please carry on', as her comments were blasted through the feed being broadcast to the Commons Chamber.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mp-says-oh-f%2A%2A%2Aing-hell-during-commons-video-link-3996680</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/12/3996680/3996680_35B97CA93E4148DD8DD8A73F3E20E583_200512_3996680_MP_Says__Oh__F___ing_Hell__During_Commons_Video__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 03:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3996798</guid>
      <title>Man Survives After Head Gets Impaled by Metal Rod</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JERUSALEM <br/> A man is lucky to be alive after falling from the second floor of a construction site onto a metal rod that pierced his head.<br/><br/>The Jerusalem Post reports Kamel Abdel Rahman, 46, was checking out how the construction of his apartment was going when turned the wrong way and fell to the first floor, headfirst onto a metal rod.<br/><br/>Rahman was found with his head impaled on the rod by family members. He told The Jerusalem Post, "I was conscious and I did not feel any pain at all. I do not know how to explain it."<br/><br/>Not only was Rahman not in pain, but imaging from his injury also showed that the rod somehow managed to avoid hitting two major arteries.<br/><br/>After a second surgery that lasted 10 hours trying to fix the mess that the face-impaling left inside Rahman's head, Rahman was released from the hospital a week ago, happy and healthy.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-survives-after-head-gets-impaled-by-metal-rod-3996798</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/12/3996798/3996798_510AE98937D0485889C479BE386A3A73_200512_3996798_Man_Survives_After_Head_Gets_Impaled_by_Metal_Ro_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2020 07:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3998809</guid>
      <title>Cop Can't Stop Smiling After 18 Pals Brake Lockdown Rules</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BIRMINGHAM, ENGLAND <br/> Lockdown rules in the U.K. right now are confusing at the best of times. Under the current lockdown restrictions, Boris Johnson has permitted unlimited outdoor exercise, however, social distancing rules must still be followed. <br/><br/>What this means is that if you exercise outside, you must do so with members of your household, however, some have gotten creative. <br/><br/>This is the bizarre moment a group of 18 mates pretended to exercise after they were caught breaking lockdown rules by coppers.<br/><br/>The footage, believed to have been recorded in Birmingham was posted by Mr. Craft and it shows the cop crack a smile as the crowd break into star jumps and jumping jacks as he approaches. <br/><br/>The video went viral with some thinking it was hilarious while others condemned the group for gathering during the lockdown.<br/><br/>One netizen said, 'My heart breaks for those working in the frontline. They sacrifice their lives to save ours and you cannot do the bare minimum of staying home.'<br/><br/>Another added, 'I just hope they're not in a hospital in a few weeks on a respirator thinking to themselves how did I catch COVID-19 and give it to my family?'<br/><br/>A West Midlands Police spokeswoman said, 'We are policing in unprecedented times. Our officers have been asked to implement new laws relating to Covid-19 and restrictions on people's movement.<br/><br/>'The legislation was passed very quickly, with little time for formal training, and given the circumstances officers have done a great job engaging with the public, educating them on the new laws, and enforcing the law where necessary.'<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cop-can-t-stop-smiling-after-18-pals-brake-lockdown-rules-3998809</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/18/3998809/3998809_848AA18A700746FD8DF16562B0A4C24A_200518_3998809_Cop_Can_t_Stop_Smiling_After_18_Pals_Brake_Lockd_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 04:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3998791</guid>
      <title>U.K. School Slammed For It's 'Crazy' Reopening Ideas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTHUMBERLAND, ENGLAND <br/> Holywell Village First School has been slammed for its 'ridiculous' set of ideas of social distancing after it revealed extreme measures in a now-deleted Facebook post.<br/><br/>The school, which will reopen on June 1 said pupils would have to remain inside a hoop marked with an 'X' when they go outside.<br/><br/>Other rules stated that toys, books, and soft furnishings will be removed from classrooms because there are not enough employees to clean them afterward.<br/><br/>Parents also raised concerns about strict rules regarding the use of toilets and children having to 'do their own first aid' if they scrape themselves. The post said children will be given specific time slots 'and will not be allowed to leave the classroom outside of their allocated toilet times.'<br/><br/>It continued with, 'If they fall over or have a toileting accident they will be encouraged to change themselves and clean their scrape or cut. We have sourced PPE which is for use only for staff protection should a child vomit, not for trips, falls, or scrapes. If it is not possible for the child to clean themselves in the event of an accident, the parent will be called to collect them so they can do that at home.'<br/><br/>The school said it did not wish to make such 'drastic' changes but that it was 'doing everything it can' to adhere to government guidance 'to keep staff and children as safe as possible.'<br/><br/>Before it was deleted the post was shared thousands of times. People raised concern that no hot meals would be provided, that parents would be banned from entering the building and that children as young as four will have to learn more independently due to teachers having to keep a two-meter distance.<br/><br/>Speaking to the Metro, one parent said that she felt the blame lay at the government for pushing schools to reopen too soon.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-k-school-slammed-for-it-s-crazy-reopening-ideas-3998791</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/18/3998791/3998791_DB6C78FD8E6D41CDA722E216C19BAD51_200518_3998791_U_K__School_Slammed_For_It_s__Crazy__Reopening_I_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 03:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4000480</guid>
      <title>'Covidiot' Pensioner Stuck on Beach on Mobility Scooter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LANCASHIRE, ENGLAND <br/> A pensioner has been branded a 'covidiot' after driving her mobility scooter onto a beach and then getting stuck, resulting in what has been labeled a 'major rescue operation.' <br/><br/>The so-far unnamed woman headed out at around 12.20 pm on Wednesday to soak up the sun at Blackpool's North Beach in Lancashire during one of the hottest days of the year, however, a passerby had to call the emergency services when she became stuck in the sand with her two dogs.  <br/><br/>Racing to the scene within 10 minutes, two response vehicles from the beach patrol attended to the matter and dragged her scooter back onto the promenade with their 4x4.<br/><br/>Witness Russ Holt who was at the incident said, 'I couldn't believe my eyes.' <br/><br/>'As she was driving onto the sand someone tried to stop her and told her she'd get stuck, but she continued anyway.'<br/><br/>He added, 'Her scooter just sunk into the sand and she couldn't get out.'<br/><br/>'Someone called the emergency services and luckily she was quickly pulled off the beach.'<br/><br/>'I know she didn't intend any harm but she clearly is a bit of a covidiot.'<br/><br/>'It seems stupid to put added pressure on what is a voluntary service - especially during lockdown.'<br/><br/>Lastly, he revealed that 'She was laughing and clearly thought it was funny. I'm just pleased she was okay.'<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-covidiot-pensioner-stuck-on-beach-on-mobility-scooter-4000480</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/22/4000480/4000480_7974B068E83F42BCA4F90A67D071C863_200522_4000480__Covidiot__Pensioner_Stuck_on_Beach_on_Mobility__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 06:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4003084</guid>
      <title>The New Hong Kong National Security Law, Explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Chinese authorities on May 28 bypassed Hong Kong's legislature to approve a national security law that threatens the foundations of the city's freedoms and autonomy. This new law, which will be implemented upon promulgation by Hong Kong's government, forbids acts of sedition, secession and subversion of China's central government.<br/><br/>This new Beijing-backed security plan raises concerns, particularly for pro-democracy activists, Chinese dissidents and journalists who could fall victim to greater extralegal persecution.<br/><br/>The new law could allow authorities to push back or silence pro-democracy lawmakers in the region. In fact, Reuters reports that on May 28, two pro-democracy lawmakers in Hong Kong were removed from the Legislative Council.<br/><br/>Their removal reportedly happened during a meeting where lawmakers were discussing the first amendment to the new law which would make it a criminal offense to insult the Chinese national anthem.<br/><br/>The announcement of this new law has alarmed Hong Kong's population and sparked a new wave of protests. One of the most obvious concerns is the loss of the 'one country, two systems' status.<br/>However, Chinese authorities deny this. According to a report by state-run press agency Xinhuanet published on May 23, "The draft decision of the legislation states clearly that China will 'unswervingly, fully and faithfully' implement the principles of 'one country, two systems,' 'the people of Hong Kong governing Hong Kong' and a high degree of autonomy."<br/><br/>The same article, which is written in a Q&A format, goes on to say that law-abiding Hong Kong residents should not fear this new law and that it targets solely "those who attempt to split the country, subvert state power, and organize and carry out terrorist activities, as well as foreign and external forces seeking to interfere in Hong Kong's affairs."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-new-hong-kong-national-security-law-explained-4003084</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/29/4003084/4003084_A6CFA3AEB71147B8A7C54EDFE9268524_200529_4003084_The_New_Hong_Kong_National_Security_Law__Explain_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2020 03:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
