<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 18:11:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3982002</guid>
      <title>Medical fetish store supplies NHS with disposable scrubs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWTON-LE-WILLOWS, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Medical fetish company, MedFet UK donated disposable scrubs after it was contacted by procurement representatives struggling to find the right equipment amid the coronavirus pandemic.<br/><br/>The fetish company tweeted, "today we donated our entire stock of disposable scrubs to an NHS hospital. It was just a few sets, because we don't carry large stocks, but they were desperate, so we sent them free of charge."<br/>"When we, a tiny company set up to serve a small section of the kink community, find ourselves being sought out as a last-resort supplier to our National Health Service in a time of crisis, something is seriously wrong. In fact, it's scandalous."<br/><br/>They added, "So when it's all over&#8230; and the doctors, nurses and other staff have done an amazing job (as they undoubtedly will despite the circumstances)&#8230; let's not forgotten, or forgive, the ones who sent the NHS into this battle with inadequate armor and one hand tied behind its back."<br/><br/>The company then took it upon themselves to share some public health advice with, "whether getting ready for some kinky fun or guarding against a virus outbreak, the single most effective method of infection control is scrupulous hand hygiene."<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/medical-fetish-store-supplies-nhs-with-disposable-scrubs-3982002</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/01/3982002/3982002_42397FACCD1440C883E48E6A60EA3CC6_200401_3982002_Medical_fetish_store_supplies_NHS_with_disposabl_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 06:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3982444</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus: Shoppers take 'creative' precautions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> Shoppers across the world are finding imaginative ways to utilize household wares and employ them into their arsenal against the Coronavirus. <br/><br/>While the classic black bin bag was used as a type of kevlar, other shoppers braving the supermarkets donned gas masks, and some even snorkeling goggles to make sure they stay out of harm's way.<br/><br/>But with the Coronavirus not going away anytime soon, some people have stepped it up a notch and just got in plastic bags. <br/><br/>There's no doubt self-isolation has assisted with their creative protective gear, but as long as people are protecting themselves, who're we to judge? <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-shoppers-take-creative-precautions-3982444</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/02/3982444/3982444_998CEB049B5745AA896F51D65F684DAA_200402_3982444_Coronavirus__Shoppers_take__creative__precaution_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 07:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3983658</guid>
      <title>Gloves And Face Masks: Do They Work?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Dr. Karan Rangarajan, a surgeon with the NHS took to Tik-Tok to explain how gloves and face masks don't necessarily protect you. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/gloves-and-face-masks-do-they-work--3983658</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/06/3983658/3983658_69642D069D5E47F7850FF9F50E0ACCAB_200406_3983658_Gloves_And_Face_Masks__Do_They_Work__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 04:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3983868</guid>
      <title>France opens terrorism probe after knife attack in southeast</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROMAN-SUR-IS&#201;RE, FRANCE <br/> French authorities have launched a terrorism probe after a knife attack killed two people and wounded five in the township of Romans-sur-Is&#232;re on April 4, Reuters reports. According to BBC News, the attack began at a tobacconist's shop in the town square.  <br/><br/>AFP reports suspect Abdallah Ahmed-Osman, a Sudanese refugee in his 30s, stabbed the owners and a customer. After that, he attacked several more people in two other stores including a butcher's shop.<br/><br/>Citing the butcher shop's owner, AFP reports Ahmed-Osman seized another knife and stabbed a customer, who died despite the shop owners' efforts to save the victim. The suspect then allegedly ran outside and attacked people queued up by a bakery.<br/><br/>According to AFP, the police arrested Ahmed-Osman as he knelt in prayer while speaking in Arabic. The police arrested a second Sudanese managed 28 at Ahmed-Osman's residence and later detained a third, younger Sudanese man who also lived in the household. Texts with religious connotations were recovered.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/france-opens-terrorism-probe-after-knife-attack-in-southeast-3983868</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/06/3983868/3983868_9DF189D6E0F641CDB6FBAE1408778CCC_200406_3983868_France_opens_terrorism_probe_after_knife_attack__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 12:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984078</guid>
      <title>CONSPIRACY: 5G Towers Set On Fire After Links To COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Conspiracy theories linking the rollout of 5G towers to the spread of the coronavirus has instigated the attack and arson on multiple cell towers last week in the U.K.<br/><br/>EE, o2, Three, and Vodafone, the top four major U.K mobile operators issued a joint statement asking for help to stop people burning 5G towers.<br/><br/>The online conspiracy theories that link the spread of the coronavirus with 5G have gathered momentum on both Facebook and Nextdoo, despite the fact, there's no scientific evidence to suggest a link.<br/><br/>In their joint statement the top four operators said, "Sadly, we have experienced cases of vandals setting fire to mobile masts, disrupting critical infrastructure and spreading false information suggesting a connection between 5G and the COVID-19 pandemic. There is no scientific evidence of any link between 5G and coronavirus. Fact. <br/><br/>They add, "Not only are these claims baseless, they are harmful for the people and businesses that rely on the continuity of our services. They have also led to the abuse of our engineers and, in some cases, prevented essential network maintenance taking place."<br/><br/>Speaking to The Verge, Vodafone confirmed that four cell towers were targeted in a 24-hour period on Friday the 3rd and EE said that one tower in Birmingham didn't even provide 5G services but was set on fire regardless. <br/><br/>Youtube has now said that it will suppress content promoting false 5G coronavirus conspiracy theories in a bid to stop the spread of disinformation. <br/><br/>The severity of the situation is as such, as the country battles with the ongoing pandemic, attacks on critical national infrastructure threaten the ability to communicate effectively therefore such unfounded theories should be ignored. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/conspiracy-5g-towers-set-on-fire-after-links-to-covid-19-3984078</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/07/3984078/3984078_9D490A21BAE442ADAF9151DBACA6DE04_200407_3984078_CONSPIRACY__5G_Towers_Set_On_Fire_After_Links_To_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 04:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984644</guid>
      <title>Boris Johnson spends second night in the intensive care unit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/>  British Prime Minister Boris Johnson is spending his second night in the intensive care unit at St. Thomas' Hospital in London after being admitted to the hospital on Sunday.<br/><br/>The BBC reports Johnson was presenting symptoms of the COVID-19 coronavirus on March 27. Later that day he tested positive for the disease.<br/><br/>By April 3, seven days after testing positive, the prime minister was still presenting symptoms while self-isolating.<br/><br/>On April 5, he was admitted to the hospital for further examinations after his coronavirus symptoms persisted.<br/><br/>Johnson was moved to the intensive care unit on April 6, where he has spent two nights under close medical supervision. Quoting foreign secretary and current deputy to the prime minister, Dominic Raab, the Guardian reports that Johnson has received oxygen but hasn't required invasive respiratory support.<br/><br/>Johnson is now one of the thousands of coronavirus cases reported in the United Kingdom, and potentially one of many more to come[f].<br/><br/>According to predictions from the Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation in Seattle, the UK is projected to have 66,000 COVID-19 deaths by August.[g]<br/><br/>However, Neil Ferguson of Imperial College London, an epidemiologist who advises the government, told the Guardian that the model, quote, "does not match the current UK situation," explaining that the health care model used for the predictions was wrong in the case of the UK.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/boris-johnson-spends-second-night-in-the-intensive-care-unit-3984644</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/08/3984644/3984644_3660EE90BEEF4B43951FCBAC76E0A565_200408_3984644_Boris_Johnson_spends_second_night_in_the_intensi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 11:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984820</guid>
      <title>Conor McGregor Slams 'Barbaric' China Over 'Inhumane Behaviour'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRELAND <br/> UFC's Conor McGregor has slammed China and cast an unforgiving light on the regime after RTE reported that some personal protective equipment or PPE delivered from China did not conform to safety standards. <br/><br/>The 31-year-old was understandably less than impressed and ripped into what he calls the "barbaric" Chinese government for, "ludicrously inhumane behavior."<br/><br/>Conor slammed China and labeled their actions "truly horrendous." He added, "not only are the prices being raised by these people on all our items. Masks, visors, gloves, ventilators, respirators, oxygen containers, screen monitors, you name it. All jacked in price.<br/><br/>"The batches coming in are now of no use! Ludicrously inhumane behavior."<br/><br/>The MMA star has urged his hundreds of millions of followers to stay at home and remain vigilant; he has also admirably donated huge sums of money to help fund the fight against the coronavirus. <br/><br/>On his Twitter account, McGregor made the following pledge: "Today I am purchasing myself, &#8364;1 million worth of personal protective equipment to be deployed to all the fighting hospitals in the Leinster region. Our most affected region, to this date."<br/><br/>The substandard medical equipment sent by Xi Jinping's government is inexcusable and such actions continue to cloud their reputation on a global scale after attempting to cover up the outbreak, to begin with. <br/><br/>McGregor has since demanded that the Irish government withdraw their gratitude for the medical equipment received from China, as let's be honest it really is inhumane. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/conor-mcgregor-slams-barbaric-china-over-inhumane-behaviour--3984820</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/09/3984820/3984820_6B401C3320FE44CB93841F50741E59E0_200409_3984820_Conor_McGregor_Slams__Barbaric__China_Over__Inhu_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 03:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985332</guid>
      <title>Pandemic Insurance: Wimbledon's Organizers Set For Huge Payout</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> The All England Lawn Tennis Association, which organizes the Wimbledon tennis tournament, is set to recover half of its losses from canceling the event thanks to the $2 million pandemic insurance it has taken out every year for the last 17 years.<br/><br/>This year's Wimbledon was scheduled to take place from June 29th to July 12th, but the outbreak of the coronavirus forced it to cancel <br/> the first time since World War Two.  <br/><br/>However, Action Network reported that the organizers are set to receive a whopping $141 million payout thanks to the coronavirus pandemic insurance policy it has paid a total of $34 million for.<br/><br/>The insurance policy was reported by The Times in March before the event was canceled.<br/><br/>But most businesses in sports aren't lucky enough or cautious enough to have taken out pandemic insurance, and Action Network claims that many are relying on a very specific clause within their contracts, something called, "force majeure," a French term that means "superior force." The clause is meant to cover unexpected acts of God or nature.<br/><br/>Interestingly, as the pandemic has taken over the world, so too have "force majeure" searches on Google; the last time the term was searched this much was 16 years ago, according to the search engine's trends data.<br/><br/>The All England Lawn Tennis Association has not yet confirmed the figures but did tell Action Network sports business reporter, Darren Rovell that the club has "always sought to buy the optimum insurance coverage available."<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/pandemic-insurance-wimbledon-s-organizers-set-for-huge-payout-3985332</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985332/3985332_D76686DC48EE4DA3847B0C034778DD54_200410_3985332_Pandemic_Insurance__Wimbledon_s_Organizers_Set_F_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 04:56:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985368</guid>
      <title>Uber Driver Died After Woman 'Coughed Repeatedly' In Cab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORWOOD, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> A 33-year-old Uber driver from Norwood, south London died from the coronavirus after expressing concern that a woman had "repeatedly coughed" in the back of his car. <br/><br/>Shortly after picking up the woman in his cab, Mr. Ayub Akhtar, a fit and healthy family man began to have breathing problems. <br/><br/>He expressed his concerns to his relatives and said he believed the passenger had the virus.<br/><br/>Mr. Akhtar, who lived with his mother and siblings, then began to show COVID-19 symptoms.<br/><br/>Speaking to The Mail Online, his brother, Yasser said: "He told us about the lady coughing behind him in his Prius a few days before and that he was worried about it."<br/><br/>He added, "I could hear his painful coughing from his bedroom at night and that he was struggling for breath."<br/><br/>Mr. Akthar was at first admitted to the Mayday Hospital in Croydon and transferred to St. George's Hospital, Tooting when he could no longer breathe properly. <br/><br/>He sent a heartbreaking text to his family from his hospital bed telling them to, "Pray for me" <br/> that text would be his last. <br/><br/>Mr. Akhtar later died alone in intensive care last Friday after he could no longer breathe. <br/><br/>His family report that he had no major illnesses prior to succumbing to the virus. <br/><br/>Remember, stay home, saves lives.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/uber-driver-died-after-woman-coughed-repeatedly-in-cab-3985368</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985368/3985368_221B25EA3E83415B86EAE7E139DEC03B_200410_3985368_Uber_Driver_Died_After_Woman__Coughed_Repeatedly_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 06:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985359</guid>
      <title>Ronaldinho Released And Now Under House Arrest In Paraguay</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ASUNCION, PARAGUAY <br/> Ronaldinho has finally been released from a maximum-security prison and placed under house arrest in Paraguay.<br/><br/>The 40-year-old Brazilain icon and 2005 Ballon d'Or winner was arrested on the 6th of March after accusations of using a fake passport when trying to enter Paraguay along with his brother.<br/><br/>The BBC reported that the duo had previously been denied bail, but since posted $800,000 each and now must stay in a four-star hotel in Asuncion, the capital of Paraguay.<br/><br/>In allowing the pair to leave prison, the judge claimed that the size of the bail paid was "significant" and would "guarantee they will not flee."<br/><br/>Ronaldinho, who was branded "stupid" by his lawyer, along with his brother both continue to deny any wrongdoing, simply stating that they didn't know the documents were fake. <br/><br/>The same lawyer called their imprisonment, "arbitrary, abusive and illegal." <br/><br/>The pair are now awaiting trial. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ronaldinho-released-and-now-under-house-arrest-in-paraguay-3985359</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985359/3985359_710646BFD34547B28AC697CC65A16DC3_200410_3985359_Ronaldinho_Released_And_Now_Under_House_Arrest_I_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 06:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986167</guid>
      <title>World Health Organization: Risking Your Life for China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> Right now we're witnessing a true crime against humanity, Xi Jinping's China and the World Health Organization are attempting something outrageous; they're trying to change the narrative of how both bodies responded to the coronavirus and they're both scheming to avoid the responsibility of now 114,175 deaths, but we won't let them and you can help by just doing one thing: don't be tricked. <br/><br/>We are currently at the mercy of the deadly coronavirus pandemic that has put millions of lives at stake, and yet there is grave cause for concern over the independence or political neutrality of the World Health Organization or WHO. <br/><br/>Specifically, it's leadership who have regularly demonstrated their bootlicking to the Chinese Communist Party; the latest example, of course, is a now-viral video interview, in which a WHO senior adviser abruptly ends the interview when asked about Taiwan, questions Beijing despises. <br/><br/>Alright, dodging questions about Taiwan to please Beijing isn't a be-all or end-all, but it is indicative of a systemic problem within WHO leadership: a subservience to Beijing that comes at the expense of its stated commitment to 'health care for all'.<br/><br/>But what if it's not dodging questions about Taiwan and instead dodging or ignoring critical advice from Taiwan that could have saved thousands of lives? <br/><br/>As far back as December last year, the WHO refused to act on or publicize Taiwan's warning that the new respiratory infection emerging in China's Wuhan could in fact pass from human to human. <br/><br/>But, in mid-January, despite accumulating evidence of patients contracting what we now know as COVID-19 from other people, the WHO repeated China's lie that there was no evidence of human-to-human transmission. <br/><br/>In a move that contradicts its slogan of "health care for all" the WHO, at Beijing's command, then blocked Taiwan from participating in critical meetings to coordinate responses to the coronavirus and even reportedly provided wrong information about the virus's spread in Taiwan, essentially condemning the Taiwanese people to death for the lack of first-hand information. Politics over people. <br/><br/>But, Taiwan which at its closest sits a mere 81-miles from the origin of the outbreak, China has a mere 388 cases. <br/><br/>So, it's safe to say that if the WHO had listened to Taiwan instead of groveling to China for some more pocket money and doing the regime's bidding, maybe many thousands of lives would have been saved. <br/><br/>Taiwan still wants to help, and the world wants to listen, but the WHO still blocks the country from its organization, the organization that we cannot allow to be used as a tool by the Chinese government, the largest financial contributor which gives five times as much money as obligated and now we know why.<br/><br/>People before politics and when this is all over, China and its little sidekick must be held accountable.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/world-health-organization-risking-your-life-for-china-3986167</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/13/3986167/3986167_6D367190FD224C548D587DDF80CC7B81_200413_3986167_World_Health_Organization__Risking_Your_Life_for_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 05:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986277</guid>
      <title>This is how the coronavirus came to Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MUNICH <br/> Here's how a saltshaker helped researchers trace back the first evidence of human to human transmission of COVID-19 on German soil.<br/><br/>According to a report from Euractiv in collaboration with Reuters, Germany's Patient Zero was a Chinese woman working at the Shanghai branch of Webasto Group, a German car parts supplier. The woman's parents visited her from Wuhan before she left for Germany to attend meetings at the company's headquarters.<br/><br/>In order to trace back the origin of the spread, doctors looked into the records of staff meetings and interviewed employees.<br/><br/>Through the information they gathered, they found that the first German person infected by the Chinese woman was sitting next to her during a meeting on January 20.<br/><br/>Evidence showed that the fourth person to be infected, or case #4, had been in regular contact with the Chinese woman. On January 22, case #4 sat back to back with a co-worker at the office canteen, where they shared a salt shaker. Researchers believe this is when the coworker became the fifth person to be infected.<br/><br/>If you're asking yourself, 'How could doctors possibly have recorded the exact moment in which a salt shaker became suspect number one in the spread of the coronavirus?' Don't worry, the doctors themselves are kerfuffled.<br/><br/>Clemens Wendtner, the doctor who treated patients that got infected through this cluster, told Reuters, 'It was a stroke of luck.' Apparently, 'all it took' was gathering information from staff and boom, case closed.<br/><br/>Thankfully, the researchers' quick actions resulted in healthy employees. In a press release published on March 4, Webasto stated that all previously infected employees had been released from the hospitals and some had already gone back to work.<br/><br/>According to the latest data from the Robert Koch Institute, the German federal agency in charge of disease control and prevention, there are currently 120,479 COVID-19 cases and 2,673 deaths due to COVID-19 in Germany. Around 60,300 people have recovered from the viral disease.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/this-is-how-the-coronavirus-came-to-germany-3986277</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/13/3986277/3986277_70610EC671294D108B2F7C39156C90B5_200413_3986277_This_is_how_the_coronavirus_came_to_Germany_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 10:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986491</guid>
      <title>64-Year-Old Falls out of Jet After Pressing Eject!</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAINT-DIZIER, FRANCE <br/> A pensioner who was given a surprise flight in an $80 million fighter jet as a retirement present was flung out at 2,500 ft after accidentally pressing the ejector button.<br/><br/>The astonishing <br/> what reads like a dark comedy <br/> news story comes to us from France at an airbase in Saint-Dizier, eastern France back on March 20th, 2019.  <br/><br/>A new report of investigations has told how the 64-year-old French defense manufacturer had been surprised by employees at his firm, who had organized a joyride in a Dassault Rafale B jet for him as a treat after obtaining special ministerial approval.<br/><br/>But his friends didn't know him as well as they thought, as the unnamed man not only had no experience flying in a fighter jet, he also had no desire to rip through the sound barrier. <br/><br/>But, not wanting to be rude, he reluctantly stepped up and entered the cockpit; investigators say that his smartwatch recorded his heart rate racing at 136-142 times a minute, they also noted that "his heart was in full tachycardia" a condition that makes your heart beat more than 100 times per minute.<br/><br/>As quickly as his heart was racing, they were taking off, piloted by a French veteran military pilot with more than 2,000 hours of flight time experience.<br/><br/>As the pilot leveled off and the plane was subjected to a negative gravitational load factor, which can create the feeling of being upside down, the passenger reached for something to hold onto, but inadvertently grabbed the ejector handle.<br/><br/>And yes, he was flung from the cockpit. <br/><br/>But, in his panic on entering the cockpit, the man hadn't actually secured his helmet, which meant that it also flew off into infinity and beyond. <br/><br/>As the pensioner hurtled towards the ground from 2,500 ft, his parachute deployed and he landed in a field, sustaining minor injuries that required him to be taken to a hospital.<br/><br/>The report calls on the French Airforce and the Defence Ministry to review its procedures for allowing civilians on military flights.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/64-year-old-falls-out-of-jet-after-pressing-eject--3986491</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/14/3986491/3986491_D5A3E92B707245238B324C1CBAE64C80_200414_3986491_64_Year_Old_Falls_out_of_Jet_After_Pressing_Ejec_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 05:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987252</guid>
      <title>VIRAL: BBC Weatherman Rocks News With His Drum Rendition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> BBC's, Owain Wyn Evans, a self-labeled "unapologetically flamboyant" weatherman has gone viral for his drum kit rendition of the BBC News outro. <br/><br/>Trending on Twitter with over three million views, the 36-year-old weather presenter who fronts North West Tonight in the U.K, rocked out on the skins and cymbals while still donning his camera-ready three-piece suit and Elton-John-esque brooch.<br/><br/>The video, although brief, has given people a much-needed smile amid the coronavirus, receiving almost 122,000 'likes' and 28,000 retweets so far to date; in his Twitter caption, he joked, "When they said try working from home I didn't realize they'd expect me to do the music too."<br/><br/>Not surprisingly, fans have called for an encore, demanding that his beats replace the shows normal outro. <br/><br/>One person on Twitter even went so far as to name him a "national treasure."<br/><br/>BBC North West also took to the social media site to lay claim to their star, boosting about their forecaster's talents and challenged other staff to step up to the drums.  <br/><br/>Saying, "North West weather forecasters are so much more talented than the Northern Irish ones&#8230; unless you can prove otherwise!"<br/><br/>Barra Best, a weather presenter on BBC Northern Ireland, replied saying, "I concede defeat." <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/viral-bbc-weatherman-rocks-news-with-his-drum-rendition-3987252</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/16/3987252/3987252_62E2031720424DBF99DD935E97B7A1E1_200416_3987252_VIRAL__BBC_Weatherman_Rocks_News_With_His_Drum_R_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 04:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987662</guid>
      <title>Desperate German Zoo Threatens to Feed Animals to Each Other</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SCHLESWIG-HOLSTEIN, GERMANY <br/> A zoo in Germany has warned that it may start feeding animals to each other in a desperate bid to stay open.<br/><br/>Located in the northern state of Schleswig-Holstein, Neumunster zoo, like all the others in Germany, has been shut down since March 15th in an attempt to impede the spread of the coronavirus. <br/><br/>And to stay financially afloat amid the lockdown, the Zoo's director, Verena Kaspari has said: "Yes, we do have a list of animals that we would slaughter first."<br/><br/>Citing German outlet, Deutsche Welle, she added that non-endangered deer and goats would be first and would be fed to the zoo's eagles, lynx, and polar bear, Vitus, who is over 11 ft tall.<br/><br/>Kapari said, "It's a worst-case scenario, we don't see it getting that way yet, but we have to think of it early enough." <br/><br/>Her fears understandably stem from the potential scenario where the delivery of fish and meat is no longer available because of a lack of funds. <br/><br/>Fortunately, other animal parks have offered to send fish and meat to feed her zoo's predators should it come to it, but Kaspari did note that the slaughter of some animals to feed others is standard practice at zoos, saying, "We have carnivorous animals, so that's nothing new."<br/><br/>If the zoo is allowed to be reopened at the end of April, Kaspari estimates it will have lost $191,000 in ticket sales and donations. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/desperate-german-zoo-threatens-to-feed-animals-to-each-other-3987662</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/17/3987662/3987662_A03330E9774749C3AA06970B4DDC514E_200417_3987662_Desperate_German_Zoo_Threatens_to_Feed_Animals_t_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 04:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987793</guid>
      <title>UK Spent $20 Million on Dud Chinese Coronavirus Test Kits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> The U.K government is scrambling for a refund after gambling on $20 million worth of Chinese-made coronavirus testing kits that did not work.<br/><br/>According to the New York Times, the two Chinese companies were offering a risky proposition: two million home test kits said to detect coronavirus antibodies for at least $20 million, take it or leave it. <br/><br/>The asking price was high, the technology was unproven and the money had to be paid upfront; furthermore, the buyer would be required to pick up the crate loads of test kits from a facility in China.<br/><br/>Despite the risk, Downing Street, desperate to get a handle on the forever climbing case numbers in the U.K, gambled and handed over the cash to both 'AllTest Biotech' and 'Wondfo Biotech', the two Chinese companies in question; both of which claim that their products met the health, safety and environmental standards set by the European Union.  <br/><br/>Whilst public health officials reviewed the specifications on paper, diplomats were dispatched in China to ensure the companies existed and to examine their products first-hand.<br/><br/>The gamble backfired as the tests, said to detect antibodies for coronavirus, did not work, according to a senior civil servant.<br/><br/>Finding antibody tests that work is seen as a critical stage in the battle against coronavirus.<br/><br/>After officials complained about the dud tests, both Chinese companies instead blamed British officials and politicians for misunderstanding or exaggerating the utility of the tests. <br/><br/>Wondfo told Global Times that its product was intended only as a supplement for patients who had already tested positive for the virus. <br/><br/>The U.K's amateur hour exposes how vulnerable and how desperate they are to win the war on the coronavirus, as all nations are.  <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/uk-spent-20-million-on-dud-chinese-coronavirus-test-kits-3987793</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/17/3987793/3987793_D0A964B440D0420093E241C4F1BB0286_200417_3987793_UK_Spent__20_Million_on_Dud_Chinese_Coronavirus__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 08:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988740</guid>
      <title>At least 17 dead in worst recent mass shooting in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HALIFAX, NOVA SCOTIA <br/> A man disguised as a police officer killed at least 17 people across Nova Scotia this weekend in one of the deadliest mass shootings in Canadian history, Canada's National Post reports.<br/><br/>Canadian police said the suspect set fires and shot at people while dressed as a Royal Canadian Mounted Police officer and driving what looked like a Royal Canadian Mounted Police cruiser.<br/><br/>The 12-hour rampage ended Sunday morning in a standoff at a gas station outside Halifax when the suspect was caught by the Royal Canadian Mounted Police. Police confirmed in a press conference Sunday evening that he was dead.<br/><br/>Among those people killed was Constable Heidi Stevenson, a 23-year veteran of the Nova Scotia RCMP.<br/><br/>The suspect has been identified as 51-year-old Gabriel Wortman. According to reports, he was a denturist who collected old police cruisers and other police memorabilia.<br/><br/>The spree was the worst mass shooting in Canada in 30 years, surpassing the death toll of the 1989 Ecole Polytechnique massacre in Montreal.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/at-least-17-dead-in-worst-recent-mass-shooting-in-canada-3988740</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/20/3988740/3988740_F7681BB5773F4F6E990A03E3EF497234_200420_3988740_At_least_17_dead_in_worst_recent_mass_shooting_i_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 07:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988692</guid>
      <title>WWII Veteran Raises Over $32,000,000 for the NHS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEDFORDSHIRE, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Captain Tom Moore, a 99-year-old veteran has raised more than 32 million dollars for the country's National Health Service by doing 100 laps of his garden. <br/><br/>Captain Tom had initially set out to raise just $1,000 before his 100th birthday on April 30th, but he quickly smashed the target once his mission came to public attention.<br/><br/>1,254,102 people have so far made donations to his JustGiving page, which is still open but has previously crashed simply due to the sheer number of donations. <br/><br/>With the aid of a walking frame, he completed the 100 laps of the 25-meter loop earlier than planned, on April 16th. Since then, thousands have backed petitions for the World War Two veteran to be knighted by the Queen, while children across the country have begun making him birthday cards in preparation for his big day.<br/><br/>Ian Lush, the chairman of NHS Charities Together said the organizations had already received over $43,000 each, with the money going towards the wellbeing of staff and helping patients connect with their families.<br/><br/>Speaking to BBC Radio 2 Captain Tom said the sum of money was "absolutely enormous" and "very difficult to imagine"<br/><br/>Captain Tom, born in Keighley, West Yorkshire, was inspired to raise the money after receiving treatment for skin cancer and a broken hip two years ago. He told the Sunday Mirror: "My message to the nation right now is, tomorrow will be a good day. We will get through this and come out of it stronger, more united and ready to face any challenge together."<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wwii-veteran-raises-over-32-000-000-for-the-nhs-3988692</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/20/3988692/3988692_B78E3186322340F8BF1525CB77C42762_200420_3988692_WWII_Veteran_Raises_Over__32_000_000_for_the_NHS_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 06:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989054</guid>
      <title>Iranian Instagram star is battling COVID-19 while serving time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN <br/> Fatemeh Khishvand, known as Sahar Tabar on Instagram, went viral a few years ago for her extremely photoshopped images. Now it appears she is battling coronavirus in prison. <br/><br/>Khishvand made headlines a few years ago after her overly photoshopped photos that made her look like a zombie version of Angelina Jolie went viral.<br/><br/>In October of last year she was arrested by Iranian authorities after she went viral and accused of a list of "offenses," which included blasphemy, insulting the Islamic veil, and encouraging youth to commit corruption.<br/><br/>Her lawyer Payam Derafshan is now asking for clemency as it appears that  Khishvand may have contracted coronavirus while detained.<br/><br/>Derafshan wrote an open letter to Ebrahim Reisei, the head of Iran's judiciary, explaining that the young woman had been placed in quarantine after displaying symptoms of the virus.<br/><br/>But if you ask Iranian authorities, all this is pure make-believe. The head of Shahr-e Rey women's prison told Iran's ISNA news agency that, "The news released by the lawyer of Fatemeh Khishvand is not true and I deny it."<br/><br/>But Khishvand's lawyer is not backing down. Derafshan is now after judge Mohammad Moghiseh of Branch 28 of the Revolutionary Court, who has repeatedly ignored pleas from the lawyer to grant Khishvand bail. <br/><br/>Unsurprisingly, after the coronavirus struck Iran judge Moghiseh has been MIA in the courthouse.<br/><br/>Important side note: According to the Center for Human Rights in Iran, Moghiseh has previously sentenced dissidents, minorities and even activists to long prison sentences.<br/><br/>Khishvand's situation seems to be dire. Derafshan told the Center for Human Rights in Iran that Khishvand is currently on a ventilator at Sina Hospital in Tehran.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/iranian-instagram-star-is-battling-covid-19-while-serving-time-3989054</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/21/3989054/3989054_759780E984C148FE885BF1ED816808CA_200421_3989054_Iranian_Instagram_star_is_battling_COVID_19_whil_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 05:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989018</guid>
      <title>Kenya Governor Puts Hennessy in Coronavirus Care Packages</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NAIROBI, KENYA <br/> Nairobi politician, Mike Sonko has come under fire for his so-called COVID-19 'care package' which, yes, includes the typical food staples one would expect but also alcohol. <br/><br/>Sonko confirmed in a media briefing last Tuesday that his care packages include a few small bottles of the cognac, Hennessy.<br/><br/>Though it was his justification for its inclusion that has left people mocking, as he explained to the crowd, it's "throat sanitizer."<br/><br/>"I think from the research conducted by the World Health Organization and various organizations, it has been believed that alcohol plays a major role in killing the coronavirus."<br/><br/>The WHO has repeatedly stated that alcohol can weaken the health of an individual and make them more vulnerable to viruses including coronavirus.<br/><br/>The global CEO of Amref Health Africa shared a video of Mr. Sonko's misinformation and urged people to "dump this the way you would dump your used COVID-19 mask".<br/><br/>Meanwhile, Hennessy has refuted through local media the claims by the Nairobi governor that its drink in particular or alcohol, in general, can ward off coronavirus contagion.<br/><br/>In a statement to Nairobi News, the company said: "Hennessy would like to stress that the consumption of our brand or any other alcoholic beverage does not protect against the virus."<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/kenya-governor-puts-hennessy-in-coronavirus-care-packages-3989018</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/21/3989018/3989018_E9EF91B1F6E44574945BAA9670AE5CD2_200421_3989018_Kenya_Governor_Puts_Hennessy_in_Coronavirus_Care_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 04:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989379</guid>
      <title>British Police Show What it's Like to Police During the Lockdown</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM <br/> West Midlands Police show us what's like to patrol during the lockdown, as the praise the 95% of people who do what must be done but bring attention to those who knowingly put themselves and others at risk. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/british-police-show-what-it-s-like-to-police-during-the-lockdown-3989379</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/22/3989379/3989379_8167CC1BB92F441BAB9696A1A07E02A3_200422_3989379_British_Police_Show_What_it_s_Like_to_Police_Dur_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 03:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989498</guid>
      <title>Death toll from Canada mass shooting rises to 23: police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HALIFAX, NOVA SCOTIA <br/> The Royal Canadian Mounted Police say the death toll from the Nova Scotia mass shooting that occurred from Saturday to Sunday has risen to 19.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Citing the Royal Canadian Mounted Police, the National Post reports that 51-year-old suspect Gabriel Wortman had masqueraded as a police constable and utilized various firearms in the killing spree.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The police did not disclose the type of weapons used.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The 12-hour rampage started in the rural town of Portapique on Saturday evening. Wortman initially drove a detailed replica of a mounted police cruiser.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The suspect committed murders at no fewer than 16 locations before being cornered and shot dead by police at a gas station near Halifax. By that time, he had obtained another silver SUV via unknown means.<br/><br/><br/><br/>As multiple buildings and cars were set ablaze, possibly by Wortman, the RMCP say they are still recovering and counting the dead.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The police say the crimes "appear to be, at least in part, very random in nature," but added that Wortman did have a connection with some victims.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Constable Heidi Stevenson, a 23-year veteran of the Nova Scotia RCMP; elementary school teacher Lisa McCully; and the suspect Wortman were among the 19 slain, a number the police say will almost certainly increase. <br/><br/><br/><br/>RCMP Constable Chad Morrison was shot in a confrontation with the suspect but he is currently recovering at home.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/death-toll-from-canada-mass-shooting-rises-to-23-police-3989498</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url=""/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 08:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989464</guid>
      <title>Heroes Climb Building to Save Old Man Hanging From Balcony</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRID, SPAIN <br/> A video from Spain has surfaced showing a group of hero residents rescuing a pensioner who was dangling from a second-floor balcony. <br/><br/>The neighbors were filmed banding together to create a human chain after a 70-year-old man was hanging from his flat in San Jose, on the outskirts of Madrid.<br/><br/>Citing local media, the man named Juan Pena was eventually lowered safely to the mattress, however, it's currently unclear why he was hanging from the balcony; <br/>nonetheless, the local media report that he was not injured.<br/><br/>The video posted to Twitter on the 19th of April has so-far received nearly 500,000 views and has been met with a series of applause.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/heroes-climb-building-to-save-old-man-hanging-from-balcony-3989464</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/22/3989464/3989464_0F267A3782684066B62E291EDA0D02F1_200422_3989464_Heroes_Climb_Building_to_Save_Old_Man_Hanging_Fr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 07:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989791</guid>
      <title>Nigerian Man Fires Machine Gun at People From Balcony</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENT, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> A Nigerian man has been arrested on suspicion of firearms offenses after reports he opened fire from a penthouse balcony in Chatham, Kent.<br/><br/>The gunman, identified as 33-year-old Michael Alunomoh, streamed himself on Instagram on the 22nd of April firing shots from his balcony at panicked shoppers while rapping to Tupac.<br/><br/>People at a nearby shopping center raced for cover fearful that the incident could be a terrorist attack.<br/><br/>Kent Police were called at 8:35 am after around 50 shots were fired where he then posted a clip of himself wielding guns and demanding onlookers to call the police; armed officers and a police helicopter raced to the scene.<br/><br/>One of his neighbors, 64-year-old Christine Tugman, said that he was shouting at officers, saying: "Shoot me, shoot me, kill me, kill me." <br/><br/>Mr. Alunomoh who calls himself 'flexingmike' on his social media pages, is listed as the chief executive of Truth or Dare Records, according to company records. The businessman is something of an online 'influencer' as he posts photos of exotic holidays and designer clothes to his 57,000 social media followers <br/><br/>Earlier in the week, he promoted his new EP on Instagram which featured five songs; his social media then fell silent until yesterday morning's rampage.<br/><br/>A Kent Police spokesman said that the man was arrested on suspicion of firearms offenses and that, "'Patrols remain at the scene where officers have located four suspected imitation firearms as part of their inquiries."<br/><br/>The weapons that were found in the flat are believed to be imitation firearms and not capable of firing live ammunition.<br/><br/>No injuries have been reported. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nigerian-man-fires-machine-gun-at-people-from-balcony-3989791</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/23/3989791/3989791_8B3E73F5741B4D52A4D5EB3CEF9BB02A_200423_3989791_Nigerian_Man_Fires_Machine_Gun_at_People_From_Ba_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 04:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991559</guid>
      <title>Dozens of 'Covidiots' Protested on Anzac Day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GIPPSLAND, VICTORIA, AUSTRALIA <br/> Dozens of protestors in Australia hijacked Anzac Day to demonstrate against coronavirus restrictions.<br/><br/>On Saturday 25th, around 75 demonstrators, including ex-servicemen and women, stood shoulder to shoulder in a park at Trafalgar Train Station in West Gippsland, Victoria calling for an end to the lockdown. <br/><br/>They claimed the government had gone "too far" in imposing rules on what the locals can do amid the pandemic, even going so far as to compare the government to Nazi Germany.<br/><br/>Some placards read 'what did our Anzacs die for?', 'locking up healthy people is tyranny' and 'give our jobs back.'<br/><br/>Many of the demonstrators served or were related to people who served for their country and frustrations grew from the inability to be able to honor them due to social distancing. <br/><br/>Ex-serviceman, Topher Field, the individual responsible for leading the event said the government's restrictions had taken freedom away from Australians.<br/><br/>He said in a live stream video of the protest, "Who would have thought in our own free country we would have to risk fines to gather and honor Anzac Day."<br/><br/>Despite four police cars present, the protest continued for more than an hour. A Victoria Police spokesperson told Australian outlet, 7NEWS that officers attended a demonstration but no infringements were issued.<br/><br/>She added, "However, investigations continue and police will be issuing fines to the organizers."<br/><br/>Since the video went viral, the protestors have been slammed by many as disrespectful.<br/><br/>One woman wrote, "Actually shaking with rage over this right now. While people all over the country were holding peaceful driveway vigils this morning, these absolute stains decided that the ANZACs apparently fought for their right to spread disease to small regional towns."<br/><br/>Lastly, Victoria has imposed the harshest coronavirus restrictions in Australia. On the spot fines of $1,652 have been given to anyone breaking coronavirus regulations which require people to stay inside unless leaving for work and education, exercise, food shopping, care reasons, and other extenuating circumstances.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dozens-of-covidiots-protested-on-anzac-day-3991559</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/28/3991559/3991559_896462DF455F48C5AE87CD143F0CA840_200428_3991559_Dozens_of__Covidiots__Protested_on_Anzac_Day_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>World</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 03:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
