<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 18:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3957794</guid>
      <title>Super-long smuggling tunnel found at U.S.-Mexico border</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO <br/> Authorities have found what they are calling the "longest" smuggling tunnel ever discovered on the U.S.-Mexico border.<br/><br/>In a statement on January 29, the U.S. Customs and Border Protection agency announced that it had uncovered the cross-border tunnel along the U.S. border with Mexico.<br/><br/>The underground tunnel has a total length of 4,309 feet, making it the longest smuggling on the southwestern border found to date.<br/><br/>Officials said that the tunnel was concealed by a small industrial building in Tijuana, Mexico, and stretched over three-quarters of a mile to San Diego, California.<br/><br/>Images shared by the U.S. border officials show that the tunnel is narrow, only two feet wide and roughly five and a half feet high. Officials said they discovered hundreds of sandbags at the end of the tunnel blocking what is suspected to be an old exit to the city of San Diego.<br/><br/>U.S. authorities also uncovered an incomplete offshoot from the main cross-border tunnel leading into the U.S.<br/><br/>The tunnel housed an extensive transport system including an elevator at the entrance and a rail system. The cross-border tunnel was also found to contain an air ventilation system, a drainage system and high voltage electrical cables.<br/><br/>U.S. officials have yet to make any arrests regarding the discovery of the tunnel.<br/><br/>Previously, authorities had found a 2,966-foot-long tunnel in San Diego in 2014.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/super-long-smuggling-tunnel-found-at-u-s-mexico-border-3957794</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957794/3957794_30EA987BEF9E46D4A9C7AE692535BD07_200203_3957794_Super_long_smuggling_tunnel_found_at_U_S__Mexico_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 06:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958505</guid>
      <title>Trump hat tips wrong state after Kansas City Chiefs win Super Bowl</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> President Donald Trump apparently watched the Super Bowl on Sunday night with the rest of the United States to see the Kansas City Chiefs come from behind to win an exciting Super Bowl against the San Francisco 49ers. <br/>After the game was over, Trump hopped on Twitter to congratulate the Chiefs and the great state of Kansas. <br/><br/>In a since deleted tweet, the commander in geography wrote, "Congratulations to the Kansas City Chiefs on a great game and a fantastic comeback, under immense pressure. You represented the Great State of Kansas, and in fact, the entire USA, so very well. Our Country is PROUD OF YOU!"<br/>Only one problem...the Kansas City Chiefs are located in Missouri. <br/>Cue the memes. Social media immediately pounced. Former Missouri Sen. Claire McCaskill tweeted out, "It's Missouri you stone cold idiot."<br/>Trump's erroneous tweet was then put in timeout, while a new one was put up congratulating the correct state. <br/>Well<br/>good thing Trump didn't take Air Force One to congratulate the Chiefs. Otherwise he'd still be flying over Kansas somewhere.<br/>Obviously what Trump should have done is just made a new map. It's not like most Americans would actually miss Kansas<br/>sorry Missouri<br/>same difference.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-hat-tips-wrong-state-after-kansas-city-chiefs-win-super-bowl-3958505</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958505/3958505_C2877CE788C049EBB174EA1B78FF6C86_200204_3958505_Trump_hat_tips_wrong_state_after_Kansas_City_Chi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958687</guid>
      <title>Some people don't have an internal monologue</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. <br/> Do you hear your own thoughts? Then chances are you have what's called an 'internal monologue.' Normal, right? Actually, there are loads of people out there that have no inner voice.<br/><br/>While this isn't exactly news, people are only just realizing this thanks to a post on social media.<br/><br/>The tweet said: "Fun fact: some people have an internal narrative and some don't as in, some people's thoughts are like sentences they 'hear', and some people just have abstract non-verbal thoughts and have to consciously verbalize them and most people aren't aware of the other type of person."<br/><br/>Russell Hurlburt, a professor of psychology at the University of Nevada, Las Vegas says that an internal monologue might not necessarily even be with words; it can also be done with images or any other symbols. <br/><br/>Netizens shared their experiences or non-experiences with an internal monologue. <br/><br/>One user said, "I don't have an internal monologue. I think if I had to listen to myself talk in full sentences all day I would stick a whisk up my nose and scramble my brains until there was nothing left."<br/><br/>Which one are you?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/some-people-don-t-have-an-internal-monologue-3958687</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958687/3958687_F87967399FB44A05A780094956826C56_200205_3958687_Some_people_don_t_have_an_internal_monologue_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 23:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959035</guid>
      <title>Iowa Democratic caucuses were a complete and utter debacle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IOWA <br/> Wow that was embarrassing<br/>and we haven't even started yet. After way too much fanfare and pregame hype, the Iowa caucuses turned out to be an utter disaster from beginning to<br/>did it even end yet?<br/>The failing New York Times reported that a "quality control" issue with a new system of reporting results led to mass confusion, which then turned into massive delays in tabulating results. <br/>Across the state, precinct chairmen and volunteers at more than 1,600 caucus sites reported widespread disarray, with a ton of people having problems with a new app for reporting results. <br/>This forced them to call in the results using the party hotline, where some people were left on hold for over an hour.  <br/>The Iowa Democratic Party also said another reason for the trainwreck was that the caucus leaders were required to report three sets of numbers to party HQ, instead of just one<br/>the delegate count.<br/>After spending way too much money and entirely too much time in Iowa, the campaigns demanded results. <br/><br/>When they didn't get those, they all just kind of declared victory<br/>especially Pete<br/>and then all bounced to New Hampshire. <br/>What was even funnier was all the live-streaming and interactive graphics of the results by all the major outlets and papers literally showing nothing but a bunch of zeros after every candidate's name all day long. <br/>On Tuesday, Iowa's Democratic Party said preliminary results from 62 percent of precincts show Pete in first, followed by the Bern, then the Native-American woman, and then hands-on Joe in fourth. <br/>But don't worry folks, this is just the beginning of a long, drawn out primary race to pick the next candidate to lose to Donald Trump.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/iowa-democratic-caucuses-were-a-complete-and-utter-debacle-3959035</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3959035/3959035_9399771EF2844B80BF52D42E50661CA0_200205_3959035_Iowa_Democratic_caucuses_were_a_complete_and_utt_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 13:52:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959193</guid>
      <title>Couple receives 55,000 pieces of post in a massive mailing mistake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CLEVELAND, OHIO <br/> An Ohio couple were left shocked after receiving 55,000 copies of the exact same letter.<br/><br/>Twinsburg resident, Dan Cain was highly suspicious when the post office clerk told him he would not be able to get his mail through the front door; Cain then drove around the back of the office and saw a couple of postal workers wheeling out two huge bins of mail and it was all addressed to him. <br/><br/>What did he receive? <br/><br/>55,000 statements for the student loan, he and his wife Dee had taken out for their daughter's college fees.<br/><br/>Cain opted to not only accept the mailing mistake but to also make two trips in his truck to get all the letters home, letters that he says are incorrect; apparently, the company had used the wrong interest rate to calculate the payment.<br/><br/>The loan company apologized to Cain and his wife for the mistakes and blamed a computer glitch for the mailing mishap; the company also said that they would send another statement, this time for the correct amount.<br/><br/>Cain said with a chuckle, "I just may start a fire, a bonfire and burn it all."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/couple-receives-55-000-pieces-of-post-in-a-massive-mailing-mistake-3959193</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959193/3959193_8A3882634FA44441B829569BF5F0FE30_200206_3959193_Couple_receives_55_000_pieces_of_post_in_a_massi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 02:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959551</guid>
      <title>Shadow Inc. CEO apologizes for Iowa caucus tech woes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IOWA <br/> The 2020 Iowa Caucus was supposed to start off this year's presidential election cycle with a bang. Instead, it got royally screwed over by an app.<br/><br/>Shadow Inc. CEO Gerard Niemira, whose tech company made the app, has come out to apologize for the embarrassing snafu, saying "we feel terrible" about it.<br/><br/>Niemira told Bloomberg that the app, which cost the Iowa Democratic Party 63 Gs to develop, was meant to help compile results quickly from the state's 1,765 precincts.<br/><br/>He claims all the data and calculations done by the app were legit, but there was a glitch in the transmission process. <br/><br/>Apparently, there was a bug in the code that transports results data to the party's main database, and that made all the catastrophic impact.<br/><br/>Theoretically, someone should've caught the glitch in the code during testing, but it was a rush job &#8211; put together in just two months, and according to the New York Times, not adequately tested.<br/><br/>Still, that's a pretty big gaffe, and it's already costing the company. CNN reports that on Tuesday, the Nevada Democratic Party said it won't be using the same app or vendor used in the Iowa caucus.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/shadow-inc-ceo-apologizes-for-iowa-caucus-tech-woes-3959551</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959551/3959551_E8104EB5C6CE45F29EA751FDD933653A_200206_3959551_Shadow_Inc__CEO_apologizes_for_Iowa_caucus_tech__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961234</guid>
      <title>A Boeing 747 broke speed records during New York to London flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> A British Airways Boeing 747-400 set the record for the fastest ever subsonic flight across the Atlantic on Sunday. <br/><br/>Flightradar24.com reports that BA112 flew consistently at Mach 0.86.  <br/><br/>CNN reports that the overnight flight from New York coincided with Storm Ciara, which boosted the Boening's speed and allowed it to arrive at London in 4 hours and 56 minutes.<br/><br/>FlightRadar 24 reports that the jet stream gave eastbound flights including BA112 a significant increase in airspeed and reduced their fuel consumption.<br/><br/>Citing the online outlet, CNN reports the plane reached a top speed of nearly 825 miles per hour.<br/><br/>CNN reports that the jet landed nearly two hours ahead of schedule at Heathrow airport at 4:43 am.<br/><br/>The plane was faster by one minute than a Virgin Airways A350 that also took advantage of the jet stream.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-boeing-747-broke-speed-records-during-new-york-to-london-flight-3961234</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961234/3961234_C827E6B7CE2C43DFAE4344B53E6656D9_200210_3961234_A_Boeing_747_broke_speed_records_during_New_York_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 13:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961648</guid>
      <title>U.S. charges four Chinese military officers over Equifax hack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (check dateline) <br/> A federal grand jury charged four Chinese military officers on Tuesday for the massive hack of the credit rating giant Equifax that occurred in 2017. The four are alleged members of the People's Liberation Army's 54th Research Institute.<br/><br/>Speaking at a press conference in Washington, U.S. Attorney General William Barr called the hack 'one of the largest data breaches in history.' Barr said the hackers stole personal information and trade secrets including data compilation and database designs.<br/><br/><br/>BBC reports that the hackers allegedly routed traffic through 32 servers in nearly 20 countries to conceal their location as they conducted the cyber attack, which occurred from May to June in 2017. <br/><br/>The U.S. Department of Justice named three of the four suspects, but their whereabouts are unknown. The Washington Post quotes FBI Deputy Director David Bowdich as saying, "We can't take them into custody, try them in a court of law, and lock them up <br/> not today, anyway."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-charges-four-chinese-military-officers-over-equifax-hack-3961648</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961648/3961648_959C9A3F1EE146EFB728139F5BD46345_200211_3961648_U_S__charges_four_Chinese_military_officers_over_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962074</guid>
      <title>Native American burial sites are being blown up for Trump's wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARIZONA <br/> Trump is blowing up Native American burial sites to build his wall.<br/><br/>The Washington Post reports that construction crews have begun controlled blasting within Arizona's Organ Pipe Cactus National Monument, which is a UNESCO recognized natural reserve.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the project is being done to prepare for the construction of Trump's border wall system, which will see a 30-foot tall steel barrier run across 43 miles of national park land.<br/><br/>The blasts are occurring on Monument Hill, on ground considered sacred to Native American tribes, which include the burial site for the Tohono O'odham Nation.<br/><br/>"It also includes an area that is believed to contain artifacts dating back 10,000 years."<br/><br/>Democratic Congressman Raul D. Grijalva described the project as 'sacrilegious' and says the Tohono O'odham Nation was not consulted by the government beforehand.<br/><br/>Under the 2005 REAL ID act, the federal government has the right to waive laws that get in the way of national security. The Trump administration has since used this to waive dozens of laws, in order to construct the wall.<br/><br/>Environmentalists are also concerned about the damage being done to the local underground aquifer, as well as to migrating wildlife in the region.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/native-american-burial-sites-are-being-blown-up-for-trump-s-wall-3962074</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962074/3962074_63C49461D56E4C56895AAADF3582352D_200212_3962074_Native_American_burial_sites_are_being_blown_up__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 09:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962229</guid>
      <title>Russian spacecraft are stalking an advanced U.S. spy satellite</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARLINGTON, VIRGINIA <br/> Two mysterious Russian spacecraft have been shadowing a U.S. reconnaissance satellite since November, coming to as close to 100 miles at times, U.S. Space Force commander General John Raymond confirmed to Time in a report dated to Feb. 10.[e]<br/><br/>Citing outside experts, Time reports that the U.S. KH-11 satellite is about the size of a bus and its spying sensors are believed to be as powerful as the Hubble Space Telescope's.<br/><br/>Citing General Raymond, Time reports that the Russians launched a Soyuz rocket in November with a payload that separated into the two stalking satellites. General Raymond says he believes the bigger satellite acted as a carrier for the small one.<br/><br/>Satellite watcher Michael Thompson <br/> who first broke the story in January <br/> tweeted that the Russian orbit was cleverly designed. The orbit the pair of satellites holds allows the two to observe KH-11 from one side during daytime and the other at night.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russian-spacecraft-are-stalking-an-advanced-u-s-spy-satellite-3962229</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962229/3962229_E16A2823790C4BED8FA591CB6C353BC4_200212_3962229_Russian_spacecraft_are_stalking_an_advanced_U_S__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 13:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962403</guid>
      <title>Dog takes itself on bus ride to get some exercise at the park</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE <br/> Eclipse is a black Labrador Retriever-cross-Mastiff and she's a hit with the local community because she rides the bus alone. <br/><br/>Her owner, Jeff Young used to walk her down to the bus stop, and then get off at Belltown dog park. <br/><br/>Eventually, Eclipse knew exactly where she was going and if Jeff was taking too long, she'd just jump on the bus without him. <br/><br/>The bus driver would recognize her and drop her off at the dog park with Jeff catching her up later. <br/><br/>After several trips, Jeff let Eclipse go on her own, and now amazingly she rides the bus alone, plays at the dog park and then catches the bus back; she even has her own bus pass attached to her collar.<br/><br/>She's got 83,000 plus followers on Facebook and everyone wants to ride along with her.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-takes-itself-on-bus-ride-to-get-some-exercise-at-the-park-3962403</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962403/3962403_91212C459A47493489A293A9B9370CB8_200213_3962403_Dog_takes_itself_on_bus_ride_to_get_some_exercis_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 03:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962396</guid>
      <title>Jussie Smollett indicted on six counts for faking attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO <br/> Former Empire actor Jussie Smollett is facing a new six-count indictment for filing false reports last year that he was the victim of a hate crime. <br/><br/>According to USA Today, Smollett had told police that he was beaten by two masked men while walking near his Chicago apartment on January 29, 2019. He said the attackers shouted racial and anti-gay slurs, poured a chemical substance over him, and wrapped a noose around his neck.<br/><br/>CNN reports that while Chicago police initially investigated the incident as a hate crime, prosecutors later claimed Smollett paid the two men &#8211; brothers Abel and Ola Osundairo &#8211; to stage the attack for publicity.    <br/><br/>Court documents indicate that on January 22, 2019, Jussie Smollett received a threatening letter at the studio where the show 'Empire' is filmed. It came with a white powdery substance that was later determined to be ibuprofen."  <br/><br/>Disappointed by the studio's handling of the letter, the actor met with the Osundairo brothers three days later, and asked them to stage an attack on him.<br/><br/>According to prosecutors, Smollett wanted the assault to happen the night of January 28 near his Streeterville apartment. He told Abel to hurt him, but not too badly, and Ola to put a rope around his neck, pour gasoline on him, and yell, "This is MAGA country!"<br/><br/>He then gave the brothers $100 to buy rope, gasoline, ski masks, gloves, and red MAGA baseball caps needed for the attack.<br/><br/>On January 27, Smollett drove the brothers to the scene where he wanted the assault to take place, pointing out a surveillance camera that would capture the incident. He instructed them to pour bleach instead of gasoline, and not to bring their cellphones, then gave a $3,500 personal check payable to Abel.<br/><br/>A flight delay on Smollett's part pushed the plan back to 2 a.m. on the 29th. The actor called Abel at 12:49 a.m. once his plane landed. Minutes later, the brothers hailed an Uber, switching to a cab midway that took them three blocks from the scene. The attack took place on 2:04 a.m. as instructed, though out of view of the camera. The brothers fled the scene afterward, taking a taxi home.<br/><br/>ABC News reports that the actor had initially been indicted in March 2019 for 16 counts of felony disorderly conduct, before charges were all dropped just weeks later. Prosecutors said Smollett had forfeited his $10,000 bail and done community service.<br/><br/>Following backlash from the dismissal, a judge assigned special prosecutor Dan Webb to look into why the original charges were dropped.<br/><br/>After weighing the extensive nature of Smollett's false police reports and the resources expended by Chicago PD to investigate his allegations, Webb determined there are reasonable grounds to further prosecute the actor, adding that it is "in the interest of justice."<br/><br/>Another factor that contributed to this decision is that the Cook County State Attorney's Office could not provide evidence of similar cases that showed Smollett's received no special treatment. <br/><br/>Smollett is due in court on February 24.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/jussie-smollett-indicted-on-six-counts-for-faking-attack-3962396</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962396/3962396_D2F4AF0E211540748C8A58773F0428C3_200213_3962396_Jussie_Smollett_indicted_on_six_counts_for_fakin_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 03:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962678</guid>
      <title>Wendy's worker fired for taking bath in kitchen sink</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRENNVILLE, MICHIGAN <br/> A worker was filmed enjoying a nice bubble bath in a sink at a Greenville Wendy's joint while other employees watched on in enjoyment. <br/>According to WXMI, a version of the now viral video was originally shared on video-sharing app TikTok, but has since been deleted. But before that happened, it was also shared on Facebook.<br/>The 23-second video shows a worker submerged in a big old industrial sink used to wash kitchen items laughing and joking with other Wendy's workers. <br/>Another worker is seen throwing something into the sink and saying "Wash yourself!"<br/>The bather responds by saying, "It feels like a hot tub," while he scrubs himself down. He doesn't have a shirt on, but with all the bubbles it's unclear what's going on down below. <br/>According to Team Schostak<br/>the company that owns the Wendy's restaurant<br/>all the workers involved in the video have been given the boot. <br/>In a statement from the vice president of Team Schostak said, "This egregious behavior is completely unacceptable and counter to our safety, training and operational standards. Upon learning of this situation, all employees in the video were terminated immediately and the restaurant is being completely sanitized." <br/>The Wendy's in question has since re-opened for business. Anyone else need a bath?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wendy-s-worker-fired-for-taking-bath-in-kitchen-sink-3962678</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962678/3962678_B3EFC5109C2048CDA52D173ECC5A2D91_200213_3962678_Wendy_s_worker_fired_for_taking_bath_in_kitchen__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 10:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962920</guid>
      <title>Tyra Banks set to open 'ModelLand' theme park</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA MONICA, CALIFORNIA <br/> Tyra Banks reveals that she's set to open 'ModelLand' later this year. <br/><br/>Almost a year ago to the day, the creator of America's Next Top Model revealed that she was going to open up a model-themed theme park called 'ModelLand'<br/><br/>Speaking on an episode of The View earlier this week, Banks said she wanted to bring "modeling to the masses." She described ModelLand as "a story-driven attraction where you can come and celebrate your own beauty." <br/><br/>Late last year, Banks labeled ModelLand as her "baby which has not yet been born." She said that the park will be a "location-based attraction where you can be a model for a day." <br/><br/>Speaking to Variety last year she revealed, "Modelland is going to be a place where the modeling world meets fantasy, meets entertainment, meets technology, meets retail, meets dining, meets your fiercest best self you could ever imagine."<br/><br/>She noted Wakanda, the fictional country from Black Panther as inspiration for the project; she also lists her own young-adult novel 'ModelLand' as an influence.<br/><br/>When will it open?<br/><br/>No one knows exactly, details are lacking, all we do know is that it is set to open in Santa Monica sometime in winter this year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tyra-banks-set-to-open-modelland-theme-park-3962920</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3962920/3962920_5CB1E6CB0E3E4BC4AFFAFE2D04B0D590_200214_3962920_Tyra_Banks_set_to_open__ModelLand__theme_park_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 02:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964077</guid>
      <title>Space engineer makes her own rotary cell phone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> A woman in New York invented an insanely awesome old school rotary style cell phone. <br/>With all the varied<br/>and often times useless<br/>functions on today's modern not-so-smartphones, finally a device that won't suck the life out of your day. <br/>According to Wired, Justine Haupt works as an astronomy instrumentation engineer at Brookhaven National Laboratory in New York.  <br/><br/>On Feb. 12, Haupt posted an article detailing how she made the DIY phone, which became so popular it caused her website to crash. <br/><br/>On her website, she details how she took a rotary dial from an old Western Electric Trimline telephone, paired it with a microcontroller and an Adafruit Fona 3G cell transceiver. She then just 3D-printed a casing and was good to go. <br/>The phone comes with a 10-LED signal meter, a power switch, quick dial buttons and a curved e-paper screen that displays incoming or missed calls. <br/>Along with photos of the whole process, Haupt also shared raw schematics and links to all of the original design files, released as open-source materials, so anyone with the know-how can build their own.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/space-engineer-makes-her-own-rotary-cell-phone-3964077</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964077/3964077_81F4FAF0CA404C02828B47CFFE03D6AC_200217_3964077_Space_engineer_makes_her_own_rotary_cell_phone_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 05:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964133</guid>
      <title>How the Nevada caucus works</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEVADA <br/> After Iowa and New Hampshire comes the third nominating contest for the Democratic presidential contenders in Nevada, the "First of the West."<br/><br/>Here's all you need to know about the upcoming Nevada caucus.<br/><br/>The Nevada Independent reports that early voting for the Nevada caucus is from February 15 to 18 at over 80 sites.<br/><br/>Voters must first check in with volunteers, whose party-purchased iPads are loaded with a PDF voter roll. After filling out a Google form and being given a voter pin, they rank their preferences on a scannable paper ballot, which is then dropped into a ballot box<br/><br/>During caucus day on February 22, voters sign in at their local precincts and must then separate into groups based on which candidate they support.<br/><br/>Candidates who receive less than 15% of the vite are deemed 'non-viable' and disqualified. Their supporters can either go to a different candidate or remain uncommitted.<br/><br/>Instead of the failed Shadow Inc. app used in Iowa, Nevada will use a Google Forms-based caucus calculator on the iPads.<br/><br/>According to ABC, this will calculate totals by combining caucus day and early voting data, although precinct chairs will still be required to fill out back-up paper reporting sheets. Should the state deem it necessary to conduct a recount, these sheets will serve as their paper trail.'<br/><br/>As required by the DNC, three sets of results will be reported on caucus day: raw votes from the first alignment, raw votes from the final alignment, and county delegate results.<br/><br/>A Nevada Democratic Official told ABC that the reporting process will include a two-source verification, with data first reported through 'a secure hotline to a trained operator.' Either the calculator or the reporting sheet will serve as an additional source.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-nevada-caucus-works-3964133</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964133/3964133_A9B305ECB7764903A071CE9BD34235A1_200217_3964133_How_the_Nevada_caucus_works_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 07:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964740</guid>
      <title>YouTuber fakes vacation to Bali with Ikea photoshoot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IKEA <br/> Even influencers need a vacation. It's tough for influencers out there busting their butts to influence as many people as possible with their influencing skills. <br/>Which is why YouTube personality Natalia Taylor went on a vacation to Bali and posted the snaps on her Instagram. Or did she? <br/>Taylor posted a few pictures on her IG saying that she was in Bali on February 7. <br/><br/>But instead of actually going to Bali, she just hopped over to her local Ikea and had herself a photoshoot. <br/>According to Fox News, the first set of photos was captioned, "The queen has arrived." Her followers then started leaving the usual IG comments. We'll spare you from those. <br/>Then a few days later, Taylor posted a video on YouTube telling everyone how she faked her Bali vacay in a nearly 14 minute-long video. <br/>In the video Taylor explains, "It's been said life on the internet isn't always what it seems, especially in today's day and age when it's so easy to pretend to be anyone you want to be." <br/>"So many influencers nowadays have actually been caught in the act of pretending to be at a particular destination when they really weren't and it's either Photoshop or it's not even them."<br/>"The point of this video is to see if you can fake it 'til you make it." <br/>She said it was tough lying to her followers, but that she was happy that she could lift the veil on social media and then warns people not to believe everything they see on the internet. <br/>Wow<br/>our species really is doomed.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/youtuber-fakes-vacation-to-bali-with-ikea-photoshoot-3964740</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964740/3964740_BD33A9E596D04FA9B6B2B65E26F6BF67_200218_3964740_YouTuber_fakes_vacation_to_Bali_with_Ikea_photos_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 10:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965339</guid>
      <title>U.S. designates China's fake news media as government operatives</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The U.S. State Department on Tuesday designated five Chinese fake news media outlets as official government entities under the Foreign Missions Act, which means they will be treated as diplomatic outposts of the Chinese government and subject to the same constraints.<br/>In plain English, the U.S. is calling Xinhua News Agency, CGTN, China Radio International, China Daily and Hai Tian Development<br/>a U.S. company linked to the People's Daily<br/>what they actually are, STATE-SPONSORED-PROPAGANDA.<br/>The failing New York Times reports that the move is the latest by the Trump Administration to counter Beijing's influence and intelligence operations in America. <br/>According to the Times, in the past month alone, prosecutors have brought cases against Chinese spy operations involving scientific research at Harvard and the 2017 hacking of Equifax. <br/>The U.S. has also charged Huawei and two of its subsidiaries with federal racketeering and conspiracy to steal trade secrets. <br/>U.S. State Department officials said the new designation would not impede the five Chinese fake news outlets from reporting, broadcasting or carrying journalistic activities. <br/>The officials said the 5 Chinese puppet organizations will be required to provide names, personal details and turnover of staff to the State Department. They would also need to report if they own or lease property in the U.S. <br/>According to the Washington Post, the U.S. decision was likely more symbolic than punitive, but either way, it's a move in the right direction.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-designates-china-s-fake-news-media-as-government-operatives-3965339</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965339/3965339_DAD5A3FD86D246CB9FB39DAB7C53ACB2_200219_3965339_U_S__designates_China_s_fake_news_media_as_gover_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 14:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965800</guid>
      <title>Utah Senate supports bill decriminalizing polygamy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SALT LAKE CITY <br/> Something is rotten in the state of Utah. Utah's state Senate has actually voted unanimously to decriminalize polygamy amoung consenting adults. <br/>The BBC reports that under current laws, anyone found to have multiple spouses could face up to five years in the slammer. <br/>Supporters of the bill<br/>so all 29 Utah Senate members<br/>say the bill would remove the secrecy surrounding the morons, sorry Mormons, who feel the more the merrier and would also allow victims to report abuse.<br/>According to the Beebs, the bill still needs to be approved by the states House of Representatives. <br/>The new proposal would mean that if you're really dumb enough to want more than one spouse, it would be considered a misdemenour, similar to a traffic violation. <br/>More serious crimes, such as forced or coerced bigamy, would be treated as a felony. <br/>According to the Associated Press, about 30,000 people in Utah live in polygamous communities. <br/>Utah is home to the Church of Jesus Freaks of Later-day Suckers, also known as the Mormon Church. <br/>If your Mormon history is a bit hazy, check out the South Park documentaries to get you up to speed.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/utah-senate-supports-bill-decriminalizing-polygamy-3965800</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965800/3965800_90B82C62B27C4B2FBEA5841E071E5929_200220_3965800_Utah_Senate_supports_bill_decriminalizing_polyga_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 13:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966455</guid>
      <title>Cop couple on date night foil armed robber</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOUISVILLE, KENTUCKY <br/> Of all the fast-food joints in all of Kentucky, one supremely unlucky criminal had to try and rob the one with the off-duty cops in it.<br/><br/>According to WHAS11, the incident occurred at a Raising Cane's Chicken Fingers store in Louisville around 10 p.m. on February 15.<br/><br/>Married Elizabethtown officers Nicole McKeown and Detective Chase McKeown were inside for date night when a masked suspect sauntered in.<br/><br/>According to the Louisville Metro Police Department, the perp, later identified as Justin Carter, flashed his gun at an employee and demanded cash.<br/><br/>The McKeown were seated at the very back of the store, but it didn't take long for them to figure out what was happening.<br/><br/>Slowly, they get up from their sears and draw their weapons, splitting up as they beeline toward the suspect.<br/><br/>When Carter sees the armed pair, he drops his weapon and runs outta there.<br/><br/>The officers follow after him, eventually detaining him about a block later.<br/><br/>WHAS11 reports that Carter has been charged with possession of a handgun by a convicted felon, receiving stolen property, and robbery.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cop-couple-on-date-night-foil-armed-robber-3966455</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/22/3966455/3966455_A48552A240354D85A9D4414A0E1DD985_200222_3966455_Cop_couple_on_date_night_foil_armed_robber_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 19:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967113</guid>
      <title>Burger King uses moldy Whopper to promote its signature product</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. <br/> Hungry?<br/><br/>Burger King is promoting the 'beauty of no artificial preservatives' with its new moldy burger ad. <br/><br/>The ad begins with someone making a fresh burger to the sound of Dinah Washington's song 'What Difference A Day Makes', and then uses a time-lapse showing it rotting over 34 days. <br/><br/>The fast-food juggernaut says the campaign is highlighting its decision to remove artificial preservatives from the product.<br/><br/>On Burger King's Twitter account they said: "The beauty of real food is that it gets ugly."<br/><br/>It plans to get rid of preservatives from the burger served in all of its restaurants this year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/burger-king-uses-moldy-whopper-to-promote-its-signature-product-3967113</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967113/3967113_04EA05080785468B902A28F731413965_200224_3967113_Burger_King_uses_moldy_Whopper_to_promote_its_si_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 02:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967272</guid>
      <title>Daredevil 'Mad Mike' Hughes killed in homemade rocket crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BARSTOW, CALIFORNIA <br/> Self-proclaimed daredevil "Mad Mike" Hughes is sadly no longer around after he crashed in his homemade rocket shortly after take off near Barstow on Saturday. <br/>Hughes was well-known for his belief in a non-round Earth, and was hoping to prove it by launching himself up into space.  <br/>According to a Space.com, Hughes had planned to shoot himself up into the sky for a Science Channel series called "Homemade Astronauts." <br/>According to Discovery<br/>which owns The Science Channel<br/>the series is supposed to follow people looking to "explore the final frontier on limited budgets." <br/><br/>Discovery's website said Hughes and Waldo Stakes built the steam-powered rocket with the intent of getting Hughes 5,000 feet into the air. <br/>Video posted to social media shows the rocket flying up and a parachute ripping off at launch. <br/>According to witnesses talking to the LA Times, the rocket went straight up in an arc and then came straight down. None of Mike's backup parachutes worked either.<br/>According to the San Bernardino County Sheriff's Office, deputies responded to the crash off highway 247 in Barstow on Saturday afternoon. A sheriff's aviation unit is now investigating the incident.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/daredevil-mad-mike-hughes-killed-in-homemade-rocket-crash-3967272</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967272/3967272_BE4508E728014F9AA0D477AF32A64EF6_200224_3967272_Daredevil__Mad_Mike__Hughes_killed_in_homemade_r_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 09:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968553</guid>
      <title>600 Ibs sea lion takes a stroll, ends up on Washington road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CASTLE ROCK, WASHINGTON <br/> A 600-Ibs sea lion was found wandering a "significant distance" on a road in Washington on February 23rd.<br/><br/>According to the Cowlitz County Sheriff's Office, the sea lion was caught in a wooded area in the city of Castle Rock.<br/><br/>They believe the sea lion wound up there after traveling up Delameter Creek from the Cowlitz River.  <br/><br/>Video footage of the capture shows the sea lion fluster as officials attempt to get the animal into a cage on the back of a trailer. <br/><br/>The Department of Fish and Wildlife triumphed and managed to remove it from the area, but only after local officials waited with the animal for several hours until wildlife staff could arrive with a trailer.<br/><br/>Fortunately, the wayward sea lion was returned to the Columbia River.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/600-ibs-sea-lion-takes-a-stroll-ends-up-on-washington-road-3968553</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968553/3968553_9410D50E03634318943D6228AB0841DC_200227_3968553_600_Ibs_sea_lion_takes_a_stroll__ends_up_on_Wash_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:07:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
