<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 18:10:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3981961</guid>
      <title>QUARANTINE: NYC man uses drone to ask out neighbour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BROOKLYN, NEW YORK <br/> Brooklyn-based photographer, Jeremy Cohen isn't usually smooth when it comes to talking to the ladies, but when he spotted his neighbour jiving on her rooftop, he let his tech do the talking. <br/><br/>The Tik-Tok video has since gone viral with the 28-year-old photographer sharing the romance to his twitter account on March 22nd, saying, "I can't believe this actually works and yes this is a real story."<br/><br/>The tweet has now been viewed more than six million times.<br/><br/>Cohen said, "flirting was normally daunting for me, but since I've been quarantining in my apartment for a week now, I was craving some social interaction." He added, "2020 has been off to a terrible start, but I still needed to shoot my shot."<br/><br/>In part 2 of the meet-cute series, they indulged in a virtual date with Cohen telling Insider, "it's very Gen Z."<br/><br/>And in part 3, the smooth streamer rolled over to meet Tori Cignarella, who eventually revealed her name on a "real" date, inside a plastic bubble to take a walk side-by-side.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/quarantine-nyc-man-uses-drone-to-ask-out-neighbour-3981961</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/01/3981961/3981961_2FACF3971F1E4D43B2A220B26F1133CE_200401_3981961_QUARANTINE__NYC_man_uses_drone_to_ask_out_neighb_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 04:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986225</guid>
      <title>Nearly 600 sailors have COVID-19 on a US aircraft carrier</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A total of 585 sailors on the U.S. Navy aircraft carrier Theodore Roosevelt tested positive for COVID-19, the Navy said in a statement dated April 12. This figure represents 12 percent of the ship's 4,800 crew and an uptick of about 170 cases in three days.<br/><br/>Speaking to a news conference at the Pentagon on April 9, the Joint Chiefs of Staff's General John Hyten said one of the carrier's sailors with COVID-19 was found unresponsive in their isolation room and transferred to the ICU on Guam Island.<br/><br/>According to the Navy's statement, 3,967 sailors of the ship have moved ashore, and 92 percent of the crew have been tested as of April 12.<br/><br/>The U.S. Navy operates 11 aircraft carriers. According to National Public Radio, at least three of the advanced warships have reported COVID-19 cases onboard, which raises troubling questions about the fleet's military readiness.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nearly-600-sailors-have-covid-19-on-a-us-aircraft-carrier-3986225</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/13/3986225/3986225_BD3EEF10996C460F98DCBDB06FB1B7F5_200413_3986225_Nearly_600_sailors_have_COVID_19_on_a_US_aircraf_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 07:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986188</guid>
      <title>Donald Trump to Hold Talks on American Funding of the 'WHO'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> President Donald Trump has yet again turned his attention to the failings of the World Health Organization and hinted that he will be holding talks about their U.S. funding next week.<br/><br/>During his White House press briefing last Friday, Trump slammed the UN organization for their handling of the COVID-19 crisis and letting China, "get the better of the argument."<br/><br/>The WHO is under fire for their continued and unwavering praise of China, despite the fact Xi Jinping's regime suppressed information about the coronavirus and inhumanely delayed efforts to prevent its outbreak.<br/><br/>Trump has also accused the WHO of being, "China-centric" while the CIA told White House officials that Beijing was feeding the WHO false numbers, a claim that holds water considering China's infamous lack of clarity.<br/><br/>Regarding funding the WHO, Trump said, "I don't like that." <br/><br/>"I don't think that's appropriate, I don't think it's fair to the American people."<br/><br/>"I tell that to President Xi, I tell that to Dr. Tedros. We are going to be talking about that next week in great detail."<br/><br/>"We want to make sure money is properly spent. Why is the US paying $500 million a year, why is China paying, this year, $42 million dollars?<br/><br/>"The answer always turns out to be in China's favor."<br/><br/>Trump said he was looking into the possibility that he would halt the United States' funding of the World Health Organization for not having informed the world community on time about the threat of the coronavirus.<br/><br/>Trump said in a tweet: "The WHO really blew it. For some reason, funded largely by the United States, yet very China-centric. We will be giving that a good look. Fortunately, I rejected their advice on keeping our borders open to China early on. Why did they give us such a faulty recommendation?"<br/><br/>His comments prompted the Director-General of the WHO, Dr. Tedros to warn that politicizing the coronavirus will mean more "body bags" as the US death toll tops 22,000, a statement coming from the head of the organization that bans Taiwan from the WHO because of politics. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/donald-trump-to-hold-talks-on-american-funding-of-the-who--3986188</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/13/3986188/3986188_0905C11C71964FA88C392A31BE827C27_200413_3986188_Donald_Trump_to_Hold_Talks_on_American_Funding_o_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 06:13:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987687</guid>
      <title>Strong winds leave truck driver dangling off a bridge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHESAPEAKE, VIRGINIA <br/>  Emergency responders save a man that was hanging off a bridge inside a trailer truck. Yes, you heard that right.  <br/><br/>Imagine you're peacefully driving your truck down the highway when suddenly a gust of wind pushes you to another lane and then blows you off a bridge, well, almost blows you off a bridge. Unfortunately for Suffolk truck driver Wayne Boone, he didn't have to imagine.<br/><br/>Citing Virginia State Police, WAVY TV 10 reports that Boone was driving his 2007 Freightliner tractor-trailer on Interstate 64 at around 8:43 a.m. when strong winds forced the vehicle to the other lane while Boone was crossing the High Rise Bridge.<br/><br/>By then the truck was doing its own thing. Boone had lost control of the steering wheel when he hit the side of the bridge. Next thing Boone knew, he was hanging 70 feet above Elizabeth River while inside the cab of the truck.<br/><br/>Thankfully, the story doesn't end there. According to Chesapeake Fire officials, Boone was successfully rescued after an emergency responder rappelled off the side of the bridge to get  Boone to safety. The story ends with Boone being taken to Sentara Hospital with a few minor injuries. <br/><br/>And before you start blaming poor Boone for the windy tractor frenzy, no, he was not driving under the influence of anything. Nature just decided to play around with him a little.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/strong-winds-leave-truck-driver-dangling-off-a-bridge-3987687</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/17/3987687/3987687_4B25731DEC414A19884C0C488CE54B11_200417_3987687_Strong_winds_leave_truck_driver_dangling_off_a_b_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 05:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989347</guid>
      <title>More minorities dying due to COVID-19 in the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Minorities in the United States are being disproportionately affected by the spread of coronavirus due to economic disparities and lack of data collection.<br/><br/>According to Politico, black and brown American communities are being heavily affected by the spread of coronavirus in the U.S. In addition, not enough information on the spread in these communities is being collected, affecting efforts to ameliorate the situation.<br/><br/>Five Florida counties stated that African American and Latino patients infected with coronavirus are being hospitalized and, at times, dying at faster rates than white patients.<br/><br/>According to a statement from Louisiana Governor John Bel Edwards, a little more than 70 percent of COVID-19 deaths in the state were from African American patients.<br/><br/>However, not all information related to the testing and treatment of these minorities is being released, making it difficult for authorities to provide proper help to curtail the spread of the virus in these communities.<br/><br/>Fewer individuals belonging to these groups have access to health insurance, further exacerbating the lack of information.<br/><br/>Data collected by doctors at the universities of Virginia and Pittsburgh, in collaboration with data-tracking firm Rubix, indicate that although thousands of individuals belonging to these minorities presented symptoms of coronavirus, they were not receiving testing.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/more-minorities-dying-due-to-covid-19-in-the-u-s--3989347</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/22/3989347/3989347_1BA846A7550F4813BF8F4F98B782AB8E_200422_3989347_More_minorities_dying_due_to_COVID_19_in_the_U_S_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 00:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989590</guid>
      <title>Woman's breast implants save her from gunshot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. <br/> Doctors believe a woman's breast implants saved her from a gunshot to the chest. <br/><br/>Superman better watch out, there's someone out there who doesn't need to be superhuman to be bulletproof. Apparently, all you need is a set of really great...silicone breast implants?<br/><br/>This isn't fake news. A woman survived a gunshot after her chest deflected a copper jacketed 0.40 caliber bullet. Her saving grace? Her 'life-saving silicone breast implants' <br/> that's how a case study published in Sage Journal referred to the incident. Here's what happened. <br/><br/>The 30-year-old woman was walking down the street minding her own business when she suddenly felt a sharp pain and warmth in her chest. Unbeknownst to her, she had been randomly shot by a stranger who, to this day, hasn't been identified.<br/><br/>The woman then nonchalantly took herself to the emergency room, where perplexed doctors extracted the bullet from her chest. Turns out, her two fake friends really had her back (or her front?).<br/><br/>Listen to this. The bullet had entered her left breast, ricocheted on her sternum and then hit her right breast, breaking one of her ribs <br/> and she still walked herself to the emergency room.<br/><br/>Maybe this should become a thing. You know, give some emergency responders a pair of girlfriends instead of having them wear bulletproof vests. It would certainly confuse the heck out of criminals.<br/><br/>Sadly the lady's life-saving bongo's had to be removed, but she was sent home with only a few antibiotics so she should be on her way to recovery.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-s-breast-implants-save-her-from-gunshot-3989590</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/22/3989590/3989590_E2830643F1534F5F857D6DC58A7380E7_200422_3989590_Woman_s_breast_implants_save_her_from_gunshot_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 11:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989810</guid>
      <title>Angry Man Throws Grocery Cart Through Customer's Window</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST MEMPHIS, ARKANSAS <br/> On Sunday the 19th of April at around 3:00 p.m a disgruntled shopper threw a grocery cart through the back of a car window. <br/><br/><br/><br/>West Memphis Police told local press that an officer was patrolling the area around a Kroger store on West Service Road when he saw the man, now identified as Robert Jones, act out in aggression; the police officer stopped him and took Jones into custody. <br/><br/><br/><br/>According to the report, the vehicle owner left her cart next to her vehicle instead of putting it back.<br/><br/><br/><br/>She said that's when madman Jones grabbed the cart and threw it in her back window. <br/><br/><br/><br/>Jones was charged with second-degree criminal mischief.<br/><br/><br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/><br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/><br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/><br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/><br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/><br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/><br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/><br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/><br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/><br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/><br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/><br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/><br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/><br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/><br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/angry-man-throws-grocery-cart-through-customer-s-window-3989810</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/23/3989810/3989810_8BD9071C4F5B476C8FDADA70945EA583_200423_3989810_Angry_Man_Throws_Grocery_Cart_Through_Customers__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 04:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3990251</guid>
      <title>"I Faked Having Covid-19 on Facebook and Got Arrested"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TYLER COUNTY, TEXAS <br/> An East Texas man was arrested after he claimed he had tested positive for COVID-19 on social media.<br/><br/>23-year-old Michael Lane Brandin knew his Facebook post would cause a stir, but what he didn't realize was that he'd be arrested, lose his job and face a trial that could see him behind bars.<br/><br/>Faced with the coronavirus dominating headlines, Brandin decided to, in his own words, "do a social experiment."<br/><br/>On March 13th he posted that he'd tested positive for coronavirus and then he added that doctors had told him that the virus was now airborne.<br/><br/>But he had made it all up. <br/> <br/>To justify his actions, he said the point was to demonstrate that you can't always believe everything you read online.<br/><br/>On Facebook, he was met with sympathy and shock, saying "I had quite a few reactions. A lot of friends messaged me to ask if I was OK, so I told them that it was fake."<br/><br/>But whilst he explained away his fake post to worried friends, what he didn't realize was that what was happening offline became far more serious as his fake news spread like wildfire across Tyler County, in Texas, where he lived.<br/><br/>This was days before any lockdown had been brought in, but anxious people began to call the local hospital and ask if the news was true: how could they now protect themselves from an airborne invisible killer?<br/><br/>So, the police got involved, told him to amend his post, and Brandin did.<br/><br/>Unfortunately, it was too little too late, as the next post to appear on Facebook was from the Tyler County Sheriff's Office who said that Brandin was now facing the criminal allegation of false alarm. <br/><br/>Faced with the inevitable, he turned himself in. <br/><br/>After a night in the cells, he was released on condition of paying a $1,000 bail bond and is now waiting for his trial to start.<br/><br/>But staying true to his justification, he said: "I have a bachelor of science degree in mass communications."<br/><br/> "I did it to prove how easy it is for anyone to post something online and cause panic."<br/><br/>"I wanted to prove that it is important for people to be educated and do their own research before assuming everything they read or hear is true."<br/><br/>"But because of a Facebook post, I lost my job, my health benefits. I couldn't start my master's program on time due to not having the money."<br/><br/>"It has put a financial burden on my entire family because they are all trying to help me pay my bills."<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-i-faked-having-covid-19-on-facebook-and-got-arrested--3990251</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/24/3990251/3990251_BDB02E0507AB4FDE884709B6DCD59647_200424_3990251__I_Faked_Having_Covid_19_on_Facebook_and_Got_Arr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 04:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991274</guid>
      <title>Florida Gator Blocks Road, Was Just Trying to Find Love</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANATEE, FLORIDA <br/> A gator that was blocking traffic was apparently just looking for a mate. <br/><br/>Manatee County Sheriff's Office took to Facebook to share a snap of a 9-foot alligator that was removed from a road for, "being aggressive with traffic." <br/><br/>In their post, they note that it's mating season, which means reptiles, "could be more mobile and aggressive than usual."<br/><br/>The gator was about 40 miles south of Tampa when he went into his display of road rage. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/florida-gator-blocks-road-was-just-trying-to-find-love-3991274</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/27/3991274/3991274_1E69175AF9734060B66E32946CD58216_200427_3991274_Florida_Gator_Blocks_Road__Was_Just_Trying_to_Fi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 07:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991263</guid>
      <title>Woman Gets 3 Years for Impersonating an FBI Agent</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MONROE, NORTH CAROLINA <br/> A woman has been sentenced to three years in prison for posing as an FBI agent on a dating website and illegally having a gun.<br/><br/>U.S. Attorney Andrew Murray announced last Thursday that 39-year-old, Riane Leigh Brownlee had been sentenced to 37 months for impersonating an FBI agent and illegally possessing a firearm.<br/><br/>Desperate to find love, Brownlee, who is also known as "Raine Leigh Webb," posted a series of 'side-facing-snaps' on dating websites, showing off her fake FBI badge and firearm. <br/><br/>On February 23rd, 2019 when Brownlee was on a date, she reportedly told the person that she was an FBI agent conducting a counter-drug operation. <br/><br/>After Brownlee was arrested later the same day, she falsely told the same person that she had to keep her identity secret from law enforcement because she was operating undercover.<br/><br/>Court records show that, in addition to the fake FBI badge, law enforcement recovered a stolen loaded gun from the stolen vehicle Brownlee was driving.<br/><br/>To top it all off, authorities also recovered a fake FBI ID bearing Brownlee's picture and the name "FBI Special Agent Alexandria Mancini."<br/><br/>She has multiple prior felony convictions, including identity theft, felony worthless checks, and possession of a stolen motor vehicle, she is also prohibited from possessing a firearm or ammunition.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-gets-3-years-for-impersonating-an-fbi-agent-3991263</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/27/3991263/3991263_4C9DDB975B17445EBA2E7176681C9E2E_200427_3991263_Woman_Gets_3_Years_for_Impersonating_an_FBI_Agen_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 07:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991597</guid>
      <title>White House Hot Mic Catches Joke, 'Everyone's Been Vaccinated'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A hot mic in the White House briefing room captured a conversation between Fox News reporter John Roberts and New York Times photographer Doug Mills saying that everyone around here has, 'been vaccinated.' <br/><br/>The video from last Monday's White House coronavirus task force briefing has sparked controversy and has since gone viral.<br/><br/>Mediaite, who was first to report on the video, stated that when White House briefings are streamed live, some outlets carry the feeds <br/> with audio and video <br/>  long before the events start.<br/><br/>Roberts is heard saying, 'You can take off the mask, the case fatality rate is 0.1 to 0.3 according to USC.'<br/><br/>Mills then apparently jokes, 'Everyone's been vaccinated around here anyway.' <br/><br/>Roberts is also heard quoting statistics, saying, 'USC and LA County public health came out with a study that found that there are 7,000 cases in California but they really believe there are anywhere from 221,000 to 442,000 people who are infected.' <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/white-house-hot-mic-catches-joke--everyone-s-been-vaccinated--3991597</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/28/3991597/3991597_3E1E4BA4707C48F1B0502B8F0E9DDE15_200428_3991597_White_House_Hot_Mic_Catches_Joke___Everyone_s_Be_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 05:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991917</guid>
      <title>COVID-19 Outbreak Now Affecting Meat Industry</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The spread of coronavirus among employees in meat factories is forcing several meat production plants in the U.S. to shut down.<br/><br/>A report by the Associated Press explains that efforts from the meat industry in the United States to curtail the spread of the virus among their employees have resulted in slower meat production which will eventually result in less meat in the market and higher prices for the meat that is available.<br/><br/>Pork production has been the most affected. According to the report, 15 of America's largest pork-packaging plants are responsible for 60 percent of all processed pork produced in the U.S.<br/><br/>This means that when one shuts down, overall pork production is severely affected. As of last week, pork processing capacity has dropped 25 percent.<br/><br/>The Associated Press reports the U.S. Department of Agriculture expects beef to rise in price by between one to two percent, poultry by 1.5 percent and pork between two and three percent.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/covid-19-outbreak-now-affecting-meat-industry-3991917</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/29/3991917/3991917_A12EA9AE01384F5DBFC0F25C919F245D_200429_3991917_COVID_19_Outbreak_Now_Affecting_Meat_Industry_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 01:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992065</guid>
      <title>Politician Quits After Tossing His Cat in Zoom Meeting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VALLEJO, CALIFORNIA <br/> The coronavirus has inadvertently thrown Zoom <br/> the video conference app <br/> into the spotlight, but recently, all for the wrong reasons.<br/><br/>You see, as more and more companies rely on the platform to keep their human cogs churning, the chances only increase that sooner or later someone screws up for all to see. <br/><br/>This is Chris Platzer, a planning commissioner from California's Vallejo and he's made headlines for launching his cat off-screen. <br/><br/>In the now-viral video of the Planning Commission teleconference on April 20th, Platzer says, 'I'd like to introduce my cat' and then, out of nowhere, tosses his kitty off-screen.<br/><br/>The Times-Herald reported that the planning commissioner was also spotted taking sips from a green bottle; and in the original footage released by the Northern California city, he was also heard making degrading comments, 'I'm going to call bullsh** on you little bit**s.'<br/><br/>Just in time before the City Council was set to remove him from his post, Platzer sent an email on Saturday, saying he had stepped down from the seven-person panel.<br/><br/>'I did not conduct myself in the Zoom meeting in a manner befitting of a planning commissioner and apologize for any harm I may have inflicted.'<br/><br/>'I serve at the pleasure of the council and no longer have that trust and backing. I extend my gratitude to those who have supported me during my tenure. I have always felt that serving Vallejo in a voluntary position is honorable because Vallejo is worth serving. We are all living in uncertain times and I certainly, like many of you, am adjusting to a new normalcy.'<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/politician-quits-after-tossing-his-cat-in-zoom-meeting-3992065</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/29/3992065/3992065_9359EE34DC0642E5B31AF65EA4552922_200429_3992065_Politician_Quits_After_Tossing_His_Cat_in_Zoom_M_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 07:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
