<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3971082</guid>
      <title>U.S. orders China fake news to cut U.S. staff in America by 40%</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The Trump administration has ordered four Chinese state-owned fake news media outlets to trim their Chinese staff in the U.S. by about 40 percent.  <br/>Bloomberg reports that measures are seen as a response to Beijing's restrictions on American reporters including the booting of three Wall Street Journal writers last month. <br/>According to two State Department officials talking to Bloomberg, starting on March 13, the four fake outlets will be allowed to have a combined 100 Chinese citizens in the U.S., down from around 160 now. <br/>Too bad that's still 100 too many Chinese spies for each Chinese state speakerbox. <br/>The pretend news outlets affected are Xinhua News Agency, China Global Television Network, China Radio International and China Daily Distribution Corp. <br/><br/>A fifth, Hai Tian Development USA, is also included in the cap, but they only have two Chinese employees on its U.S. payroll. So who are all these sellout Americans working for Hai Tian?<br/>According to another senior administration official, the U.S. also plans to limit how long Chinese citizens are allowed to stay in the country on journalist visas. <br/><br/>That would match a Chinese requirement restricting foreign reporters to as little as 30 days before they must seek an extension.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-orders-china-fake-news-to-cut-u-s-staff-in-america-by-40--3971082</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/04/3971082/3971082_7D628B7A08D149B9B0A86EFCF29D83E6_200304_3971082_U_S__orders_China_fake_news_to_cut_U_S__staff_in_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 05:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971024</guid>
      <title>Sleeping man trapped by car crashing into his bedroom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIVERSIDE, CALIFORNIA <br/> A man was asleep in his bed when a car outside swerved off the road, knocked down a utility pole, drove through two front yards and came to a crashing stop through his bedroom wall at 1 a.m.<br/><br/>The incident on Saturday the 29th of February saw the man pinned between the vehicle and a wall of his house and had to be rescued by firefighters.<br/><br/>As he was trapped between a car and a hard place, he had to be removed with the 'jaws of life'.<br/><br/>Fortunately, the man avoided serious injuries and went to the hospital in minor condition.<br/><br/>Speaking to the Southern California News Group, Fire Department Battalion Chief Bruce Vanderhorst said, "He got very lucky." <br/><br/>The Police arrested a 22-year-old man, on suspicion of DUI, while the passenger was arrested on suspicion of public intoxication; both escaped injury, but not the law. <br/><br/>The fire department said that four people were living in the destroyed house, which was rendered uninhabitable. <br/><br/>According to their report, the total damage cost was a huge $200,000. <br/><br/>That'll wake anyone up.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sleeping-man-trapped-by-car-crashing-into-his-bedroom-3971024</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/04/3971024/3971024_7E50C81FEBB84028A8F93530D244E035_200304_3971024_Sleeping_man_trapped_by_car_crashing_into_his_be_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 03:14:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971532</guid>
      <title>Astronomers spot biggest space explosion since the Big Bang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Astronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by x-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.<br/><br/>According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.<br/><br/>The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.<br/><br/>BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. <br/><br/>A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.<br/><br/>The study's lead author Simona Giacintucci at the Naval Research Laboratory is cited by MIT Technology Review as saying the cavity is so large that 15 Milky Way galaxies could fit inside its volume in a row.<br/><br/>According to co-author Professor Melanie Johnston-Hollitt at the Murchison Widefield Array, the gap is so vast that light traveling across its distance from one end will not reach the other for 1.5 million years.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/astronomers-spot-biggest-space-explosion-since-the-big-bang-3971532</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/05/3971532/3971532_9DECB05DD19242D3AE1A96762A742015_200305_3971532_Astronomers_spot_biggest_space_explosion_since_t_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 05:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971451</guid>
      <title>Shoving a potato up the poop shoot won't cure hemorrhoids</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> When your backdoor is burning from a bad case of piles, what do you do when there's no Preparation H laying around? Home remedies of course. <br/>According to Vice, the UK edition of Reader's Digest decided to write up a list of nine home remedies for treating hemorrhoids. <br/>Some ideas the magazine suggests include nestling a warm teabag right against your backdoor while sitting on the can. <br/>Then there's also slathering on some Vicks Vaporub around the outside of your bum orifice.<br/>Apparently, grating up a raw potato and holding it against your rear entrance also works. <br/>You know one thing that doesn't work? Shoving an entire frozen potato wedge up the backside like WalesOnline suggests. <br/>According to the website, inserting a frozen potato slice into the poop shoot for 30 seconds several times of three to five days will clear those piles right up. <br/>It's pretty clear from the article that whomever wrote it, isn't a medical professional. Meanwhile, actual doctors are telling people not to do it. <br/>So who are you going to trust? WalesOnline or some know-it-all-doctor?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/shoving-a-potato-up-the-poop-shoot-won-t-cure-hemorrhoids-3971451</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/05/3971451/3971451_CD2C0D3D7B4E4443954BC498130C31F3_200305_3971451_Shoving_a_potato_up_the_poop_shoot_won_t_cure_he_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 02:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971618</guid>
      <title>Astronomers spot biggest space explosion since the Big Bang</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Astronomers say they caught a glimpse of the biggest explosion in the cosmos ever observed by x-ray and radio telescopes. The huge eruption occurred in the Ophiuchus cluster, a constellation of galaxies 390 light years distant from Earth in the Virgo Cluster.<br/><br/>According to the paper that will be published in The Astrophysics Journal, a supermassive black hole in the core of the cluster's central galaxy had expelled matter and energy so violently that it smashed a vast hole in the surrounding gas.<br/><br/>The black hole created jets that accelerated electrons to nearly the speed of light, which resulted in radio waves that filled the cavity left in the eruption's wake.<br/><br/>BBC reports astronomers first noticed something strange with the cluster's central galaxy when NASA's Chandra X-ray Observatory telescope in 2016 saw the unusual curve of its edge. <br/><br/>A second science team later used the data from radio telescopes to confirm that a black hole had blasted the cavity into existence by tracking the radio plasma in the gap.<br/><br/>The study's lead author Simona Giacintucci at the Naval Research Laboratory is cited by MIT Technology Review as saying the cavity is so large that 15 Milky Way galaxies could fit inside its volume in a row.<br/><br/>According to co-author Professor Melanie Johnston-Hollitt at the Murchison Widefield Array, the gap is so vast that light traveling across its distance from one end will not reach the other for 1.5 million years.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/astronomers-spot-biggest-space-explosion-since-the-big-bang-3971618</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/05/3971618/3971618_B1162F21599746A48641CD77C2B40104_200305_3971618_Astronomers_spot_biggest_space_explosion_since_t_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 07:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971972</guid>
      <title>Tito's Vodka asks you to stop using their vodka to make hand sanitizer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS <br/> Amid the shortage of hand sanitizers, Tito's Vodka, or 'America's Original Craft Vodka' is being used as a substitute, but the company wants you to stop. <br/><br/>They took to Twitter today to urge people to stop using its product to make their own hand sanitizer after several people on the platform have referenced a misinformed recipe that surfaced online. <br/><br/>The formula claims that vodka can be mixed with aloe vera gel and essential oils to make homemade hand sanitizer.<br/><br/>The Texas-based company wants you to know, as does common sense, that, "per the CDC, hand sanitizer needs to contain at least 60% alcohol. Tito's Handmade Vodka is 40% alcohol, and therefore does not meet the current recommendation of the CDC."<br/><br/>A Tito's spokesperson spoke to The Daily Beast saying, "while it would be good for business for our fans to use massive quantities of Tito's for hand sanitizer, it would be a shame to waste the good stuff, especially if it doesn't sanitize."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tito-s-vodka-asks-you-to-stop-using-their-vodka-to-make-hand-sanitizer-3971972</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/06/3971972/3971972_BF180626F7D1436898833F14A737294A_200306_3971972_Tito_s_Vodka_asks_you_to_stop_using_their_vodka__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 04:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971924</guid>
      <title>1.5 billion-year-old Earth was a 'Waterworld'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO <br/>  New evidence from Iowa State University and the University of Colorado suggests that 1.5 billion years ago, the planet was covered by a vast ocean and had no continents.<br/><br/>Published in Nature Geoscience, the research examined more than 100 ancient samples of seafloor, located now in the outback of northwestern Australia. Its rocky scenery of craggy seafloor preserves a hydrothermal system dating back 3.2 billion years.<br/><br/>Lead study author, Benjamin Johnson told Live Science that when the Earth was 1.5 billion years old, the ocean had high levels of isotope oxygen-18.<br/><br/>Their computer models showed that continental landmasses leach oxygen-18 from the oceans, but in the ancient samples, he observed an abundance of it. <br/><br/>So, in the absence of continents, the oceans would carry more oxygen-18, which implies a "Waterworld."<br/><br/>The continents appeared later, as plate tectonics drove enormous, rocky landmasses upward to breach the sea surfaces. <br/><br/>The prospect of an ancient Waterworld Earth also offers a new perspective on another intriguing question: where the planet's earliest forms of life appeared and how they evolved.<br/><br/>Questions the team hopes to answer.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/1-5-billion-year-old-earth-was-a-waterworld--3971924</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/06/3971924/3971924_BA6C69C5820245EB8EFAE578AEDC5385_200306_3971924_1_5_billion_year_old_Earth_was_a__Waterworld__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 00:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976120</guid>
      <title>Fast moo-ving cow on the loose, wanted by police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PEMBROKE PINES, FLORIDA <br/> A deceptively fast moo-ving cow is on the loose in sunny Florida, which police have been trying weeks to catch.<br/>According to the Associated Press, the Pembroke Pines Police Department on Wednesday said the heifer was seen near Interstate 75 in southern Broward County. <br/>Apparently it's been on the lam since late January. <br/>The police tweeted out a photo titled "Wanted Unknown Cow" with the caption, "Description: Female cow. Brown with a white head. Faster than it looks. Talented fence jumper. Enjoys pool." Sounds kind of like a Tinder profile.<br/>Police spokeswoman Amanda Conwell said cops and wranglers have not been able to catch the animal and have backed off when it gets too close to roads with a lot of traffic. <br/>Authorities also say the cow is guilty of "MOOving violations, uddering false checks, and fleeing and eluding police."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/fast-moo-ving-cow-on-the-loose-wanted-by-police-3976120</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/17/3976120/3976120_A931D51DE7E34D36ABA1DB55692399AE_200317_3976120_Fast_moo_ving_cow_on_the_loose__wanted_by_police_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 05:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976586</guid>
      <title>Amazon seller who stockpiled 17,700 bottles of hand sanitizer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHATTANOOGA, TENNESSEE <br/> Matt Colvin, an Amazon seller from Tennessee bought 17,700 bottles of hand sanitizer, ready to exploit and profit from a pandemic. <br/><br/>After the first fatality of the Coronavirus in the U.S, Matt's brother, Noah drove 1,300 miles across Tennessee and Kentucky, filling a U-Haul truck with thousands of bottles of hand sanitizer and anti-bacterial wipes. <br/><br/>Meanwhile, Matt prepared for pallets of even more wipes and sanitizer and started listing them on Amazon, where he sold 300 bottles immediately for between $8 and $70, saying, "it was crazy money."<br/><br/>The next day, Amazon kicked his items off the shelf and warned others too, 'if you keep running up prices, you'll lose your accounts.' eBay soon followed in tow and enforced even stricter rules, banning any U.S. sales of masks or sanitizer. <br/><br/>Mr. Colvin is now sitting on a stash he can't shift, and people like Mikeala Kozlowski, a nurse in Massachusetts, have been searching for hand sanitizer since before she gave birth to her first child; now she says she can't buy any in-store and could only find them listed on Amazon for around $50. <br/><br/>He says, "It's been a huge amount of whiplash. From being in a situation where what I've got coming and going could potentially put my family in a really good place financially to 'What the heck am I going to do with all of this?'"<br/><br/>Amazon said, "Price gouging is a clear violation of our policies, unethical, and in some areas, illegal. In addition to terminating these third party accounts, we welcome the opportunity to work directly with state attorneys general to prosecute bad actors."<br/><br/>According to The Times, Tennessee has a price-gouging law that bars people from charging "unreasonable prices for essential goods and services, including gasoline, in direct response to a disaster."<br/><br/>On Saturday, after The New York Times published this story, the Tennessee attorney general's office said it had sent investigators to Mr. Colvin's home, given him a cease-and-desist letter and was now investigating his case.<br/><br/>Of course, Mr. Colvin does not believe he was price gouging, despite the fact he charged $20 on Amazon for two bottles of Purell that retail for $1 each. <br/><br/>Mr. Colvin has since stated he was exploring ways to donate all of his supplies.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-seller-who-stockpiled-17-700-bottles-of-hand-sanitizer-3976586</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976586/3976586_F4DA753839554951849DBBAAAA051864_200318_3976586_Amazon_seller_who_stockpiled_17_700_bottles_of_h_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 05:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977135</guid>
      <title>Floating US Navy hospital coming to New York</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK CITY<br/> New York's getting a floating hospital to deal with the coronavirus, reports CNN.<br/><br/>According to Fox 5 New York, the US Navy will deploy two hospital ships to the country's east and west coasts over the coming weeks. The USNS Comfort is headed to New York City Harbor.<br/><br/>The vessels will not treat COVID-19 patients. They will instead focus on the overflow of other cases from local hospitals.<br/><br/>According to Popular Mechanics, the Mercy class ships are 272.5m long and have a beam of 32.2m. They can be staffed by 1,200 medical staff, 70 crew members and other specialists.         <br/><br/>Popular Mechanics reports that both ships also contain around 1,000 beds for patients and 12 operating rooms. They can also receive patients via helicopter or boat. The ships are outfitted with a pharmacy, medical laboratory and radiology equipment.<br/><br/>Citing New York Governor Andrew Cuomo, Fox 5 New York reports that the USNS Comfort will arrive in the state around mid-April.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/floating-us-navy-hospital-coming-to-new-york-3977135</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/19/3977135/3977135_E5BB222829BE440BAF5902F22F918368_200319_3977135_Floating_US_Navy_hospital_coming_to_New_York_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 08:27:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978187</guid>
      <title>Trump signs $1B bill to replace Huawei equipment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> President Donald Trump signed a bill into law last Thursday that will fork over $1 billion to help small telecom providers get rid of all their Huawei and ZTE Chinese garbage. <br/>AP reports that the U.S. government considers the Chinese companies a security risk because of their close ties to the CCP. <br/>Both companies have denied that China uses their junk for spying. Good thing China and Chinese companies have a great track record when it comes to telling the truth. <br/>According to the AP, the FCC has already voted to bar U.S. phone companies from using government subsidies to buy Huawei and ZTE contraptions. <br/>This bill will mostly affect small, rural companies because the major U.S. network providers don't use Chinese equipment. <br/>The law creates a reimbursement program that small telecom providers can use when tossing out made in China spy crap. <br/>In a statement the White House said, "The administration will not risk subjecting  America's critical telecommunications infrastructure to companies that are controlled by authoritarian governments or foreign adversaries."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-signs-1b-bill-to-replace-huawei-equipment-3978187</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/22/3978187/3978187_65A0581CE0BE4DD58BE5E79C60874958_200322_3978187_Trump_signs__1B_bill_to_replace_Huawei_equipment_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 04:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978441</guid>
      <title>Costco will not take back your hoarded TP or bottled water</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MURICA <br/> Now that Americans have hoarded enough toilet paper and bottle water to last until the end of humanity, Costco has announced that it won't let you return these items.  <br/>According to Today, signs are starting to pop up at several Costco locations saying that they will not be accepting returns for high-demand things like toilet paper, bottled water and sanitizing wipes. <br/>Today reports that several Instagram accounts that follow Costco news, but not affiliated with the company, have posted different signs at many locations listing items that can not be returned. <br/>Some of the lists include products like, toilet paper, paper towels, sanitizing wipes, water, rice and Lysol. <br/>Today says it's unclear if this is a company-wide policy, or one that has been started by stores in individual locations. <br/>Empty shelves have been seen across the country as panic buying has gone viral due to the spread of the Xi Jinping Virus-19.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/costco-will-not-take-back-your-hoarded-tp-or-bottled-water-3978441</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/23/3978441/3978441_CEE59125A3124B9AA9E26FB83833B97D_200323_3978441_Costco_will_not_take_back_your_hoarded_TP_or_bot_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 02:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978578</guid>
      <title>Start-up wants to track COVID-19 via your poop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON <br/> Massachusetts-based Biobot Analytics has launched a program to test community sewers for COVID-19.<br/><br/><br/><br/>According to Popular Mechanics, the virus can live in human waste. Biobot Analytics aim to track and trace COVID-19 by having communities use their devices to collect samples over a 24-hour period.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The company will analyze the data collected and use it to report their findings to impacted areas. If it works, the company says on its website that it will give communities a dynamic map of the virus as it spreads to new areas.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/start-up-wants-to-track-covid-19-via-your-poop-3978578</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/23/3978578/3978578_BFB5DC02498E46E88143E8ACDA442729_200323_3978578_Start_up_wants_to_track_COVID_19_via_your_poop_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 08:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979422</guid>
      <title>Man facing terror charge over alleged coronavirus cough threat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANALAPAN, NEW JERSEY <br/> A New Jersey man is in major trouble this week after allegedly coughing on a woman and telling that her he was infected with the coronavirus, Reuters reports. <br/><br/>According to NJ.com, 50 year-old George Falcone was at the prepared foods section of a Wegmans Grocers on Sunday night when a female staff member asked him to take a few steps back.<br/><br/>Prosecutors say Falcone then stepped close to the woman and began coughing and laughing. He allegedly told her he had the coronavirus.<br/><br/>NJ.com reports that Falcone then told two other workers that they were lucky to be employed. But, he told Reuters via a Facebook message that he didn't cough or say that he had the coronavirus.<br/><br/>He's been charged with making terroristic threats, obstruction and harassment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-facing-terror-charge-over-alleged-coronavirus-cough-threat-3979422</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/25/3979422/3979422_978FA9C9423F4AE596D84B59F5197104_200325_3979422_Man_facing_terror_charge_over_alleged_coronaviru_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 08:16:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979849</guid>
      <title>Are container ship exhaust fumes delaying climate change?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE <br/> New research suggests that exhaust fumes from container ships could be delaying the effects of climate change.<br/><br/>According to the University of Washington, exhaust fumes from container ships have sulfate particles that attract water molecules. These transform into cloud droplets that can pack clouds and, in turn, reflect solar radiation before it warms the ocean. <br/><br/>Researchers looked at satellite data from one of the busiest Atlantic shipping lanes from between 2003 and 2015. They calculated what the lane would've looked like with emissions and without. They say that the difference helps to clarify how much industrial pollution influences clouds.<br/><br/>The University of Washington posits that without the cooling effect of these sulfate particles the Earth may have already heated by 1.5 degrees Celsius. This is a change deemed to have significant societal impacts by the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/are-container-ship-exhaust-fumes-delaying-climate-change--3979849</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/26/3979849/3979849_F0ADCFC9077842AAB58AD3C2171941BA_200326_3979849_Are_container_ship_exhaust_fumes_delaying_climat_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 08:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3980385</guid>
      <title>U.S. will waive environmental laws to build border wall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Donald Trump's new plans to quicken the construction of the border wall poses a great threat to biodiversity and the environment, and in particular the jaguar.<br/><br/>On March 16, the Department of Homeland Security announced it will waive a number of environmental laws and regulations to accelerate the construction of border walls in Pima, Santa Cruz and Cochise counties in Arizona. <br/><br/>According to the Center for Biological Diversity, parts of the new border walls will run through remote natural environments and block jaguars from migrating between Mexico and the southwestern U.S.<br/><br/>They will also isolate a small breeding population of northern jaguars in Sonora, Mexico <br/> hindering repopulation efforts.<br/><br/>The jaguar is the largest cat in the Americas and one of the four big cats of the Panthera genus, the others being the lion, tiger and leopard.<br/><br/>Inhabitat reports other animals that will be negatively impacted by the new border walls are the Mexican gray wolf, the lesser long-nosed bat, the ocelot, the Sonoran pronghorn and the cactus ferruginous pygmy owl.<br/><br/><br/>A 2017 report by the Center for Biological Diversity states that: 'a minimum of 93 species at risk of extinction will be further imperiled by construction of Trump's border wall, including impacts to critical habitat for 25 of these species.']]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-will-waive-environmental-laws-to-build-border-wall-3980385</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/27/3980385/3980385_E96276AC9F104E4C9AE8D836AB593E52_200327_3980385_U_S__will_waive_environmental_laws_to_build_bord_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 10:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
