<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 18:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3914843</guid>
      <title>Deadspin writers quit en masse over 'stick to sports' memo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> Most of the staff at Deadspin have unfortunately said adios in an open revolt against a top brass mandate to stick to sports.<br/>USA Today reported that the resignations came at the end of a contentious few months between staff and douchey new ownership. <br/>According to the New York Post, trouble started on Monday after the editorial director of Deadspin's parent company, G/O Media, issued a staff memo to "write only about sports and that which is relevant to sports in some way."<br/>So in typical Deadspin fashion, the editorial staff began filling the site with exclusively non-sports stories. <br/>Then on Tuesday, Deadspin deputy director Barry Petchesky said that he'd been axed for not following the directive. <br/>Petchesky tweeted, "Hi, I've just been fired from Deadspin for not sticking to sports." <br/>The Washington Post reported that this then led to close to a dozen Deadspin writers and editors announcing their resignations over Twitter in protest on Wednesday and Thursday. <br/>According to Business Insider, shortly after that the Gizmodo Media Group issued a statement over Twitter accusing the company's CEO, Jim Spanfeller, of "curtailing [Deadspin's] most well-read coverage because it makes him personally uncomfortable."   <br/><br/>Many long time readers, sports nutz and fellow journalists have all taken to Twitter to commend the former Deadspin staff for their integrity and courage. <br/>Apparently in an attempt to deaden the backlash, G/O has shut off all comments on Deadspin. <br/>Maybe it's time for a name change<br/>perhaps just call it DEAD from now on.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/deadspin-writers-quit-en-masse-over-stick-to-sports-memo-3914843</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61C/228/61C2288973831BF127A61704443B3E32.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914843/3914843_FA082C7159C142699663F3DF59F44D2E_191101_3914843_Deadspin_writers_quit_en_masse_over__stick_to_sp_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 11:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916142</guid>
      <title>Measles could give your 
Immune system amnesia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON <br/> Scientists have found that measles is a lot more devastating to the immune system than previously thought.<br/><br/>According to the WHO, measles is a highly contagious airborne disease caused by a virus in the paramyxoviridae family.<br/><br/>Symptoms of a measles infection usually include a cough, fever, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash erupts on the face and neck after several days, and spreads to the rest of the body over the next three to four days.<br/><br/>The Guardian reports that the body has two key lines of immune response in dealing with viruses. Memory B-cells remember previous infections the body has had before and protects against them. Naive B-cells, meanwhile, defend against new infections.<br/><br/>A study published in the journal Science Immunology found that measles wipes out a substantial number of memory cells reduces the diversity of the naive b-cells.<br/><br/>This causes 'immune amnesia', where the immune system to forget how to respond to infections, leaving the body vulnerable to other diseases.<br/><br/>Another study published in Science looked at antibodies in the blood of unvaccinated children in the Netherlands before and after a measles infection.<br/><br/>They found that the measles destroyed 11 to 78% of the children's antibody memory bank.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, babies are born with limited antibodies that become more varied as they grow older.<br/><br/>Measles resets the immune system to an immature, baby-like state, with only a narrow range of antibodies to work with, and a limited ability to fight off new infections.<br/><br/>A way to avoid this is by getting the MMR vaccine, which eliminates the risk of catching a measles infection. Revaccination also helps with those whose immune system memories have already been ravaged by the disease.<br/><br/>Bottom line, please vaccinate your kids.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/measles-could-give-your-%0Aimmune-system-amnesia-3916142</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D8F/114/D8F114854AA493BA8B8758335B5E3AB2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3916142/3916142_A51F82FD54CA454D8CFB026244878D24_191104_3916142_Measles_could_give_your__Immune_system_amnesia_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 15:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916599</guid>
      <title>TSA stopped a guy after finding a toilet-paper roller 'gun' in his bag</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWARK, NEW JERSEY <br/> A man trying to ROLL his way through a TSA checkpoint at the Newark Liberty International Airport found it a bit harder to PASS through than usual. <br/>Whoever is writing the local press releases at the TSA deserves a big fat raise for this piece titled, "How not to roll through a checkpoint&#8230;" <br/>It appears that on October 29, an unidentified man was trying to pass security when TSA agents spotted a revolver in his carry-on bag. <br/>According to CNN, after a closer inspection, agents were relieved to find out it was only a gun-shaped toilet paper holder. <br/>The TSA then DUMPED this line, "yes, this most unusual revolver was not designed to spin bullets. It was designed to spin toilet paper." <br/>CNN reported that the TP roller triggered an alarm as it went through the X-ray machine. <br/>The agency said, "TSA does not permit travelers to bring real or replica firearms through a checkpoint." <br/>The guy was given a few options: take the roller back to his car, put it in his checked luggage, give it to a friend not traveling, or gift it to the TSA.<br/>He chose to give it to his pals at the TSA. Hopefully someone there can do some damage with it.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tsa-stopped-a-guy-after-finding-a-toilet-paper-roller-gun-in-his-bag-3916599</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/691/944/691944504831C30540706DBFDC74E1E5.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916599/3916599_AD103C332E0C461EA0B00B8292A69F18_191105_3916599_TSA_stopped_a_guy_after_finding_a_toilet_paper_r_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 13:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916807</guid>
      <title>Trump's 'virtually impenetrable' border wall foiled by $100 saw</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> What does it take to break into a big, beautiful wall? Apparently not very much.<br/><br/>According to the Washington Post, the new border wall system U.S. President Trump is building features steel and concrete bollards up to 30 feet tall, and concrete foundation that defeats tunneling.<br/><br/>U.S. Customs and Border Protection tweeted on October 24 that it has built 75 miles of Trump's new border wall and aims to finish 450 miles by 2020. <br/><br/>The Post reports that although Trump called the wall "virtually impenetrable," smugglers have been able to cut through with cordless power saws costing as little as US$100.<br/><br/>They go through the resulting gap one at a time and often move the damaged bollards back in place for future crossings.<br/><br/>U.S. officials confirmed that there have been multiple breaches, but added that smugglers targeted sections of the wall not yet equipped with electronic vibration sensors.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that when it is completed, Trump's border wall will feature steel barriers, all weather roads, cameras, and other technology.<br/><br/>According to the Washington Post, the wall has cost US$10 billion so far.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-s-virtually-impenetrable-border-wall-foiled-by-100-saw-3916807</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C37/EB9/C37EB9A6E1D80EBFD3478BDD761E7985.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3916807/3916807_8B1D0EE9099F4C7BAE2B6AFF784F49DC_191106_3916807_Trump_s__virtually_impenetrable__border_wall_foi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 03:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917088</guid>
      <title>Man wanted for running 'bootleg' zoo with hundreds of animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROMULUS, MICHIGAN <br/> Law enforcement in Michigan have issued a felony warrant against this man, Javon Pherras Stacks, for alleged animal cruelty, abandonment and neglect following a police raid that seized over 500 animals from a "bootleg zoo" at a Romulus storefront.<br/><br/>According to the Romulus Police Department, officials found a ton of animals including rabbits, iguanas, a peacock, a python, kangaroos and hedgehogs at the fake zoo two months ago. They were tipped off by a concerned resident who helped officials locate the animals.<br/><br/>After seizing the animals, the police conducted a thorough investigation and have now issued a felony warrant for the 36-year-old.<br/><br/>The police said all the animals were given to experts who can take care of them properly.<br/><br/>In a Facebook post, officials told the public to contact the police department if anyone knows where Stacks is, or encourage him to turn himself in.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-wanted-for-running-bootleg-zoo-with-hundreds-of-animals-3917088</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/492/26B/49226B713C9281A545D2F36B2AB103ED.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3917088/3917088_6C20DCA2771F43CF950115EFD36BF9AD_191106_3917088_Man_wanted_for_running__bootleg__zoo_with_hundre_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 11:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916895</guid>
      <title>Fake cop arrested by real cops after chasing suspect vehicle</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WILSON, NORTH CAROLINA <br/> Police in North Carolina have arrested a man after he impersonated a cop and joined in on the chase after a potential murder suspect.<br/><br/>Wilson police conducted a traffic stop on October 5 at a Food Mart to apprehend a suspect, WNCN reports. <br/><br/>As soon as the occupants of the car noticed officers approaching, they fled the scene.<br/><br/>The police gave chase when suddenly a Ford Taurus with blue lights drove past the police car, past the suspects' car and cornered the suspect's vehicle between his Taurus and the police car.<br/><br/>The man in the Taurus, David Adams Jr., got out of his car and, at gunpoint, ordered the driver of the suspect vehicle to exit his car. Four other passengers exited the suspect vehicle.<br/><br/>Adams handcuffed one of the suspects and began searching him. The real police officers had their doubts and ordered him to stop.<br/><br/>Adams then left the scene without speaking to the police officers. The police later determined that Adams was not a sworn law enforcement officer and obtained a warrant to arrest him.<br/><br/>After searching the suspect vehicle, officers found a handgun, an assortment of pills and US$708.<br/><br/>Real police officers then arrested all five passengers in the suspect vehicle. One of the men in the car was the brother of the murder suspect they were looking for.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/fake-cop-arrested-by-real-cops-after-chasing-suspect-vehicle-3916895</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/84D/93F/84D93F1B611F189E662306696B90D790.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3916895/3916895_EEE04635FBF64FC1B2030E8763DED19B_191106_3916895_Fake_cop_arrested_by_real_cops_after_chasing_sus_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 07:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917322</guid>
      <title>Researchers to pay people $3,300 to be infected with H1N1</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARYLAND <br/> Getting sick with the flu could get you a couple of Gs from scientists eager to study the pesky little virus.<br/><br/>According to WBALTV, researchers at the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases are looking for volunteers to participate in a flu study, for the generous sum of $3,300.<br/><br/>All participants need to do is get the H1N1 virus sprayed up their sniffer, and stay a week in an inpatient facility until they stop being infectious.<br/><br/>During that time, researchers are hoping to glean as much information as they can from the sneezing, heaving, feverish virus-filled volunteers. Sounds like a lovely time.<br/><br/>Curiously, there's not much info about treatment, but it's a medical facility <br/> surely they'll administer one...right?<br/><br/>Guess there's at least the sweet sweet cash. Worth it?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-to-pay-people-3-300-to-be-infected-with-h1n1-3917322</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F17/662/F176627829300DD7C4EF2C7725B49617.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/07/3917322/3917322_62CA1990D11541D4B83866BECE756880_191107_3917322_Researchers_to_pay_people__3_300_to_be_infected__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 02:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919496</guid>
      <title>Michael Bloomberg warming up for 2020 White House race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALABAMA <br/> Looks like the Democratic race for the White House in 2020 just became a little less of a snoozefest as billionaire former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg signals he's ready to rumble<br/>maybe.<br/><br/>According to the failing New York Times, Bloomberg submitted paperwork last Friday ahead of a deadline to enter the 2020 presidential primary in Alabama.<br/>The move is a necessary step to join the scramble to take on the Teflon Don in next year's election. <br/>The 77-year-old towering giant has yet to formally announce his candidacy, but many of his friends and allies say he intends to throw down. <br/>That's because he apparently thinks the current Democratic candidates all suck. He may be right.<br/>The overstuffed Democratic field currently has hands on Joe Biden, Native-American Elizabeth Warren and heart stopping Sanders leading the pack.<br/>The problem with Biden is that he's a borderline idiot, while Warren and Sanders are way too progressive for the average U.S. voter. <br/>As for Trump, he told reporters on Friday that, "there is nobody I'd rather run against than little Michael."<br/><br/>Well<br/>if the Democrats continue on their current trajectory, Trump may just get his wish.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/michael-bloomberg-warming-up-for-2020-white-house-race-3919496</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/040/5F3/0405F3E595394F8DE68582442A4FEAC2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/11/3919496/3919496_DE231FA0DF24473B99DA760C66D9756F_191111_3919496_Michael_Bloomberg_warming_up_for_2020_White_Hous_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 12:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919953</guid>
      <title>Speeding Porsche goes airborne into second story of building</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOMS RIVER, NEW JERSEY <br/> A speeding Porsche lost control and went airborne into the second story of an unoccupied New Jersey building.<br/><br/>According to CBS New York, two men are sadly no longer around after a freak morning accident on November 10.<br/><br/>Police say 22-year-old Branden DeMartin was driving a Porsche Boxster with 23-year-old Daniel Foley in the passenger seat. <br/>According to authorities, the sports car was traveling northbound on Hooper Avenue at Fast and Furious speeds. <br/>The car then appears to have lost control and crossed over the southbound lanes, before hitting the curb. <br/>The Porsche then started tumbling before hitting a ditch which launched it up into the second floor of an office building, landing upside down.  <br/>Police say it was around 6:30 a.m. when the vehicle and bodies were found. <br/><br/>CBS New York reported that firefighters and other responders pushed out bricks out of the way, so that a crane could lift the car out around noon. <br/>After the Boxster was towed away, investigators stayed on scene for several more hours.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/speeding-porsche-goes-airborne-into-second-story-of-building-3919953</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FCE/135/FCE1355BAE1FAEAEFB9AF8EA4A2F3EE5.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919953/3919953_4E4918EDAC3F4838A28E7AEF9A26B5B6_191112_3919953_Speeding_Porsche_goes_airborne_into_second_story_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 11:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919900</guid>
      <title>Popeyes workers spotting making chicken sandwich on trash can</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FAIRFAX, VIRGINIA <br/> As Popeyes chicken sandwich continues to cause chaos in overcrowded lines across America, it looks like things are pretty nuts behind the scenes as well. <br/>Stomach-gurgling photos obtained by TMZ show Popeyes workers at one restaurant in Fairfax actually putting the sandwiches together over a garbage can in the kitchen. <br/>TMZ reports that the snaps were taken last Friday and show one employee working like a maniac slapping them together on top of a tray that was resting on top of a trash can<br/>YUMMY!<br/>According to the owner of the franchise shop, the restaurant had only been open a few days, and then it happened to get hit with a 100 chicken sandwich order. <br/>The owner also tried to shift the blame, telling TMZ that all the employees were brand new and didn't know any better. He also said the trash bin was empty at the time. Oh<br/>that's reassuring.<br/>He has since ordered a table which arrived this week, so unfortunately, no more trash can chicken sandwiches.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/popeyes-workers-spotting-making-chicken-sandwich-on-trash-can-3919900</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C9E/917/C9E91730CB10EEBCD7F6BD0595F34DBB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919900/3919900_60CA842F618A4FDA8E5ED8682437C2CF_191112_3919900_Popeyes_workers_spotting_making_chicken_sandwich_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 10:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919803</guid>
      <title>Gender reveal party causes plane crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TUKEY, TEXAS <br/> An unnamed couple in West Texas chose innovation over safety when they used a crop-duster to reveal the gender of their baby on September 7th.<br/><br/>The intended plan was to pour 350 gallons of pink water by the gender reveal party, instead, the plane crashed. <br/><br/>According to an accident report by the National Transportation Safety Board, 49-year-old pilot and friend of the couple Raj Horan was flying at a low altitude with a passenger when the plane "got too slow" and stalled before crashing and flipping over.  <br/><br/>An inspector of the National Transportation Safety Board also noted that the aircraft wasn't designed to carry two people, and was actually a single-seat plane.<br/><br/>Pilot Raj Horan was not injured, however, his passenger Jennifer J. Hurrell suffered minor injuries.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/gender-reveal-party-causes-plane-crash-3919803</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F45/FC5/F45FC57A90FBBE2477FB110AD53A5D4A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919803/3919803_510B227A359845EAB6EDDD02FE0B32C6_191112_3919803_Gender_reveal_party_causes_plane_crash_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920421</guid>
      <title>Disney+ slammed with technical glitches on launch day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BURBANK, CALIFORNIA <br/> Disney launched its much anticipated online streaming service Disney+ on Tuesday in selected areas, only to be immediately slammed by technical glitches. <br/>BBC reports that social media was flooded with people complaining about problems accessing the site, while other users shared screenshots of Disney-themed error messages. <br/>According to glitch-tracker Down Detector, there were only 8,300 complaints about Disney+ issues over a 15-minute period starting at 9 a.m. Eastern Standard Time. <br/>Reuters reported that some people trying to get on Disney+ were instead treated to a Mickey Mouse on a blue screen, with a message telling them to exit the app and try again. <br/>According to Reuters, other users had trouble locating the Disney+ app in Apple's App Store.  <br/>Disney claims that the glitches were caused by excessive demand. <br/>Disney+ hasn't been rolled out worldwide yet. It's currently only available in the U.S., Canada and the Netherlands.<br/>The service costs $7 a month and features about 500 movies and 7,500 TV episodes. It was designed to take on Netflix and Amazon Prime. <br/>Disney said it was "working quickly" to fix all the glitches. Until then...Netflix anyone?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/disney%2B-slammed-with-technical-glitches-on-launch-day-3920421</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/62D/BB8/62DBB8AC38E2B9466A81B57CD1FFBC3F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920421/3920421_8B5EA542890D4C05965ABCF47B43F31D_191113_3920421_Disney__slammed_with_technical_glitches_on_launc_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920344</guid>
      <title>Michigan man uses battle ax to strike down home intruder</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KALAMAZOO, MICHIGAN <br/> A man in Michigan managed to hold his own during a home invasion thanks to some eccentric hobbies.<br/><br/>According to Wood TV, 36-year-old Ben Ball was playing video games in his Kalamazoo apartment late Wednesday night when someone who once dated his ex-roommate came knockin' and eventually kicked the door in.<br/><br/>Now, a more conventional American household would have a gun or baseball bat around to use as a weapon, but not Ben. Ben does ritualized combat for fun, and has an arsenal of replica weapons from the Middle Ages.<br/><br/>So when that intruder burst in, your man Ben thought fast and grabbed a battle ax replica that he calls "my baby." <br/><br/>He wielded it against the intruder, 33-year-old Alex Rawls, striking him once in the torso.<br/><br/>The pair then grappled with each other all around the apartment and pretty much destroyed the place before Rawls finally made a run for it.<br/><br/>Police who arrived at the scene deployed a K9 unit to follow the trail of blood that Rawls oh-so-conveniently left. <br/><br/>Kalamazoo County officials say Rawls' wounds were substantial enough that he had to spend a night at the hospital before being thrown to jail, and is now facing home invasion charges.<br/><br/>Officials say avoiding robbers or intruders is usually the best course of action for most folks. Not everyone does combat every weekend and has an arsenal of weapons stashed at home, but hey,  if you got the goods, use 'em.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/michigan-man-uses-battle-ax-to-strike-down-home-intruder-3920344</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/914/56D/91456DB7DF5FC389EF48C6A6396A933D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920344/3920344_780CF8CE728948BF9557B8FED1B30632_191113_3920344_Michigan_man_uses_battle_ax_to_strike_down_home__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 08:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920970</guid>
      <title>Homeless guy dumps bucket of hot mudbutt on L.A. woman</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES <br/> A woman had herself quite a crappy night after some random guy dumped a bucket of hot man-made chocolate sauce over her head. <br/>NBC Los Angeles reported that Heidi Van Tassel was getting into her car after dinner near the Hollywood Walk of Fame when it quickly turned into the walk of shame. <br/>According to NBC L.A., a male resident of the streets ran across Hollywood Boulevard and got her out of the vehicle, and into the middle of the street. <br/><br/>That's when he introduced a bucket of hot runny twos right onto her dome.<br/>Unfortunately, the human Hershey's syrup then got everywhere all because of some gravity. <br/>NBC Los Angeles reported that paramedics arrived and rushed Van Tassel to Hollywood Presbyterian Hospital where she was then tested for infectious diseases. <br/>She now needs to be retested every three months.  <br/>According to court records, the man with muddbutt was identified as Jere Blessings, and was charged with battery and taken to jail. <br/>However because he had mental issues, he was eventually assigned to a residential facility for treatment. He was released in August. <br/>As for Van Tassel, she says the incident has given her PTSD. In this case, guess that means post traumatic stress doo doo.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/homeless-guy-dumps-bucket-of-hot-mudbutt-on-l-a-woman-3920970</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CE1/882/CE1882CB1ED1E5D3D4AC2737EFD6556C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/14/3920970/3920970_0447E6AB62ED4CDB9A2D58A399F6CCA5_191114_3920970_Homeless_guy_dumps_bucket_of_hot_mudbutt_on_L_A__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 11:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920933</guid>
      <title>Murderer who briefly died says
his life sentence is now served</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IOWA <br/> 66-year-old Iowa inmate, Schreiber was sentenced to life without parole in 1997 for first-degree murder, but says since he died momentarily after falling ill, his life sentence is now served. <br/><br/>Schreiber developed large kidney stones back in March 2015 which led to septic poisoning. <br/><br/>Citing court documents, The Des Moines Register state that he was rushed to a local hospital where his heart was restarted five times.<br/><br/>In April 2018, he filed for post-conviction relief claiming that because he died at the hospital, his life sentence has already been served and therefore should be released immediately.<br/><br/>He goes on to say that he was sentenced to life without parole, "but not to life plus one day."<br/><br/>The district court found his claim "unpersuasive and without merit."<br/><br/>On Wednesday, the Iowa Court of Appeals backed the district court, agreeing that Benjamin Schreiber's sentence isn't up until a medical examiner declares he is deceased.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/murderer-who-briefly-died-says%0Ahis-life-sentence-is-now-served-3920933</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ED0/7B0/ED07B0719252401DBDD336146A8EF073.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/14/3920933/3920933_698303D5CCBA4874B067B9AC5EA50C7C_191114_3920933_Murderer_who_briefly_died_says_his_life_sentence_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 10:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3921206</guid>
      <title>Cat put in solitary after masterminding mass feline breakout</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#FreeQuilty #QuiltyNotGuilty #NoMoreDoors<br/><br/>HOUSTON, TEXAS <br/> A six-year old cat named Quilty was sentenced to solitary confinement at an animal shelter, according to CNN.<br/><br/>According to Friends for Life shelter, the cat's alleged crime was helping his oppressed feline brethren to escape the shelter.<br/><br/>Shelter staff said that the firebrand was accused of inciting mutiny among the aged internees of the senior cat room and orchestrating mass escape on multiple occasions.<br/><br/>Worse for his human jailors, Quilty is something of a feline Houdini.<br/><br/>According to staff, Quilty would jump then pull on the door handle to open the door, allowing 14 other cats to escape.<br/><br/>Quilty was nicknamed "Door Ninja" for his prowess at escape and also "Spicy A-hole."<br/><br/>The liberated cats would roam the facility until they were caught and surveillance footage later identified Quilty as the culprit.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cat-put-in-solitary-after-masterminding-mass-feline-breakout-3921206</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/052/8AD/0528AD2C26C41B508648A173473EBA0A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921206/3921206_503D8ADF8F224F66BEEAE6CB6CDB20A7_191115_3921206_Cat_put_in_solitary_after_masterminding_mass_fel_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 01:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3922826</guid>
      <title>Inmate with Popeyes chicken sandwich melts internet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST PALM BEACH, FLORIDA <br/> As the Popeyes chicken sandwich craze continues to sweep across the country, people have gone to increasingly impressive lengths to get their hands on it, none more so than Marcus J. Elliot. <br/>The Daily Mail reports that last week, 22-year-old Elliot, who goes by the social media handle Frank Gutta, went viral after images of him munching on an infamous Popeyes chicken sandwich send the internet into a meltdown. <br/>Images posted to Elliot's Facebook page and shared across Twitter shows the inmate sitting back in his cell on his cot enjoying the $3.99 chicken sandwich. <br/>In his Facebook stories, the captions say "trying to see what all the hype bout," and "Thanks Bae." <br/>The photos were shared on Twitter by a user on November 14 and has since racked up more than 67,000 likes and 23,000 retweets. <br/>Online records show that Eliot is doing time at the West Palm Beach Community Release Center, and is expected to get out in September 2020. <br/><br/>He is currently listed as being on the community watch, which means he's allowed to work in the community before returning back to the holding facility.  <br/>In the meantime, hopefully his bae will keep the supply of chicken sandwiches coming.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/inmate-with-popeyes-chicken-sandwich-melts-internet-3922826</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61C/0BC/61C0BC6385B0B2D058B34C3162DA70C0.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922826/3922826_B48454ACDBDD48C7B0F41568EE3279B1_191118_3922826_Inmate_with_Popeyes_chicken_sandwich_melts_inter_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 11:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923352</guid>
      <title>Popeyes worker fired for bringing son to make chicken sandwiches</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLONY, TEXAS <br/> Popeye's has been causing all types of commotion across the country as everyday Americans seem to be losing their minds all over a chicken sandwich. <br/>According to Inside Edition, the demand has been so intense that one Texas father decided to enlist the help of his family<br/>aka, his son. <br/>It appears the man took bring your son into work day a bit too literally after a customer captured footage of the tiny worker wearing a Popeyes apron helping prepare chicken in the kitchen. <br/>According to the customer, the Popeyes in question, located in the Dallas suburb of Colony, had a line out the door and was getting slammed with orders for the infamous chicken sandwich. <br/>Unfortunately for the father, there are those pesky federal and state child labor laws that forbid minors from working.<br/>Obviously those people working in the federal and state offices haven't tried the sandwich yet. <br/><br/>Too bad for the dad, he's now out of a job after the owner of the Popeyes franchise gave him the boot. <br/>Hey, at least they weren't making the chicken sandwich on top of a garbage can.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/popeyes-worker-fired-for-bringing-son-to-make-chicken-sandwiches-3923352</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/79B/44B/79B44B2F25D9148E713E18FEB8601525.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923352/3923352_22EB9CD3BE234030BC19F38A11ADE03A_191119_3923352_Popeyes_worker_fired_for_bringing_son_to_make_ch_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 11:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923420</guid>
      <title>Popeyes chicken sandwich is causing traffic mayhem in Jersey</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUTHERFORD, NEW JERSEY <br/> Traffic in Jersey is a heckuva lot more brutal than usual, and it's all thanks to the chicken sandwich everyone and their mother wants to get their hands on.<br/><br/>According to the Bergen Record, insane demand for the chicken sandwich at a Popeyes in Rutherford, New Jersey is causing traffic to back up all the way to a state highway. It's extra horrible during rush hour.<br/><br/>The location shares a single driveway with Starbucks, so it's always been a headache. But now that the caffeine junkies have been joined by chicken sandwich fanatics, it's a nasty migraine.<br/><br/>Rutherford police have had it, and put up an electronic sign outside the Popeyes that says "A sandwich isn't worth a ticket. Do not delay traffic."<br/><br/>Basically, people would rather wait a lifetime at the drive thru and inconvenience a whole city just so they don't have to get out of the car. Meanwhile, going inside and picking the sandwich up themselves takes all of 10 minutes.<br/><br/>For real, people need to get up, get going, and get over themselves. Some of us have places to be and better food to eat.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/popeyes-chicken-sandwich-is-causing-traffic-mayhem-in-jersey-3923420</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/25A/8AD/25A8ADAB806FF64CF7B0372D6CB494EE.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923420/3923420_4E2E07C8D4724941922A8B6FEB44AEE3_191119_3923420_Popeyes_chicken_sandwich_is_causing_traffic_mayh_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 14:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923403</guid>
      <title>Passenger shares snap of crusty feet hanging over headrest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE FRIENDLY SKIES <br/> An airline passenger posted a horrifyingly hilarious selfie of herself and a pair of stanky feet hanging over her headrest. <br/><br/>The image boarded Reddit last week with the caption, "This is the one thing I am most worried about before getting on a plane." <br/><br/>It has since taken off for some strange reason that we can't quite seem to put our foot on. <br/><br/>The photo shows an unidentified woman with someone's bare, slightly crusty, and dirty dogs resting conveniently on top of the headrest.  <br/>It's unclear what airline the funky feet photo was taken on, but it appears to be one that has seats.   <br/>Reddit users were quick to put their foot down in opposition to the appalling behavior with suggestions ranging from reasonable to hilarious.  <br/>But remember folks, next time you're flying, please keep your feet to yourself.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/passenger-shares-snap-of-crusty-feet-hanging-over-headrest-3923403</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B89/274/B892743BA87B37BDE469807D34904C9C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923403/3923403_5A1E05013CF24B1DB5A738697DB60E04_191119_3923403_Passenger_shares_snap_of_crusty_feet_hanging_ove_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 13:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923793</guid>
      <title>Man punches firefighters for taking too long to put out car fire</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS <br/> A man whose car was on fire went after two firefighters for being too slow to rescue his car.<br/><br/>According to the St. Louis Post-Dispatch, police got a call around 5:50 p.m. on November 15 that a car had caught on fire after crashing into another vehicle.<br/><br/>KMOV reports that firefighters arrived and began trying to put out the fire. But the owner of the burning car was impatient and thought they were doing it way too slowly, so what does he do? He starts punching two of them, because sure, that'll get 'em to do it MUCH faster.<br/><br/>Video taken by a witness shows the man being held down on the ground by firefighters. When he's let go, he lunges at them.<br/><br/>He then tries to throw a punch at one of the firefighters, who deftly ducks, and tackles the dude to the ground.<br/><br/>The man was taken into custody, but firefighters have said they didn't want him charged, and would like instead to see him get the help he needs.<br/><br/>That's gonna be a whole lotta counseling and anger management classes, but guy still lucked out with these good guys.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-punches-firefighters-for-taking-too-long-to-put-out-car-fire-3923793</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0B3/E0D/0B3E0D442D771F79439F5B79B16763F8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/20/3923793/3923793_4C6761684D234DAB99F698A0609A12F1_191120_3923793_Man_punches_firefighters_for_taking_too_long_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924009</guid>
      <title>Man arrested after shooting
at his own car that was stolen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLOOMINGTON, INDIANA <br/> Police arrested a man after he chased down his car that had been stolen and squeezed off a few at the fleeing thief.<br/><br/>37-year-old Paul Clark, was warming up his car outside his apartment Monday morning, but when he looked out of his window he saw his 2004 Chrysler 300 being stolen.<br/><br/>The incident occurred around 5:30 a.m with local police saying Clark then armed himself and grabbed the keys to his girlfriend's SUV.<br/><br/>Clark tracked the thief down to the Marathon gas station at East Winslow Road and South Walnut Street.<br/><br/>Citing Bloomington Police Department Captain Ryan Pedigo, Fox59 says Clark took aim and popped off 13 shots at the suspect before the criminal managed to flee once again.<br/><br/>Police later found the stolen Chrysler abandoned at a nearby apartment complex, they say, there was no blood inside and unfortunately, they didn't find the thief.<br/><br/>Several calls about the commotion alerted the cops to the Marathon station where officers recovered 13 shell casings.<br/><br/>Police later arrested Clark on charges of criminal recklessness with a deadly weapon, pointing a firearm and carrying a handgun without a license.<br/><br/>Captain Ryan Pedigo warns that Clark taking the law into his own hands could not have only seriously injured civilians but could have killed someone.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-arrested-after-shooting%0Aat-his-own-car-that-was-stolen-3924009</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7DA/E75/7DAE75A033EE0E19015809A3EE75A533.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/21/3924009/3924009_2D0270476C784A03AE73513ACC7B517B_191121_3924009_Man_arrested_after_shooting_at_his_own_car_that__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 02:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924868</guid>
      <title>Man was dead for 3 years before he was found in apartment</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DESOTO, TEXAS <br/> A Navy veteran who lived in Texas had been deceased for around three years before his body was discovered inside his apartment. <br/>According to WFAA, Ronald Wayne White had a job working for a defense contractor, which caused him to have to travel extensively. <br/>White, who would have been 51 when he died, had moved several times over the years but always kept in touch with his family. <br/>Three years ago, those calls suddenly stopped. Unfortunately, his mother in New York didn't have enough money to hire private investigators to help locate White. <br/>And because of his travel history, several police departments were unable to treat the case as a missing persons case. <br/><br/>Authorities say White's rent was automatically withdrawn from his bank account every month. <br/>Police told WFAA that White's body was discovered when apartment workers were investigating units where no water had been used for a long period of time. <br/>The third-floor apartment was new and had all the windows sealed. Inside the residence were diabetes medications dated 2016. <br/><br/>Police say there was zero indication of foul play. Toxicology tests have been ordered to determine his cause of death.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-was-dead-for-3-years-before-he-was-found-in-apartment-3924868</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B35/44E/B3544E260E7713C2534B701A5B5DFEF3.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924868/3924868_CA5979DC534C4A059F20F7E762A9708C_191122_3924868_Man_was_dead_for_3_years_before_he_was_found_in__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924983</guid>
      <title>Man shoots up strip club over rejected debit card</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WATERLOO, IOWA <br/> An Iowa man went crazy outside a gentlemen's club, and all over a declined debit card. Some people and their tempers.<br/><br/>The Waterloo-Cedar Falls Courier reports that according to court records, James Allen Wells showed up at a Waterloo strip club late Friday, and got himself a lap dance.<br/><br/>The 67-year-old bust out his debit card to pay for the private service, but it got declined. <br/><br/>Upset, Wells stormed out of the club, pulled out a .38-caliber revolver, then went trigger happy shooting five rounds in the parking lot. <br/><br/>Let me get this straight <br/> dude stiffed the club and essentially got a free lap dance, and HE'S mad? Boomers these days.<br/><br/>According to the Coutrier, Wells' five shots hit a bunch of parked vehicles, including a Dodge Durango, a Chrysler Town and Country, and a Chevy Impala.<br/><br/>He then got into his own car and skedaddled, but got into a short chase with some cops who tried to pull him over for speeding.<br/><br/>Wells eventually crashed his car into a curb and ended up getting apprehended by officers following a short scuffle.<br/><br/>He has since been charged with criminal mischief, reckless use of a firearm, assault on a peace officer and reckless driving.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-shoots-up-strip-club-over-rejected-debit-card-3924983</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E10/84B/E1084BAFB56D9F3307855A5A40102EBA.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924983/3924983_45B9EF730626465BAE6259A0FC0643EE_191122_3924983_Man_shoots_up_strip_club_over_rejected_debit_car_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926647</guid>
      <title>Dog puts car in reverse, does doughnuts for about an hour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORT ST. LUCIE, FLORIDA <br/> A Florida dog decided to take his owner's car for a quick spin around the cul-de-sac last week in Port St. Lucie. <br/>According to Port St. Lucie police in a statement to the New York Post, the owner apparently made a wrong turn onto the street, which prompted her to stop and get out of the vehicle to assess her situation. <br/>She then absent mindedly closed the door with the car still running and her black labrador Max inside. <br/>According to WPTV, that's when Max hopped into the driver's seat and popped the car into reverse. <br/>Max then proceeded to do doughnuts slowly in reverse for about an hour or so as neighbors, and eventually police watched on. <br/>He was doing pretty well too, not hitting anything<br/>at first. In the end, he did love tap a mailbox and some garbage cans, but let's give him a break. It WAS his first time behind the wheel. <br/>WPTV reports that police finally put a stop to the joyride after punching in the passcode into the driver's side door. <br/><br/>Police say no one was hurt in the oh-so-Florida-esque incident. <br/><br/>As for Max, maybe he'll spin this into a part-time job as an Uber or Lyft driver.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-puts-car-in-reverse-does-doughnuts-for-about-an-hour-3926647</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/751/5AA/7515AA176AA4C3B75DA69B1F56F73429.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926647/3926647_5C8D55C0BC1649F1A7DEF68822C996FA_191126_3926647_Dog_puts_car_in_reverse__does_doughnuts_for_abou_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927280</guid>
      <title>Somebody shotgunned winged freedom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS, MISSOURI <br/> A female American bald eagle took two pellets to the wing last week, ABC News reported on Tuesday citing state conservation officials.<br/><br/>They say a landowner sighted the bird hanging around the same area for a few days in a row before he reported her.<br/><br/>The bald eagle named "Dorothy Parker" by rescuers was down but not out.<br/><br/>The department says the wounded bird tried to flee agents by hopping away. They eventually caught her with a blanket.<br/><br/>According to the department, University of Missouri's Raptor Rehabilitation Project is taking care of the eagle's broken wing.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/somebody-shotgunned-winged-freedom-3927280</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E17/C0D/E17C0DD29FAB6A1C1E8A69506A2FDFC8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3927280/3927280_9E51256B9D0947B682D4E5BA3E196985_191127_3927280_Somebody_shotgunned_winged_freedom_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 13:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927275</guid>
      <title>Man creates dating app where he is the only guy allowed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GREENSBORO, NORTH CAROLINA <br/> Swiping left or right to find mister right can be easier said than done in today's overcrowded world of dating apps.<br/>That's why 31-year-old North Carolina native Aaron Smith might have possibly created the best dating app of all time called Singularity. <br/>Why is it called Singularity? Because while it allows as many women to sign up as possible, Smith is the only guy available on the app<br/>GENIUS.<br/>After striking out on traditional dating apps, Aaron noticed all of them had a major deficiency. <br/>Talking to CBS affiliate WFMY, Smith said, "the biggest problem with the other apps is that my face is not featured prominently."<br/>So what do you do when you have so much competition? You eliminate the competition. <br/>Aaron explained, "If life gives you lemons, you should first make lemonade. Then make sure no other companies can produce or distribute their own soft drinks. So the only game in town is lemonade." <br/>So Smith got his software engineer friend Scott McDowell to design Singularity for him. <br/><br/>Women using the app won't be flooded with endless pictures of guy after guy. Instead, they just get different pictures of Smith. <br/><br/>Smith even made a hilarious commercial for his dating app. He hasn't had a ton of downloads yet, but the app is still in its early days.<br/><br/>So ladies, what are you waiting for? Download Singularity today and start swiping.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-creates-dating-app-where-he-is-the-only-guy-allowed-3927275</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BE6/AC1/BE6AC122955D82DBCAF42B844B343E84.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3927275/3927275_8B9BCB81A52841178523D614D37C7C87_191127_3927275_Man_creates_dating_app_where_he_is_the_only_guy__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 13:25:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927534</guid>
      <title>WeChat is banning Chinese Americans for political speech</title>
      <description><![CDATA[This week on Made in China: Tencent's WeChat has started banning and censoring Chinese-American citizens for commenting on the recent Hong Kong elections.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wechat-is-banning-chinese-americans-for-political-speech-3927534</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2A5/F65/2A5F65E1CE72C150C5F19C36A07D51FC.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927534/3927534_3D63BCDF2AF94D63B51732629A5DFDC1_191128_3927534_WeChat_is_banning_Chinese_Americans_for_politica_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 04:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927715</guid>
      <title>Veterans, airlines push back against untrained service animals</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Back in the day, a dog dumping runny deuces inside a plane full of passengers was the stuff of nightmares. Now, thanks to 'emotional support animals' it's an increasingly typical reality.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports that cheapskates who want their pets to fly for free turn to websites offering service animal "certification."<br/><br/>This has led to a boom of untrained dogs, birds, rodents, reptiles and amphibians in plane cabins...and lots of disgruntled staff.<br/><br/>Meanwhile, the people with legit, properly trained service animals are getting a bad rep.<br/><br/>It's even worse for people with disabilities that aren't visible, like brain injuries or PTSD.<br/><br/>This is why veterans and disability groups are now wanting new transportation rules, and local or federal regulations that would necessitate animal certification for public spaces. <br/><br/>According to the New York Times, airlines are working to cut down on the number of animals onboard.<br/><br/>Some are sympathetic to the veterans, and already have policies that make it harder for those who are just out for a free ride.<br/><br/>Airlines have also joined forces with veteran groups to crack down on bogus emotional service animals. This means only allowing species that can fulfill service functions, aka, probably not a hamster, sloth, or turtle.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/veterans-airlines-push-back-against-untrained-service-animals-3927715</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/187/FFB/187FFBA1F6F603AE8253F4E8707E5309.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927715/3927715_7A94A9918F4542A98CC51B2AD8BFBF14_191128_3927715_Veterans__airlines_push_back_against_untrained_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 09:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3928013</guid>
      <title>Gamer sells friend's $1m character for $500</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SICHUAN, CHINA <br/> A Chinese gamer sold his friend's character several hundred thousand dollars short of its $1m plus value, reports the South China Morning Post.<br/><br/>According to Sichuan High Court, mega rich gamer Lu had been letting his pal Lee play as his character on MMORPG "Justice Online".<br/><br/>The South China Morning Post reports that Lu had sunk close to $1.4m US dollars into the character. <br/><br/>Lee then tried to sell the character back to Lu on the NetEase server.  However he made a $1.4m typo by mistakenly selling the character to the wrong guy for just $500.<br/><br/>Lee explained that he was dizzy from too much gaming.<br/><br/>An enraged Lu sued everyone including Lee,  the buyer and NetEase. <br/><br/>According to the South China Morning Post, the court settled the case last week. Netease revoked the transaction and the buyer got nearly 13 large in damages.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/gamer-sells-friend-s-1m-character-for-500-3928013</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AF9/042/AF9042D36728D75542290309B76FB377.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928013/3928013_AB5048DD2EC74CCEBF6D04B46B31FE89_191129_3928013_Gamer_sells_friend_s__1m_character_for__500_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 02:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3928246</guid>
      <title>Sex &amp; Violence is for Kids?! YouTube Overrides TomoNews</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Taipei <br/> We ask why YouTube has set 140 of our videos with themes of sex and violence as "Made for Kids."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sex--violence-is-for-kids--youtube-overrides-tomonews-3928246</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/33B/489/33B48988F86CF86595C43B63C767D873.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928246/3928246_DA8B70C8732A479EAA4D23BF7616F1A8_191129_3928246_Sex___Violence_is_for_Kids___YouTube_Overrides_T_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 09:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3928215</guid>
      <title>Couple surprises their Denny's waitress with a new car</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GALVESTON, TEXAS <br/> A kindhearted couple gave a Texas waitress a brand new ride after finding out she walked 14-miles every day for work.<br/>According to KTRK, waitress Adrianna Edwards works at Denny's and said she has to walk seven miles just to get to the restaurant. <br/>A Galveston couple found out about Adrianna's story during breakfast on Tuesday. They also found out that she was saving money to buy a car. <br/>That's when the generous couple hopped on over to a car dealer and bought a 2011 Nissan Sentra. <br/>A few hours later, they returned to the Denny's and gave Edwards the surprise of her life. <br/>The couple, who requested to remain anonymous, gave Edwards the ride with no strings attached. Okay, maybe with one tiny string. <br/>They asked that hopefully one day Edwards can return the favor and pay it forward. <br/>And with Adrianna's new wheels, her five hour commute to and from work is now only a half an hour.  <br/>She told KTRK, "I still feel like I'm dreaming. Every two hours, I come look out my window to see if there's still a car there. When I see somebody in need, I'll probably be more likely to help them out to do everything that I can to help them out."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/couple-surprises-their-denny-s-waitress-with-a-new-car-3928215</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9DE/883/9DE883DC52331FBDFD3446E5CA306C5A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/29/3928215/3928215_851B97DF18DE4D7CAA665E45258727FF_191129_3928215_Couple_surprises_their_Denny_s_waitress_with_a_n_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 08:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
