<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 18:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3929271</guid>
      <title>Handyman fired after ceiling full of rats falls on him</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> A New York handyman whose bosses skimped on safety gear had a ceiling full of rats collapse on him, only to get a hospital stay and termination for his trouble.<br/><br/>According to a lawsuit obtained by the New York Post, Robert Petersen had been tasked with installing a new wall at a West 147th Street building. <br/><br/>Since it involved dealing with rat droppings, he asked his boss for safety gear, but was shot down and told not to be a baby about it.<br/><br/>The 45-year-old said his boss, Crystal Fernandez, made it sound like he'd get axed if he didn't do the work, so he did, even without the proper gear.<br/><br/>Petersen claims he was cleaning rat droppings and urine on soaked pieces of insulation, and was surrounded by rodents <br/> both dead and alive <br/> while he was working.<br/><br/>After 16 hours of working that filthy job, he was then called to repair a leaking hole in a ceiling <br/> again without any gear on him.<br/><br/>This time, the poor man had to stick his head in the hole and deal with all the rats running around his head.<br/><br/>While pulling down a board from the ceiling, the whole thing collapsed on him, raining down rats, droppings, and all things nasty and disgusting.<br/><br/>Peterson got itchy welts on his face and arms and began vomiting. He had to check into the hospital for a week, during which his lovely boss threatened to give him the boot.<br/><br/>According to court documents, Petersen filed a complaint with OSHA over his filthy work conditions. He was fired 10 days after returning from work, but only told it was "not going to work out."<br/><br/>The lawsuit alleges that the handyman's termination was in direct retaliation for his OSHA complaint.<br/><br/>Here's hoping Peterson's crappy boss and company get what's coming to them.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/handyman-fired-after-ceiling-full-of-rats-falls-on-him-3929271</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/002/D0E/002D0EC834D46B77BE3560D141E4504B.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929271/3929271_67857040438B4B4399F993EE43146903_191202_3929271_Handyman_fired_after_ceiling_full_of_rats_falls__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 03:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929608</guid>
      <title>Maine man shot dead by his own home booby trap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VAN BUREN, MAINE <br/> A man in Maine lost his life after getting shot by his own home booby trap.<br/><br/>According to the Van Buren Police Department, Ronald Cyr called 911 on Thanksgiving night saying he'd been shot.<br/><br/>The cops who arrived at his home to provide medical assistance discovered that the front door had been rigged with a homemade booby trap.<br/><br/>65-year-old Cyr had apparently designed it so a handgun would fire should anyone try and enter the door, which a friend later said was because he had been "robbed too many times."<br/><br/>Problem is, Cyr then unintentionally triggered the device and ended up getting shot himself, according to the police investigation.<br/><br/>He was taken to the hospital, but ended up succumbing to his injuries.<br/><br/>Police later found other unknown devices inside the home, which prompted them to contact the state bomb squad.<br/><br/>The Washington Post reports that although Maine law allows the use of deadly force against home intruders in certain cases, it's illegal to use booby traps to defend property.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/maine-man-shot-dead-by-his-own-home-booby-trap-3929608</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BC0/21D/BC021DD60DA699DF079572EE20713898.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929608/3929608_A99A06B48C7D497E80011508E2CF8A33_191202_3929608_Maine_man_shot_dead_by_his_own_home_booby_trap_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929528</guid>
      <title>Woman hit by train after falling onto tracks talking on her phone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO <br/> A 28-year-old woman had an up close and personal meet and greet with a train in the Windy City after she ended up on the tracks. <br/>ABC News reports that according to a Chicago police spokesperson, the really intelligent woman, who was not identified, was talking on her cellphone when she fell onto the tracks.  <br/><br/>The Chicago Sun Times reports that the boneheaded incident happened at 9:25 a.m. at the 328 S. Dearborn St. station.   <br/>Police initially said the woman accidentally fell backward onto the tracks, but after reviewing surveillance video footage said it looked like she appeared to step forward onto them. <br/>Authorities say initial eyewitness statements did not match the footage captured at the station. <br/>Luckily for the absent-minded woman, the Blue Line train was able to stop in time, but not before giving her a bit of a love tap.<br/>Windy City boys in blue say she was found partially under the lead car of the train.  <br/>Officials say the woman was then transported to Northwestern Memorial Hospital in critical condition.  <br/>According to the Chicago Transit Authority, Blue Line service was partially suspended for about an hour after the incident. Service was back to normal by midafternoon.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-hit-by-train-after-falling-onto-tracks-talking-on-her-phone-3929528</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/490/368/490368B06296AC703F696766040918B3.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929528/3929528_9A194F8DA1F943E1B36FE0BBFC04EFB0_191202_3929528_Woman_hit_by_train_after_falling_onto_tracks_tal_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 12:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929748</guid>
      <title>104-Year-Old Grandma VS Buck</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PHILLIPS, WISCONSIN <br/> Retirement isn't for everyone and 104-year-old Florence Teeters is the perfect example.<br/><br/>Born in 1915, Florence may just be the oldest person to have taken down a deer in Wisconsin, after her son helped her to obtain her hunting license just days before. <br/><br/>Speaking to NBC15, her youngest of five children Bill said that he took his mother to a hunting blind recently when a buck showed up around 30 yards away. <br/><br/>He told reporters that he tapped her on her knee and pointed out to the unsuspecting buck; she nodded, grinned and then took her shot. <br/><br/>The Wisconsin Department of Natural Resources is currently looking into the claim that Teeters may be the oldest registered hunter in the state.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/104-year-old-grandma-vs-buck-3929748</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/22E/016/22E0161D1FC976E6901361F3BC825E97.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929748/3929748_7AF10E5BD8EB469082E72218C1B810CA_191203_3929748_104_Year_Old_Grandma_VS_Buck_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 02:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930100</guid>
      <title>Florida woman fakes medical issue to get bigger plane seat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENSACOLA, FLORIDA <br/> A Florida woman is in custody after she hatched the perfect plan to fake a medical issue on an hour and forty minute-long flight in order to get a bigger seat. <br/><br/>Okay<br/>maybe her plan had a few tiny holes before lift off.<br/>NBC News reports the incident occurred on an American Airlines flight from Pensacola to Miami last Friday morning.  <br/>According to an American Airlines statement to NBC News, American Eagle 3508 took off at 5:43 a.m. <br/>After the plane was in the air, the woman, who has not been identified, started pretending she had trouble breathing as part of her scheme to get a free upgrade. <br/>She reportedly told flight attendants, who then told the pilot, who then turned the entire plane around<br/>and around<br/>and around some more before finally landing back at Pensacola at 6:26 a.m. <br/>According to NBC News, flight crews then called the police to Pensacola International Airport, where the woman admitted she had made up the problem to get a bigger seat on the plane. <br/>At first, Little Miss Sunshine refused to get off the plane, which then prompted a complete evacuation of the plane. <br/>She finally got her behind off the plane and was then taken into custody by the police. <br/>The flight finally got on its way at 7:41 a.m. <br/>Criminal charges have not been filed yet against the woman, but she still may get charged. <br/>Imagine what she would have come up with if this had actually been a long haul flight.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/florida-woman-fakes-medical-issue-to-get-bigger-plane-seat-3930100</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C31/B30/C31B305D33981B73B8496F04E7472C65.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3930100/3930100_49BD3DF1FCDB410593BDE272745BD6C1_191203_3930100_Florida_woman_fakes_medical_issue_to_get_bigger__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 12:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931112</guid>
      <title>McDonald's is testing a new chicken sandwich</title>
      <description><![CDATA['MURICA <br/> Everyday Americans have been going absolutely bonkers over chicken sandwiches as of late with no signs of slowing down.  <br/>As the Chicken Sandwich Wars have been raging, Popeyes and Chick-fil-A have been slugging it out, while Mickey D's has been left out in the cold watching from the sidelines. <br/>That could all change soon as CNBC reports McDonald's is testing out two new Southern-style chicken sandwiches at locations in Houston, Texas and Knoxville, Tennessee. <br/>Pictures of the new crispy chicken sandwich show a fried chicken fillet topped with butter and pickles. <br/>If you're having trouble picturing what that looks like, just think of a Chick-fil-A or Popeyes chicken sandwich with a Mickey D's wrapper around it<br/>VOIL&#192;!!   <br/>The deluxe crispy chicken sandwich comes with tomatoes, lettuce and mayo on top of the chicken fillet. <br/>According to Business Insider, the test will run from December 2 through January 26, 2020. <br/>According to CNBC, McDonald's has apparently been trying to get a decent tasting chicken sandwich together for quite a few months now. <br/>With Chick-fil-A catching up in the rearview and Popeyes dominating recently, can McDonald's McCopied chicken sandwich save the day?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mcdonald-s-is-testing-a-new-chicken-sandwich-3931112</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F42/BBC/F42BBCC5351E2DBB29C1AB6C281D2F79.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3931112/3931112_E5C29A3B47A44591BE589B96033576AE_191205_3931112_McDonald_s_is_testing_a_new_chicken_sandwich_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 12:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932823</guid>
      <title>$120,000 banana art taken down after idiotic crowds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI <br/> A slippery piece of artwork that was nothing more than a banana duct taped to the wall, which actually sold for $120,000 last week, had to be taken down because too many idiots<br/>sorry, people<br/>wanted to see it. <br/>According to the New York Post, Maurizio Cattelan's controversial banana piece titled "Comedian" had to be taken down on Sunday morning at the request of the art fair's organizers.<br/>This was just one day after a New York-based performance artist showed up at the Art Basel in Miami and ate the banana. <br/>Cattelan's gallery Perrotin announced, "Art Basel collaboratively worked with us to station guards and create uniform lines."<br/>Hold on...COLLABORATIVELY worked with us? So they just mean, "WORKED with us." <br/>Anyways, the statement went on, "however, the installation caused several uncontrollable crowd movements and the placement of the work on our booth compromised the safety of the artwork around us, including that of our neighbors. In the end, I would like to warmly thank all those who participated in this memorable adventure."<br/>Art Basel also confirmed that the $120,000 banana was no longer on display. <br/>But not to worry, if you really want to see the FART-work for yourself...just get a wall, a banana and some tape. And don't forget to call yourself an artist too.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-120-000-banana-art-taken-down-after-idiotic-crowds-3932823</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/647/9A0/6479A07FB1F04BAEDC86AAABCCA36EBF.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932823/3932823_B14D447602474F1BBC4A3A340CE86FC2_191209_3932823__120_000_banana_art_taken_down_after_idiotic_cro_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 12:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933087</guid>
      <title>The FBI is investigating Pensacola base shooting as a terrorist attack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PENSACOLA, FLORIDA <br/> A Saudi trainee at the US Navy Pensacola Air Station carried out a shooting early morning on Friday that the FBI is assuming to be a terrorist attack.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports that federal investigators identified the shooter as Saudi air force Second Lieutenant Mohammed Alshamrani in a press event on Sunday.<br/><br/>The commanding officer of the base told the New York Times that three sailors tried to tackle the shooter in order to save others and were killed in the attack.<br/><br/>Deputies responding to the emergency fatally shot Alshamrani. The incident left three sailors dead and eight injured, including two deputies who were shot in the limbs.<br/><br/>The Times reports that one Saudi national was on the scene and videoed the shooting. The FBI has detained this individual alongside with two other Saudis on base for questioning.<br/><br/>According to the FBI, Alshamrani was carrying a 9 millimeter Glock 45 pistol with a 33 round magazine and several spare magazines when deputies shot him.<br/><br/>FBI special agent in charge Rachel Rojas, who identified the weapon, said the shooter "purchased the weapon legally and lawfully."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-fbi-is-investigating-pensacola-base-shooting-as-a-terrorist-attack-3933087</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DA4/410/DA44103F07E157D73892A4D430F152B2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933087/3933087_4426A639CD574C7F9259C0A567005C0A_191210_3933087_The_FBI_is_investigating_Pensacola_base_shooting_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 07:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933445</guid>
      <title>Woman stung by scorpion on United Airlines flight</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO / ATLANTA <br/> A woman on a United Airlines plane got a nasty stowaway that turned what should've been a relatively uneventful flight into a painful one.<br/><br/>According to TMZ, the lady was on a flight from San Francisco to Atlanta Thursday morning when she felt a stinging sensation on her leg. She went to the lavatory when it intensified, and that's when a very much alive scorpion fell out of her pants leg and scurried away.<br/><br/>As if snakes on a plane wasn't bad enough, now we gotta worry about these venomous little buggers?!<br/><br/>Flight attendants <br/> bless them <br/> eventually caught the scorpion.<br/><br/>According to a United Airlines statement, medics treated the passenger as soon as the plane landed in Atlanta. She was taken to the hospital, and is going to be just fine.<br/><br/>No word on how the scorpion ended up on the plane, but we've got a few ideas.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-stung-by-scorpion-on-united-airlines-flight-3933445</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/551/2C5/5512C5AA651849AC1676CF4DC92ECF7B.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933445/3933445_43D7339C7BB6486886E23B3873E9C833_191211_3933445_Woman_stung_by_scorpion_on_United_Airlines_fligh_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933512</guid>
      <title>Dentist rode hoverboard while pulling patient's tooth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANCHORAGE, ALASKA <br/> A dentist all the way up in Alaska is currently on trial after allegedly yanking out a tooth from a sedated patient<br/>all while riding a hoverboard. <br/>NBC News reports that according to court records, prosecutors say 34-year-old Seth Lookhart engaged in an "unlawful dental act" that "does not conform to minimum professional standards of dentistry." <br/>According to NBC News, the fantastic dentist supposedly performed the tooth extraction on Veronica Wilhelm in July 2016 while he was riding a hoverboard in his office. <br/>And how does the world even know about this? Because like a true dumb dumb, Lookhart filmed himself doing it and then had the good sense to send the video to at least eight friends.<br/>Investigators say that according to phone records, Lookhart boasted in his text messages that his actions were a "new standard of care." <br/>In the video, hovermaster is then seen raising his arms in victory like a true douchebag as he rolls down the hallway. <br/>What's worse is that the woman whose tooth that was pulled didn't even know what had happened until investigators contacted her.   <br/>Wilhelm said in court that she had to be sedated for the yanking because she is allergic to medicines used for local anesthetics. <br/>Unfortunately for Lookhart, he's also facing charges for allegedly engaging in a scam to defraud Medicaid of at least $1.8 million in fraudulent billing and stealing $250,000 from business partners. <br/>His own lawyer even apologized to Wilhelm in court, but denied his client was guilty of the other charges he's facing.      <br/>Clearly the only practical solution would be to let Wilhelm do all of Lookhart's dental work going forward<br/>on hoverboard, naturally.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dentist-rode-hoverboard-while-pulling-patient-s-tooth-3933512</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/982/213/9822133D28A764DCD7754FD3073E0BF4.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933512/3933512_A170350B38CB4F23A96CCA406E400C53_191211_3933512_Dentist_rode_hoverboard_while_pulling_patient_s__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 03:38:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934012</guid>
      <title>Bus full of kids evacuated because of too much Axe body spray</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARRISH, FLORIDA <br/> Someone in Florida thought it would be a good idea to prank an entire school bus of kids with a ridiculous amount of Axe deodorant, and it ended just about how you'd expect <br/> BADLY. <br/><br/>WFTS reports that on Monday, the bus was on the way to Buffalo Creek Middle School with 30 students on board, when one or a couple of 'em decided to release the kraken. <br/>The kraken, in this case, was a crap ton of Axe body spray. <br/><br/>Oh, those poor children.<br/><br/>Everyone who's caught a whiff of Axe knows that stuff is potent, so just imagine being hotboxed with all of that man deodorant. It was BAD. <br/><br/>So bad, it triggered an evacuation. According to Fox News, a second deodorant-free bus had to be called to the scene to take the students to a nearby high school, where parents could then pick them up.<br/><br/>No one was seriously injured, but at least 15 middle schoolers were treated for "mild respiratory irritation." Yep, that's the Axe effect.<br/><br/>Officials are now reviewing the bus cameras to figure out the mastermind behind the crop-dusting.<br/><br/>Dunno about you, but our money's on a coordinated Murder-on-the-Orient-Express-style ploy to get out of school.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/bus-full-of-kids-evacuated-because-of-too-much-axe-body-spray-3934012</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F5/951/1F5951E7DBF90BD5E5E8B3ECF83F3CB2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934012/3934012_9E2929FAABDD40A4A5A558C8AADEFCDC_191212_3934012_Bus_full_of_kids_evacuated_because_of_too_much_A_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 03:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934397</guid>
      <title>How the Jersey City shooting unfolded</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JERSEY CITY, NEW JERSEY <br/> Investigators are not sure why two shooters launched a deadly attack at a New Jersey kosher grocery store, federal and state officials said on Wednesday. <br/>Reuters reports that six people, including two shooters, three civilians and a police officer, died in a series of events that ended in a police shootout on Tuesday in Jersey City. <br/>According to NBC News, New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy, Attorney General Gurbir Grewal and other law enforcement leaders at the state and federal level held a press conference Wednesday to detail what took place during the incident. <br/>According to Grewal, it is believed at some point Tuesday, 47-year-old David Anderson and 50-year-old Francine Graham encountered and killed Jersey City police Det. Joseph Seals in the Bayview Cemetery in Jersey City.<br/>At roughly 12:21 p.m., a white U-Haul van driven by Anderson parked directly across the street from the JC Kosher Supermarket. <br/>Seconds later, Anderson exited the driver side door armed with a rifle as he walked toward the supermarket and immediately began shooting. <br/>Graham, who was sitting in the passenger's side of the van, then followed Anderson into the store. <br/><br/>Inside the supermarket, the suspects encountered four civilians. Three of these civilians were killed and one survived a gunshot wound. <br/>Around 12:38 p.m., a bystander called 911 to report Seals' body in the cemetery. <br/>Grewal said that at approximately 12:43 p.m. Jersey City Police Department personnel arrived on scene and engaged the two suspects in an hours-long shootout. <br/>At approximately 3:25 p.m., an armored police vehicle broke through the front of the supermarket. <br/>Around 3:47 p.m., law enforcement discovered Anderson and Graham's bodies inside the supermarket. <br/>According to NBC News, authorities are currently in the process of identifying all available video footage from the incident.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-jersey-city-shooting-unfolded-3934397</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/009/163/009163B53153766D988A083F9C93DAA2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934397/3934397_849D04F3BD2C4862BBDC34704B965134_191212_3934397_How_the_Jersey_City_shooting_unfolded_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934950</guid>
      <title>Sinkhole swallows road, cars in Xiamen</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIAMEN, CHINA <br/> A massive sinkhole swallowed up several cars and part of a busy road intersection in Xiamen, China at 9:50 pm on Thursday, Chinese officials told China News.<br/><br/>The state-run media reports that 500 square meters of the road had collapsed near Xiamen Metro's Lucuo Station. <br/><br/>Social media footage on China News shows at least two cars that had fallen into the pit. <br/><br/>Chinese officials told the outlet that all personnel trapped in the sinkhole had been rescued and that no one was injured in the incident.<br/><br/>According to China News, an underground pipe or pipes was damaged during the incident and caused flooding to the area.<br/><br/>Citing Chinese netizens on Weibo, Taiwan's Liberty Times speculated that the water main might have been damaged prior to the incident and had caused the collapse to occur.<br/><br/>The incident went viral on Chinese social media and netizens posted videos of brown water inundating Lucuo station up to ankle depth.<br/><br/>Chinese officials say that the subway system will resume normal operations by 8:30pm on Friday.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sinkhole-swallows-road-cars-in-xiamen-3934950</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2F8/930/2F8930713E755202E05C2E86DACCA924.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934950/3934950_07EE9FBD2B564C1B83AE27722BBCB06A_191213_3934950_Sinkhole_swallows_road__cars_in_Xiamen_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 11:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935134</guid>
      <title>Iowa teen uses Siri to call for help after car plunges into icy river</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MASON CITY, IOWA <br/> An Iowa man was saved from an icy demise after using Siri to call for help.<br/><br/>According to KIMT, Gael Salcedo was driving to class when his Jeep hit a frozen patch on the road. He turned right, and ended up plunging into the freezing Winnebago River.<br/><br/>When the 18-year-old realized his car was in the river, he quickly rolled the windows down for fear that the vehicle would sink.<br/><br/>He also couldn't find his iPhone, but thank god for voice assistants.<br/><br/>Salcedo only had to call out "Hey Siri, call 911" for Siri to come through and call for help...and help him find his phone.<br/><br/>Mason City firefighters arrived soon after, approaching from the passenger's side because the strong river current was pinning the driver's door shut. They had not so great news for Gael though: he'd have to walk out.<br/><br/>So walk out he did <br/> in the freezing cold of the river, while struggling against the current. It was an ordeal, for sure, but with the help of the firefighters, he made it back to land and into an ambulance.<br/><br/>Salcedo was treated for shock at the hospital but was released just three hours later.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/iowa-teen-uses-siri-to-call-for-help-after-car-plunges-into-icy-river-3935134</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/162/67C/16267C2C77EAFFEF339C3240A5578C45.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/14/3935134/3935134_4489B9DA266E4806BAC19E6A90CF1C93_191214_3935134_Iowa_teen_uses_Siri_to_call_for_help_after_car_p_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 19:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936218</guid>
      <title>Worker steals $88,000 from bank, arrested after social media posts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO <br/> An ex-employee was busted by the FBI on Dec. 4 for allegedly stealing over $88,000 in cash from a Wells Fargo vault in North Carolina. <br/>He might have gotten away with it too<br/>probably not<br/>if only it weren't for his damn social media posts.  <br/><br/>According to an unsealed indictment released last Friday by the United States Attorney's Office for the Western District of North Carolina, 29-year-old Arlando Henderson had access to the Wells Fargo vault in Charlotte where he worked. <br/>According to the indictment, on at least 18 occasions in 2019 he stole money from cash deposits made by the bank's customers to the vault, and then deposited some of it at a nearby ATM. <br/>The indictment alleges that Henderson then destroyed certain documents and made<br/>or caused others to make<br/>false entries in the bank's books and records to cover his tracks.   <br/>He is accused of using the cash to pay for personal expenses, including a $20,000 down payment on a 2019 Mercedes-Benz. <br/>Why do we know any of this? Because between July and August 2019, Henderson had the genius to hop on Facebook and Instagram to post a boatload of pictures with him holding huge stacks of cash. <br/>Henderson is now facing a ton of charges, including two counts of financial institution fraud and 19 counts of theft. Guess it's time for a new Facebook update.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/worker-steals-88-000-from-bank-arrested-after-social-media-posts-3936218</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/49B/868/49B868656654217162E8F4967745332A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936218/3936218_F80BF7B310B64A26B6190B8294172CE3_191216_3936218_Worker_steals__88_000_from_bank__arrested_after__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936694</guid>
      <title>Guy rescues dog after leash gets caught in elevator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOUSTON <br/> A Pomeranian from H-town is probably wishing for a new owner after being rescued by a 27-year-old man when its leash got caught in an elevator door.<br/><br/>Security camera footage captured the heart-pounding moment Johnny Mathis saved the little pooch from becoming elevator dinner. <br/>Mathis told NBC News that he was coming home late from work last Monday night and exited the lift on the floor to his apartment. <br/>That's when a new tenant walked into the elevator dragging her dog on a leash behind her.<br/><br/>Most pet owners would probably check if their animals made it in before shutting the doors. This woman doesn't appear to be one of those. <br/><br/>Video Mathis filmed from his building's security camera shows the elevator doors shut on the dog's leash. <br/>Mathis is seen running over to the Pomeranian and struggling to free the dog from its leash as the elevator was heading up to the top floor. <br/>He told NBC News, "I tried to break it at first. I tried to lean down on it with all my weight but it wouldn't snap. <br/>Luckily Mathis was able to get the collar off and save the doggo just in the nick of time.<br/>Pay attention to your pets people...or just don't have any. Have some kids instead. Those are much easier to handle.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/guy-rescues-dog-after-leash-gets-caught-in-elevator-3936694</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6A1/7C9/6A17C94D86F2BF1F39CE8110FC38923F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936694/3936694_A754410A04314B3A9806FA1EC9D20A5D_191217_3936694_Guy_rescues_dog_after_leash_gets_caught_in_eleva_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 10:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936698</guid>
      <title>How the brain sees the world</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANNOVER / NEW HAMPSHIRE <br/> Researchers say that the visual world humans perceive is produced by parts of the brain lying outside of the visual cortex, according to a new study published in Current Biology.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Dartmouth College says that the findings have significant implications for the debate about what human consciousness is and where it occurs in the brain, in a press release dated to December 13.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The study used MRI technology to scan test subjects who observed a screen displaying a visual illusion created by the so-called Gabor patch.<br/><br/><br/><br/>As the patch moves in one direction, the flickering shape tricks the brain into seeing that it is moving in a perceived path that is different from its actual path.<br/><br/><br/><br/>According to the study, the brain scans then allowed researchers to identify the visual cortex as the area of the brain that senses the patch&#8217;s actual physical path.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Further, the scans showed that seeing the illusion directly corresponds to activity in the frontal lobes. This suggests that the frontal lobes also process visual information. <br/><br/><br/><br/>According to co-author Patrick Cavanagh, the study establishes that the frontal lobes are not only responsible for decision making and thinking, but also provides the end step for perceiving where objects are.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-brain-sees-the-world-3936698</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936698/3936698_D80E2A7698284D75AD29BA1DB5E075C1_191217_3936698_How_the_brain_sees_the_world_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937368</guid>
      <title>Company to impose smell check for bathroom time over 10 mins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOME STINKIN' COMPANY <br/> A crappy company is raising eyebrows and middle fingers after it put up a sign threatening smell checks for employees who are in the bathroom for too long.<br/><br/>Fox News reports that the sign was posted on a workplace bathroom at an unidentified business, and first appeared on Reddit. <br/><br/>The text reads: "If in bathroom for more than 10 minutes, a smell check will be completed to ensure employee not on phone." Presumably, the new measure is an attempt to reclaim company time and prevent workers from slacking off on the toilet.<br/><br/>The sign goes on to say that if no stink is sniffed, then the employee in question would then be "reported to office."<br/><br/>It's such a ridiculous scenario, many are wondering if it's a joke, or who the stinkin' manager is that came up with such a crappy idea.<br/><br/>Everyone agrees though, that there's only one loser here: the poor schmuck who has to be on sniff duty.<br/><br/>Because honestly, if that's how management wants to play this game, it's easy enough to comply.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/company-to-impose-smell-check-for-bathroom-time-over-10-mins-3937368</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E89/3B8/E893B8A6B2EADF2ABBDA1100ECB84AD8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/18/3937368/3937368_8821666D3F114E86A4A2EC06E533A24A_191218_3937368_Company_to_impose_smell_check_for_bathroom_time__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937847</guid>
      <title>Man jacks $500 of shrimp by shoving it in his pants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIVERSIDE, CALIFORNIA <br/> California cops are looking for a small-time crook who apparently is really into frozen shrimp. <br/>You could say he thinks they're SHRIMPRY the best.<br/>According to KTLA, police are on the hunt for a man who jammed 30 bags of shrimp down his pants and lifted them from a Riverside grocery store.<br/>Riverside police said in a press release that the "Shrimp Bandit" stuffed the frozen shellfish down his trousers in the frozen-food section of a Vons supermarket. <br/>The incident occurred around 12:30 p.m. on Dec. 4. <br/>Investigators say the super shrimp fan had to make three separate trips over 15 minutes with his trousers packed full of frozen goodies to complete the heist. <br/>KTLA reports that the man was caught on surveillance camera leaving the store. <br/><br/>Police say he is a white dude in his 50s, about 5-foot-10 and between 150 and 180 pounds, plus or minus the 30 bags of shrimp on his person.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-jacks-500-of-shrimp-by-shoving-it-in-his-pants-3937847</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/320/1C0/3201C0775A9836990F14EA5D866F718B.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937847/3937847_10499315310544EA9E1C16034FDE0B5F_191219_3937847_Man_jacks__500_of_shrimp_by_shoving_it_in_his_pa_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 12:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3938454</guid>
      <title>Trump impeached by House in historic vote. Now what?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  <br/> Donald Trump has now been officially impeached, making him the third U.S. president after Andrew Johnson and Bill Clinton to face removal from office.<br/><br/>According to CNN, the House of Representatives on Wednesday voted to impeach President Trump on two articles of impeachment: abuse of power and obstruction of Congress.<br/><br/>The article on abuse of power accused Trump of withholding aid to pressure Ukraine into investigating his political rival Joe Biden. It passed 230 votes to 197, with only two Democrats opposing.<br/><br/>The second article, which passed 229 to 198, charged Trump over his refusal to cooperate with the impeachment inquiry and his urging of witnesses and government agencies to do the same.<br/><br/>No House Republicans supported impeachment.<br/><br/>CBS reports that the next steps would be for Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi to name the impeachment managers that will argue to case to senators, and transmit the impeachment articles to Senate.<br/><br/>A trial will then be held in the Senate, presided over by the Supreme Court Chief Justice, with senators acting as jury.<br/><br/>A two-thirds majority vote is needed to remove Trump from office. But with the Republicans controlling the Senate with at least a 51-seat majority, and Senate leader Mitch McConnell claiming he's working with the White House, the president will likely be exonerated.<br/><br/>According to the New York Times, Pelosi has suggested that the House might delay sending the articles to the Senate, in order to negotiate the terms of the proceedings.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that this could put off the trial for an indefinite amount of time, effectively denying Trump the acquittal he expects.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/trump-impeached-by-house-in-historic-vote-now-what--3938454</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C75/DBE/C75DBE29468F67735AD7704F2E8CFE93.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938454/3938454_77C34D48A6C7491FA7AB312B11016499_191220_3938454_Trump_impeached_by_House_in_historic_vote__Now_w_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939848</guid>
      <title>Frozen beef patties recalled over possible plastic contamination</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CINCINNATI <br/> There's another recall of food that was sent to schools, and Tyson Foods Inc is involved again.<br/><br/>The U.S. Department of Agriculture announced that Tyson Foods subsidiary AdvancePierre Foods is recalling 15,738 pounds of its beef patty products as they may be "contaminated with extraneous materials, specifically small, green soft plastic."<br/><br/>The USDA is classifying this as a Class II Recall. This means there is a remote probability that use of the product may result in adverse health consequences.<br/><br/>In a statement, the company said that it is voluntarily recalling the product CN Fully Cooked Flamebroiled Beef Patties as a precaution after receiving complaints from a foodservice establishment.<br/><br/>AdvancePierre Foods says only two of the patties were found to be contaminated.<br/><br/>The company is recalling 1,043 cases, or roughly half a truckload of product, that were produced in September 2019.<br/><br/>According to the USDA, the product was shipped to a warehouse in Iowa, then distributed to institutions including schools as part of a commercial sale. The product was not sold in retail stores.<br/><br/>AdvancePierre Foods says it has not received any reports of injuries or illnesses due to consumption of the beef patties. The USDA urged institutions that have purchased the product to either discard it or return it to the place of purchase.<br/><br/>In April of this year, AdvancePierre Foods recalled over 20,000 pounds of beef patties after consumers found pieces of soft, purple plastic in the product.<br/><br/>AdvancePierre Foods' parent company, Tyson Foods, which has been involved in a series of food scandals, voluntarily recalled more than 5,000 cases of its crispy chicken fritters after plastic was found in the product in June 2019.<br/><br/>The company said that the product was not sold at stores, though it was distributed to schools across the country.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/frozen-beef-patties-recalled-over-possible-plastic-contamination-3939848</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/987/9F3/9879F335E428B5AC8182AB099FD75C59.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939848/3939848_954AF9B0314D4248B5D9AD548004B5F3_191224_3939848_Frozen_beef_patties_recalled_over_possible_plast_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 07:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940219</guid>
      <title>Police dog caught on cam stealing toys from charity bin</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FRANKLIN, MASSACHUSETTS <br/> A police therapy dog may have landed himself on Santa's naughty list after being caught stealing from the charity bin.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the Franklin Police Department had been collecting toys for the Santa Foundation, which donates presents to needy families on Christmas. <br/><br/>For some reason though, the toys kept disappearing, so the cops started to look into it.<br/><br/>It didn't take long to figure out that the Christmas toy thief was one of their own &#8211; a furry four-legged pup named Ben Franklin.<br/><br/>Officers caught the adorable golden retriever red-handed, carrying a toy baby in a carrier through the station.<br/><br/>Turns out Ben had thought the toys were his, and had been hoarding them in his secret lair beneath a desk.<br/><br/>Franklin Police Deputy Chief James Mil says Ben has since been banned from the collection room. All the toys he took were also replaced after he got slobber all over them.<br/><br/>We're just kidding about the naughty list, Ben. You're still a good boy!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/police-dog-caught-on-cam-stealing-toys-from-charity-bin-3940219</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/97D/BE0/97DBE01C1643F9FF12125C2BB839CAD2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940219/3940219_5577F1AC830A4343A9BC5D918E29657C_191225_3940219_Police_dog_caught_on_cam_stealing_toys_from_char_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 02:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940406</guid>
      <title>Wisconsin city to allow snowball fights after 50-year ban</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WAUSAU, WISCONSIN <br/> After a more than 50-year ban on snowball fights, residents of Wausau, Wisconsin could soon freely pelt each other with balls of ice.<br/><br/>Wisconsin Public Radio reports that the city had a rarely-enforced ordinance banning projectiles on city property, which included hurling rocks, shooting arrows, and yes, throwing snowballs.<br/><br/>It's only been used to issue tickets 10 times in the past 15 years, with only two instances involving snowballs being thrown, both at passing cars. <br/><br/>In early December, the city got called out by several news outlets for the snowball ban, which was inaccurately reported as new. One even dubbed Wausau "the worst town in America" for stamping out winter fun. <br/><br/>Well, officials weren't having that, and put out a video to set the record straight, featuring cops having a snowball fight and the Deputy Chief of Police hitting a bullseye on the mayor's head.<br/><br/>The city council also voted last week to remove "snowball" from the local law banning projectiles. <br/><br/>But while snowball fights between friends or enemies are fine, chucking a fast one at a moving vehicle on the highway is still going to land you in hot water with the cops.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wisconsin-city-to-allow-snowball-fights-after-50-year-ban-3940406</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E62/B62/E62B6207EDA1369A86C56B26783C2A4D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940406/3940406_1181D2B0CE9C4AB0AEB8FDB1CC4F886C_191225_3940406_Wisconsin_city_to_allow_snowball_fights_after_50_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 10:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940934</guid>
      <title>Man throws money into the air after robbing bank on Christmas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLORADO SPRINGS <br/> A man with a striking resemblance to Santa Claus was feeling the spirit of the holidays when he decided to rob a bank two days before Christmas and then redistributed the cash by throwing it out into the streets.<br/>According to Colorado 11 News, police say 65-year-old David Oliver entered the Academy Bank in Colorado Springs around lunchtime on Monday afternoon. <br/>Authorities say he entered the bank, claimed to have a weapon in his pocket and then made off with the loot. <br/>According to eyewitness Dion Pascale talking to Colorado 11, Oliver "robbed the bank, came out, threw the money all over the place."<br/>"He started throwing money out of the bag and then said, 'Merry Christmas!'"<br/>And what do you do after robbing a bank? You get a coffee of course. <br/>Witnesses said Oliver then casually made his way over to a Starbucks, sat down in front of the coffee shop, and waited for the cops to arrive. <br/>Colorado 11 News reported that bystanders were reported to have picked up all the cash from the street and then returned it back to the back.   <br/>Oliver was eventually taken into custody and is currently being held on $10,000 bond.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-throws-money-into-the-air-after-robbing-bank-on-christmas-3940934</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3ED/783/3ED78329995C542AF268FD6E7215D0EF.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/26/3940934/3940934_F56745E5B0C74115B18F7D43458A7D05_191226_3940934_Man_throws_money_into_the_air_after_robbing_bank_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940930</guid>
      <title>Woman with cold gets $28,395.50 bill for a throat swab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> A New York woman with a case of the sniffles who visited the doctor was hit with a $28,395.50 bill, most of which her insurance coughed up. <br/>According to NPR, Alexa Kasdan popped into see Dr Roya Fathollahi, a primary care physician at Manhattan Specialty Care, back in November because of a lingering sore throat.  <br/><br/>Kasdan told NPR she was going to go on vacation so she wanted to make sure she wasn't hit with strep while on break. <br/><br/>NPR reports that she popped in for a quick visit and had her throat swabbed and some blood drawn and was sent on her way with some antibiotics. <br/>Her vacay went fine, but then the sickness came. <br/>Dr. Fathollahi's office had left messages and an email saying her insurance company was sending her family a check for MORE THAN 25 grand to cover some out-of-network lab tests. <br/>Tests that would have cost only $653 had the throat swab been sent to Kasdan's in-network provider. <br/>They told Kasdan that these tests were normal and that actual bill was an insane $28,395.50. The doctor's office also said it would waive her portion of the bill, which came out to $2,530.26.<br/>Another possible reason for such an astronomically expensive bill is there could be a connection between the out-of-network lab and Dr. Fathollahi. <br/>According to NPR, Kasdan's bill shows the tests were done by Manhattan Gastroenterology, which conveniently has the same phone number and locations as her doctor's office. Damn, that's COLD.   <br/>In the end Kasdan paid her usual $25 copay and a $9.61 fee for some separate lab tests<br/>So what's the lesson of the day? American healthcare is a total sham.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-with-cold-gets-28-395-50-bill-for-a-throat-swab-3940930</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ACB/D00/ACBD001C37E84A977AA349A10D72E97F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/26/3940930/3940930_24D2159EF0604113800127D219045D99_191226_3940930_Woman_with_cold_gets__28_395_50_bill_for_a_throa_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 13:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941102</guid>
      <title>AA back to squeezing in tighter seats on Boeing 737s</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FORT WORTH, TEXAS <br/> American Airlines is back to retrofitting their fleet of Boeing 737-800 planes with a newer, tighter, and much less comfy interior. <br/><br/>According to View From the Wing, the retrofit program was paused back in March after 737 Max planes were grounded following the fatal Lion Air and Ethiopian crashes.<br/><br/>At the time, American didn't want to take any more planes out of service and risk cancelling even more flights. <br/><br/>But now, they're back at it again, squeezing in 12 more seats per plane at the expense of passengers' ever-shrinking legroom. <br/><br/>The seats are harder, with less padding and less recline ability.  The divider between first and economy is gone, and there's no seatback video screen, either!<br/><br/>The only thing that did get bigger are the overhead storage bins, but that's so the airline won't have to keep gate-checking bulky bags, which can cause delays.<br/><br/>If you think that's a tight fit, wait til you see the bathroom, described by one AA pilot as "the most miserable experience in the world."<br/><br/>There's no way anyone will be happy flying in this sardine can, so we're not sure where AA President Robert Isom heard the nice responses customers supposedly gave.<br/><br/>Hate to break it to ya, Bobby boy, but your Project Oasis is really more of a mirage, and definitely not a "real success."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/aa-back-to-squeezing-in-tighter-seats-on-boeing-737s-3941102</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/86A/6D9/86A6D9967CAD2BCA3BAEB917035E09A4.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941102/3941102_31B7043263544E40BA71B66466049CA7_191227_3941102_AA_back_to_squeezing_in_tighter_seats_on_Boeing__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 03:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941394</guid>
      <title>Man fires gunshots out of a moving car, gets arrested</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EL PASO, TEXAS <br/> A man in Texas was arrested on Monday after a video surfaced online of the guy randomly firing gunshots through an open window of a moving car.<br/><br/>In the video, the man is seen smiling in the backseat as he starts firing while cars pass by on El Paso's Patriot Freeway.<br/><br/>The video was initially posted on to social media after which it was picked up by a local gossip site Fit Fam El Paso, according to ABC News. <br/><br/>This caught the attention of the El Paso police. Authorities posted a tweet on December 21 saying that they are looking into the incident.<br/><br/>The next day, the police called for the unidentified man to turn himself in and "make it a lesson learned."<br/><br/>On December 23, Jonathan Jay Oneal, turned himself in. The cops said that he was arrested on charges of discharging a firearm in certain municipalities.<br/><br/>In a news release, the police said that Oneal was booked into the El Paso County Detention Facility on a US$50,000 bond.<br/><br/>The police said no one was injured in the incident.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-fires-gunshots-out-of-a-moving-car-gets-arrested-3941394</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/788/22F/78822FE7ABA56AAED20C5AE96C52C576.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941394/3941394_2120886A038748BABB8DF0C873590C19_191227_3941394_Man_fires_gunshots_out_of_a_moving_car__gets_arr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:40:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941530</guid>
      <title>Utah bro implants Tesla key and other chips into his hands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPRINGVILLE, UTAH <br/> Carrying keys, wallets or purses are increasingly becoming things of the past as more and more people embrace mobile technology. <br/>But would you go so far as to have cybernetic implants shoved under your skin all for the sake of some marginal convenience? <br/>According to ABC 7, that's exactly what Ben Workman did. The self-described "cybernetics enthusiast" studies human and machine interaction. <br/>He's had four different chips jammed inside him so he can unlock doors at work, log on and off of his computer and share contact information. You need to have implants for those things?<br/>According to Workman, it was hard to find people in the beginning to turn him into Tony Stark Beta. He eventually recruited a family member for his first try. <br/>And then came Ben's Tesla Model 3. Who can be bothered carrying around car keys anymore? <br/>Workman had to enlist the help of a piercing studio to get the larger Tesla key implant into his hand.   <br/>Ben apparently also had a magnet implanted into his left hand, that he uses for "magic tricks" and "fun stuff." <br/>Hopefully he doesn't get a new car<br/>or carjacked.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/utah-bro-implants-tesla-key-and-other-chips-into-his-hands-3941530</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0D9/A59/0D9A591EB4B9388FB9D9AEAC71ADD17E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941530/3941530_A0A9F9D70D92461B9101FF887351B66F_191227_3941530_Utah_bro_implants_Tesla_key_and_other_chips_into_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 15:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942431</guid>
      <title>Monster halo could unravel the Earth's antimatter mystery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA's Fermi telescope discovered a vast halo around a neutron star that could explain why there is so much antimatter near Earth.<br/><br/>According to NASA, there is higher than expected amount of antimatter near Earth, a phenomenon which scientists have struggled to find an explanation for. <br/><br/>NASA published its study in Physical Review D Tuesday last week.<br/><br/>According to NASA's news release, when a giant star dies and explodes into a supernova, its remaining core sometimes becomes a neutron star. <br/><br/>The neutron star named Geminga is a pulsar, which constantly discharges electrons and their antimatter counterpart known as positrons into space.<br/><br/>As charged positrons and electrons collide with photons from starlight, the added energy charge the light into gamma rays.<br/><br/>Since the path of gamma rays are scrambled by the magnetic fields they encounter, scientists have been unable to trace the positrons back to their origins until now. <br/><br/>Using the Fermi data, a NASA affiliated team removed background gamma radiation from the readings and determined that Geminga is in fact the source of the extra positrons.<br/><br/>According to the study's co-author Silvia Manconi at Aachen University, the pulsar contributed about 20 percent of positrons detected near Earth.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/monster-halo-could-unravel-the-earth-s-antimatter-mystery-3942431</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1A4/DCB/1A4DCB11DEC5E525DC6608CAE916FED1.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942431/3942431_7F0FC4D5CE0D4BDDA75A6F9B29276DBE_191230_3942431_Monster_halo_could_unravel_the_Earth_s_antimatte_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 08:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942899</guid>
      <title>Louisiana town crop-dusted with 100 gallons of holy water</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COW ISLAND, LOUISIANA <br/> Hashtag blessed just took on a whole 'nother meaning. <br/><br/>NPR reports that after church on the Saturday before Christmas, Catholic residents of Cow Island, Louisiana got over a hundred gallons of water blessed by their parish priest.<br/><br/>He didn't do it at church though, but at an airstrip, where the newly holy H2O can go straight into a crop dusting plane and bless absolutely everyone &#8211; whether you like it or not.<br/><br/>Word of the mass blessing got out fast enough that families who sauntered out of their houses got a big dose of holy from the heavens above.<br/><br/>Rev. Fr. Matthew Barzare, who blessed the water, assured everyone there was no pesticide residue in the tank around this time of the year.<br/><br/>Good to know we're not creating pesticide mutants in the image of God.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/louisiana-town-crop-dusted-with-100-gallons-of-holy-water-3942899</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/934/7E1/9347E174BA038F08018088769A051F0D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942899/3942899_16C578E6A49F4F579C5A970698869F45_191231_3942899_Louisiana_town_crop_dusted_with_100_gallons_of_h_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 08:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
