<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 18:10:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3944108</guid>
      <title>Doctor rescues dog from choking to death on leash stuck in elevator</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAMPA BAY, FLORIDA <br/> Dog is sunny Florida will luckily live to bark another day all thanks to the quick actions of doctor Mohammad Awad. <br/>CNN reported that the Tampa Bay doctor had just gotten off a shift on Monday when he arrived back at his apartment building. <br/><br/>Awad told CNN that as he walked up to the elevator, his neighbor had just gotten off with her dog, but the leash was still inside the elevator door. <br/>The doctor shared surveillance camera footage from his building's security camera on his Facebook page. <br/><br/>Video footage shows the door shut on the leash, suddenly the dog is yanked up into the air. <br/>Awad instantly jumps into action, dropping his plate of food and dashing over to the doggo to try and break the leash. <br/>The doc's first attempt fails as he stumbled backwards. <br/>Awad told the least trusted name in news that he could hear the dog make whimpering and choking sounds. <br/>Luckily on Awad's second try, the leash snapped and the dog dropped safely to the floor. Doggy disaster averted.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/doctor-rescues-dog-from-choking-to-death-on-leash-stuck-in-elevator-3944108</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ABD/75B/ABD75B38B5A00C65A3C9D9370F6866EB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3944108/3944108_92AF488A263C4AE8AAB0A1AB5ED8726F_200102_3944108_Doctor_rescues_dog_from_choking_to_death_on_leas_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 15:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944497</guid>
      <title>Giant fish chows down on whole shark</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE DEEP SEA <br/> The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration captured rare footage of a wreckfish trying to gobble up an entire shark while swimming in the deep sea. <br/><br/>The video also shows a bunch of sharks swimming towards a dead swordfish and feasting on the creature's skin and muscle tissue as it lies still on the seafloor.<br/><br/>On their website, NOAA explains that deep-sea sharks aren't usually seen gathering together like unless there is food available in the surrounding area. <br/><br/>The footage was captured by the remotely operated vehicle Deep Discoverer during the NOAA's Windows to the Deep expedition last year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/giant-fish-chows-down-on-whole-shark-3944497</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/239/C8B/239C8BB19D93497044480ECEDD9A195C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944497/3944497_234A64358E1E4AE9BAD8F55F93EDDABE_200103_3944497_Giant_fish_chows_down_on_whole_shark_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 10:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944758</guid>
      <title>Four Amish men were arrested for driving a horse and buggy drunk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEAVERTON, MICHIGAN <br/> Four Amish bros were busted in Michigan for being tipsy while operating a horse and buggy. <br/>MLive reported that around 4 p.m. on Sunday, Dec. 29, Gladwin County Sheriff's deputies got a call from a motorist notifying them about a horse and buggy that was acting kind of buggy. <br/>The driver said the men were apparently tossing empty cans onto the street. <br/>After police located the buggy in question, they pulled the guys over and asked them to cough up their IDs. <br/>Police said the group first gave the cops bogus ages and refused to give them their names.  <br/>Upon further investigation, deputies discovered several more cans of beer inside the buggy. They also added that all four were obviously loaded. <br/>Levei Mast, 20, Andrew Zook, 19, Joseph Miller, 20 and Joseph Troyer, 19, were all charged with felony obstruction of justice and disorderly conduct. <br/>They were also hit with civil infractions for being minors in possession of booze. <br/>Each was released on Monday on $3,500 bond.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/four-amish-men-were-arrested-for-driving-a-horse-and-buggy-drunk-3944758</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/04/3944758/3944758_0D969AAD1B7C4A9DB248D3F6A87F47E8_200104_3944758_Four_Amish_men_were_arrested_for_driving_a_horse_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 18:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945807</guid>
      <title>Hackers from Iran target U.S. government website</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A U.S. government website was targeted by a group of Iranian hackers on Saturday January 4, amid ongoing tensions between Iran and the U.S. over the killing of Qassim Suleimani, a high ranking Iranian commander. <br/><br/>According to AFP, the Federal Depository Library Program's website was replaced with a page called "Iranian Hackers!"<br/><br/>As soon as the site was opened, visitors were shown a picture of U.S. President Donald Trump bleeding through the mouth and being punched in the face by what seems to be the fist of an Iranian Revolutionary Guard.<br/><br/>The website also showcased images of Iran's leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, the flag of Iran and a message from the country's leader which expresses support for the oppressed people in the Middle East.<br/><br/>In a statement, a spokesperson from the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency told CNN that the site has since been taken offline and is no longer accessible.<br/><br/>The official said that there is no confirmation of whether or not the hacking operation was part of Iran's state-sponsored activities.<br/><br/>Suleimani was killed on January 3 by a U.S. airstrike ordered by President Trump after the U.S. Department of Defense accused him of developing plans to attack American military personnel and diplomats in Iraq and the Middle Eastern region, as reported by CNN. <br/><br/>The Pentagon also says he was responsible for the deaths of hundreds of Americans and wounding thousands more.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hackers-from-iran-target-u-s-government-website-3945807</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945807/3945807_419DF1D55DAE445EAFEB35E3B249C747_200106_3945807_Hackers_from_Iran_target_U_S__government_website_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945789</guid>
      <title>Almost the whole US military has gone to war against TikTok</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> When the U.S. Army, Navy and Marines recently went into battle against Chinese video sharing app TikTok, it was only a matter of time before reinforcements were sent in.<br/>Now according to the Wall Street Journal, the Air Force and Coast Guard have also said they are no longer allowing TikTok on government-issued devices. <br/>According to Engadget, it's unclear if the ban will also extend to the Super Space Force. <br/>Apparently there are no restrictions of the app on personal devices, but officials have encouraged personnel and their kids to ditch it. <br/>The recent bans come amid U.S. concerns that the Chinese government could pressure TikTok to hand over sensitive data.   <br/>Spokeswoman Major Malinda Singleton told the Wall Street Journal, some of the issues are "not unique" to any one social media platform. Bad guys could possibly recruit people through social networks, and there's a chance that personnel could inadvertently reveal military secrets or expose themselves to attack. <br/>But if anything, the TikTok ban has to make you think. U.S. soldiers are damn young.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/almost-the-whole-us-military-has-gone-to-war-against-tiktok-3945789</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945789/3945789_FD6AD764B0424D918926295BF96A96B4_200106_3945789_Almost_the_whole_US_military_has_gone_to_war_aga_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946392</guid>
      <title>Someone released bedbugs inside a Pennsylvania Walmart</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EDINBORO, PENNSYLVANIA <br/> Someone in Pennsylvania apparently hates Walmart so much they deliberately tried to cause a bedbug infestation.<br/><br/>[CUT 1]<br/>According to CNN, a manager at an Edinboro Walmart found a closed pill bottle filled with live bed bugs inside a boy's jacket that was for sale.<br/><br/>The next day, an employee from health safety company Ecolab visited the store and spotted the little parasitic critters crawling all over the men's changing room. <br/><br/>After a second closed bottle with dead bed bugs inside was found later in the men's department, Walmart staff finally reported the incident to the cops.<br/><br/>NBC reports that state police are now investigating the incident, and itching to find whoever's responsible.<br/><br/>Itching is right. Bed bugs may not spread disease, but they're definitely a pain to deal with.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/someone-released-bedbugs-inside-a-pennsylvania-walmart-3946392</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946392/3946392_1E799E34471940A4B6210FF332E91275_200108_3946392_Someone_released_bedbugs_inside_a_Pennsylvania_W_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 03:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947105</guid>
      <title>Starbucks introduces new nondairy drinks, tests oat milk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE <br/> Good new overpriced coffee lovers, Starbucks unveiled two new dairy-free coffee drinks and announced it would be testing oat milk in select markets.  <br/>For those prone to the squirts when downing dairy, the Seattle coffee juggernaut has got your bowels covered with their new Almondmilk Honey Flat White and Coconutmilk Latte. <br/>In a Jan. 7 press release, the coffee chain said their new minus-the-moo drinks will be available at all locations in the U.S. and Oh Canada. <br/>Starbucks describes the Almondmilk Honey Flat White concoction as a "coffee-forward beverage with real honey to complement the almond flavor with a touch of sweetness." <br/>That's a lot of words for a coffee with almond milk. <br/>If you're wondering how they came up with the Coconutmilk Latte<br/>HINT, it's in the name<br/>product developers slapped shots of Starbucks Blonde Espresso with steamed coconut milk and sugar, aka Starbucks secret ingredient.    <br/>Customers at 1,300 participating stores in Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Michigan, Minnesota, Missouri and Wisconsin will also get the chance to be lab rats as Starbucks tests out oat milk as another non-dairy option. <br/>Here's a question...if you live in the Midwest, can you order an Almond Coconut Oat Milk super triple threat combo latte?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/starbucks-introduces-new-nondairy-drinks-tests-oat-milk-3947105</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947105/3947105_D5AA5A1709574C1DBD567245E9F05C58_200109_3947105_Starbucks_introduces_new_nondairy_drinks__tests__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948647</guid>
      <title>Taco Bell robber makes himself a meal and has a nap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAWRENCEVILLE, GEORGIA <br/> A burglar who broke into a Taco Bell in Georgia made the opposite of a quick getaway after he made himself a snack and then had a nap. <br/>According to ABC News, the Gwinnett County Police Department released photos and surveillance video of a guy who broke into the Taco Hell on Dec. 25, because they need help locating him. <br/>Surveillance footage shows the man crawl through the drive-thru window around 12:15 a.m.  <br/>After getting in, he then makes a run for the <br/> fryers, which he proceeds to turn on. <br/>The taco thief then walks into the cooler and comes out with a whole mess of food, which he then whips up and scarfs down like a champ.  <br/>That's apparently when he gets hit with a serious case of the itis, which knocks him out for a good couple of hours right on the floor.  <br/>Sleepy head finally wakes up from his slumber around 3 a.m. <br/><br/>He then five finger discounts a laptop and a tablet, before making his way out the back door, which triggers an alarm.  <br/>When the cops showed up on scene, the burrito bandito was nowhere to be seen. <br/>Officers were called back to the fine dining establishment when it opened because a manager found the suspect's headphones and black beanie cap.<br/>The manager told police that the suspect might have worked at Taco Bell before as he knew how to use the fryer and where all the fine quality food was located.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taco-bell-robber-makes-himself-a-meal-and-has-a-nap-3948647</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948647/3948647_F9B604126A6A42DC8A1FAF18BB6E9B5F_200113_3948647_Taco_Bell_robber_makes_himself_a_meal_and_has_a__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 03:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948642</guid>
      <title>Taco Bell robber makes himself a meal and has a nap</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAWRENCEVILLE, GEORGIA <br/> A burglar who broke into a Taco Bell in Georgia made the opposite of a quick getaway after he made himself a snack and then had a nap. <br/>According to ABC News, the Gwinnett County Police Department released photos and surveillance video of a guy who broke into the Taco Hell on Dec. 25, because they need help locating him. <br/>Surveillance footage shows the man crawl through the drive-thru window around 12:15 a.m.  <br/>After getting in, he then makes a run for the <br/> fryers, which he proceeds to turn on. <br/>The taco thief then walks into the cooler and comes out with a whole mess of food, which he then whips up and scarfs down like a champ.  <br/>That's apparently when he gets hit with a serious case of the itis, which knocks him out for a good couple of hours right on the floor.  <br/>Sleepy head finally wakes up from his slumber around 3 a.m. <br/><br/>He then five finger discounts a laptop and a tablet, before making his way out the back door, which triggers an alarm.  <br/>When the cops showed up on scene, the burrito bandito was nowhere to be seen. <br/>Officers were called back to the fine dining establishment when it opened because a manager found the suspect's headphones and black beanie cap.<br/>The manager told police that the suspect might have worked at Taco Bell before as he knew how to use the fryer and where all the fine quality food was located.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taco-bell-robber-makes-himself-a-meal-and-has-a-nap-3948642</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948642/3948642_49A5D0033CF44E90A5AE4FB2E5C5133C_200113_3948642_Taco_Bell_robber_makes_himself_a_meal_and_has_a__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 02:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949937</guid>
      <title>Dog-walking app Wag loses another doggo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN ANTONIO <br/> It appears that the dog-walking app Wag is really great at walking your dog, however it's the returning your pet part that has them perplexed.<br/>According to the New York Post, Wag has already been accused of losing more than a dozen doggos across the country<br/>well, it looks like they can add another one to the list. <br/>San Antonio resident Cody Martinez told the Post that he travels a lot for work and used the app to take care of his two huskies Sozin and Ozai while he was out of town. <br/>Martinez said that on Oct. 4 while he was working in Philadelphia, he got a call from a Wag representative saying Sozin had gotten loose from his collar during a walk and was missing.<br/><br/>The rep told him to relax, and said the company would be putting up flyers in the area and that it was opening up a tip line so people could call in sightings. <br/><br/>Guess what? The flyers didn't work, but Wag kept giving Martinez the run around and failed to take other actions like dispatching dog trackers. <br/>Even though he repeatedly asked for more help besides flyers, he wasn't offered a tracker until 10 days after Sozin went missing. <br/><br/>By the time the tracker was actually sent, three weeks had passed. The tracker then told Martinez that if she would have gotten there earlier, they might have had a better shot.  <br/>Wag was then kind enough to call Martinez last Friday, more than three months after Sozin went missing, to say they were cutting ties and giving up the search. <br/>A Wag spokesperson said it had suspended the walker who lost Sozin and that it continues to monitor the tip line for any Sozin sightings.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dog-walking-app-wag-loses-another-doggo-3949937</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949937/3949937_B7E1FE96621C4952A92A7A03D3971B55_200115_3949937_Dog_walking_app_Wag_loses_another_doggo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 14:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949906</guid>
      <title>Delta aircraft dumps fuel on school before landing at LAX</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOS ANGELES <br/> Delta Airlines Flight 89 was enroute to Shanghai from Los Angeles International Airport on Tuesday when the plane experienced an engine issue shortly after takeoff. <br/><br/>The plane then proceeded to return to the airport and release jet fuel before conducting an emergency landing. The jet fuel was dumped over a Los Angeles schoolyard and school buildings, reports NBC News. <br/><br/>According to the Los Angeles County Fire Department, at least 20 children and 11 adults are being treated for minor injuries for fuel exposure. Those affected were being treated by firefighters on the scene for skin irritation and breathing problems.<br/><br/>The fire department said none of the injured needed to be hospitalized.<br/><br/>The airline explained the release of fuel is required as part of standard procedure to reach a safe landing weight, Reuters reports, citing a statement from Delta Airlines.<br/><br/>In a statement on Twitter, the Federal Aviation Administration explained that there are special fuel-dumping procedures which require airplanes to release jet fuel over designated unpopulated areas. The agency said that the fuel is typically released at higher altitudes so that it dissolves before reaching the ground.<br/><br/>The FAA said in the same statement that it is "thoroughly investigating" the circumstances around the incident.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/delta-aircraft-dumps-fuel-on-school-before-landing-at-lax-3949906</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949906/3949906_E9A1A5EF689846FAB0A92D1B7F3BEC5A_200115_3949906_Delta_aircraft_dumps_fuel_on_school_before_landi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 13:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950079</guid>
      <title>Man challenges ex-wife to 'trial by combat' to settle legal dispute</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHELBY, IOWA <br/> A man has filed a plea to challenge his ex-wife to 'trial by combat' after claiming that along with her attorney, have both "destroyed him legally."<br/><br/>40-year-old David Ostrom, from Kansas, appealed to a judge in Iowa that he should be granted the right to 'trial by combat' to end his ongoing dispute with his ex-wife, Bridgette Ostrom and her attorney, Mr. Hudson. He claimed that trial by combat has "never been explicitly banned or restricted as a right in these United States." <br/><br/>He then went on to ask the judge for 12 weeks, so he could either "source" or "forge" Japanese samurai swords.<br/><br/>Ostrom said his ex-wife could nominate her attorney as "her champion," however, faced with the prospect of death, her attorney argued the possibility of loss of life outweighed the ramifications of property tax and custody issues. <br/><br/>Mr. Hudson also asked the court to suspend Ostrom's visitation rights and order him to undergo a court-ordered psychological evaluation. The judge, Craig Dreismeier said that he won't be issuing a decision anytime soon and that no further action would be taken at this time.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-challenges-ex-wife-to-trial-by-combat-to-settle-legal-dispute-3950079</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950079/3950079_8E338E45638A41E49A8D22EE4B817621_200116_3950079_Man_challenges_ex_wife_to__trial_by_combat__to_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 02:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952376</guid>
      <title>Man hiding for weeks in grocery store ceiling still at large</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUBURN, WASHINGTON <br/> You've heard of people living in airports, attics, even in cupboards under the stairs. But living in a store ceiling <br/> that might be a first.<br/><br/>Cops in Auburn, Washington released surveillance footage of a man they say has been living in the rafters of a grocery store for weeks and emerging only to pilfer goods.<br/><br/>King5 News reports that on Christmas Day, police were called to Haggen Northwest Fresh Market for what was initially thought to be a burglary. They found evidence that someone had accessed a vent in the roof, including jackets, gloves, tools, debris, and even a length of rope.<br/><br/>The cops only realized someone was living inside the store after Haggen employees heard footsteps overhead and saw someone's legs dangling out of the storage closet ceiling.<br/><br/>When they pulled surveillance footage, they saw a perp wearing a face mask and an all-black ensemble, walking the aisles with thousands of dollars worth of cigarettes in a bag.<br/><br/>Police spent about four and a half hours up in the rafters trying to hunt the thief, but no dice. Even heat-mapping infrared technology and K9 units were no use.<br/><br/>So basically, the perp managed to outsmart and out-hide the po-po and is still somewhere in there, living off the store. <br/><br/>Gotta give him props though. What better place to squat in that inside a grocery store.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-hiding-for-weeks-in-grocery-store-ceiling-still-at-large-3952376</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952376/3952376_7EFAFCCB825949E8B9ED8F94DF958024_200121_3952376_Man_hiding_for_weeks_in_grocery_store_ceiling_st_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 04:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953049</guid>
      <title>Amtrak quotes two wheelchair users $25K for train ride</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHICAGO <br/> You're charging HOW MUCH for a train ticket?!<br/><br/>For normal people, hopping on an Amtrak to go from Chicago to Bloomington costs all of 16 bucks. But for two disabled riders using power wheelchairs, Amtrak quoted a whopping $25,000 for the same two-hour train ride.<br/><br/>NPR reports that the two are part of a group from the disability service and advocacy organization Access Living, and had reached out to Amtrak for travel arrangements to go to a conference in Bloomington.<br/><br/>The group's transportation policy director Adam Ballard says they've been booking train trips with Amtrak for years.<br/><br/>In the past, larger groups with 10 to 15 wheelchair users have been accommodated on the trains. Amtrak simply took out seats to fit in more wheelchairs, for only a couple hundred dollars extra.<br/><br/>But Amtrak agents cited a new policy for reconfiguring a train car, saying taking out extra seats would now cost over 25 Gs, as it means taking a car out of service.<br/><br/>For that price, Ballard and company might as well just buy themselves a car.<br/><br/>Unsurprisingly, Amtrak received serious backlash when news of the sky-high ticket prices got out.<br/><br/>Senator Tammy Duckworth, a veteran who lost both legs in the Iraq War, called the price quote "outrageous" and said Amtrak "must do better moving forward." <br/><br/>Fortunately, the PR folks at Amtrak realized how hot of a mess they were in and quickly backpedaled. NPR reports they told Access Living on Monday that they would accommodate all the wheelchairs onboard for the price of a regular ticket.<br/><br/>It only took a crap ton of media and public criticism but hey, all's well that ends well.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/amtrak-quotes-two-wheelchair-users-25k-for-train-ride-3953049</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953049/3953049_648C2AF6ECAA450D844CF740C9711F67_200122_3953049_Amtrak_quotes_two_wheelchair_users__25K_for_trai_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 09:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953634</guid>
      <title>Feral cats break into body farm to eat cadavers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WHITEWATER, COLORADO <br/> Feral cats broke into a Colorado body farm to munch on some choice cadavers. But scientists don't mind &#8211; it's all in the name of science!<br/><br/>For the uninitiated, body farms aren't as gruesome as the name implies. It's simply a facility where scientists observe and record how the body decomposes over time. So less horror flick and more CSI.<br/><br/>At this farm &#8211; Colorado Mesa University's Forensic Investigation Research Station &#8211; there were fences both above and below ground as well as infrared cameras. <br/><br/>Newsweek reports that donor bodies were placed three meters apart and checked weekly for decomp.<br/><br/>The cadavers of man and a woman in their 70s had been placed five or six days earlier when a pair of feral cats broke in and started scavenging the bodies.<br/><br/>Like bobcats, their favorite bits were soft tissues in the shoulder and arms. Housecats, when they do munch on cadavers, tend to go for facial tissue.<br/><br/>The felines came by for a snack twice, but stopped coming when the bodies began going into moist decomposition. Clearly, it doesn't matter whether cats are feral or domesticated &#8211; they're still finicky!<br/><br/>Scientists weren't really upset about the break-in &#8211; they actually thought it helped them learn how to distinguish cause-of-death injuries from damage inflicted postmortem. <br/><br/>Guess it's a win-win situation for man and cat!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/feral-cats-break-into-body-farm-to-eat-cadavers-3953634</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953634/3953634_EC9F6AE27B264C7FBDD0A537C1E25996_200123_3953634_Feral_cats_break_into_body_farm_to_eat_cadavers_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 08:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955119</guid>
      <title>Woman waiting for call from God drives into oncoming traffic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEATHERLY, PENNSYLVANIA <br/> Oh lord. A woman who has somehow managed to survive more than 31 years on this planet actually drove into oncoming traffic as a way to test out her faith. <br/>According to Lehigh Valley Live, Nedejda Reilly is charged with aggravated assault and other offenses over allegations she purposely caused an accident on Jan. 7 on Route 93 close to Weatherly, about 45 miles north of Allentown.<br/>Reilly told state troopers she had been driving around for a few hours waiting for a calling from God. <br/>After driving with traffic got her nowhere, she decided to drive straight toward an oncoming vehicle instead. <br/>Trooper Bruce Balliet said in an arrest affidavit that, "Reilly related God took care of her by not having her injured."<br/>"Reilly expressed no concerns or remorse for the victims. Reilly also stated she did not care if the other people were injured because God would have taken care of them."<br/>Well God must have been busy because the two other people in the other car had to be taken to the hospital and treated for injuries. <br/>The online court docket indicated Reilly's $50,000 bail was revoked last week.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-waiting-for-call-from-god-drives-into-oncoming-traffic-3955119</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955119/3955119_2C14534BEB1F4D81848AEEF6A60266C3_200127_3955119_Woman_waiting_for_call_from_God_drives_into_onco_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955101</guid>
      <title>Kobe Bryant, daughter die in helicopter crash in California</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CALABASAS, CALIFORNIA <br/> One of the greatest athletes to ever play the game of basketball<br/> Kobe Bryant<br/>has died in a helicopter crash in California. <br/>The New York Times reports that the 41-year-old retired NBA player and his 13-year-old daughter Gianna tragically lost their lives in the crash in Calabasas on Sunday. <br/>CNN reports that Bryant and Gianna were supposed to be at the Mamba Sports Academy in Thousand Oaks for a basketball game on Sunday. <br/>According to CNN, there was extremely low visibility at the time of the crash and conditions were foggy and cloudy with drizzle. <br/><br/>LA County Fire Department Capt. Tony Imbredna said he didn't immediately know whether the Sikorsky S-76B helicopter radioed a distress signal. <br/>He told reporters, "individuals that saw the aircraft said it was coming down at a fairly significant rate of speed and impacted the ground on the hillside."<br/><br/>According to Los Angeles County sheriff Alex Villanueva at a press conference, Kobe was among 8 passengers traveling aboard the aircraft along with one pilot. All nine people were killed in the accident. <br/>According to Los Angeles County Fire Department Chief Daryl Osby, the chopper crashed about 30 miles northwest of downtown L.A. and caused a brush fire. <br/>Bryant leaves behind his wife and three daughters. His passing has sent shockwaves across the NBA and around the world. Rest in peace Mamba.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/kobe-bryant-daughter-die-in-helicopter-crash-in-california-3955101</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955101/3955101_DC619715E978466E9C55F1BEC103E4F6_200127_3955101_Kobe_Bryant__daughter_die_in_helicopter_crash_in_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 08:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955323</guid>
      <title>US Space Force logo boldly goes when others have gone before</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> President Donald Trump officially dropped the brand spanking new U.S. Space Force logo on January 24, and it boldly went where no man has gone before<br/>except maybe Star Trek. <br/>Space reports that Donald unveiled the new Space Force logo over Twitter, his unofficial spokesman. <br/>According to Space, Trump has been using social media recently to announce news for the newest branch of the U.S. military that included the service's new threads and the swearing in of Gen. John W. Raymond as Chief of Space Operations. <br/>Trump tweeted, "After consultation with our Great Military Leaders, designers, and others, I am pleased to present the new logo for the United States Space Force, the Sixth Branch of our Magnificent Military!"<br/><br/>Twitter users being Twitter users couldn't help but point out the striking resemblance to the Star Trek logo. Set phasers to copy. <br/>However, others pointed out that the new logo got its inspiration from the existing Air Force Command logo.<br/>That being said<br/>it still kind of looks like a close Trekky cousin.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/us-space-force-logo-boldly-goes-when-others-have-gone-before-3955323</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955323/3955323_337CA34C8C1F4F0694B4D9DD8F4EC265_200128_3955323_US_Space_Force_logo_boldly_goes_when_others_have_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 03:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956763</guid>
      <title>Harvard professor charged with hiding illegal ties to China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS  <br/> A Harvard professor is in big trouble with the feds for lying about his ties with China.<br/><br/>According to court documents, Charles Lieber headed Harvard University's Lieber Research Group, and got over $15 million in grants from the U.S. National Institutes of Health and Department of Defense.<br/><br/>What he failed to mention was that he was also on another country's payroll. <br/><br/>The BBC reports that in 2011, Lieber was recruited by China into its Thousand Talents Plan, which is designed to lure foreign scientists and research specialists to China.<br/><br/>He joined the Wuhan University of Technology as a scientist, and was paid a salary of $50 Gs a month and up to $158,000 in living expenses to set up a research lab, apply for patents, and publish articles on the Chinese university's behalf.<br/><br/>Lieber was arrested at his office on Tuesday for concealing his Chinese funding, and remains in federal custody.<br/><br/>Prosecutors also announced charges for Boston University robotics researcher Yangqing Ye, who sent documents and information to China and hid the fact that she was a lieutenant for the People's Liberation Army.<br/><br/>Just last month, authorities also nabbed a Chinese cancer researcher for stealing specimen vials from a lab and attempting to smuggle them back into China inside a sock in his luggage.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/harvard-professor-charged-with-hiding-illegal-ties-to-china-3956763</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956763/3956763_266CED41CBA74BE0A7CC258C430DCC22_200131_3956763_Harvard_professor_charged_with_hiding_illegal_ti_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>US</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 09:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
