<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3929989</guid>
      <title>Spoilt man-child keys BMW so daddy has to buy it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGXI, CHINA <br/> Surveillance footage from inside a BMW showroom caught a 22-year-old man key a dark blue BMW because he wanted his dad to buy it for him.  <br/><br/>Pear Video reports that when local police arrived, the man explained that his dad had promised to buy him a new car as a gift for passing his driving test, however, he had yet to make good on his word, prompting his son to force his hand by keying the BMW.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/spoilt-man-child-keys-bmw-so-daddy-has-to-buy-it-3929989</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/882/7D9/8827D95AF2943C820786B8871E727A72.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929989/3929989_890E271F37B240FE9BA7606C38F8E47F_191203_3929989_Spoilt_man_child_keys_BMW_so_daddy_has_to_buy_it_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 09:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929964</guid>
      <title>India tiger searches for prey, mate in longest walk ever</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALL OVER INDIA <br/> A tiger in India has gone on the longest walk ever, logging in over 1,300 kilometers in just five months.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the two-and-a-half-year-old male was fitted with a radio collar, and has been on the move since it left its home in a wildlife sanctuary in June.<br/><br/>The tiger, called C1, travelled around the western state of Maharashtra, walking back and forth over farms, waterways, and highways. At one point, it even popped into the neighboring state.<br/><br/>It hides during the day and comes out at night, and has been surviving on wild pigs and cattle. Experts believe it's likely on the lookout for territory, food, and a mate. But since most of the potential tiger areas have no vacancy, it's had to explore a heckuva lot more.<br/><br/>Most humans in the area are oblivious that a big striped cat has been schlepping around. And except for accidentally injuring one man who came across it, there's been no serious conflict.<br/><br/>Still, wildlife officials say C1 needs to be recaptured and relocated to the forest to avoid any other accidents. There's also a chance they'll lose contact soon, since the battery on the collar is down to 20%.<br/><br/>So really, who knows until when we'll all be privy to the giant cat's journey?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/india-tiger-searches-for-prey-mate-in-longest-walk-ever-3929964</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BA1/132/BA11321E1420EE6C80590170D85C92DC.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929964/3929964_F6C1228E615C4D22B6B47AF8F684C74E_191203_3929964_India_tiger_searches_for_prey__mate_in_longest_w_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 09:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930788</guid>
      <title>Three missing in Chinese sinkhole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TIANHE, GUANGZHOU, CHINA <br/> Three people have been missing since Sunday morning after falling into a massive sinkhole in the southern Chinese city of Guangzhou.<br/><br/>The road in the city's Tianhe district suddenly caved in around 9:30 a.m local time, just as a street-cleaning vehicle and a scooter were driving over it. <br/><br/>Chinese outlet, The National Business Daily report that the area below the road was, in fact, a subway line that was undergoing construction; the estimated depth of the collapse is thought to be around 38 meters. <br/><br/>In an effort to find the missing three people, more than 1,100 rescue workers, and 192 rescue vehicles have taken to the hazardous area, however, search and rescue efforts have been delayed as the collapse continues to expand outwards.<br/><br/>Workers tried to fill the expanding hole to reinforce its slopes to avoid further collapses.<br/><br/>The individuals of the street cleaning vehicle were identified as a 51-year father and his 26-year-old son. The rider of the scooter has yet to be identified.<br/><br/>Construction workers in the metro tunnel below were evacuated. The cause of the incident, however, is still under investigation.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/three-missing-in-chinese-sinkhole-3930788</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B67/548/B67548E8B258AEDDC65562F20ACE0CB1.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3930788/3930788_14383A975EF74083906B80A7D1AE8F23_191205_3930788_Three_missing_in_Chinese_sinkhole_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 02:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931070</guid>
      <title>Beijing employs 'influencers' to spread communism</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> China's United Front Work Department aims to enlist online 'influencers' to spread the core values of the communist party. <br/><br/>Officials from China's cyber administration along with propaganda specialists from across the country met to discuss ways to adopt influencers such as makeup teachers and stunt performers into their arsenal.<br/><br/>You Quan, the department head of the United Front, said, "We need to build an online personnel team, to guide them to play an active role in leading public opinion and other areas."<br/><br/>He added, "We will work hard to surround them by the Communist Party's side, to concentrate the wisdom and power for achieving the rejuvenation of the Chinese people and the Chinese dream."<br/><br/>From last year, China's United Front Work Department has since expanded, with it now getting a say in areas such as ethnic policies and religious affairs. <br/><br/>The term "online personnel" was defined as those who command influence among their followers, either by shaping public opinion or by encouraging the public to react to an event in a certain way. <br/><br/>Author and political commentator, Sonny Lo Shiu-Hing said that it wasn't at all surprising Beijing wanted to "woo" online influencers, because the communist party wants to control all media.<br/><br/>The United Front set out three recruitment tasks, train the influencers, encouraging them to produce "healthy content" and most worryingly make them actively engage in major online propaganda.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/beijing-employs-influencers-to-spread-communism-3931070</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B77/1E0/B771E0D1ADD939249E866690A45D92E8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3931070/3931070_033E1E8E6F1B4704B79C33E1FD84435F_191205_3931070_Beijing_employs__influencers__to_spread_communis_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931424</guid>
      <title>Zhengzhou subway in China using face recognition at all stations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHENGZHOU, CHINA <br/> As cities across China continue to testing face recognition payment systems for subways, Zhengzhou has become the first to roll out the tech at all their stations. <br/>Forget to bring your wallet, metro card or mobile phone with your QR code? No worries, just use your face.  <br/>According to the Henan Daily, starting this week all commuters can pay at any Zhengzhou subway station using an optional face scan. <br/>The SCMP reported that according to the Henan Daily, since trials began in September, almost 200,000 commuters in Zhengzhou have given up their biometric data in order to use the metro face-scan payment app. <br/>All people have to do after they register is to show up at a subway turnstile scanner to scan their beautiful mugs. <br/>They get in right away while the fare is deducted through a pre-set payment plan. <br/>While Zhengzhou is the first city to roll out the face scanners at all stations, subways in other Chinese cities like Guangzhou, Nanjing and Shenzhen have also been testing out the tech. <br/>And as for privacy concerns? Hold on, what's privacy?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/zhengzhou-subway-in-china-using-face-recognition-at-all-stations-3931424</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FAC/B6F/FACB6FF7BF8F00504B35705DD4777775.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931424/3931424_2746A6D0984D454EA73B950CDD2AF298_191206_3931424_Zhengzhou_subway_in_China_using_face_recognition_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 07:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931729</guid>
      <title>China turns 'Great Cannon' on Hong Kong webforum</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> A Chinese cyberweapon dubbed the Great Cannon is launching DDoS attacks on a Hong Kong webform after years of silence, AT&T Cybersecurity reported on Wednesday.<br/><br/>The internet security developer says analysis indicates that the Cannon begin attacking the webforum named LIHKG in August.<br/><br/>According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Hong Kong activists have been using the forum to coordinate protests.<br/><br/>The Citizen Lab at the University of Toronto reported previously that the Great Cannon represents a "significant escalation in state-level information control."<br/><br/>AT&T Cybersecurity states that the Cannon inserts malicious Javascript code into browsers when users access servers within China's Great Firewall.<br/><br/>The Great Cannon then uses the code to send numerous requests to overwhelm the targeted domain's resources and to make it unavailable.<br/><br/>According to AT&T Cybersecurity, Great Cannon caused global disruption in 2015, when it was deployed against Github and the online freedom group GreatFire.org.<br/><br/>The security firm says that the Chinese-language news website Mingjingnews.com was attacked from two years ago and that it expects more attacks against LIHKG.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-turns-great-cannon-on-hong-kong-webforum-3931729</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C49/7F7/C497F7567B896512094313D9E0BCD83D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931729/3931729_E0E215EAD1904BA98067CC299A724FD6_191206_3931729_China_turns__Great_Cannon__on_Hong_Kong_webforum_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 14:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931715</guid>
      <title>Chinese kid gets stuck in claw machine trying to get prize</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHONGSHAN, CHINA <br/> A little dude in China is really into claw machine games, so much so that he actually got stuck in one. <br/>According to video posted to Miaopai, the boy was apparently out for a day at the mall with his mom in the Guangdong city of Zhongshan. <br/>While little man's mom was doing some shopping, a claw machine named "Come on baby" GRABBED the boy's attention. <br/>Staring back at the boy from inside the machine were plush toys galore, so he came up with an ingenious plan to get his hands on them.<br/>Using his Jack Ma-esque build, he was able to wiggle his way into the prize chute. <br/>But unfortunately, getting in proved to be a tad bit easier than extricating himself out of the grabber machine. <br/>At some point, people realized that the boy probably wasn't supposed to be there, so they called for help. <br/><br/>Video shows firefighters using a crowbar to gently pry the machine open and get the boy out. <br/>In the end, little guy made it out in one piece. <br/><br/>Hopefully this will be a lesson learned. Next time look for one with a bigger prize chute.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-kid-gets-stuck-in-claw-machine-trying-to-get-prize-3931715</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/618/8ED/6188ED64B2AC07F3E144748DF8D71785.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931715/3931715_DEC965816EE2407E81ADD1CCE882CA21_191206_3931715_Chinese_kid_gets_stuck_in_claw_machine_trying_to_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 13:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931976</guid>
      <title>Taipei ranked best city for expats to live and work...China numba 43</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> Taiwan is numba one for expats!<br/><br/>For the second year in a row, Taipei has been ranked the best city for expats to live and work in, while Shanghai and Beijing eat dust in 43rd and 60th place.<br/><br/>The survey by Internations asked about 25 different aspects of life, divided into: Quality of Urban Living, Getting Settled, Urban Work Life, and Finance and Housing.<br/><br/>Taipei reigned supreme as far as quality of life, transportation, healthcare, friendliness, and cost of living.<br/><br/>Shanghai was okay in the transportation, safety, and disposable income department, but people weren't crazy about air pollution and the Chinese intranet.<br/><br/>As for Beijing &#8211; how are they not lower on the list?? <br/><br/>No doubt China is going to get its panties in a twist about this ranking &#8211; not that anyone cares, because we all know Taiwan numba one, China numba forty three[b]!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taipei-ranked-best-city-for-expats-to-live-and-work--china-numba-43-3931976</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/194/A92/194A92AF7452081B5B4D6D2D3A02152C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/07/3931976/3931976_813C1CC65DE141B38F26C0B3AFC175E3_191207_3931976_Taipei_ranked_best_city_for_expats_to_live_and_w_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 09:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932870</guid>
      <title>China makes propaganda game that lets you hit HK protesters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> China is hitting back against the "Liberate Hong Kong" game by coming up with a version that lets you beat the protesters instead.<br/><br/>The anti-protest propaganda video game, called "Everyone Hit the Traitors," tells you right off the in big bold letters that "Hong Kong is part of China" and "can't be meddled with by outside powers."<br/><br/>When you click to play, it starts by saying there's a bunch of traitors colluding with Western powers and instigating protests in Hong Kong.<br/><br/>These traitors include activist Joshua Wong, media tycoon Jimmy Lai, and former Hong Kong chief secretary Anson Chan <br/> who are all depicted as caricatures.<br/><br/>Once you've chosen a traitor to target, it's time to beat him and his horde of young protesters, or "useless youths," by tapping them with a hand, flip-flop, or baseball bat. You can choose!<br/><br/>If any of the protesters make it across the screen, you lose <br/> but that's highly unlikely because they're lumbering so slowly.<br/><br/>The traitor needs a bit more tapping to be defeated and then arrested, but it's still not rocket science <br/> really, the only way to fail is if you do it on purpose.<br/><br/>In case you're interested in playing this Chinese propaganda game, it's free on dalaoshu.net, dalaoshu being the Chinese for "big rat." <br/><br/>Wow, subtle.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-makes-propaganda-game-that-lets-you-hit-hk-protesters-3932870</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/000/44C/00044C9DED0C3179D142CA26B6B6944F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932870/3932870_1B03122A073C447BBF4E2D1A81D4034F_191209_3932870_China_makes_propaganda_game_that_lets_you_hit_HK_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 14:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933067</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman swallows a massive tube</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGZHOU, CHINA <br/> 22-year-old Ms. Lu went to the hospital complaining about some nagging pains after she swallowed a straw, but not all is as it seems.<br/><br/>She said she was drinking a bubble tea when she suddenly swallowed the straw, however, on examination, the medical team discovered it was definitely not a straw. <br/><br/>The woman was immediately taken for scans at the Third Affiliated Hospital of South Medical University in Guangzhou, where doctors found a long plastic tube measuring 30 centimeters in length and 1.9 centimeters thick, deep in her esophagus and stomach. <br/><br/>Fortunately, Doctor Yue Hui removed the mysterious tube from her esophagus, pulling it out through her mouth.<br/><br/>The doctor explained that the woman suffered from stomach ulcers as a result of the tube, however, she is expected to make a full recovery.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-woman-swallows-a-massive-tube-3933067</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/61E/E37/61EE37696EFFF620CFCE6B8D2DBDABF8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933067/3933067_20B7853A68F3461CA1C342834819ED90_191210_3933067_Chinese_woman_swallows_a_massive_tube_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 06:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933509</guid>
      <title>Indian dancer shot for pausing during wedding performance</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TIKRA, INDIA <br/> An Indian dancer actually took one in the chin for stopping in the middle of a wedding performance in northern India.   <br/><br/>According to the Press Trust of India, the incident occurred on November 30 in Tikra village in the district of Chitrakoot in Uttar Pradesh. <br/>Video footage shows the woman dancing for the wedding celebration when the music system develops a bit of a glitch. <br/>And what do you do when you're dancing to music and the music stops? You pause and catch a breather. <br/><br/>Unfortunately, the 22-year-old dancer, identified only as Hina, caught a bullet to the face instead. <br/>Two others in the audience were also lucky enough to sustain minor gunshot wounds as well.<br/>According to police, Hina was taken to the hospital where she was treated for her injuries and was said to be out of danger.  <br/>Authorities say two men have been arrested for the boneheaded incident and are now facing attempted murder charges.  <br/>Hopefully the courts order these two knuckleheads to become dancers at weddings where everyone attending is strapped. That seems fair.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/indian-dancer-shot-for-pausing-during-wedding-performance-3933509</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D0F/416/D0F416823ACF5A276DCD0AE474865651.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933509/3933509_CA71CD7114BC4893AA8B13BBFA7C094E_191211_3933509_Indian_dancer_shot_for_pausing_during_wedding_pe_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 03:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934063</guid>
      <title>Chinese driver stuck waiting as thousands of geese cross road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANHUI PROVINCE <br/> Why did the goose cross the road? Apparently to join the thousands and thousands of fellow geese on the other side.<br/>Hilarious video footage posted to Weibo shows probably the most unlucky driver in the world on some random road in China's Anhui province stuck behind a mini army of geese. <br/>The driver, surnamed Yin, filmed his feathery roadblock consisting of a single-file line of geese about the length of the Great Wall.<br/>As the geese slowly and surely move in front of Yin, the massively long line can be seen extending off into the horizon. <br/>According to Yin, he waited for a good 15 minutes before the owner of the geese showed up to clear a path for him.   <br/>Yin then got on his way, while the geese did the same.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-driver-stuck-waiting-as-thousands-of-geese-cross-road-3934063</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/005/476/005476DDD1BCB8A1BEF1AFB38B882A3F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934063/3934063_204F0756ABB442038A3D6EAA4EA7B077_191212_3934063_Chinese_driver_stuck_waiting_as_thousands_of_gee_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 05:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933980</guid>
      <title>Airport official axed for making ambulance pick up friends</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> Getting to and from airports these days is annoying enough to make any person want to give up traveling all together. That is unless you have friends in high places. <br/>Chinese netizens were outraged yet again over the weekend after a video of an ambulance picking up a group of douchey travelers outside the Shanghai Pudong International Airport went viral.<br/>According to a report by Shanghai's airport authority, a manager surnamed Yu called an airport ambulance and demanded the driver race over to Terminal 1 to pick up his wife, kid, and three friends, who had just arrived back from vacation. <br/>Oh yeah, they also had a small army of duty-free shopping bags with them. <br/>Video shows the ambulance with its lights on parked in a no parking zone as the people load their booty into the emergency vehicle. <br/>The ambulance apparently then drove the shopaholics to an airport parking lot.  <br/>Nothing like a good old abuse of power to start the day. Unfortunately for Yu, he was given the axe and will also receive a nasty Communist Party finger wagging. <br/>As for the ambulance guys, one driver was given the boot while another was given some demerits. <br/>And if you're wondering how all the duty-free shopping bags are doing, after being transported to the hospital for a thorough examination, they were released and are doing okay.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/airport-official-axed-for-making-ambulance-pick-up-friends-3933980</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/58F/137/58F1375651AE4E1CB8AC42F84279C32A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3933980/3933980_4981F56E8E444ABB8B2D26A3BDFE59C1_191212_3933980_Airport_official_axed_for_making_ambulance_pick__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 01:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934589</guid>
      <title>Xiamen subway collapses in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIAMEN, CHINA <br/> A subway in Xiamen, China has collapsed.<br/><br/>At around 9:52 last night, a sinkhole suddenly opened up. The collapse damaged underground water pipes, leading to a burst of sewage flooding the station and railroad tracks. The underground soil was washed away, causing the road surface to sink and form a 500 square meter hole. <br/><br/>Two cars fell into the hole created by the collapse, the two drivers were able to evacuate safely.<br/><br/>Xiamen Metro Line 2 just passed examination 2 weeks ago with officials claiming the construction as good. <br/><br/>It is unclear if people have been trapped or injured due to the collapse.<br/><br/>As of 8:30 (GMT+8) this morning, all subway lines have resumed operation.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/xiamen-subway-collapses-in-china-3934589</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/003/D46/003D4658C713124D5758F0276FD102AD.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934589/3934589_2CAF566CAA274661A1299B76FA96F851_191213_3934589_Xiamen_subway_collapses_in_China_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 03:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935011</guid>
      <title>Nintendo Switch now on sale in China with only one game</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> The wait for Chinese video game aficionados is finally over as the Nintendo Switch is now officially on sale.<br/>The console, which first hit markets in 2017, can be hooked up to the TV or played on the go. <br/>And with over 1900 games<br/>according to Wikipedia<br/>gamers have no shortage of selection. <br/>Only one problem though. In China, video games have to be approved by the super fun-loving government before they can be sold to the public. <br/>So remember the 1900 plus games we mentioned earlier? Just subtract all but one from that. <br/>That's right<br/>Super Smash Bros is the only official Nintendo game you can buy in China if you drop $298 for the Switch console. <br/>According to BBC, in order to do business in China, Nintendo was forced to partner with Chinese firm Tencent. <br/>Nintendo is hoping Mario Kart 8 Deluxe and Mario Odyssey will also be added to their amazing China selection, but have yet to be given the old Panda nod. <br/>They said they hope to have between 10 and 20 games for the China Switch by the end of 2020. Ten to 20?? Let's be real, they may not be able to even get that many. <br/><br/>But with a power packed selection like that, Chinese gamers will no doubt SWITCH in no time.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nintendo-switch-now-on-sale-in-china-with-only-one-game-3935011</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/795/A98/795A986B3B9057067F048F86830D6BCA.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3935011/3935011_14BE1B7C52F044B1B784DB0C0CEA6F69_191213_3935011_Nintendo_Switch_now_on_sale_in_China_with_only_o_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 13:34:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936369</guid>
      <title>China blocks football game over player's Uyghur tweet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Arsenal's German midfielder, Mesut Ozil took to social media to condemn China's treatment of Uyghur Muslims. China retaliated by removing Arsenal's English Premier League fixture from state TV.<br/><br/>In his social media post, Ozil, who is a Muslim, called Uighurs, "warriors who resist persecution" and criticized both China and the silence of Muslims in response. <br/><br/>China, however, denies the mistreatment of Muslims and always has, standing by the fact they are instead being "educated" in "vocational training centers" to combat violent religious extremism. <br/><br/>The Global Times, a Chinese state-run paper, described Ozil's comments as "false" and claimed he had "disappointed" football authorities. The Chinese Football Association said Ozil's comments were "unacceptable" and had "hurt the feelings" of Chinese fans. <br/><br/>The BBC reported that CCTV instead showed Sunday's game between Tottenham and Wolves.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-blocks-football-game-over-player-s-uyghur-tweet-3936369</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1AA/76F/1AA76F153A522885B06542FB46250A83.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936369/3936369_EDC9588BDDF04A698925ADBE4DEA4F34_191217_3936369_China_blocks_football_game_over_player_s_Uyghur__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 01:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936752</guid>
      <title>Man folded in half for 28 years finally stands straight up</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA <br/>  A Chinese man is looking at the world from a whole new perspective now that he's finally able to stand straight after suffering from an aggressive form of arthritis that left his face jammed up against his thighs for almost three decades. <br/>According to Chinese media, 46-year-old Li Hua was diagnosed with ankylosing spondylitis in 1991 when he was only 18. <br/>The intense pain in his joints forced him to become more and more hunchbacked over time. <br/>His family from the Hunan city of Yongzhou didn't have the money to get medical treatment so his entire upper body eventually folded onto his lower limbs in a permanent bending pose. <br/>According to Li, his condition got a lot worse over the past five years to the point where he couldn't sit up straight or lie down flat, and was having trouble eating and drinking.<br/><br/>Surgeons from the Shenzhen University General Hospital broke and rebuilt Li's entire spine in a series of four operations this year.<br/>During the four-phase surgery, Li was able to first sit up, then lift his head, then lie flat. <br/>Li is now able to stand tall after 28 year long years. He is now able to get around with the help of a walker, and should regain normal mobility with a couple of months of physical therapy. <br/>Guess things really are looking up for Li.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-folded-in-half-for-28-years-finally-stands-straight-up-3936752</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A9A/691/A9A691791F61F67AB36FDB440583C140.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936752/3936752_F8EDCD33645E4483BF574DF02D0D85A8_191217_3936752_Man_folded_in_half_for_28_years_finally_stands_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 12:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936685</guid>
      <title>Cobras are invading home toilets in Jakarta</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WEST JAKARTA, INDONESIA <br/> Imagine going to your bathroom and coming face to face with a cobra rearing its flared head.<br/><br/>That's the kind of terror residents in West Jakarta, Indonesia faced on Sunday after tens of the venomous snakes invaded their crappers.<br/><br/>All in all, there were 18 cobras averaging a length of 20 centimeters, which took four firemen 30 minutes to round up. They will eventually be handed over to the Indonesia Sioux Snake Foundation.<br/><br/>The Jakarta Post reports that according to a homeowner named Hera, the snakes crept inside through the drainage system, which is connected to a warehouse.<br/><br/>Workers there had previously encountered snakes too, likely because of its proximity to a cemetery and plot of land where bamboo trees grow and where the cobras breed.<br/><br/>The cemetery was just renovated, so the slippery serpents were probably scouting for a new pad when residents spotted them in the toilets and slithering into bedroom. <br/><br/>According to reptile observer Arbi Krisna, the snake invasion isn't surprising, since we're in the middle of snake hatching season. <br/><br/>So peep before you pee, and make sure to clean the moist, dark, and quiet places where snakes lay their eggs.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cobras-are-invading-home-toilets-in-jakarta-3936685</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/285/F7E/285F7EF33215AFB18C0A02CBD2A60EFA.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936685/3936685_0C63B99F1FA14ABFB1D3112631772765_191217_3936685_Cobras_are_invading_home_toilets_in_Jakarta_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937463</guid>
      <title>Couple's photo session burns down forest</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGYUAN, GUANGDONG, CHINA <br/> A couple have been detained after triggering a huge forest fire during a photoshoot atop a mountain. <br/><br/>The couple began setting off fireworks which resulted in the trees below catching ablaze, sending flames roaring up the mountainside.<br/><br/>The pair were since detained for 15 days, however, as it stands it's unknown if they will face further charges.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/couple-s-photo-session-burns-down-forest-3937463</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/99D/06C/99D06CED3A147A8C96C25C6084428105.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937463/3937463_DB1B63A37E054063B0C7C959D3A09D24_191219_3937463_Couple_s_photo_session_burns_down_forest_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 01:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3938443</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman left with 4 melons after botched boob job</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA <br/> Bigger is always better and the more the merrier<br/>okay, maybe not in this case. <br/>A Chinese woman who intelligently spent $32,500 for a new rack was left with a bit more than she bargained for. Where there were two, now there are four. Huh!?<br/>According to a report on Bilibili, a mother of one from Shenzhen felt unsatisfied with mother nature's plans for her figure after childbirth, so she decided to put work in to get it all back. <br/>Actually, she just went under the knife instead. <br/>Unfortunately for the lady, the plastic surgeons from IF Aesthetic Surgery in Guangzhou slightly miscalculated the number of implants needed and went with four.  <br/>The woman said she was told by the plastic doctors that she should buy two pairs of implants. No alarm bells went off at this point?<br/>Despite getting knocked out, the woman said she also woke up during the surgery. And after it was over, she also found a large scar on her arm, which doctors say was a burn mark. <br/>Talking to a local reporter about her botched surgery, the woman said, "the upper parts are bigger, the lower parts are smaller; the upper parts are hard, the lower parts are soft."<br/>Apparently the Barbie doll doctors offered the woman a refund as well as an extra $4,300 for pain and suffering. <br/>Well, maybe next time she should go for six.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-woman-left-with-4-melons-after-botched-boob-job-3938443</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE8/8F4/EE88F448A8CCD6532F7B99F6ABBBEF1D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938443/3938443_3E5F55D1D59D45D698F87F3C5CB9D523_191220_3938443_Chinese_woman_left_with_4_melons_after_botched_b_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939499</guid>
      <title>North Korea has expanded its ballistic missile launcher factory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGSONG, NORTH KOREA <br/> Civilian satellite imagery by Planet Labs has revealed an expansion to the March 16 factory in North Korea's Pyongsong, NBC News reports.<br/><br/>Citing expert analysis given to the channel, NBC reports that these activities could mean North Korea will soon resume the testing of intercontinental ballistic missiles.<br/><br/>Analysis Jeffrey Lewis told the channel that a temporary structure has been erected at the March 16 factory.<br/><br/>Lewis, director of the East Asia Nonproliferation Program at the Middlebury Institute of International Studies, speculated that the structure is built to accommodate efforts to raise a missile launcher arm.<br/><br/>Lewis told CNN the March 16 factory is involved in manufacturing civilian vehicles and missile launchers.<br/><br/>Citing Lewis, CNN reported that the heavy-duty trucks built at the factory are powerful enough to transport large missiles.<br/><br/>Lewis told NBC the facility's expansion occurred after North Korea's leader Kim Jong-un visited the factory in June.<br/><br/>NBC speculates that the revelation could mean North Korea will test launch a missile designed to be capable of reaching the U.S.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-has-expanded-its-ballistic-missile-launcher-factory-3939499</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E03/73B/E0373BE8FBBB4E6E17AB2EB580CBA58E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939499/3939499_8941932864424CDE9B3B6600F6FEED7F_191223_3939499_North_Korea_has_expanded_its_ballistic_missile_l_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 11:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939555</guid>
      <title>Master thief tries to steal money from ATM, gets trapped by door</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGYING, CHINA <br/> A master thief who tried to boost some cash from an ATM almost made a clean getaway if only it weren't for<br/>the door. <br/>According to a Pear Video, CCTV footage from a bank ATM in the Shandong city of Dongying captured a play by play of the finely planned heist on December 17. <br/>In the video, the man is seen walking up to the ATM, as the door closes behind him, which activates an automatic voice welcoming him. <br/>This clearly freaks the man out, which causes him to try and open the door to get out. Let's just say doors aren't this guy's forte. <br/>He fiddles with the pesky lock, but gets nowhere. It must have been made in China.<br/>The man then grabs the lid to the trash can and proceeds to smash it into the door with Hulk-like strength. <br/>When that doesn't work, he turns his focus to the ATM screen and starts to pound on it with the metal lid. <br/>He wasn't able to get the door open, or any money out of the machine, but he did succeed in setting off an alarm. <br/>Genius eventually got the door, but by that time, the cops had already shown up and promptly arrested him<br/>DOH.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/master-thief-tries-to-steal-money-from-atm-gets-trapped-by-door-3939555</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE5/7A1/EE57A172B9475AB6829CF98BFFA7731F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939555/3939555_78FD2A2BD9FA40F5B559B596A575B966_191223_3939555_Master_thief_tries_to_steal_money_from_ATM__gets_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 13:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939550</guid>
      <title>Tesco stops production at Chinese factory over alleged 'forced' labor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> Tesco has halted production of Christmas cards at a factory in China after a British girl found a message from workers inside one of them. <br/>The BBC reports that Florence Widdicombe found a note inside the card allegedly written by prisoners in Shanghai saying they were "forced to work against our will."<br/><br/>The message also said to, "please help us and notify rights organizations." <br/>Tesco naturally said they were "shocked" and added, "we would never allow prison labor in our supply chain." <br/>Well, then why are you guys having things made in China<br/>the home of forced labor?<br/>According to BBC, Florence was writing cards for her classmates when she found one that had already been written in. <br/>In all capitals, the message said, "We are foreign prisoners in Shanghai Qingpu prison China. Forced to work against our will. Please help us and notify human rights organizations."<br/>The message also asked anyone who found the message to contact British journalist Peter Humphrey who himself had also wasted time in Chinese prisons four years ago. <br/>Tesco claims that it has a "comprehensive auditing system" to ensure suppliers are not using prison labor. Clearly it's not that comprehensive. <br/>According to Tesco, the factory in question, Zhejiang Yunguang Printing, apparently was checked last month with no signs of prison labor. AKA<br/>they didn't have the prisoners working on the day the Tesco people were COMPREHENSIVELY doing their checks. <br/>Unfortunately for the prisoners, things will now probably just get worse for them as China clearly isn't going to stop using forced labor. <br/>Merry Christmas everyone!!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tesco-stops-production-at-chinese-factory-over-alleged-forced-labor-3939550</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/FD7/277/FD7277385B6F2A1F0C625A493E450C72.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939550/3939550_FBB0CC8A01194166AF83861C34120F87_191223_3939550_Tesco_stops_production_at_Chinese_factory_over_a_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 13:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939717</guid>
      <title>China removes Mesut Ozil from video game after Uyghur tweets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> In response to Mesut Ozil's tweets condemning China for its treatment of Uyghurs, the country has removed the Arsenal midfielder entierly from the Chinese version of the popular video game franchise, Pro Evolution Soccer.<br/><br/>NetEase, the publisher of PES, said Ozil had also been deleted from three existing titles too.<br/><br/>In a statement on Weibo, they said, "The German player Ozil posted an extreme statement about China on social media. The speech hurt the feelings of Chinese fans and violated the sports spirit of love and peace. We do not understand, accept or forgive this!"<br/><br/>Ozil's club, Arsenal has since distanced themselves from Ozil's comments and branded themselves as "apolitical."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-removes-mesut-ozil-from-video-game-after-uyghur-tweets-3939717</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/542/5A6/5425A6622DF5D14AD909A9C0D2147547.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939717/3939717_0B4B9A54DB9D4C8E94817C0AE3ED18D9_191224_3939717_China_removes_Mesut_Ozil_from_video_game_after_U_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 03:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940034</guid>
      <title>Couple gets hit in same spot 10 minutes apart for not looking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YICHANG, CHINA <br/> A couple in China were clearly meant to be after being struck trying to cross an insanely busy street in the exact same spot only 10 minutes apart for totally ignoring traffic rules.<br/>According to The Paper, police released CCTV footage of the hilarious incident which took place in the Hubei city of Yichang on December 17.<br/><br/>The wife is seen attempting to cut through traffic riding an electric bike when she totally doesn't look to see if, you know, a car might be coming, and gets up close and personal with the front end of a car in the right turn lane.  <br/>She gets pretty good airtime and falls off her bike, losing a shoe in the process. <br/>As the woman gets up, police come over and get her to the side of the road. <br/>End of story. Well, maybe not quite yet because about 10 minutes later, her dear hubby seeing all the commotion comes running over, choosing the exact same route his wife took. <br/>Guess we can all see where this wreck is headed. <br/>The guy makes his way successfully through the rows of cars until he was no longer successful. He then manages to get hit in the exact same spot as his wife. <br/>The match made in heaven didn't quite get to heaven, but they did get taken to the hospital. Lucky for them, neither have life-threatening injuries. <br/><br/>Guess there really is someone for everyone.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/couple-gets-hit-in-same-spot-10-minutes-apart-for-not-looking-3940034</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EA7/EA1/EA7EA13115036263ABE3D91C94377B00.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3940034/3940034_6D9FA2B25F2E444E9589B6378CA4FFE8_191224_3940034_Couple_gets_hit_in_same_spot_10_minutes_apart_fo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 11:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939971</guid>
      <title>Man jams 18-cm long bottle into his behind to scratch an itch</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA <br/> No one likes an itchy backside, but sometimes finding the right tool to help scratch that itch can be easier said than done. Just ask this man from China.<br/>According to a report over Weibo, a real do-it-yourself kind of guy from the Guangdong city of Dongguan had a serious case of the itchy itchies, but had nothing to scratch with. <br/>The 60-year-old man then enlisted the help of a 18-cm long glass bottle to do the dirty work. <br/>Unfortunately for the man, the bottle decided to get a bit cheeky and went it for a deeper look<br/>and then got stuck. <br/>The man then got himself over to the hospital and told doctors he was having trouble passing gas and dropping the kids off at the pool. <br/>It didn't take long for physicians to get to the BOTTOM of the discomfort after some all to clear x-rays. <br/>The doctor who treated the lucky man told local media that he could feel the bottle when touching the man's stomach. <br/>In the rear end, doctors were able to successfully extricate the man's bottle back scratcher via surgery. All's well that ends well.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-jams-18-cm-long-bottle-into-his-behind-to-scratch-an-itch-3939971</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D42/817/D4281744AB1BC932AEF033C1D3B64CF7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939971/3939971_7C0E43A6E798425185AE98D54BF0F387_191224_3939971_Man_jams_18_cm_long_bottle_into_his_behind_to_sc_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 09:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939943</guid>
      <title>Beijing bans medium and large dog breeds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Beijing has hit a new low as far as animal rights, banning medium to large dogs and threatening to sick the cops on them if the owners don't comply.<br/><br/>According to a legal notice reposted by Taiwan's Green Party, Beijing's southeast district of Tongzhou is banning residents from raising dogs taller than 35 centimeters.<br/><br/>Pet owners are given a three-day grace period after receiving the notice to "dispose" of their fur babies. If they don't comply, police officers will come and impound the animal, which in China basically means beating them to death in public.<br/><br/>Rather than risk such a brutal end for their beloved pets, many owners have chosen the lesser evil of having their fur babies euthanized at the vet.<br/><br/>CTS reports that some folks on Weibo can't afford to properly euthanize their pets, and have had to suffocate or kill the poor pups themselves.<br/><br/>Beijing animal rescue group CaliPaw has also been looking for volunteers with travel plans to San Francisco or L.A. to help rescue the dogs.<br/><br/>Tongzhou police say the Draconian ban is actually part of a list of dog management regulations that took effect in 2003, and justified its enforcement by saying there have been complaints since November about misbehaving dogs.<br/><br/>Yeah, no one's buying that. Congratulations, China, for reaching a whole 'nother level of cruel.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/beijing-bans-medium-and-large-dog-breeds-3939943</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/294/954/294954609C1125ED3D855CF1364F2A99.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939943/3939943_A45232DCC5E0412EAE64DF076D0A3607_191224_3939943_Beijing_bans_medium_and_large_dog_breeds_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 09:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940231</guid>
      <title>Taiwan seals the deal for advanced F-16 fighters with U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI, TAIWAN <br/> Taipei has signed a U.S. arms deal for 66 F-16V fighters while upgrading older models to F-16V standard earlier in December, Taiwan's state run Central News Agency reports on Saturday.<br/><br/>According to Lockheed Martin, the F-16V is the latest variant of the F-16, a multirole fighter that features advanced weaponry, targeting systems, electronics, and radar. <br/><br/>Citing an unnamed military source, CNA reports that the F-16Vs have better weapons than the older generation J-11 fighters used by China's People's Liberation Army.<br/><br/>According to the source, the F-16V may not be a match for the PLA's J-20 stealth fighter, but Taiwanese jets could utilize friendly early warning aircraft to contain the threat.<br/><br/>Jane's Information Group reports that Lockheed Martin will establish an F-16 maintenance center in Taiwan with the locally owned Aerospace Industrial Development Corporation.<br/><br/>According to Jane's, the facility will provide maintenance and logistical support to Taiwan's F-16 fleet, in addition to refurbishing 140 F-16A/Bs[e] to F-16Vs.<br/><br/>The PLA deploys about 700 fighters in China's southeastern coast, which is double the size of Taiwan's tactical air arm.<br/><br/>CNA cites the source as saying that the combination of F-16Vs and air defense systems give Taiwan's military a needed boost to combat the PLA's superior numbers.<br/><br/>Citing associate professor Lin Ying- yu[f] at the National Chung Cheng University, the CNA reports that China's carriers are now a threat to Taiwan's eastern defensive perimeter.<br/><br/>CNA cites Lin as saying that the F-16Vs and anti-ship missiles will serve as a deterrent to Chinese carriers and aircraft operating in the seas east of Taiwan.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-seals-the-deal-for-advanced-f-16-fighters-with-u-s--3940231</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/927/470/9274704727127A01D512B9D2FC7FDC3D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940231/3940231_0AF97BE188CF4E44B8684E41BC6F62A2_191225_3940231_Taiwan_seals_the_deal_for_advanced_F_16_fighters_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 03:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940374</guid>
      <title>Chinese man caught smuggling 90 iPhones taped to his body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHUHAI, CHINA <br/> A Chinese man was caught trying to cross the border from Macau to mainland China on Monday with a whole boatload of iPhones wrapped around his person. <br/>According to China News, the man was at the Gongbei border crossing in beautiful Zhuhai when he was stopped by customs officials. <br/>Apparently the guy was looking a bit on the "bloated" side with strange bulges protruding from his waist and legs, so he was stopped for a search. <br/>After dropping trow, customs officers were shocked to find 90 iPhones strapped to the man's body. <br/>The Apple phones were wrapped in plastic wrap and a whole bunch of tape around his waist, lets, thighs and ankles. <br/>China News reports that the case has now been transferred to the anti-smuggling department for further investigation. <br/>Uh oh<br/>it looks like someone's social credit score is going to take a big hit this holiday season.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-caught-smuggling-90-iphones-taped-to-his-body-3940374</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/269/72C/26972CF3758C6BC1BE3828041684027E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940374/3940374_C74C717392D04057B8B76D5E81C36D41_191225_3940374_Chinese_man_caught_smuggling_90_iPhones_taped_to_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940371</guid>
      <title>Marathon leader runs off course 200 meters from finish, loses race</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA <br/> A North Korean marathon runner steps away from certain victory blew it right before the finish line when he unfortunately veered off course. <br/>According to World Athletics, Ri Kang Bom of the super Democratic People's Republic of Korea was out front at the Asian Marathon Championships in Dongguan on December 22. <br/>Ri had a real comfortable lead over second-place Japanese runner Daichi Kamino with only 200 meters left and was cruising along nicely as he headed into the final corner.  <br/>That's when a TV broadcast motorcycle pulled in front of Ri and then exited the course right ahead of the finish line. Unfortunately for the North Korean Usain Bolt, he followed.<br/><br/>WIth only half a minute left in the race and the end in sight, Kamino turned on the afterburners for the last leg of the race. <br/>By the time Ri figured out that he was going the wrong way and returned back to the course, his lead had evaporated. <br/>Kamino then dramatically overtook Ri in the last 40 meters and finished with a time of 2:12.18. Ri took second only 3 seconds behind at 2:12.21.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/marathon-leader-runs-off-course-200-meters-from-finish-loses-race-3940371</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/93A/9EF/93A9EF232CA87555452FCE108772E589.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940371/3940371_7C15E0B7501A4BA59EFA20621ABDA817_191225_3940371_Marathon_leader_runs_off_course_200_meters_from__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 09:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941422</guid>
      <title>China builds airport in Cambodia, raising fears about its ambitions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DARA SAKOR, CAMBODIA <br/> China's construction of an airstrip in Cambodia is raising alarms about its military ambitions, according to the New York Times.<br/><br/>Bloomberg reports that Beijing now controls 20 percent of Cambodia's coastline via the lease of Dara Sakor, where a contractor is building an airport, a deep water port, medical facilities and a resort.<br/><br/>According to the New York Times, the Chinese claim the Dara Sakor airport <br/> which will feature the longest runway in Cambodia <br/> is a civilian facility.<br/><br/>However, the newspaper reports that the construction's scale and its tight turning bays which accommodate fighter jets point to a military purpose.<br/><br/>China-based Union Development Group holds the 99 year lease to the Dara Sakor investment zone.<br/><br/>Citing political scientist Sophal Ear at Occidental College, the New York Times reports that China's construction of the airport is to project power in the region. <br/><br/>According to the New York Times, the construction in Cambodia is likely a move to further Beijing's military strategy known as the "string of pearls."<br/><br/>This strategy involves establishing infrastructure and military bases that stretch from the South China Sea to the Indian Ocean and beyond.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-builds-airport-in-cambodia-raising-fears-about-its-ambitions-3941422</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/733/337/733337E08441637D6718EE08AA9A630C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941422/3941422_46F2B6345B5E442F974248F5BF769F81_191227_3941422_China_builds_airport_in_Cambodia__raising_fears__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 11:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942862</guid>
      <title>North Korea 'ghost ship' washes up on Japanese island</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SADO ISLAND, JAPAN <br/> Japanese authorities discovered the bow of a wooden boat believed to be from North Korea on the coast of Japan's Sado Island in the Sea of Japan on December 27.<br/><br/>Seven partially skeletonized remains were found inside the vessel, reports NHK World News. <br/><br/>Three bodies were found with heads, two bodies were found without heads and two heads were found without bodies, the Associated Press reports, citing officials. <br/><br/>All of the bodies were confirmed to be male, though officials said it is unclear whether or not the separate heads and the bodies came from the same people.<br/><br/>According to NHK World News, the side of the boat bore Korean characters and numbers that were painted in red.<br/><br/>The vessel's bow was measured to be roughly 7.6 meters long and 2 meters in height."<br/><br/>These boats could have been involved in illegal fishing operations in the Sea of Japan, Nikkei Asian Review reports, citing authorities. <br/><br/>Mitsuhiro Mimura, a researcher at Japan's Economic Research Institute for Northeast Asia, told the publication that this is partially due to the fact that North Korea sold fishing rights around its own coastal areas to China, forcing North Korea fishermen to go further out at sea in run down wooden boats.<br/><br/>A number of wooden boats typically wash ashore during this time of the year after northwesterly winds blow the vessels off course, as reported by NHK World News.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-ghost-ship-washes-up-on-japanese-island-3942862</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EF3/691/EF36918D054B3EC3DDF5061B331A8ED4.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942862/3942862_B097B63A64D64C36BA07EAF52C3E3FC3_191231_3942862_North_Korea__ghost_ship__washes_up_on_Japanese_i_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 07:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
