<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 18:05:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3993801</guid>
      <title>North and South Korean troops exchange gunfire in the DMZ</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEOUL <br/> North and South Korean troops exchanged small arms fire in the demilitarized zone on May 3. <br/><br/>Citing a statement from the South Korean joint chiefs of staff, the Korea Herald reports North Korea fired first but inflicted no casualties on South Korean forces.<br/><br/>According to the Yonhap News Agency, North Korean troops fired multiple shots at a South Korean outpost early in the morning, while the garrison returned two shots.<br/><br/>The South Korean military states North Korea apparently fired "unintentionally."<br/><br/>The state-funded news agency cites the military as saying the morning's fog would have obscured firing targets. <br/><br/>Additionally, the ground occupied by North Korean troops offered no tactical advantage over the outpost.<br/><br/>The 155-mile or 250-km-long DMZ is heavily defended by mines, fences and guard posts, and rates as the world's most militarized border.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/north-and-south-korean-troops-exchange-gunfire-in-the-dmz-3993801</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/04/3993801/3993801_034EB2E81A114DACA21AAA0067CE0CE3_200504_3993801_North_and_South_Korean_troops_exchange_gunfire_i_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 08:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994098</guid>
      <title>Japanese Aquarium Wants You to Video Chat Eels</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> A Japanese aquarium is asking you to video call its eels for fear of them forgetting who we are. <br/><br/>Sumida Aquarium in Tokyo says that social isolation is even affecting its eels. The claim comes after caretakers spotted garden eels burrowing down into the sand as they passed the tank. <br/><br/>The aquarium believes the new avoidance behavior is because the eels have become unfamiliar with humans since the aquarium closed on March 1st due to the coronavirus. <br/><br/>While such behavior is natural to the species when frightened, the aquarium is concerned that the burrowing will affect scientists' ability to study them. <br/><br/>In a press release, they said, 'The disappearance of the Chinese eels made it difficult for the breeding staff to check whether they are doing well, whether they are healthy, are they thin, and are they ill.'<br/><br/>To help the eels feel more at home, the aquarium has launched an 'emergency' three-day event calling on people around the world to video call the eels to get them acclimatized to us again. <br/><br/>The face-time event began on the 3rd and ends on the 5th. <br/><br/>This is the first time they have used technology to remind animals that humans exist, therefore they are not sure if it will be a success.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/japanese-aquarium-wants-you-to-video-chat-eels-3994098</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/05/3994098/3994098_2AFF8B0008634AAB8629F4A2105A8CE5_200505_3994098_Japanese_Aquarium_Wants_You_to_Video_Chat_Eels_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 06:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994599</guid>
      <title>Monkey on Scooter Tries to Kidnap Kid in Viral Video</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SURABAYA, INDONESIA <br/> A monkey riding a tiny motor scooter has been filmed trying to kidnap a toddler. <br/><br/>According to local outlet, Indonesia Expat, the incident occurred on Saturday in the East Java city of Surabaya and involved a traditional form of street entertainment known as 'masked monkey.'<br/><br/>In the video, the primate rides his tiny bike down a narrow residential street to the tune of gamelan percussion music before slamming on the brakes by a wooden bench where a woman is sitting with a baby and two young children.<br/><br/>The monkey hops off and makes an attempt for the kid, dragging the infant several meters. <br/><br/>When the monkey brings the abduction to an end, the girl gets up and makes a run for it, fortunately, she only suffered abrasions to her forehead. <br/><br/>Indonesian's netizens have condemned the handler of the monkey, arguing that it's wrong to enslave it for human entertainment. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/monkey-on-scooter-tries-to-kidnap-kid-in-viral-video-3994599</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/06/3994599/3994599_591D78D4127243B38685CBE1EB3CA524_200506_3994599_Monkey_on_Scooter_Tries_to_Kidnap_Kid_in_Viral_V_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 04:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3994591</guid>
      <title>New Kim Jong-un Photos Spark Body Double Theory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA <br/> Kim Jong-un reappeared in dramatic fashion last weekend when he was shown on North Korean media cutting the ribbon on a fertilizer factory, hushing those who said he was ill or even dead. <br/><br/>However, the photos released by state media from the ribbon-cutting function have given way for a new theory that it's a body double. <br/><br/>Web sleuths have noted discrepancies in facial, hairline, and dental features when compared with previous appearances.<br/><br/>The International Business Times says that it is a 'well-known fact Kim uses body doubles.'<br/><br/>British tabloid, The Sun even shared a video back in 2017 seemingly showing Kim nattering to two body doubles.<br/><br/>According to IBT, human rights activist Jennifer Zeng was the first to draw attention to the dissimilarities between the two so-called 'versions' of Kim, noting differences in their teeth and ears.<br/><br/>She took to Twitter, questioning, 'Is the Kim Jong-un on May 1st the real one?' Along with a side-by-side comparison of Kim's 'old and new' appearance. <br/><br/>Former British Member of Parliament Louise Mensch said, 'Don't know, don't care. See no reason to alter my earlier stance. These aren't the same man.' <br/><br/>Writer and podcaster Akilah Hughes noted that a body double wouldn't be so far-fetched, saying, 'we really believing that's Kim Jong Un when it could absolutely be a dude w plastic surgery?? If I was a murderous dictator I'd have clones.' <br/><br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-kim-jong-un-photos-spark-body-double-theory-3994591</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/06/3994591/3994591_C69F09E1CC0940A98C4192CCCB7149B5_200506_3994591_New_Kim_Jong_un_Photos_Spark_Body_Double_Theory_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2020 04:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3995343</guid>
      <title>Kim's Recent Appearance: What Really Happened?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  <br/> NK Daily, a South Korean newspaper with informants on the bad side of the border claim that the hermit kingdom's Pyongyang officials scrambled together in a 48-hour panic and mysteriously organized that ribbon-cutting function of the fertilizer factory we saw just to prove he was alive.  <br/><br/>The report also claims that the factory is unfinished and inoperable.<br/><br/>The newspaper's informant said, 'for two days the construction workers fully devoted themselves to preparing for the ceremony. They worked themselves to the bone day and night to create the appearance of a finished factory, coating the outside of the building and fitting it with glass.'<br/><br/>The source claims that in addition, all factory personnel, and even their families were mobilized to plant flower beds and clean the roads within the factory grounds.<br/><br/>Despite this mass mobilization of labor, no one had any idea that it would be their supreme leader, Kim Jong-un that would be opening the factory. <br/><br/>The insider said, 'nobody onsite expected that the event would involve Kim Jong-un himself.'<br/><br/>'Everyone knows that construction was not complete.'<br/><br/>The factory has also encountered difficulties importing modern machinery and raw materials to produce the phosphatic fertilizer it was built for or being built for. <br/><br/>The Central Committee of North Korea reportedly issued an order that the factory must have 'at least two' production lines running by October 10th, the anniversary of the founding of North Korea's communist party.<br/><br/>Currently, the majority of the fertilizer used in North Korea comes from their pals in China.<br/><br/>Kim Jong-un's sudden reemergence at the factory after a strange three weeks out may have been an attempt to draw attention to the fruits of North Korea's 'frontal breakthrough' strategy, as well as to rally and inspire increased food production amid the country's food shortages.<br/><br/>However, this doesn't explain why he was away from the public eye for so long.<br/><br/>Mintaro Oba, a former US official who worked on North Korea, told ABC, 'The blunt truth is that we can speculate all we want about where Kim Jong-un was and why he disappeared, but we simply don't know.' <br/><br/>If he was hiding out to protect himself from the coronavirus, as South Korea said, then that would contradict North Korea's claims of zero coronavirus cases. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/kim-s-recent-appearance-what-really-happened--3995343</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/08/3995343/3995343_95DBF28C97B64128B6384EB535AD066F_200508_3995343_Kim_s_Recent_Appearance__What_Really_Happened__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 03:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3996316</guid>
      <title>China Offers Help to North Korea Despite Their Claims of Zero Cases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Chinese President Xi Jinping responded to a message that he received from North Korea's Kim Jong-un; and in doing so, may have just outed the country's claims of zero coronavirus cases.<br/><br/>Kim Jong-un said of Xi that he is 'highly appreciating that he is seizing a chance of victory in the war against the unprecedented epidemic.'<br/><br/>Xi said that he too highly appreciated Kim's support during China's outbreak and, 'showed his personal attention to the situation of the pandemic and people's health' in North Korea; a statement that would contradict the narrative Kim Jong-un has been pushing. <br/><br/>Xi said that more efforts were required to strengthen cooperation in preventing the spread of the virus, adding that China is 'willing to continue to provide assistance within its own capacity for [North Korea] in the fight against Covid-19.'<br/><br/>With Pyongyang being slow to accept public offers of help from the U.S., and with peace talks with Washington stalling, if North Korea accepted, or even looked like they accepted China's help the CPP would surely assert itself as Kim's true ally. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-offers-help-to-north-korea-despite-their-claims-of-zero-cases-3996316</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/11/3996316/3996316_B7742E48666A47AEBB65F91B143D9299_200511_3996316_China_Offers_Help_to_North_Korea_Despite_Their_C_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 03:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3997172</guid>
      <title>Chinese Chef Spits And Leaves Cigarette Butt in Food</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XI'AN, CHINA <br/> A diner watched surveillance footage of a chef spitting into his dish while cooking it for him.<br/><br/>The customer gained access to the video after finding a cigarette butt in a stew he had ordered and then complained about it to the restaurant.<br/><br/>He said he saw the chef 'spitting especially' into the stew but the restaurant worker claimed he was experiencing tightness in the throat and spat on the ground.<br/><br/>Local media reported that the incident took place at around 2 pm on Sunday at the Sufuji Restaurant in Xi'an.<br/><br/>Mr. Zheng, the disgusted diner said he had ordered the stew for his child and sent it back to the kitchen initially due to its poor taste.<br/><br/>Demanding access to kitchen surveillance, he was further shocked to discover that the chef had been cooking without a face mask and then spat in his dish.<br/><br/>The restaurant claimed that the 22-year-old chef, Mr. Wang, had spat on the edge of the wok, not inside.<br/><br/>The restaurant which is located inside a mall said it had ordered the store to shut and 'dealt with the chef seriously.'<br/><br/>Taking to social media, the restaurant said it was very ashamed of the incident.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-chef-spits-and-leaves-cigarette-butt-in-food-3997172</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/13/3997172/3997172_4BBA9A4D3098472FA00A4797B7BB0E5A_200513_3997172_Chinese_Chef_Spits_And_Leaves_Cigarette_Butt_in__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 07:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3998290</guid>
      <title>China May Hold Major Military Exercise in South China Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> China's People's Liberation Army Navy plans to conduct a large-scale amphibious assault drill off Hainan Island in August, according to the Japan Times.<br/><br/>Citing unnamed Chinese sources, the Japan Times reports the drill will involve landing ships, hovercraft and helicopters, while the carrier Shandong has been deployed in Hainan since December last year. <br/><br/>The exercise is designed to simulate a navy and marines attack on the Taiwan-held Pratas, a strategically important islet that sits astride China's military egress from Hainan to the Pacific Ocean.<br/><br/>According to Reuters, Taiwan in April announced plans to buy arms from France to upgrade its fleet of six French-made La Fayette-class frigates.<br/><br/>The U.S. Naval Institute reports a U.S. Navy Arleigh Burke-class destroyer made a transit through the Taiwan Strait to warn Beijing's leadership against taking aggressive action in the region.<br/><br/>The Japan Times reports U.S. electronic warfare aircraft may have passed the strait 14 times in April alone.<br/><br/>According to Taiwan's state-run Central News Agency, a Chinese Y-8 aircraft flew into Taiwan's air defense identification zone before being headed off by fighter jets on April 8.<br/><br/>This is the seventh time Chinese military planes flew near Taiwan's airspace this year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-may-hold-major-military-exercise-in-south-china-sea-3998290</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/16/3998290/3998290_808CB638CAE14E7DB56BBE0AC81EA3F2_200516_3998290_China_May_Hold_Major_Military_Exercise_in_South__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 03:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999203</guid>
      <title>Disgusting Woman Filmed Spitting on Fruit in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANSHUN, CHINA  <br/> A female vendor was filmed on May 11th, in a now-viral video, sipping water from a bottle and then to mist her waxberries, spat the water from her mouth all over the fruit. <br/><br/>The clip which was shared to the Chinese platform Weibo has led the farmers market to terminate the woman's contract and stick her on the blacklist for life. <br/><br/>The video comes after growing international concern over China's open animal markets causing the spread of coronavirus. <br/><br/>But in a twist, Ms.Yang, the vendor says she has been wronged, as she was in fact spraying water around the berries on the floor to keep the dust down.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/disgusting-woman-filmed-spitting-on-fruit-in-china-3999203</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/19/3999203/3999203_547809D45F5043769FEC7D8640293EE1_200519_3999203_Disgusting_Woman_Filmed_Spitting_on_Fruit_in_Chi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 05:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3999769</guid>
      <title>Super Cyclone to Make Imminent landfall on India and Bangladesh</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KOLKATA, INDIA <br/> India and Bangladesh are evacuating millions before the path of Tropical Cyclone Amphan, which is expected to make imminent landfall on the evening of May 20. <br/><br/>Amphan is the second-ever super cyclone on record to hit the Bay of Bengal. The powerful storm was sustaining an airspeed of 172 km per hour at the time of report.<br/><br/>Citing India's weather department, the BBC reports the storm will bring a 3 to 5-meter surge, and the authorities have called on fishing boats to stay ashore.<br/><br/>The U.S. Pacific Center says up to 33.6 million people in India and 5.3 million people in Bangladesh are exposed to the storm, with capital exposures of up to $273.9 billion.<br/><br/>The cyclone will likely fall on the India-Bangladesh border and the projected path will bring the storm near the Indian city of Kolkata.<br/><br/>More than 14 million people reside in this densely populated urban center. <br/><br/>Thumbnail credit: FLICKR / VINOTH CHANDAR]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/super-cyclone-to-make-imminent-landfall-on-india-and-bangladesh-3999769</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/20/3999769/3999769_96EFDBF422EB4118873A5EC315AB9FD6_200520_3999769_Super_Cyclone_to_Make_Imminent_landfall_on_India_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2020 09:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4000422</guid>
      <title>7-Eleven Staff Sprays Customer in Face With Hand Sanitizer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BANGKOK <br/> A 7-Eleven worker was caught on CCTV accidentally spraying a customer in the face with hand sanitizer. <br/><br/>In the video, the customer walks in with a mask covering her face and advances to get her temperature checked, which is common practice at stores across Thailand.<br/><br/>The member of staff, who is equipped with a face shield, mask, and thermometer then lifts the device up to the customer's forehead, however, she then swaps out her thermometer for the sanitizer and proceeds to spray then the woman in the face. <br/><br/>The customer recoils holding her face. The member of staff then guides the woman to the back of the store, presumably to administer medical aid.<br/><br/>The video has since gone viral with shrewd Facebook users in Thailand saying it's likely the store clerk was confused and that it was an accident. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/7-eleven-staff-sprays-customer-in-face-with-hand-sanitizer-4000422</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/05/22/4000422/4000422_DF9567A47BBB48E589D6FC15A35D0233_200522_4000422_7_Eleven_Staff_Sprays_Customer_in_Face_With_Hand_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 03:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
