<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3970147</guid>
      <title>Tokyo Olympics could be axed if coronavirus not controlled</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> In what would be considered a major blow, Dick Pound, senior IOC member, says the Tokyo Olympic Games could be canceled if the you-know-what's-it-19 isn't under control.<br/>The Guardian reports that according to senior member of the International Olympic Committee Dick Pound, an outright cancellation of the Games, instead of postponing or relocating would be likely if things aren't under control in a few months. <br/>The Summer Games are currently scheduled to be held on July 24. Pound, who has been an IOC member since 1978, thinks there's about a two- or three-month window before making a final decision. <br/>So this means they could probably wait till like, late May.   <br/>Dick told the AP, "In and around that time, I'd say folks are going to have to ask: 'Is this under sufficient control that we can be confident about going to Tokyo or not?" <br/>And let's be honest...who knows how well the rest of the world will be doing in a few months. <br/>As the Games get closer, Dick Pound said, "A lot of things have to start happening. You've got to start ramping up your security, your food, the Olympic Village, the hotels. The media folks will be in there, building their studios."<br/>Pound said, "you're probably looking at cancellation" if the IOC decides the games cannot go forward as planned in Tokyo.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tokyo-olympics-could-be-axed-if-coronavirus-not-controlled-3970147</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/02/3970147/3970147_F260B16878984A5EA8F3C5EDDDD2E6A8_200302_3970147_Tokyo_Olympics_could_be_axed_if_coronavirus_not__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 02:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970143</guid>
      <title>Kazuhisa Hashimoto, the inventor of the Konami code has died</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN <br/> Kazuhisa Hashimoto, the inventor of the world-famous 'Konami Code' has died.<br/><br/>You may not be familiar with him by name, but you'll likely know of him via his understated contribution to the gaming industry.<br/><br/>Up, up, down, down, left, right, left, right, B, A and then Start.<br/><br/>It's a cheat code, rather, the "Konami code" and one that can be used in most Konami games.  <br/><br/>According to Nintendolife, the rumour is, Hashimoto, a programmer and developer of the 1985 arcade shooter, Gradius, was actually struggling to beat the game. <br/><br/>Hashimoto then invented the code to give himself back-door access and test the entire game. <br/><br/>The best part? He accidentally left it in when the game went out on sale.<br/><br/>Codes like this were initially used by developers to test out portions of a game or potential new pieces of code, but, of course, it didn't take long before players started finding out about them for themselves.<br/><br/>Fearing the mass complications of removing it, Konami decided to actually leave the code or 'cheat' in the game. <br/><br/>They eventually put the code in most of their games as the use of it by gamers became more popular.<br/><br/>Cheats may not be such a big deal anymore, but they once were and to think, a simple hack created to make a person's job easier may have helped you complete a level or two and that's quite a cool legacy to leave behind.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/kazuhisa-hashimoto-the-inventor-of-the-konami-code-has-died-3970143</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/02/3970143/3970143_64409B56293D4E3891975C93690AA2DC_200302_3970143_Kazuhisa_Hashimoto__the_inventor_of_the_Konami_c_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 02:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970570</guid>
      <title>Chinese manufacturing hits record lows amid Wuhan virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Some great news coming out of China amid the whole Wuhan virus debacle.<br/><br/>Chinese manufacturing activity plummeted at a record rate in February, while the boys in Beijing were lying to the world about the extent of the coronavirus.<br/>According to the Beebs, the country's official manufacturing activity <br/> the Purchasing Manager's Index (PMI) <br/> dropped to 35.7 from 50 in January. <br/>This means the made in China virus is having a much bigger impact than the subprime mortgage crisis that rocked the financial world in 2008.    <br/>The BBC reports that the data also hints that factories are having a hard time finding enough workers.<br/>And since China makes up a third of global manufacturing and is the world's biggest exporter, this PMI drop will have an effect on other countries. <br/>According to the BBC, companies like Apple, Diageo, Jaguar Land Rover and Volkswagen have all been affected. <br/>Many companies rely on China's 300 million migrant workers, a third of which are still under quarantine. <br/>Bloomberg Economics reports that Chinese factories are operating at 60 percent to 70 percent of capacity this week.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-manufacturing-hits-record-lows-amid-wuhan-virus-3970570</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/03/3970570/3970570_8A2B4FC6D13B46C1B6A9BFD1329DD573_200303_3970570_Chinese_manufacturing_hits_record_lows_amid_Wuha_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 02:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971447</guid>
      <title>Cat to be deported over coronavirus fears</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENNAI, INDIA <br/> Hysteria over that-which-must-not-be-named has struck again and this time it involves an unlucky stowaway pussy cat, India Today reports.<br/><br/>According to the Khaleej Times, the feline in question arrived in Chennai port around 3 weeks ago inside a shipping container from China and has been held there on fears it has been infected. <br/><br/>Citing PETA India, the Khaleej Times reports that the organization has told the port that cats cannot transmit or contract that which must not be named. But, according to India Today, Chennai port quarantine has decided to send the cat back to whence it came after detaining it for over 20 days.  <br/><br/>But did it really come from China? And is it really the wisest decision to send it back there? PETA India doesn't seem to think so. <br/><br/>India Today reports that Chennai-bound ships often stop in Singapore and Sri Lanka. And PETA India says that in China, cats are often killed for their meat and fur. The organization has offered to help find the cat a fur-ever home after quarantine and other checks have been completed.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cat-to-be-deported-over-coronavirus-fears-3971447</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/05/3971447/3971447_9C15D2D050B042B48068B78D00EC60C9_200305_3971447_Cat_to_be_deported_over_coronavirus_fears_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 02:25:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973134</guid>
      <title>10 dead after coronavirus quarantine hotel collapses</title>
      <description><![CDATA[QUANZHOU, CHINA <br/> Scores of people under coronavirus quarantine in Quanzhou, China were trapped over the weekend after the hotel they were in suddenly collapsed, reports the South China Morning Post. <br/><br/>The collapsed Xinjia Express Hotel being used for Co-Vid 19 quarantine was 7 stories tall and 66 rooms, according to state-run newspaper The China Daily.  At least 10 people were killed.<br/><br/>According to the state-run Xinhua News, two supermarkets on the ground floor of the hotel were undergoing remodeling when the building collapsed around 7 p.m. on Saturday. <br/><br/>The area's top housing official Zhang Yi told Xinhua News that he received a phone call from construction workers moments before the collapse reporting a damaged pillar.<br/><br/>Citing local authorities, the South China Morning Post reports that 8 people escaped as the building collapsed, while 38 have been pulled from the rubble. Many remain unaccounted for. <br/><br/>The South China Morning Post reports that more than 1,000 emergency responders were sent to the site of the collapse. The newspaper reports that those trapped include 58 people under quarantine and government medical workers. <br/><br/>All guests had tested negative for the virus but had still been subject to a mandatory 14-day quarantine.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/10-dead-after-coronavirus-quarantine-hotel-collapses-3973134</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/09/3973134/3973134_E75B3B5C5EBB43C2BB5410CADAC50333_200309_3973134_10_dead_after_coronavirus_quarantine_hotel_colla_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 08:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973431</guid>
      <title>China says it will soon have no new Wuhan virus cases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> With numbers of Co-China-19 cases supposedly declining in the lovely Middle Kingdom, Chinese health officials are using the opportunity to make some highly questionable predictions. <br/>According to the SCMP, a senior Chinese researcher, who is a part of a 14-member team sent from Beijing to Hubei province, claims that there will be no more new Wuhan virus cases in China by the end of March.<br/>Well...no new cases as long as you don't count the new cases that pop up in Hubei province<br/>you know, the epicenter of this latest global Panda-demic.  <br/>Zhang told fake China news outlet the People's Daily, "We have analyzed the infections trend. So far, the daily infections in places other than Hubei have almost gone down to zero since February." <br/>"According to our analysis of the statistics, we expect cities other than Wuhan in Hubei province will be basically free of coronavirus patients in the middle of March. The hope is that Wuhan won't have daily new cases in late March." <br/>Good thing "hope" has been proven to be an effective cure against the China-Cough-19. <br/>Zhang then went on to say people in other parts of China might be able to ditch their masks in April, but that did not mean that the Wuhan virus would be completely gone and there could still be cases, including people arriving from overseas. <br/>See what he did there at the end? China is now trying to spin this by saying people are bringing the Wuhan virus into the country. <br/>Hey China...there's a reason it's called the Wuhan virus.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-says-it-will-soon-have-no-new-wuhan-virus-cases-3973431</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/10/3973431/3973431_7BBB01BD9A544540B34918308247EF61_200310_3973431_China_says_it_will_soon_have_no_new_Wuhan_virus__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 04:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973491</guid>
      <title>Chinese man rides horse to buy groceries for a quarantined pal</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HEILONGJIANG CITY, CHINA <br/> A Chinese man who was caught riding his horse through the streets claims he was running an errand for a cordoned-off friend. <br/><br/>The traffic police had to remind the man that, despite his noble aims, he was in breach of traffic regulations.<br/><br/>The man was sent on his way home.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-rides-horse-to-buy-groceries-for-a-quarantined-pal-3973491</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/10/3973491/3973491_EEB88EB1DD654A1FBCD778662005663B_200310_3973491_Chinese_man_rides_horse_to_buy_groceries_for_a_q_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 06:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973862</guid>
      <title>Wuhan residents: "It's all fake!"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> The devoted minds of the Chinese government have attempted to shift the narrative to both sweep under the carpet their lackluster response to the cough-19  and to convince its people that King Xi Jinping has somehow single-handedly steered this huge struggle in the right direction.<br/><br/>However, in a rare shift, the people of China, specifically the people of Wuhan have demonstrated something completely unexpected, they ain't buying it.  <br/><br/>Videos have surfaced that appear to show Wuhan residents shout "everything is fake!" at Communist China's Vice Premier, Sun Chunlan, as she toured the sectioned-off community at the hub of the outbreak last week on the 5th. <br/><br/>In the videos that quickly surfaced online, residents can be heard shouting in both the Wuhan dialect and Mandarin, "Fake! Fake! Fake!" and, "Everything is fake!"<br/><br/>They can also be heard shouting, "They are taking advantage of the people to put on a show."<br/><br/>This open criticism of the Chinese government is almost unheard of and shows signs of a telling people that have had enough of its government's lies and continued coverups. <br/><br/>But, even more surprisingly, in an exceptionally unusual move by the regime, China's state-controlled media such as the Global Times and the People's Daily shared short clips of the now-viral incident.<br/><br/>They had made out that they would investigate the situation and ensure a "level of satisfaction by the general public."<br/><br/>But, as one Twitter user mentioned, the broadcast edited the videos to make it seem as though there was only one voice, rather than the truth.<br/><br/>Could it be that the communist government's rare turn of events of showing the video is actually being set-up to use Sun as a scapegoat? <br/><br/>Only time will tell.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-residents--it-s-all-fake--3973862</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/11/3973862/3973862_8DA99A0F9CF0472AAA3E302D0F3DAC36_200311_3973862_Wuhan_residents___It_s_all_fake___2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 05:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973824</guid>
      <title>Xi Jinping goes on choreographed "visit" to Wuhan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> With cases of the Co-Sniffles-19 supposedly declining in fantastic China, Chinese dictator Xi Jinping has pumped the propaganda machine into overdrive. <br/>In a highly choreographed visit to the epicenter of the world's latest troubles, emperor Xi made his first visit to Wuhan since the Chinese viral outbreak started more than two months ago.  <br/>According to China's fake news outlet Xinhua, Xi "went straight to Huoshenshan Hospital" after touching down in Wuhan were he "visited patients" and "sent regards" to medical workers, "encouraging them to firm up confidence in defeating the epidemic."<br/>Actually...Xi didn't have the gonads to see them in person. He talked to them over video in a conference room that was nowhere near the actual makeshift hospitals. What a brave leader. <br/>Xi then toured a Wuhan neighborhood with quarantined residents who have been stuck inside for weeks. <br/>But because last week Wuhan residents heckled Vice Premier Sun Chunlan while she was visiting one neighborhood, police were deployed in people's apartments so that Xi wouldn't be welcomed by any shouting residents. <br/>China claims new cases of Chinese people being infected with the Wuhan virus have plummeted. <br/><br/>And since China has been nothing but transparent and open about all the actual cases and deaths the world can now breathe a big sigh of relief<br/>right?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/xi-jinping-goes-on-choreographed-visit-to-wuhan-3973824</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/11/3973824/3973824_98C06E53ED5448589866A164FF5BA2D9_200311_3973824_Xi_Jinping_goes_on_choreographed__visit__to_Wuha_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974229</guid>
      <title>Taiwanese kids fight Wuhan virus with a lego robot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KAOHSIUNG, TAIWAN <br/> With just 81 miles between them and China, Taiwan, a country of 23 million people has managed to curb the epidemic and of March 10th, some four months later, the country has just 48 cases of Covid-19. <br/><br/>With everyone pulling in the same direction, it should be no surprise then to see students at an elementary school in Kaohsiung fighting the disease in their own unique way, and in this case, an automated disinfectant dispenser built from Legos. <br/><br/>Kids from the ages of six to 12 use every chance they can to get in line and use their self-built disinfectant robot. <br/><br/>What's more, the student-built bot cheers, "washing hands is super!" after it senses a pair of hands in front of its ultrasonic sensor. <br/><br/>Beside their disinfecting bot, are scenes crafted by the younger students showing various situations that require hand washing: an operating table, a toilet, and even a flower garden.<br/><br/>Teachers at the school in Linyuan, which is situated in an industrial area, decided that after the Fukushima disaster in 2011, students should know the basic principles of robotics; that way, they could help solve problems in the future such as air pollution and gas explosions.<br/><br/>Unsurprisingly, the school has represented Taiwan in many international competitions and won several prizes. <br/><br/>Tackling this pandemic starts with all of us.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwanese-kids-fight-wuhan-virus-with-a-lego-robot-3974229</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/12/3974229/3974229_DDE40A6AB9CD4E07B8310055FAD1CD3F_200312_3974229_Taiwanese_kids_fight_Wuhan_virus_with_a_lego_rob_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 05:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974673</guid>
      <title>Wuhan delivers pork rations in trash trucks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GANDU, WUHAN, CHINA <br/> On Wednesday the 11th of March at around 8 p.m, a garbage truck was used to transport pork meat to local residents in Gandu, Wuhan as part of a committee's scheme to deliver rations to its people.<br/><br/>Unfortunately, before the unsanitized method of transportation was noticed by the community, the truck that was delivering 1,000 pieces of pork had already delivered 530. <br/><br/>Local residents were left appalled by the committee's choice of logistics, with some claiming the meat even smelt bad. <br/><br/>The committee soon sent out an apology message via its official Weibo account and organized staff to apologize to the local residents and collect and "destroy" the pork that had already been distributed. <br/><br/>The committee promised to deliver the same quantity of pork for the following day, however, this time in a sanitary way that complies with the "strict food safety requirements" that they chose to ignore. <br/><br/>The local government in Qingshan that governs Gandu, decided to fire both the secretary and vice-chair of the local committee after being left red-faced for what they call a "professional error."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-delivers-pork-rations-in-trash-trucks-3974673</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/13/3974673/3974673_CD37EFE6BC3249BE9FBC67258587BA98_200313_3974673_Wuhan_delivers_pork_rations_in_trash_trucks_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 05:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975642</guid>
      <title>Nepal shuts off access to Mount Everest amid Wuhan virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEPAL <br/> Anyone feel like climbing Mount Everest? Unfortunately<br/>you may have to wait awhile.<br/>BBC reports that Mount Everest has been closed for the rest of the expedition season as the Chinese coronavirus wreaks havoc across the world. <br/><br/>Nepal's government said it would be canceling all climbing permits from March 14 till April 30. <br/>China had already axed expeditions from the northern, Chinese-controlled, side of the mountain. <br/>The Kathmandu Post reports that Nepal earns $4 million a year by issuing Everest climbing permits, in addition to other tourism revenue. <br/>According to the Secretary of the Prime Minister's Office Narayan Prasad Bidari, "As of now, all issued permits and permits yet to be issued for the 2020 Everest season will be cancelled."<br/>According to the BBC, most climbers come from the US, India, China, UK, Japan and South Korea. <br/>Guess all those rich people will have to wait until next season to dump all their garbage on the top of the world.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nepal-shuts-off-access-to-mount-everest-amid-wuhan-virus-3975642</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/16/3975642/3975642_A81E3197865D44E796D150D85688C991_200316_3975642_Nepal_shuts_off_access_to_Mount_Everest_amid_Wuh_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 02:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976556</guid>
      <title>Nara deer leave park in search of food amid Chinese coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NARA, JAPAN <br/> The Chinese Wuhan Coronavirus has gotten so bad around the world that even Nara deer are being affected.<br/>According to SoraNews 24, videos popping up on social media are showing herds of deer roaming the streets in search of food. <br/>Usually, the famous deer of Nara are kept properly fed by the hordes of tourists. <br/>Unfortunately, the Wuhan Virus has killed all of that. The dramatic drop in people visiting Nara have caused the deer to leave to park in search of food. <br/>Several TV news reports have shown deer sightings at unfamiliar spots around the city. <br/>Residents report that deer have been devouring shrubs and flowers on the sidewalks. <br/>Hopefully things will get back to normal soon. And if you happen to be in the neighborhood, be a DEAR and toss a few rice crackers their way.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nara-deer-leave-park-in-search-of-food-amid-chinese-coronavirus-3976556</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976556/3976556_6F2A32136EDB4C8DB93699A0C2141078_200318_3976556_Nara_deer_leave_park_in_search_of_food_amid_Chin_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 04:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976502</guid>
      <title>Rival monkey gangs wage street war over banana</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOP BURI, THAILAND <br/> Rival monkey gangs fought a bitter street battle over a banana last week in Lop Buri Thailand, according to the Chiang Rai Times.<br/><br/>Citing a video posted to Twitter, the Thai outlet reports that monkeys can be seen fighting each other and chasing one who appears to have a banana. <br/><br/>According to the Bangkok Post, Lop Buri is home to two rival simian gangs, the temple monkeys and city monkeys. Each faction has their own turf.<br/><br/>The Chiang Rai Times reports that a slump in tourism to the popular temple area has led to a lack of food for the local monkey population who are usually fed by holidaygoers.<br/><br/>That, in turn, may have drove to the mass monkey brawl seen on social media last week.<br/><br/>According to Thai news site Khaosodo English, the monkeys are mostly fed high-sugar and fatty human foods.  All that junk food, the website reports, even led to one becoming obese. <br/><br/>WIKIMEDIA COMMONS<br/>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Monkeys_at_Prang_Sam_Yot_(Monkey_Temple)_-_Lop_Buri_-_Thailand_-_05_(35028507555).jpg<br/>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Monkey_Buffet_Lopburi_01.jpg  <br/>THUMB VIA FLICKR / JON RAWLINSON<br/>https://www.flickr.com/photos/london/25772226]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/rival-monkey-gangs-wage-street-war-over-banana-3976502</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976502/3976502_F7CE206AA389452A9AB8A144A85DF410_200318_3976502_Rival_monkey_gangs_wage_street_war_over_banana_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 02:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977056</guid>
      <title>China announces it's booting American journalists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> China's feelings have been hurt once again, so now it has decided to boot US reporters working for the New York Times, The Wall Street Journal and The Washington Post. <br/>According to the New York Times, the Chinese have also demanded that those outlets, in addition to the Voice of America and Time magazine, give the Chinese government detailed information about their operations. <br/>That's easy<br/>they report the news, something that is non-existent in fabulous China.<br/>China's Ministry of Foreign Affairs made the announcement after the Trump administration limited to 100 the number of Chinese citizens working in the U.S. for five fake Chinese news outlets that produce nothing but good old fashioned CCP propaganda. <br/>The ministry said US journalists, whose press credentials are due to expire before the end of 2020, must notify Chinese authorities within four days and hand back their press passes within 10 days. <br/>The statement also said, "They will not be able to continue working as journalists in the People's Republic of China," including Hong Kong and Macau. <br/>Secretary of State Mike Pompeo called the move "unfortunate" and said he hoped Beijing would reconsider. <br/>What the U.S. should do is just shut down Xinhua, CGTN, China Radio, China Daily and The People's Daily and ship all their workers back to China.<br/>They'll have much more fun reporting on the real news going on in China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-announces-it-s-booting-american-journalists-3977056</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/19/3977056/3977056_E948D19CB1C64D82B68E26D0847A3E41_200319_3977056_China_announces_it_s_booting_American_journalist_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 05:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977045</guid>
      <title>Man reserves 1,873 seats at baseball games for privacy</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OSAKA, JAPAN <br/> Here's a question. What would be the best way to watch your favorite sports team? <br/><br/>A Japanese man says reserve nearly 2000 seats and then cancel them so you get yourself some serious privacy. <br/><br/>Kiyoshi Shibamura, a 41-year-old fan of the Orix Buffaloes baseball club from the Japanese city of Osaka, came up with an ingenious-yet-costly plan to watch his favorite team compete against the SoftBank Hawks on the 28th and 29th of September last year. <br/><br/>The allure of spectating his boys in privacy prompted the devotee to create 1,873 fake names and then reserve a seat for each fabricated person. <br/><br/>He then canceled all but his own reservation right before the end of the reservation period, making sure that no one else managed to sit anywhere near him. <br/><br/>Heard of the Orix Buffaloes? Probably not, as it has one of the smallest fan bases in Japan, so having 1,873 empty seats is probably not a big deal, right? <br/><br/>Wrong! You see, this was no ordinary game, this was one of the last games of the season and the SoftBank Hawks would go on to win last year's national title, so the stakes were pretty damn high and so were ticket prices.<br/><br/>The ingenious reservation stunt cost the team 10.86 million yen, roughly $105,000, a considerable sum for such a small team. <br/><br/>Unsurprisingly, an internal investigation was launched and it wasn't that hard to discover the culprit, considering he was the only person sat in the empty patch of 1,873 chairs, that and he didn't deny it. <br/><br/>"I wanted to watch the game comfortably with no people around. I wanted to stand out on TV."<br/><br/>It's unclear whether Shibamura is facing only a fine or actual jail time.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-reserves-1-873-seats-at-baseball-games-for-privacy-3977045</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/19/3977045/3977045_0172C751322D48328849942611497B19_200319_3977045_Man_reserves_1_873_seats_at_baseball_games_for_p_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 05:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976949</guid>
      <title>Korean man tries to disinfect his cash by microwaving it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BUSAN, SOUTH KOREA <br/> The internet is currently swamped with ill-informed homemade kits and methods on how to eliminate the coronavirus from our lives, but what about money? What method are people taking to clean their cash?<br/><br/>One man in Busan, South Korea gathered up a total of 39 10,000-won notes, roughly $328, stuffed them into his microwave, and switched it on; unsurprisingly his cash burnt. <br/><br/>He took his browned cash into the bank asking for help, in the end, 33 notes were salvageable meaning he only lost $50. <br/><br/>This isn't the first time though that someone has attempted to clean their money using a microwave, a Chinese woman in Jiangsu province tried the very same, only this time upped the risk and put $449 in the microwave.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/korean-man-tries-to-disinfect-his-cash-by-microwaving-it-3976949</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/19/3976949/3976949_A928AA10B2F34D41AE6A4FD1F53688AD_200319_3976949_Korean_man_tries_to_disinfect_his_cash_by_microw_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 01:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978847</guid>
      <title>500-year-old well-preserved body dug up in Anhui, China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUAINING, ANHUI, CHINA <br/> After spending the last five centuries buried deep beneath the earth, a man's corpse was dug up in Huaining county in Anhui province. <br/><br/>The unsuspecting villagers unearthed the man's coffin while leveling off some ground; inside was a body that certainly does not look a half-millennia dead.<br/><br/>As residents trampled through the mud to get a closer look, they saw that the tombstone marked the man as being buried during the reign of the Zhengde Emperor which was in 1505-1521, in the Ming dynasty.<br/><br/>As quickly as they unearthed it, the local cultural relics bureau confirmed the dating and then deemed it of no real archaeological value. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/500-year-old-well-preserved-body-dug-up-in-anhui-china-3978847</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/24/3978847/3978847_2C736590C5634FB5970C9ED5CA7125E9_200324_3978847_500_year_old_well_preserved_body_dug_up_in_Anhui_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 03:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981185</guid>
      <title>WHO doctor ends call after question about Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN <br/> The World Health Organization or 'WHO', a body that promotes "health for all" shockingly continues to block Taiwan from its organization and access to first-hand data despite the current pandemic. <br/><br/>Taiwan is a country that sits a mere 81-miles from China, the epicenter of the outbreak and yet impressively has just 298 cases as of the 30th of March. Taiwan then, could share crucial information on how to manage the Coronavirus if granted membership, a membership that potentially could save thousands of lives globally; so why are they blocked by the WHO? <br/><br/>It's simple, China tells them to. Politics take precedence over people's lives and none are more guilty than WHO Assistant Director-General, Bruce Aylward.<br/><br/>In an interview with RTHK producer Yvonne Tong, the epidemiologist plays deaf and pretends not to hear her question about whether the UN body would reconsider Taiwan's membership. "I'm sorry, I couldn't hear your question, Yvonne&#8230; let's move to another one then," he says, before hanging up. <br/><br/>When Tong called him back to ask again about Taiwan and its coronavirus measures, Aylward shockingly said: "Well, we've already talked about China." A controversial comment that flirts with China's stance that Taiwan belongs to the communist regime. <br/><br/>Aylward has regularly featured in Chinese state media after he led a WHO mission to the country during the outbreak; he has repeatedly praised the country's leadership and, at one press conference, stated that, if he was infected with the disease he would want to be treated in China.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/who-doctor-ends-call-after-question-about-taiwan-3981185</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/30/3981185/3981185_2B5E5E2FE91C42DB9F5AE95D7FB87BD4_200330_3981185_WHO_doctor_ends_call_after_question_about_Taiwan_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 05:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981623</guid>
      <title>WHO Director-General blames Taiwan for his bad reputation</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN <br/> The Director-General of the World Health Organization, Tedros Adhanom is pointing his finger at Taiwan for his now soiled reputation amid the Coronavirus outbreak.<br/><br/>According to ETtoday, a netizen going by 'Osuka Yip' started a petition on Change.org on January 23rd, which demanded that Adhanom be replaced as the leader of the World Health Organization or 'WHO'. <br/><br/>The user believed that Adhanom's initial refusal to declare the Wuhan Coronavirus outbreak a global health emergency has led to millions being infected by the disease.<br/><br/>Yip said, "a lot of us are really disappointed, we believe that the WHO is supposed to be politically neutral. Without any investigation, Adhanom solely believes in the death and infected numbers that the Chinese government provided them."<br/><br/>As of today, nearly 700,000 people have signed this petition and the Ethiopian health official is reported to have accused Taiwanese netizens for the bulk of that. <br/><br/>Up Media state that the U.S. government has informed Taiwan's Ministry of Foreign Affairs that the Director-General believes the accusations of incompetence are all part of some elaborate scheme carried out by Taiwanese keyboard warriors, as opposed to there being any truth to the claim he failed in his position. <br/><br/>Despite his beliefs that the Taiwanese are behind his soiled reputation, many international leaders, including U.S. President Donald Trump, have publicly bashed him and his team for their delayed response to the Coronavirus. <br/><br/>Furthermore, during a House of Councillors meeting on March 26th, Japanese Deputy Prime Minister Taro Aso also mocked WHO's supposed political neutrality, saying a lot of people believe its name should be changed to "CHO," or "Chinese Health Organization."<br/><br/>Not helping his case, on the 24th of March the Taiwanese government did actually confirm that it had warned the WHO about the human-to-human transmission of the virus last December but was ignored. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/who-director-general-blames-taiwan-for-his-bad-reputation-3981623</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/31/3981623/3981623_59D63C51C73B43A68A161532272868AA_200331_3981623_WHO_Director_General_blames_Taiwan_for_his_bad_r_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
