<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 18:05:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3943710</guid>
      <title>China opens up knockoff Charles &amp; Keith stores called Cherlss &amp; Keich</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Few civilizations throughout the course of history have impacted the world as much as glorious China.  <br/><br/>Beijing has always been the global leader when it comes to innovation and trademark protection, which is why it makes this next story so outrageous. <br/>According to Business Insider, Singapore fashion brand Charles & Keith has 95 stores in China<br/>that is, as long as you don't count the knockoff stores as well. <br/>According to Hong Kong news site hk101.com, apparently some Chinese consumers have been duped by copycat stores called Cherlss & Keich. <br/>The fake stores are owned by a Chinese company called Guangzhou Yuantai Leather and opened last year. <br/>You can find Cherlss & Keich stores in Guangdong, Sichuan, Hunan and Shanghai. <br/>And if you take a look at their website, it bears a striking resemblance to the actual Charles & Keith site. <br/>It looks like quite a few Chinese shoppers thought they were buying the real thing, only to be tricked. <br/>Well<br/>this is most likely a one off as the Chinese have nothing but the utmost respect for trademarks.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-opens-up-knockoff-charles--keith-stores-called-cherlss--keich-3943710</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B0C/E28/B0CE283A087DA174D2F6B5B02FD5091B.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943710/3943710_5B0A3FBB37B742AAB9882925C892CAB9_200102_3943710_China_opens_up_knockoff_Charles___Keith_stores_c_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 01:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944008</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong kicks off 2020 with mass anti-government protests</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> Hong Kong has welcomed the new year by continuing the anti-government protests that have rocked the city since June 2019.<br/><br/>Tens of thousands of protesters took to the streets on New Year's Day in a peaceful march that soon turned violent, as reported by the South China Morning Post. <br/><br/>According to Reuters, police began firing rounds of tear gas and water cannons at the activists as they started throwing petrol bombs and forming roadblocks across several districts in Hong Kong.<br/><br/>Protesters were also seen spray painting graffiti, smashing ATM machines and setting fire to at least five different HSBC branches throughout the city.<br/><br/>A bronze lion at the bank's headquarters was splattered with red paint and set ablaze.<br/><br/>According to the South China Morning Post, the protesters turned against HSBC as they accuse the bank of having a hand in the recent police crackdown against a fundraising platform to support the activists. <br/><br/>At least 400 people were arrested for illegally gathering and for possession of weapons, the South China Morning Post reports, citing Hong Kong police. <br/><br/>Activists were seen holding signs that stated "Freedom is not free" and "Liberate Hong Kong, Revolution of our Times."<br/><br/>The protesters have continued to pressure the Hong Kong government to meet their core demands which include universal suffrage, an independent inquiry into police brutality, amnesty for all the protesters arrested and for the Hong Kong government to stop referring to the protests as "riots."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hong-kong-kicks-off-2020-with-mass-anti-government-protests-3944008</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/737/407/737407955D4F722BEBFD0AAF6168A55E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3944008/3944008_64ACF2FD72AC477E8D445982C1706F6C_200102_3944008_Hong_Kong_kicks_off_2020_with_mass_anti_governme_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944102</guid>
      <title>Man dies after falling into meat mincing machine in Malaysia.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MASJID TANAH, MALAYSIA <br/> A man unfortunately had to meet his maker after having an accident at a meat factory in Malaysia. <br/>According to the Star, a 47-year-old Nepalese worker was involved in the incident at a meat processing facility near Masjid Tanah. <br/>An official from the Malacca fire department said that the man was doing maintenance with three other workers in the morning at the factory on December 30. <br/>For some reason during the check, the meat-mincing machine suddenly turned on and caught the man at his waist.<br/><br/>The Star reported the other workers called for emergency crews at 7:45 a.m. and authorities arrived on the scene in under 10 minutes. <br/><br/>He unfortunately succumbed to his injuries on the spot.  <br/>The Star also said that it took the Masjid Tanah Fire and Rescue Department around 30 minutes to extricate the guy.   <br/>An investigation is being launched into the incident. <br/><br/>State news agency Bernama reported that around 360,000 Nepalese are working in Malaysia, with most of them doing security, construction or hospitality jobs.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-dies-after-falling-into-meat-mincing-machine-in-malaysia--3944102</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9C9/AD0/9C9AD003F426C54EDD3299924377D756.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3944102/3944102_B0470EF927774CBA8A180306461C6B6B_200102_3944102_Man_dies_after_falling_into_meat_mincing_machine_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 15:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944583</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's top general killed in Blackhawk helicopter crash</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW TAIPEI CITY, TAIWAN <br/> Taiwan's Chief of General Staff, General Shen Yi-ming, was en route to visit troops at a military base in Yilan when the Blackhawk helicopter he was traveling in crashed on Thursday, killing him and seven other officers.<br/><br/>Citing a military spokesman, the Liberty Times reports that the reason for the incident is unknown as visibility was good that day. <br/><br/>According to the United Daily News, the pilots reported favorable conditions for landing in their last communication at 8:07 p.m.<br/><br/>Shortly afterward, the military lost contact with the helicopter as the radar signature disappeared over a naval base in Yilan.<br/><br/>Citing first responders, the Liberty Times reports that the helicopter crashed to the west of its last reported location in the mountains between New Taipei City and Yilan.<br/><br/>Eight high-ranking officers and aircrew were killed, including Sheng. Five other passengers were rescued.<br/><br/>The United Daily News reports that a Military News Agency journalist, who was pinned by the wreckage, was able to call for help with her cellphone. She was rescued with injuries.<br/><br/>Another wounded officer helped guide rescuers to the crash site through heavy mist by blowing a rescue whistle.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-s-top-general-killed-in-blackhawk-helicopter-crash-3944583</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944583/3944583_23EB7C9A3F1F46689A251CD57622E040_200103_3944583_Taiwan_s_top_general_killed_in_Blackhawk_helicop_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 12:03:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944763</guid>
      <title>Tesla ready to start delivering made in China Model 3s</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> The first deliveries of Tesla Model 3 sedans made in lovely China for Chinese consumers are all set to go.<br/>Reuters reports that the company delivered its first Chinese made cars on Monday to 15 employees. <br/>The U.S. electric car company will start making deliveries to the public at its Shanghai factory at an event on Jan. 7.  <br/><br/>According to the NY Post, this comes exactly a year after CEO Elon Musk broke ground on the US$2 billion "Gigafactory."<br/>According to Reuters, the China-made Model 3s are $50,000 before subsidies. Imported Model 3s start at $63,000 for the longer-range version, while the same model in the U.S. costs under $40,000. <br/>The fun-loving Chinese government has been ultra supportive of the Tesla factory, the first wholly foreign-owned car plant in the country. <br/><br/>Guess that will make it a tad easier for China to get its grubby little hands on Tesla's trade secrets. <br/>Tesla has said its Shanghai factory will have a production capacity of 150,000 vehicles annually. <br/>So what are you waiting for China? Go get your shiny new Tesla today!!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tesla-ready-to-start-delivering-made-in-china-model-3s-3944763</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/04/3944763/3944763_AA150A13A7B94B71BAEE9836AAB36944_200104_3944763_Tesla_ready_to_start_delivering_made_in_China_Mo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 18:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945409</guid>
      <title>$17,000 fine for passenger who threw coins at plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANQING, CHINA <br/> A Chinese passenger has been fined $17,000 for throwing coins at a plane. <br/><br/>28-year-old, Lu was boarding a flight from Anqing to Kunming in February last year and told staff he threw the coins to ensure the plane avoid hazards.<br/><br/>'Lucky Air' the carrier, pursued the case and sued Mr. Lu for his actions, actions that caused significant delays to all 163 passengers including Mr. Lu who was initially detained for ten days. <br/><br/>On Wednesday, a court in Anqing ruled that he must pay a $17,000 fine. Mr. Lu then attempted to shift blame by saying the airline failed to tell him that he couldn't throw coins at the plane.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-17-000-fine-for-passenger-who-threw-coins-at-plane-3945409</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945409/3945409_4C9925C66E7140B0B8E0F82BC4358FEB_200106_3945409__17_000_fine_for_passenger_who_threw_coins_at_pl_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 02:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945800</guid>
      <title>Vietnamese influencer dumps on makeup in hospital for boyfriend</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VIETNAM <br/> A so-called social media influencer in Vietnam found herself on the wrong end of some online backlash for dumping mountain loads of makeup on while in the hospital.<br/>According to China Press, the influencer of all influencers was recovering in the hospital back in October when she decided to encase herself in some cosmetics.<br/>Apparently she found out that her boyfriend was on the way over and shared a Facebook post saying, "My boyfriend is coming to see me!"<br/>The ultra influencer then posted a crap ton of pictures of herself hooked up to a respirator wearing a truckload of foundation on as well as fake eyelashes, blush, eye shadow, eyeliner, nail polish and jewelry. <br/>And of course you can't be a real deal influencer if you don't take selfies of yourself pretending to sleep. <br/>Isn't it about time they have selfies drones that can do that kind of thing for you? Just think of all the influencing an influencer could influence. <br/>Well, we here at TomoNews wish nothing but the best for this woman and hope that she gets back up on her feet as quickly as possible because the world surely isn't going to influence itself.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/vietnamese-influencer-dumps-on-makeup-in-hospital-for-boyfriend-3945800</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945800/3945800_29975D3FF80040EC9E35FE53056D809C_200106_3945800_Vietnamese_influencer_dumps_on_makeup_in_hospita_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945910</guid>
      <title>Carlos Ghosn's escape: How it happened</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN <br/> According to Turkish private jet firm, MNG, two of their aircraft were used to facilitate ex-Nissan boss, Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan. MNG state that two separate private jets to two different clients were leased using faked documents forged by an employee of the company who acted within "his own capacity."<br/><br/>According to Business Insider, Ghosn was seen fleeing his home in Tokyo on the 29th of December. MNG state that the first private jet used in his escape flew from Osaka's Kansai Airport at 11 p.m. and landed in Istanbul the following day. At 6 a.m. just forty-five minutes after landing, Ghosn then took a second MNG flight bound for his home in Beirut, Lebanon.<br/><br/>65-year-old Ghosn, who holds Brazilian, French and Lebanese nationalities, reportedly entered Beirut legally using his French passport and his Lebanese identification despite Japanese lawyers stating they had possession of all three of his passports. Japanese outlet, NHK, however, reported that Mr. Ghosn had a duplicate French passport.<br/><br/>On Wednesday the 1st of January 2020, Turkish private jet firm, MNG filed a criminal complaint concerning the illegal use of its aircraft in relation to Carlos Ghosn's escape from Japan.<br/><br/>Mr. Ghosn is now a fugitive in Lebanon, which has no extradition treaty with Japan. Interpol has since filed a "red notice" for his arrest with authorities there.<br/><br/>Carlos Ghosn released a statement saying, "I am now in Lebanon and will no longer be held hostage by a rigged Japanese justice system where guilt is presumed, discrimination is rampant, and basic human rights are denied."<br/><br/>"I have not fled justice <br/> I have escaped injustice and political persecution."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/carlos-ghosn-s-escape-how-it-happened-3945910</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3945910/3945910_D38055E34A134C6D9F5AEA8E9B5896CA_200107_3945910_Carlos_Ghosn_s_escape__How_it_happened_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 03:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946361</guid>
      <title>Chinese man climbs into X-ray scanner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> A man was caught climbing into the security scanner at the Beijing West Railway Station, but why?<br/><br/>Accompanied by his wife, the couple was traveling home when security checks required them to place their coats and bags through the X-ray machine. Suddenly, the man climbed onto the conveyor belt and went through the machine, appearing out the other side before being detained. <br/><br/>On questioning, the man explained that he felt it was too much hassle to remove all of his belongings, so opted to scan himself instead.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-climbs-into-x-ray-scanner-3946361</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946361/3946361_497D65781C9E4054BACEB63BB3B916B0_200108_3946361_Chinese_man_climbs_into_X_ray_scanner_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 23:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946734</guid>
      <title>Plastic ban causes Thai shoppers to think outside the bag</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BANGKOK <br/> Thai shoppers are having to think outside the bag after a single-use plastic bag ban went into effect at the start of the year. <br/>According to a viral Facebook post with more than 70 pictures, a number of shoppers have decided to get creative with their reusable shopping containers. <br/>Thai citizens are hopping on board the environmental push by using earth-friendly reusable tote bags as well as some more unconventional carriers.  <br/><br/>From buckets and baskets to rice sacks, shoppers at major stores, supermarkets and convenience stores have taken to social media to post snaps of themselves going green. <br/><br/>Other methods of carting off purchases that deserve a hat tip include a wheelbarrow and a fishing net. <br/>Oh, there were also vases, pots, people using their own shirts and some random dude on his scooter. <br/>According to Reuters, Thailand was ranked sixth in the world's top countries that dump plastic garbage into the sea. However, over the past five months, they've dropped down to the 10th.  <br/><br/>Hopefully after the initial excitement of going green just for likes on social media wears off, consumers can stick to permanently cutting down plastics use.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/plastic-ban-causes-thai-shoppers-to-think-outside-the-bag-3946734</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946734/3946734_DF5BA83F49C4432F872C89014EFE5C21_200108_3946734_Plastic_ban_causes_Thai_shoppers_to_think_outsid_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 13:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946728</guid>
      <title>Can Impossible dumplings and Beyond buns make it in China?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> Impossible Foods and Beyond Meat want to tackle the Chinese market but face an uphill battle getting through governmental and cultural hoops. <br/>According to the failing New York Times, both Impossible Foods and Beyond Meat have both turned from niche start-ups into major food companies. <br/>They have made deals with fast-food giants like Mickey D's and Burger King, and have gained recognition for introducing plant-based products that are healthier and less harmful to the environment. Okay<br/>maybe not SO healthy.<br/>But can both companies find a foothold in China? <br/><br/>Because there are so many damn people in China, it makes them the world's largest consumer of meat.<br/><br/>Unfortunately, as the demand in China for pork and beef continues to rise, so will the temperature of the planet.    <br/>According to the New York Times, the two companies could find it difficult to get through China's complex regulatory process that involves a ton of Red China tape. <br/>Impossible and Beyond Meats could also face cultural challenges like making sure their faux meats meet Buddhist vegetarian laws and Chinese aversion to genetically modified foods. <br/>But let's be realistic, it's only really Americans that have such an aversion to veggies and fruit. Getting the rest of the world, especially Asia, to get on board with plant-based alternatives shouldn't be BEYOND IMPOSSIBLE.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/can-impossible-dumplings-and-beyond-buns-make-it-in-china--3946728</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946728/3946728_E1D2B6A9F5D9438980E57C7D28D72632_200108_3946728_Can_Impossible_dumplings_and_Beyond_buns_make_it_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 13:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947126</guid>
      <title>Chinese jaywalkers cross six-lane road by squeezing through crack</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINING, CHINA <br/> Why did the pedestrians cross the road? So they could use a tiny hole in the middle of a median barrier that wasn't meant for people. <br/>Pedestrians from the city of Xining located in fabulous Qinghai province have found themselves between a concrete median and some metal fencing. <br/>According to Pear Video, people having to hoof it along a massively long, six-lane street with few crosswalks have been forced to take matters into their own hands. <br/>People have been forced to squeeze themselves through a tiny opening in the middle of the busy street because walking down to actual crosswalks could take as long as 20 minutes, according to one person interviewed by Pear Video. <br/>The tiny crack definitely saves people a lot of time, but it also depends on how low you can go.  <br/>And then there's the whole risking your life trying to get across the road part that people also need to deal with. <br/>Either way, this is a clear cut example of some top notch civil engineering.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-jaywalkers-cross-six-lane-road-by-squeezing-through-crack-3947126</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947126/3947126_69E527595042456FBAF54EC70026CAD8_200109_3947126_Chinese_jaywalkers_cross_six_lane_road_by_squeez_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 11:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947332</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman rams into illegally parked car eleven times</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHEJIANG, CHINA <br/> A Chinese woman turned herself in to police after a spot of parking rage. <br/><br/>The woman known only as Yang had difficulties leaving her parking space Saturday night after a black vehicle illegally parked in front of her. She tried to contact the owner of the car and waited for 10 minutes; with no response, she took matters into her own hands and rammed into the car a total of 11 times.  <br/><br/>The surveillance footage went viral with some people empathizing with her whilst others claimed that she could have pulled out of the space had she been more careful.<br/><br/>Yang turned herself in to police the following day in Tonglu county in Zhejiang. They said that despite the fact the other vehicle was parked illegally she could still be charged with various crimes.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-woman-rams-into-illegally-parked-car-eleven-times-3947332</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947332/3947332_BFF7182652744AD48C52702036EB0538_200110_3947332_Chinese_woman_rams_into_illegally_parked_car_ele_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947759</guid>
      <title>Mystery pneumonia virus identified in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Scientists have identified a new virus as a possible cause for the mysterious pneumonia outbreak in China's Wuhan.<br/><br/>Citing researchers, China's Central Television reports that the pathogen is a coronavirus in the same family with the deadly MERS and SARS viruses.<br/><br/>Citing experts involved in the effort, the channel reports tests showed that an isolated sample to have appearances similar to the coronavirus.<br/><br/>The lab was also able to reconstruct the virus's genome sequence from 15 patient samples.<br/><br/>CNN reports that the symptoms of the mystery pneumonia include having difficulty breathing and fever, adding that the condition does not appear to be deadly.<br/><br/>According to CCTV, eight patients have been discharged from hospitals as of Thursday.<br/><br/>The pneumonia outbreak occurred in December and some of the patients were employed at a local seafood market.<br/><br/>According to Chinese authorities, there has been no clear evidence of a human to human infection and no fatalities have been reported.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mystery-pneumonia-virus-identified-in-china-3947759</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947759/3947759_B653121606B74A2A951915E5A31A6B5F_200110_3947759_Mystery_pneumonia_virus_identified_in_China_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 14:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948877</guid>
      <title>Taiwan President Tsai wins 2nd term in massive landslide</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN <br/> Taiwanese voters young and old hit the polls en masse on Saturday, voting President Tsai Ing-wen to a second term and giving the Democratic Progressive Party control of the legislature once again.<br/><br/>According to Focus Taiwan, Tsai received 57 percent of the vote<br/>earning a record 8,170,231 votes<br/>in a three-way race against panda hugging KMT candidate Han Kuo-yu with 38 percent and PFP candidate James Soong with only 4 percent.<br/>Focus Taiwan reports that voter turnout hit a whopping 74 percent, higher than 2016's 66.38 percent turnout. <br/>The DPP importantly retains control of the Legislative Yuan, which will allow Tsai to continue with her reform agenda. <br/>According to the failing New York Times, Tsai's incredible victory highlighted how effectively her campaign tapped into an electorate that isn't fooled at all by China's intentions. <br/>Another factor influencing the vote were months of protests in Hong Kong against Beijing's strong arm tactics and encroachment into the city.<br/>But by far, the biggest deciding factor in the historic election was the younger generation, who consider themselves Taiwanese, hitting the polls in force. <br/><br/>The people have spoken and the message is clear, Taiwan and the Taiwanese people are here to stay.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-president-tsai-wins-2nd-term-in-massive-landslide-3948877</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948877/3948877_1BB1F1E0613E4D1D9297151EB156C524_200113_3948877_Taiwan_President_Tsai_wins_2nd_term_in_massive_l_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 10:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949112</guid>
      <title>Man finds cigarette butt in his fancy Haidilao hot pot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BAOJI, CHINA <br/> A Chinese man enjoying some hot pot at China's most popular chain was lucky enough to find a cigarette butt in his yummy-for-the-tummy broth. <br/><br/>According to Pear Video, a customer surnamed Liu was eating at a Haidilao location in the Shaanxi city of Baoji. <br/><br/>Unfortunately for Liu, lurking inside his delicious broth was a nastly old cigarette butt. Either that, or he was eating tobacco flavored hot pot. <br/>Anyways, it looks like Liu called up the chain's headquarters and demanded 14 cents in compensation and that the location be shut down for one week. <br/>Haidilao refused to close the location in question, but they did offer the man $144 instead. Too bad Liu turned them down. <br/><br/>Guess we'll have to wait and see what happens. <br/>According to the Shanghaiist, Haidilao now has more than 190 stores through fun-loving China and in cities like L.A., Singapore, Seoul and Tokyo.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-finds-cigarette-butt-in-his-fancy-haidilao-hot-pot-3949112</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949112/3949112_C5F430A496A84036B727491D89333E66_200114_3949112_Man_finds_cigarette_butt_in_his_fancy_Haidilao_h_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 02:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949278</guid>
      <title>Sinkhole swallows up public bus in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINING, CHINA <br/> Anyone else getting a sinking feeling in your stomach? Oh that's just the entire road collapsing. <br/><br/>On January 13, a road in Xining, China suddenly opened up and swallowed half of a public bus while waiting for passengers to get on.<br/><br/>Footage from Chinese social media shows people fleeing the scene as soon as the road begins to give way.  Some bystanders tried to help passengers escape, but as the sinkhole got bigger they all said screw it and just ran away instead. <br/><br/>After that, an explosion is seen occurring at the front of the bus. It's unclear what caused the blast. <br/><br/>According to Sina News, 15 people are injured while 10 are missing. Authorities say they will continue searching for those missing and will investigate the cause of the incident.<br/><br/>Just last month, two giant sinkholes, one in Guangzhou and the other in Xiamen, appeared over underground railways that were under construction in China. <br/>For the Guangzhou subway, three people actually went missing while in Xiamen the sinkhole gobbled up passing vehicles.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sinkhole-swallows-up-public-bus-in-china-3949278</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949278/3949278_4B023587483844C89BB61EF1D06C980C_200114_3949278_Sinkhole_swallows_up_public_bus_in_China_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 08:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950368</guid>
      <title>Distracted dad almost puts son through X-ray scanner</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUIGANG, CHINA <br/> Who hasn't been there before? Running late for a flight or the train with a little one in tow and a boatload of luggage for extra fun. <br/>A father at a train station in the Guangxi city of Guigang clearly had some other things on his mind when he almost sent his son through a security checkpoint X-ray scanner by accident. <br/>According to video posted to Miaopai, the distracted daddy was pushing his luggage, which was also doubling as a ride for his 3-year-old son on January 12.  <br/>Security camera footage shows dad of the decade approach the security check and get in line.   <br/>When it's his turn, he just starts going through the motions and grabs his son and puts him right onto the conveyor belt.<br/>It isn't until security and another traveler point at that lil man isn't baggage that the dad jumps into action and rescues him from a free X-ray.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/distracted-dad-almost-puts-son-through-x-ray-scanner-3950368</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950368/3950368_890265BE221F4A8297D2D124845E4A21_200116_3950368_Distracted_dad_almost_puts_son_through_X_ray_sca_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950538</guid>
      <title>Villagers in India flee after being terrorized by army of monkeys</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NARASAPURAM VILLAGE, INDIA <br/> In a plot straight out of the Planet of the Apes films, villagers in India were forced to flee their homes after being menaced by a crazed army of over 400 monkeys.<br/><br/>According to the Daily Star, the whole thing started 15 years ago, when a troop of mischievous macaques were kicked out of Hyderabad and abandoned near the village of Narasapuram.<br/><br/>They were a nuisance, but it wasn't until they bred and multiplied into an army of over 400 that they REALLY became a problem.<br/><br/>Village chief Srivarama Krishna told the Daily Star that the pesky primates became more brazen and opportunistic, stealing snacks and groceries out of people's hands, and even sneaking into houses to grab pots of food.<br/><br/>They also turned more aggressive, and started attacking people, which in turn led to  about 20 families packing their bags and fleeing the village.<br/><br/>According to the New Indian Express, village chief Krishna asked expert monkey catchers to help nab the macaques in exchange for money from the villagers.<br/><br/>Over 100 monkeys were caught and released deep in the forest, prompting old residents to come back now that the village's primate population has gone down.<br/><br/>Here's hoping Planet of the Apes doesn't rise again anytime soon.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/villagers-in-india-flee-after-being-terrorized-by-army-of-monkeys-3950538</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950538/3950538_3889C82A802B4674A807F2A649D7B7B8_200117_3950538_Villagers_in_India_flee_after_being_terrorized_b_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 16:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950813</guid>
      <title>Chinese 'quantum' speed reading institutes ordered to shut down</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/>Remember those "quantum" speed reading classes in China? Turns out it was a total scam.<br/><br/>In a video from last year, kids at a "quantum" speed reading competition were seen flipping pages at superspeed, staring as the pages went by.<br/><br/>One teacher actually claimed that this technique allows children to read 100,000 characters in a span of one to five minutes. <br/><br/>According to the Shanghaiist, this speed reading technique was developed by Japanese teacher Yumiko Tobitani who claimed that as a person flips the pages, images start appearing in your head which helps a person to understand the content of the book.<br/><br/>Tobitani even went so far as to claim that the technique works on foreign text as it will be translated to your native language through images as you flip the pages.<br/><br/>According to the Shanghaiist, parents have shelled out as much as US$7,000 for their kids to pick up "quantum" speed reading.<br/><br/>On Thursday, China's Ministry of Education released a statement saying that at least five institutes with "quantum" speed reading courses have been ordered to shut down for operating without proper licenses required for teaching or running a business.<br/><br/>The ministry also called on local governments to launch an investigation into other institutions to prevent false advertising.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-quantum-speed-reading-institutes-ordered-to-shut-down-3950813</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950813/3950813_02DECB20706B42189070E016FC1DCABE_200117_3950813_Chinese__quantum__speed_reading_institutes_order_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:20:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950810</guid>
      <title>Chinese man pays $21,000 for ant-sized parking space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XIAN, CHINA <br/> A massive baller in China dropped over $21,000 on a money parking space. Unfortunately, it looks like it was made for ants. <br/>According to Pear Video, the man surnamed Yu showed local media his unbelievable awesome space in the Shaanxi city of Xi'an.<br/>The man told reporters that he moved into the building in 2008, but didn't spring for a parking space until 2019. <br/>Unfortunately for the man, when he actually saw the space, he realized that there was a massive slab of concrete blocking him from actually opening his door. <br/><br/>What's even more money is that if the a car is parked in the parking spot next to him, the only way he can get in and out of his vehicle is through the sunroof. <br/>Yu then measured the space himself and found it to only be 1.9 meters wide and 4 meters long. <br/>The funny thing is that when Yu told building management about his crappy space, they told him that he would need to blow even more money in order to get a new spot.  <br/><br/>Guess Yu better get used to using that sunroof, or maybe we should call it a sundoor.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-pays-21-000-for-ant-sized-parking-space-3950810</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950810/3950810_F5E4E6B5D42E415B8A755A69C34A9156_200117_3950810_Chinese_man_pays__21_000_for_ant_sized_parking_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952169</guid>
      <title>Rich woman angers China with Forbidden City photoshoot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> A very intelligent woman decided to brag over Chinese censored social media about being in the Forbidden City on a day it was closed to the public<br/>which for a country that gets its feelings hurt REAL easily<br/>probably wasn't the best idea. <br/>According to the BBC, the woman, who calls herself Lu Xiaobao on China's Twitter knockoff Weibo, decided to flaunt her high level commie connections by posting snaps of herself, some other spoiled brat and a Mercedes SUV in a completely empty Forbidden City in lovely Beijing.  <br/>She was also kind enough to include the caption saying, "On Monday the Palace Museum is closed, so I hurried over, hid from the crowds, and went to play in the Forbidden City."<br/><br/>The BBC reports that the old palace complex usually closes on Monday to allow for maintenance and renovation work. <br/>Well<br/>cue the outrage. The incredibly douchey photos instantly went viral. Lu then realized she had made a mistake and deleted the pictures.  <br/>One user left a comment that has been shared more than 400,000 times saying, "deleting the pictures is useless; the entire Chinese nation has seen them." <br/>According to the Shanghaiist, the Palace Museum had to issue an apology Friday night saying they would increase security and not let something like this happen again. <br/>But let's be honest, in a country where people connected to the CCP can do whatever they want, stuff like this will clearly happen again. Long live China!!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/rich-woman-angers-china-with-forbidden-city-photoshoot-3952169</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952169/3952169_06089F0C2E2F4110A95DB976EAC6CE1C_200120_3952169_Rich_woman_angers_China_with_Forbidden_City_phot_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952163</guid>
      <title>China teen gets intestinal bubble tea blockage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINXIANG, CHINA <br/> A teen from Henan had to make a trip to the emergency room after experiencing some severely unpleasant abdominal pain. Turns out the culprit was bubble tea. <br/>According to Pear Video, he was sent for a checkup and an X-ray at the First Affiliated Hospital of Xinxiang Medical University, which showed signs of intestinal blockage. <br/><br/>In strict medical terms, the pipes were all backed up. <br/>It appears the boy had drunk two bubble teas one week before he started feeling abdominal discomfort. Unfortunately, rather than chew the bubble tea pearls, he pretty much just swallowed them.<br/><br/>Bubble tea pearls are made out of tapioca starch and corn flour which could take a while to digest. Some places may also add thickening agents to the pearls which make them even harder to get rid off. <br/><br/>And then let's not forget the whole made in China factor. <br/>Doctors had to go in and remove the two bubble tea blockages through surgery. Nature then took its course for the remaining pearls over the next couple of days after the operation. <br/>Lesson of the day? Maybe add some chewing into the inhaling process.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-teen-gets-intestinal-bubble-tea-blockage-3952163</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952163/3952163_FE7981E60E4A469FA3BE5CB9EC7F0889_200120_3952163_China_teen_gets_intestinal_bubble_tea_blockage_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 12:49:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952386</guid>
      <title>Pig forced to bungee jump in China for LNY theme park stunt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHONGQING, CHINA <br/> As African Swine Flu continues to decimate China's oink oink population and a new SARS cousin spreading like mad within the country, it's good to see people are still in the Lunar New Year's spirit. <br/><br/>According to the SCMP, workers from some two-bit theme park in the Sichuan city of Chongqing decided to celebrate the opening of a bungee jump attraction by hurling an animal off of it. <br/>Footage shows the animal-loving employees haul the 200-pound unwilling participant pig up the 70-meter tall tower. <br/>The pig clearly isn't having any of it, but that doesn't stop park staff from suiting it up. <br/>Porky then gets launched off the 20-story tower squealing like mad the entire way down. <br/>And of course because the video was shared online it caused instant and massive backlash. And by massive backlash we mean some netizens leaving some comments online. <br/>The theme park owner told local media that since it was the opening day, they wanted to, "let the pig make the first jump because pork prices have been very high this year and recently they dropped a bit." <br/><br/>The owner also said the cruel stunt was planned to mark the end of the Year of the Pig and the beginning of the Year of the Rat, which begins Saturday.<br/><br/>The theme park owner kind of sounds like a rat. <br/><br/>As for the hog, when asked for a quote about the whole incident it said...]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/pig-forced-to-bungee-jump-in-china-for-lny-theme-park-stunt-3952386</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952386/3952386_8BB08FA5D8734F2AB48FAC550494EDFB_200121_3952386_Pig_forced_to_bungee_jump_in_China_for_LNY_theme_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 05:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952703</guid>
      <title>Bow-tie wearing rabbit flies business-class to Japan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN <br/> A bunny with some pretty incredible fashion sense named Coco lives better than you do.<br/>Photos recently went viral of the bowtie-wearing rabbit flying business class from San Francisco to Japan onboard a United Airlines flight with her owner, who was starting a new job there a couple of years ago. <br/>According to Insider, the bougie bunny incident took place in late 2018, but the pictures are just going viral now after recently appearing on sites like Metro. <br/>Owner Takako Ogawa was moving back to Japan, but was worried Coco might not make the trip back in the hold, so she registered it as an emotional support animal and only had to pay $100 to let Coco join her in the cabin in a carry case. <br/>After the flight took off, flight attendants let Ogawa know the seat next to her was empty, so they let Coco have it. <br/>How considerate of United to let a rabbit use the seat rather than some unlucky person jammed in crappy economy.  <br/>People will be happy to hear that when it was time for ice cream, Coco wasn't left out. She was given her own plate of almonds and nuts to munch on.  <br/><br/>Ogawa said she also remembers being prepared if Coco had any accidents, but apparently the rabbit didn't make a mess. <br/>So just remember next time you hop on board your next flight, this bad & bougie bunny has you beat.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/bow-tie-wearing-rabbit-flies-business-class-to-japan-3952703</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952703/3952703_103554728D284C08916B5F2E64120F54_200121_3952703_Bow_tie_wearing_rabbit_flies_business_class_to_J_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 13:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952833</guid>
      <title>Chinese school rewards top students with bags of pork</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FUYANG, CHINA <br/> A middle school in Fuyang City rewarded its top students with a choice of either bags of pork weighing 2.5kg or two large carps. <br/><br/>In an interview with Pear Video, the principal told reporters that this was the second year his school rewarded its students with food; going on to say that a rough 5500kg of pork had been distributed to 2200 students.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-school-rewards-top-students-with-bags-of-pork-3952833</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3952833/3952833_73B681E8689A4ED795AEE16532855DA3_200122_3952833_Chinese_school_rewards_top_students_with_bags_of_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 23:49:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952917</guid>
      <title>China to implement single-use plastic ban over 5 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> China will be implementing a ban on single-use plastics over the next five years.<br/><br/>A new policy will ban plastic bags in all major Chinese cities, such as Shanghai and Beijing, by the end of 2020 and in all Chinese towns by 2022, Reuters reports, citing China's National Development and Reform Commission. Markets that sell fresh produce will be exempt until 2025.<br/><br/>Restaurants will be banned from providing single-use straws by the end of this year, while takeaway food services will not be allowed to provide single-use utensils by 2025. <br/><br/>China aims to reduce single-use plastic consumption in its restaurant industry by 30 percent in the next five years.<br/><br/>Other plastic items such as plastic courier packaging will be phased out by the end of 2025.<br/><br/>China also stated that the production and sale of plastic bags thinner than 0.025 millimeters, as well as plastic film for agricultural use that is less than 0.01 millimeters thick, would be banned.<br/><br/>According to the online publication Our World in Data based at the University of Oxford, China produced nearly 60 million tons of plastic waste in 2010. The research noted that the projections are expected to be similar up to the year 2025.<br/><br/>The research also said that mismanaged plastic waste around the world is at "significant risk" of leaking and impacting our environment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-to-implement-single-use-plastic-ban-over-5-years-3952917</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3952917/3952917_DDF5E5D8DABA47F9B71C722CEDD07122_200122_3952917_China_to_implement_single_use_plastic_ban_over_5_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 05:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953082</guid>
      <title>Chinese teen with grandmother face gets brand new mug</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENYANG, CHINA <br/> A teenage Chinese girl with a medical condition that gave her the face of a grandmother finally has something to smile about<br/>a brand new mug. <br/>According to Chinese Twitter knockoff Weibo, 15-year-old Xiao Feng from Heishan County in Liaoning province suffers from Hutchinson-Gilford Progeria syndrome.<br/><br/>One of the more noticeable symptoms is premature aging. Unfortunately, there is currently no cure for the condition. <br/>Things had gotten so bad for Feng that she had to drop out of school because she was getting made fun of so much. <br/>But then it all turned around after she wrote a letter to Chinese philanthropist Guo Mingyi asking for a helping hand. <br/>After a few weeks of back and forth, Sunline Plastic Surgery Hospital said it would waive 70 percent of the $72,000 surgery, while Guo picked up the rest of the tab. <br/>A team of plastic surgeons then went to work on building a new face for Xiao in a three-part operation. <br/>Physicians first had to get rid of all the wrinkles in her skin, which took a bit more time because it was so loose and lacking elasticity.<br/>After that was taken care of, doctors then went about reconstructing her nose and lips. <br/>And only three weeks after going under the knife, Xiao was able to show off her brand new face to a backed house on January 20. <br/>For now, Xiao said she plans to go back to school and in the future hopes to become a doctor or nurse someday.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-teen-with-grandmother-face-gets-brand-new-mug-3953082</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953082/3953082_B8C3AAEBCFA141198977DB8D38AFB44A_200122_3953082_Chinese_teen_with_grandmother_face_gets_brand_ne_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 09:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953015</guid>
      <title>Malaysia ships back containers of 'illegal' plastic waste to the West</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUALA LUMPUR <br/> Malaysia announced that it has returned 150 shipping containers filled with plastic waste to their country of origin after they were found to be contaminated and mixed in with other trash.<br/><br/>Malaysia has sent back 3,737 metric tons of plastic waste to a total of 13 countries, including France, the United Kingdom, the United States and Canada, according to the BBC. <br/><br/>France received 43 containers, while the United Kingdom received 42 containers. The United States and Canada received 17 and 11 containers, respectively.<br/><br/>Malaysian authorities said that they hope to send back another 110 containers by mid-2020. Sixty of the containers are from the U.S., 15 from Canada and 14 from Japan.<br/><br/>Malaysia's environmental minister Yeo Bee Yin said the shipping companies and the countries that shipped out the containers will be responsible for the cost of the returns, CNN reports. <br/><br/>Many countries export recyclable waste abroad as this reduces domestic landfill, helps them meet recycling targets and is also inexpensive.<br/><br/>In a Facebook post, Yeo said that their government will ensure that Malaysia does not become the "garbage dump of the world."<br/><br/>Malaysia is not the only country in Southeast Asia facing this problem. According to the BBC, Indonesia and the Philippines have all sent back unwanted plastic waste to developed countries over the past year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/malaysia-ships-back-containers-of-illegal-plastic-waste-to-the-west-3953015</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953015/3953015_A0DA5D56A3CA4359AF000B82E58D41E3_200122_3953015_Malaysia_ships_back_containers_of__illegal__plas_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 08:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953494</guid>
      <title>Chinese city apologizes for pajama shaming its residents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SUZHOU, CHINA <br/> Officials in the city of Suzhou in China's Anhui province got all the hate for shaming residents who go out and about in their nightwear.<br/><br/>According to the New York Times, wearing pajamas in public is a thing in China. And honestly, can you blame them? Those things are comfy!<br/><br/>But government officials in Suzhou don't like the practice, so they used facial recognition tech to police folks strutting the streets in their sleepwear.<br/><br/>The party poopers posted the surveillance photos online and outed the identities of the pajama wearers to shame them for their "uncivilized behavior."<br/><br/>Suzhou officials claimed they were trying to win a national "civilized city" competition and banned residents from wearing their PJs out on the street. Not cool!<br/><br/>Spitting in the streets, cutting lines, throwing wild public tantrums - that's uncivilized. But what the heck is wrong with pajamas?! <br/><br/>Chinese netizens are asking the same thing. Many online are pissed at the pajama shaming and are calling the city government out for infringing on its citizens' privacy.<br/><br/>Suzhou officials later apologized and said they'd blur the photos in the future.<br/><br/>Hey geniuses, maybe try focusing on legit public matters instead of policing people's clothing choices.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-city-apologizes-for-pajama-shaming-its-residents-3953494</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953494/3953494_2D21C30C86CA4534BA00AD46B128D099_200123_3953494_Chinese_city_apologizes_for_pajama_shaming_its_r_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 04:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955501</guid>
      <title>College student returns to China, gets jailed over US tweets</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Beijing got its feelings so hurt over some tweets posted by a Chinese student studying at the University of Minnesota, they actually threw him in jail the first chance they got.<br/>According to a Chinese court document viewed by Axios, some of the tweets contained images deemed to be unflattering portrayals of a "national leader."<br/>Now what national leader could they possibly be talking about in China? <br/>Axios reports the document says that in September and October 2018, while 20-year-old Luo Daiqing was a Golden Gopher, he used Twitter to post more than 40 comments "denigrating a national leader's image and indecent pictures," which "created a negative social impact." <br/>Some of the images which got some panties in a serious ruffle where Chinese propaganda slogans pasted over images of cartoon bad guy Lawrence Limburger. <br/><br/>Other pictures that helped land him behind bars were those of Winnie the Pooh, a cartoon that is off limits because Xi Jinping looks like the fat cartoon bear<br/>except just more dictatory. <br/>Chinese police snatched Luo in his hometown of Wuhan in July 2019 when he went back for summer break. <br/>After months of just waiting in a fun-loving Chinese jail, he was sentenced in November 2019 to six months in prison for "provocation."  <br/>According to Axios, the case represents a dramatic escalation of Beijing's efforts to shut down free speech abroad and a global expansion of a Chinese police campaign to hunt down Twitter users in China critical of the douchey government.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/college-student-returns-to-china-gets-jailed-over-us-tweets-3955501</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955501/3955501_E97F649D3A2249FDA03CE7F8E3D43E0F_200128_3955501_College_student_returns_to_China__gets_jailed_ov_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 11:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955497</guid>
      <title>Chinese media uses stock image to show hospital building progress</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> As the Wuhan novel coronavirus continues to spread like wildfire throughout China, it's nice to see Beijing still using good old propaganda to deal with the situation. <br/>To handle the exponentially increasing number of patients infected with this latest coronavirus, officials in Wuhan announced last week that they would build a 1,000-bed hospital in just six days. <br/>Hey, God created Earth in just seven, so six days should be more than ample time for a hospital<br/>especially a prefabricated one.  <br/>On Monday, the Hubei Daily bragged that the first building of the Huoshenshan Hospital being completed in only 16 hours. <br/>They were then kind enough to attach a stock photo to prove the pop-up hospital was almost ready to receive the walking dead. <br/>By using the latest technology<br/>a reverse image search<br/>it was quickly discovered the photo was in fact nothing but a stock photo from a Chinese construction company. <br/>The Hubei Daily has since deleted the post, but luckily one of the CCP's official speaker boxes<br/>the People's Daily<br/>is still trying to pass it off as real. <br/>The Huoshenshan Hospital is supposed to be up and running by February 2. What could possibly go wrong?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-media-uses-stock-image-to-show-hospital-building-progress-3955497</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955497/3955497_B7CC3DE96EB04B3CA2BE0DD8A3EBD428_200128_3955497_Chinese_media_uses_stock_image_to_show_hospital__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 11:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956590</guid>
      <title>Starbucks shuts 2,000 Chinese stores over coronavirus fears</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Starbucks has shut down half of its stores in China amid the coronavirus outbreak in order to protect its staff and support government containment efforts.<br/><br/>NPR reports that the coffee behemoth has temporarily shut more than 2,000 outlets as the number of infected have skyrocketed throughout the country.    <br/><br/>According to the BBC, Starbucks warned that the latest epidemic could affect its financial performance. Which is all anyone really cares about, right? <br/>The Beebs reports that the coffee chain has almost 4,300 stores in China, making it the company's biggest market outside the U.S. <br/>Starbucks CEO Kevin Johnson said the company was "navigating a very dynamic situation." <br/>As the Wuhan coronavirus threatens to spiral out of control, Chinese authorities have tried all types of measures including the locking down of a bunch of cities with tens of millions of people. <br/>According to Business Insider, other fast food chains such as McDonald's, KFC and Pizza Hut have also been shutting down stores in response to the virus.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/starbucks-shuts-2-000-chinese-stores-over-coronavirus-fears-3956590</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956590/3956590_BB48B2ECDB4A49118519D3D48326FDC2_200131_3956590_Starbucks_shuts_2_000_Chinese_stores_over_corona_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 03:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956857</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus might infect people faster than Ebola</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Chinese Researchers find that the novel coronavirus epidemic doubled in size every 7.4 days during the initial outbreak from December last year to early this month.<br/><br/>The statistical study published in the New England Journal of Medicine suggests human to human transmission occurred early in the outbreak's beginning.<br/><br/>Examining the first 425 confirmed cases of coronavirus infection, the scientists estimate that the mean incubation period was 5.2 days.<br/><br/>Before January 1, 2020, 55 percent of the symptomatic cases were linked to the Wuhan wet market, but just 8.6 percent of the subsequent cases were connected to the market."<br/><br/>The authors say that it is clear that human-to-human transmission is occurring and that the epidemic has been spreading in recent weeks.<br/><br/>MedPage Today reports that virus' reproductive number of 2.2 means a carrier will infect two people on average, which is more than Ebola.<br/><br/>Citing Infectious Diseases Society of America, the outlet reports that the reproductive number is situational and quarantining a patient could reduce the number to zero.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-virus-might-infect-people-faster-than-ebola-3956857</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956857/3956857_41A5D997CBC54B4CB917F35CE10DE612_200131_3956857_Wuhan_virus_might_infect_people_faster_than_Ebol_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 11:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956702</guid>
      <title>The Wuhan coronavirus has spread to every region in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> China has confirmed its first case of novel coronavirus in Tibet. <br/><br/>This means the Wuhan virus has now spread to every single region across China, bringing up the total number of confirmed cases to nearly 9,800 as of Friday, according to the New York Times.<br/><br/>According to CNN, the number of coronavirus cases has already surpassed the number of SARS cases, which was 5,327, inside China back in 2003. The virus has taken the lives of 213 people in China.<br/><br/>The novel coronavirus has spread to at least 19 other nations including Japan, South Korea, Vietnam, Cambodia, Malaysia, Singapore, the U.S. and Canada, reports BBC News. <br/><br/>Since the outbreak, countries including Japan and the U.S. have rushed to evacuate their citizens out of the Chinese city of Wuhan, where the virus is believed to have originated.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports health officials in the U.S. reported its first human to human transmission of the coronavirus. A woman who had traveled to Wuhan had spread the virus to her husband who had not been to China. Both of them have now been hospitalized for treatment.<br/><br/>According to CNN, other countries including Australia, Germany, Italy and Spain said that they are working with local authorities in China and are expected to repatriate their citizens out of Wuhan later this week.<br/><br/>On Thursday, the World Health Organization declared the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak a global health emergency.<br/><br/>A large number of countries are advising their citizens to avoid all non-essential travel to China, BBC News reports. <br/><br/>Symptoms of the coronavirus include severe coughing, fever and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.<br/><br/>The coronavirus is believed to have originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there are now documented cases of the virus being transmitted between humans.<br/><br/>The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention advised the public to wear facemasks and cover the mouth when coughing or sneezing to prevent the spread of the coronavirus. The CDC also advised the public to avoid using unwashed hands to touch their eyes, nose and mouth, and to avoid sharing items that could easily be infected.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-wuhan-coronavirus-has-spread-to-every-region-in-china-3956702</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956702/3956702_76D84EDAD66D4354B0A53B3BAB6EC1B6_200131_3956702_The_Wuhan_coronavirus_has_spread_to_every_region_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 07:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956962</guid>
      <title>Chinese people making DIY coronavirus helmets, masks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> As the Wuhan virus continues to fan out across all parts of China, the number of confirmed cases is already over 9,400, with another 12,000 plus suspected cases and over 200 dead.  <br/>And these are numbers coming out of China, so clearly the actual numbers are obviously higher than what's being reported. <br/>Amongst all the madness, Chinese travelers have started to take matters into their own hands and have started to think outside<br/>REAL outside the mask.  <br/>People have been spotted in and around China with all types of do-it-yourself coronavirus helmets and masks.<br/>One popular type appears to be the plastic water jug helmet. Chinese people have been spotted on planes, trains and automobiles sporting the stylish not-so-protective gear.<br/>This guy appears to be going for a Kylo Ren-esque look with his water jug and water bottles. <br/>For those that can't spring for the water jug, don't worry, a motorcycle helmet will suffice. Probably not, but what the hell. <br/>Then there are the more eco-friendly masks made from fruit. <br/>But what if you can't find or make any of these masks yourself? Here's one way you can stop the flow<br/>of contaminated air you breathe.  <br/>So are any of these methods effective? Probably not. <br/><br/>Are they safe? Well, one of the first things you learn as a child is to never put your head in a plastic bag. Guess that doesn't apply in China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-people-making-diy-coronavirus-helmets-masks-3956962</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956962/3956962_097EAB4495834D22912D15EEA4033541_200131_3956962_Chinese_people_making_DIY_coronavirus_helmets__m_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 15:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
