<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 18:05:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3982433</guid>
      <title>Stacks of Coronavirus urns cast doubt on official Wuhan death toll</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> As China's regime pushes a narrative of how Xi Jinping is winning the war on the Coronavirus, and that Wuhan only suffered a very questionable 2,548 deaths, images surfacing online of stacks of urns and long queues at funeral homes cast doubt over their dubious claims. <br/><br/>According to Bloomberg, the families of those who succumbed to the virus in Wuhan were allowed to collect their cremated ashes at numerous funeral homes last week, and as they did, photos began to circulate online that show thousands of urns being shipped in. <br/><br/>According to Chinese media outlet Caixin, outside one funeral home, trucks delivered around 2,500 urns on both Wednesday and Thursday. <br/><br/>Another picture showed 3,500 urns stacked on the ground inside; that one funeral home alone already exceeds the official number of those dead.<br/><br/>Residents in Wuhan claim 500 urns have been handed out to grieving families every day from seven separate funeral homes all serving the city.<br/><br/>This means the ashes of 3,500 people are distributed every 24 hours.<br/><br/>The funeral homes in Hankou, Wuchang and Hanyang have told grieving families that they will receive the ashes before April 5th, the date of the Qing Ming festival where people tend the graves of their ancestors. <br/><br/>This means that 42,000 urns could be distributed in that 12-day period.<br/><br/>On the 27th March, one Wuhan resident going only by his surname Zhang told Radio Free Asia, "It can't be right because the incinerators have been working round-the-clock, so how can so few people have died?"<br/><br/>Another local resident, Chen Yaohui told RFA that nobody believes the official death toll, saying "they transferred cremation workers from around China to Wuhan to keep cremating bodies round-the-clock."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/stacks-of-coronavirus-urns-cast-doubt-on-official-wuhan-death-toll-3982433</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/02/3982433/3982433_68DB1B08A10B4967A1A99612F416A7D2_200402_3982433_Stacks_of_Coronavirus_urns_cast_doubt_on_officia_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 06:38:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3982726</guid>
      <title>Beijing cemetery staff will honor your dead for you</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> The coronavirus has halted almost all aspects of daily life, but crowd prevention regulations in China are making the Qingming Festival, or Tomb Sweeping Day especially difficult.<br/><br/>Tomb Sweeping, a day of tidying the graves of loved ones falls on April 4th this year and those unable to do so, because of said regulations can apply to have cemetery workers do it for them.<br/><br/>While the holiday usually bears witness to masses gathering at cemeteries across the country, authorities this year are capping the number of people to avoid those big crowds. <br/><br/>An online reservation system has been rolled out, but if you aren't able to book your spot, workers at Beijing's Babaoshan Cemetery can and will honor your dead for you. <br/><br/>Photos published online to ChinaNews.com show a three-person team dressed in protective gear; they scrub tombstones, leave flowers behind and then bow. <br/><br/>Similar systems have since been set up at Shanghai's cemeteries where all 160,000 Tomb Sweeping Day slots have now been taken.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/beijing-cemetery-staff-will-honor-your-dead-for-you-3982726</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/03/3982726/3982726_5CC2A5F73BBB4E0DA022566F66B63284_200403_3982726_Beijing_cemetery_staff_will_honor_your_dead_for__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 03:15:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3983750</guid>
      <title>China Holds 3-Minute Silence To Mourn Those Lost To Coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> To mourn those who succumbed to the Coronavirus, China's 1.38 billion people stood silently on Saturday morning to the tune of cars, trains, and ships sounding their horns for three minutes. <br/><br/>The three minutes of silence symbolically occurred on the Qingming Festival or Tomb Sweeping Day in China on the 4th at 10 a.m. <br/><br/>All public activities were suspended with flags at half-mast; the subway trains in Shanghai also stopped running for the duration and sounded their horns too. <br/><br/>The mass event commemorates the deaths of more than 81,000 people in China, including 14 frontline medical workers who have been declared "martyrs" of the epidemic. <br/><br/>Most memorable, of course, is none other than Dr. Li Wenliang who was punished by Chinese authorities for sounding the alarm about the outbreak back in December; a mind-boggling move that potentially enabled the then epidemic to become a pandemic. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-holds-3-minute-silence-to-mourn-those-lost-to-coronavirus-3983750</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/06/3983750/3983750_C9417139B84E4359A9309CAB0F0B1B22_200406_3983750_China_Holds_3_Minute_Silence_To_Mourn_Those_Lost_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 08:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984090</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus: Doctor Dies One Day Before Seeing Her Family</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> After returning from the frontline of the Coronavirus outbreak in Hubei province, a Chinese doctor tragically passed away before she was reunited with her family. <br/><br/>According to a report on the Chinese social media platform, Weibo, Dr. Zhang Jingjing spent a total of two months in the city of Huanggang before returning to Shandong province on the 21st of March. <br/><br/>She was then put into a 14-day isolation period upon her arrival back.<br/><br/>However, on April 5th, just one day away before being allowed home, Zhang suffered a fatal heart attack; efforts to save her proved unsuccessful and she was declared dead on Monday evening.<br/><br/>The report claims that she leaves behind a 5-year-old daughter and a husband, who is working in Africa and hasn't been able to fly home.<br/><br/>Zhang, who was only in her mid-thirties tested negative three times for COVID-19; therefore it's not currently clear what caused her cardiac arrest.<br/><br/>A number of doctors in China did die from exhaustion alone, after working for weeks straight combatting the outbreak.<br/><br/>One such doctor was a 51-year-old woman who died after working 18 days straight in February; she was posthumously labeled a "role model for other medics" by provincial officials a label that surely pressures doctors to work to exhaustion and to death.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-doctor-dies-one-day-before-seeing-her-family-3984090</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/07/3984090/3984090_02F3F397C0724E6D9CC7E73667E7130A_200407_3984090_Coronavirus__Doctor_Dies_One_Day_Before_Seeing_H_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 05:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985298</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus Lockdown Spurs Pandas To Finally Mate</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ABERDEEN, HONG KONG <br/> If there's one good thing to come of quarantine, it's that in our absence some timid pandas finally mated after 10 years. <br/><br/>Ying Ying and Le Le are two 14-year-old giant pandas from Hong Kong's Ocean Park and keepers have been trying, albeit unsuccessfully, to get them to mate for the past ten years. <br/><br/>Unsurprisingly, it seems that all they needed was a little privacy, which given the current circumstances, was granted. <br/><br/>Pandas are notoriously difficult when it comes to breeding. They are extremely picky about choosing their mates, which means that even if a male and female panda are kept in the same enclosure for years, there is no guarantee the pair will mate.<br/><br/>Michael Boos, the CEO of operation and zoological conservation explained in a statement released by Ocean Park, "Ying Ying and Le Le arrived in Hong Kong in 2007 and there have been attempts at natural mating since 2010. Nevertheless, they have not been successful until this year, after a long time of testing and learning."<br/><br/>Because of the pandemic, the park has not received visitors since January and these welcomed moments of intimacy between the pair coincided with the breeding season that occurs every year between March and May. <br/><br/>Female pandas enter heat for one to three days, and that's the only window in which the male panda can hop on and get on.<br/><br/>According to the statement, sometime in late March after more than a month of unfamiliar privacy, Ying Ying began spending more time in the water; meanwhile, Le Le began leaving a trail of scents around his habitat and on Monday the 6th, the two were seen cuddling. <br/><br/>Ocean Park proudly announced that the two pandas had succeeded in natural mating that day at 9:00 a.m.<br/><br/>Michael Boos said, "The successful natural mating process today is extremely exciting for all of us, as the chance of pregnancy via natural mating is higher than by artificial insemination."<br/><br/>The zoo had told us to bear with, but promises to keep us all updated about this momentous occasion.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-lockdown-spurs-pandas-to-finally-mate-3985298</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985298/3985298_C1F4AE937E0D45E9A6E77A6402D37F75_200410_3985298_Coronavirus_Lockdown_Spurs_Pandas_To_Finally_Mat_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 02:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986531</guid>
      <title>Indonesian Village Uses 'Ghosts' to Scare You Into Social Distancing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAVA, INDONESIA <br/> As the British government racks its brain on how to keep facetious citizens indoors, a village in Indonesia has taken a different tactic: ghosts.<br/> <br/>As reported by the BBC, the Indonesian village has reportedly taken to using volunteers dressed as ghosts to literally spook people into social distancing over the coronavirus. <br/><br/>The village on Java Island started deploying the bed-sheet patrols at night last month. <br/><br/>In Indonesian folklore, ghostly figures known as "pocong" are said to represent the trapped souls of the dead. <br/><br/>According to Reuters news agency staff who traveled to see the volunteers in action, they felt the 'pocong' actually had the opposite effect as people were coming out to try and spot them. <br/><br/>Despite this, locals say that matters of social distancing have since improved with the new haunting.<br/><br/>One resident told Reuters, "Since the pocong appeared, parents and children have not left their homes. And people will not gather or stay on the streets after evening prayers."<br/><br/>Although slightly bizarre, this is not the only unusual measure that has been used to try to raise awareness of the disease's dangers around the world.<br/><br/>In India for example, police have taken to patrolling streets in virus-shaped helmets in a bid to bring attention to the dangers of the outbreak. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/indonesian-village-uses-ghosts-to-scare-you-into-social-distancing-3986531</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/14/3986531/3986531_F615DCB16DE74455AC0CCCB32F4CC02F_200414_3986531_Indonesian_Village_Uses__Ghosts__to_Scare_You_In_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 06:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986967</guid>
      <title>China Bans COVID-19 From Games</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Now that China is trying to stifle coronavirus research in a bid to control the narrative of its origin, Xi Jinping's far-reaching blanket of control is now trying to suffocate gaming, well, even more so than before.<br/><br/>We at TomoNews have come across a new game regulations notice coming out of China and you guessed it, it's targeting players, zombie-related content and that elusive COVID-19, China keeps denying a birthplace.<br/><br/>In a post to CK101, a forum cited a Chinese game outlet, Youxiputao, claiming that the authorities in Beijing, Shanghai, and Guangdong are about to demand that all gamers must use their actual legal names as their username; interestingly, the source also claims that they will ban all content related to zombies, pandemics or anything relating to  COVID-19, and those that use a worldwide server.<br/><br/>The user from the forum claims that some gamers in Animal Crossing may be accountable for these changes, as they used the game to create politically sensitive images and slogans about pro-democracy.<br/><br/>"In principle, mini-games and console games require real-name authentication by the operating platform."<br/><br/>"Illegal advertisements shall not be implanted in games, such as the promotion of unapproved game advertisements, if found, they shall be held accountable according to the law."<br/><br/>These two points here essentially shut down an anonymous gamer posting "unapproved" content, such as the promotion of free speech, democracy or any message for that matter that Xi hasn't already preapproved. <br/><br/>But what about those terrifying zombies and mentions of COVD-19 that China is trying so hard to deny responsibility for?<br/><br/>"No zombies, plagues or other themes corresponding to the Wuhan pneumonia epidemic should be allowed in the game, to ensure that the game chat does not allow inappropriate comments." <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-bans-covid-19-from-games-3986967</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/15/3986967/3986967_14AF19C6E9824311B8020BAA6CBA3088_200415_3986967_China_Bans_COVID_19_From_Games_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 09:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987345</guid>
      <title>McDonalds Sorry for, 'No Blacks Allowed' Chinese Sign</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUANGZHOU, CHINA <br/> McDonald's was forced to apologize after a video went viral showing a laminated sign posted in one of its Chinese restaurants.<br/><br/>The sign read, "Notice: We've been informed that from now on black people are not allowed to enter the restaurant."<br/><br/>McDonald's spokeswoman, Regina Hui said last Saturday, "McDonald's China apologizes unreservedly to the individual and our customers."<br/><br/>McDonald's has since pledged to use the sign incident to, "further educate managers and employees on our values, which includes serving all members of the communities in which we operate."<br/><br/>McDonald's removed the sign, closed down the location and issued a statement that the sign was "not representative of our inclusive values."<br/><br/>The sign is merely one instance of increasing racism in the city, as Chinese citizens have blamed African natives for spreading the coronavirus. <br/><br/>Guangzhou has China's largest African community of about 4,500 individuals and according to the Washington Post, over the past two weeks African residents say they've faced forced evictions, rejections from hotels, involuntary testing without results and sequestration into two-week long quarantines even if they test negative for the virus, haven't recently traveled or had no contact with any individuals known to be infected with COVID-19.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mcdonalds-sorry-for--no-blacks-allowed-chinese-sign-3987345</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/16/3987345/3987345_B680AA7F55134D458531A0A8C922AB35_200416_3987345_McDonalds_Sorry_for___No_Blacks_Allowed__Chinese_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 08:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987302</guid>
      <title>Singapore may have flattened the curve on COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE <br/> According to Singapore's The Strait Times, COVID-19 has an infection number between 2 and 3 globally, meaning each patient infects two or three more people.<br/><br/>The newspaper reports the infection number in the city-state has dropped to 1 since the government-ordered lockdown on April 8, citing Alex Cook, associate professor of public health at the National University of Singapore.<br/><br/>By limiting exposure to carriers, social distancing could slow the spread of COVID-19, even if the biological factors remain hard to tackle.<br/><br/>Cook was cited as saying Singapore's confirmed cases have risen to 1,481 as of April 7.<br/><br/>However, he claims most were imported and Singapore should be able to control the disease if the nation shuts its borders.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/singapore-may-have-flattened-the-curve-on-covid-19-3987302</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/16/3987302/3987302_B33EA42F7ECA40B989EE70FAD6369F47_200416_3987302_Singapore_may_have_flattened_the_curve_on_COVID__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 06:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988668</guid>
      <title>China Implementing Orwellian Health Tracking System</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Alibaba and Tencent will now host a new health code system that uses QR codes to indicate the health status of citizens. <br/><br/>Keeping the coronavirus at bay is priority number one for China now that many cities are coming out of lockdown, but could the coronavirus just be an excuse for China (and many other countries) to become more Orwellian? Well, take a look at the mobile health system China is now implementing to track its citizens.<br/><br/>According to a report from CNN, apps from Chinese tech giants Alibaba and Tencent will now host a new health code system that uses QR codes to indicate the health status of citizens. This is part of an effort to contain the spread of coronavirus now that businesses are reopening in the country. Alipay launched the new system on February 11.<br/><br/>Chinese nationals have to input their national identity number or passport number along with their phone number into the system. Citizens also have to share their travel history and list what symptoms they may be experiencing.<br/><br/>After the information is officially verified, citizens are assigned a colored QR code depending on their health status. Green QR codes mean you are safe, yellow QR codes mean you came in contact with a sick person and red means you cannot go out in public.<br/><br/>Several businesses in China are now placing QR codes outside their venues so clients and customers can scan and show their health status codes to employees before entering a business.<br/><br/>Oh, and how many people are under this system? Well, according to state-run Science and Technology Daily, Tencent's health code system has been in use in more than 300 cities since March.<br/><br/>To be fair, China is not the only country that's tracking its citizens amid this pandemic. According to a report published in The Guardian on March 6, people in South Korea were receiving texts with information about the whereabouts of people that had tested positive for the virus. The texts were eerily specific and, honestly, too revealing of people's personal lives.<br/><br/>For example, one man and his secretary were being scrutinized after it was revealed that both had tested positive for the virus after they both returned from a trip to Wuhan.<br/><br/>According to ZDnet, the UK is also turning to technology to control the spread of the coronavirus. British authorities have confirmed that their National Health Service is developing a voluntary contract-tracing app to help curtail the spread of the virus.<br/><br/>We all knew this was coming <br/> the whole blatant civilian data mining we mean. It was a matter of when rather than if. What do you think TomoSapiens? Is all this privacy invasion going to stick around even during post-pandemic days?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-implementing-orwellian-health-tracking-system-3988668</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/20/3988668/3988668_9B5E410CAC81440390DFDC08D8BAB064_200420_3988668_China_Implementing_Orwellian_Health_Tracking_Sys_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 05:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988645</guid>
      <title>China Blocks Lawyer From Going Home Even After Prison Release</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> A prominent Chinese human rights lawyer has been barred from returning home even after his prison release two weeks ago.<br/><br/>Wang Quanzhang, who had taken on politically sensitive cases, such as defending activists and members of the banned religious group Falun Gong, was released on the 4th of April after serving four and a half years on the blanket charge of "subversion of state power"; in a trial which was conducted behind closed doors with journalists and foreign diplomats barred from the courthouse. <br/><br/>On his release, his wife, Ms. Li along with rights groups fear authorities are now using the coronavirus quarantine protocol as a pretext to hold him indefinitely under de facto house arrest.<br/><br/>Despite their promise that he would be free-to-go after 14 days, he has still been barred from returning to Beijing; Ms. Li said, "Today is the 15th day and he still can't return to Beijing."<br/><br/>And in spite of being a so-called 'free man' who is simply being held in quarantine, she said that Wang was only able to hold phone conversations with her under the supervision of police, who controlled the content and length of his communications.<br/><br/>She added that Wang had called her on Saturday, saying he was unable to go home because he had "just come out and needed to get used to everything." A statement that made her question whether he was speaking of his own accord, saying "This is not the Wang Quanzhang I knew."<br/><br/>Reported by the BBC on the 5th of April, his wife claimed that his speech was being restricted. She added that in a phone call he suspiciously said he would go to Jinan, to which she responded: "Is this what a rational person would do after being separated from their wife and child for almost five years?"<br/><br/>The executive director of Hong Kong-based China Human Rights Lawyers Concern Group, Francine Chan, said: "The harassment, surveillance and effective house arrest of Wang Quanzhang after his 'release' vividly illustrate China's use of the pandemic to extend Wang's imprisonment in violation of Chinese and international law."<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-blocks-lawyer-from-going-home-even-after-prison-release-3988645</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/20/3988645/3988645_7FC2A025F76C41EEA515AE84CEE51FC8_200420_3988645_China_Blocks_Lawyer_From_Going_Home_Even_After_P_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 04:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989088</guid>
      <title>Kim Jong Un in 'Grave Danger' After Heart Surgery?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA <br/> It is being reported that North Korea's Supreme Leader, Kim Jong Un is gravely-ill after undergoing heart surgery.<br/><br/>The 36-year-old leader's condition is supposedly being monitored by US intelligence officials, who were told that Kim was "in grave danger" after the cardiovascular operation, CNN claim, citing a U.S. official with direct knowledge of the matter.<br/><br/>Quoting South Korean news website the Daily NK, Bloomberg reports that the infamous leader was "mostly-recovered" from the procedure; the website obtained the story from a single anonymous informant based in North Korea and has been unable to obtain further details on Kim's condition.<br/><br/>Bruce Klingner, a former CIA deputy division chief for North Korea told CNN that previous rumors about Kim being in poor health had turned out to be not true and that the country's extreme secrecy made it difficult to establish facts, saying: "There have been a number of recent rumors about Kim's health. If Kim is hospitalized, it would explain why he wasn't present on the important April 15th celebrations."<br/><br/>Unsurprisingly, North Korea's highly-secretive government has yet to comment on Kim's alleged illness, or issue any sort of statement through its state-controlled mouthpieces.<br/><br/>Kim, who is known to be a chain-smoker has been shown in state media in recent months appearing at military drills and riding a white horse in a power-move display of propaganda.  <br/><br/>The poverty-stricken nation has reported, impossibly, no cases of COVID-19, saying, "not a single person" in the country has been infected. Kim's absence from the public eye may just be precautionary, or he just may be on his way out. <br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/kim-jong-un-in-grave-danger-after-heart-surgery--3989088</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/21/3989088/3989088_4118ACC11A3D4780B69C4E525A010AF5_200421_3989088_Kim_Jong_Un_in__Grave_Danger__After_Heart_Surger_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 07:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992585</guid>
      <title>Where is Kim Jong-un? Trump Can't Say?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA <br/> Quoting U.S. Secretary of State, Mike Pompeo, the BBC wrote that U.S. officials 'haven't seen' North Korea's leader since the 36-year-old last appeared in state media on April 12th; his absence has led to mass speculation that he was seriously ill, however, officials in South Korea later said such reports were untrue. <br/><br/>In the many theories surrounding his absence from his adoring public, there have also been suggestions that he is waiting out the coronavirus at a sea resort.<br/><br/>When asked by Fox News to comment on the recent reports on Kim's health, Pompeo said on Wednesday, 'We haven't seen him. We don't have any information to report today, we're watching it closely.'<br/><br/>'There is a real risk that there will be a famine, a food shortage, inside of North Korea too.'<br/><br/>And on Monday, Trump claimed that he had a, 'very good idea' about Kim's condition, but added, 'I can't talk about it.'<br/><br/>Kim Jong-un failed to appear for the celebration of his grandfather's birthday on April 15th, an event that he has never missed.<br/><br/>However, none of the claims that have made headlines surrounding his disappearance can be substantiated.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/where-is-kim-jong-un-trump-can-t-say--3992585</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/30/3992585/3992585_D92F98E456F2446B88347F213763F8E7_200430_3992585_Where_is_Kim_Jong_un__Trump_Can_t_Say__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 08:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
