<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3914847</guid>
      <title>Man with 9 toes on left foot has surgery to remove freeloaders</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANWEI, CHINA <br/> A 21-year-old man born with some ultra amazing kung fu grip to the tune of 9 toes on his left foot has finally had the four extra digits surgically removed.<br/>According to the Yangcheng Evening News, the man, who goes by the name Ah-jun, since birth has had the ability to almost count to 10 using just one foot.<br/>Why did it take so long to get corrective surgery? Thank Ah-jun's superstitious parents. <br/><br/>Apparently when he was younger, his parentals took him to see a fortune teller who said the extra toes were "a gift from the heavens." <br/>This made his parents reluctant to get surgery, which unfortunately made Ah-jun reluctant to ever wear sandals or show his bare feet.<br/>The condition is actually called Polydactyly. It's a rare birth defect that occurs when a person has extra fingers or toes. It's also more common among dudes. <br/>But finally after years of only being able to swim in a circle, Ah-jun went to see some surgeons at the Shunde Heping Surgical Hospital in Foshan for help. <br/>After a nine-hour long surgery that required a whole bunch of heavy reconstruction, doctors were able to create a new big toe and get rid of the extra foot freeloaders. <br/>Ah-jun is now recovering in the hospital and will soon be able to put his best foot forward.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-with-9-toes-on-left-foot-has-surgery-to-remove-freeloaders-3914847</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9CF/983/9CF983FF275F7A91E130D72F6DF216A1.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/01/3914847/3914847_54141A3DBEBB4B45A303A196A3FDB1E6_191101_3914847_Man_with_9_toes_on_left_foot_has_surgery_to_remo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 11:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3915967</guid>
      <title>Chinese cafe gets backlash for dyeing dogs to look like pandas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHENGDU, CHINA <br/> A pet cafe in China couldn't get their hands on actual pandas, so they did what the Chinese do best<br/>imitate.<br/><br/>Reuters reports that the owner, 21-year-old Lu Yunning, thought dog, cat, alpaca, raccoon, and duck cafes were all pretty basic, and wanted something novel for his own joint in Chengdu.  <br/><br/>He happened to have Chow Chow puppies and got the bright idea to dye them to look like China's fat n' furry national treasure.<br/><br/>The gimmick was a hit, drawing in dozens of customers who wanted photos with the panda pups. <br/><br/>Some fur parents also signed their own pets up for the panda treatment, which is available for $212.<br/><br/>Not everyone's a fan, though. The cafe and its dyeing service have gotten much flak from animal activists, who really want to give Lu a taste of his own medicine. <br/><br/>Honestly, Chow dogs are adorable enough as they are<br/>why mess with a good thing?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-cafe-gets-backlash-for-dyeing-dogs-to-look-like-pandas-3915967</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B78/537/B7853779E7242FE2813B2B223680B97D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3915967/3915967_855FDA15E3AC47F4BD7646F46392EB73_191104_3915967_Chinese_cafe_gets_backlash_for_dyeing_dogs_to_lo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 09:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916086</guid>
      <title>Chinese researchers using live pigs as crash test dummies</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Disturbing photos have emerged showing live pigs being used as crash test dummies in China. <br/>The results were published for a study in the International Journal of Crashworthiness in January of this year.  <br/>According to Metro, fifteen pigs between 70 and 80 days old were starved for 24 hours before being strapped into children's car seats, so they could be used in crash simulations.  <br/>The Chinese scientists justified their use of pigs saying the animals' anatomic structure was "similar" to that of human children. The unlucky pigs were supposed to correspond to children aged 6 years old. <br/>According to the study, seven of the animals were killed on impact, while the others only lasted 6 hours after crash tests were administered. <br/>The pigs suffered injuries ranging from abrasions, contusions, lacerations, bleeding, to fractures.  <br/>Pigs were previously used in the U.S. for crash tests up until the 90s, after pressure from animal right's groups ended the practice.   <br/>Animal rights groups like PETA have condemned the experiments and have contacted China's Research Institute for Traffic Medicine.<br/>Considering how much Beijing pays attention to human rights, PETA's actions will undoubtedly mean the end for all animal experiments in China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-researchers-using-live-pigs-as-crash-test-dummies-3916086</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E77/EE3/E77EE3A8D373EB067D704958E7866066.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/04/3916086/3916086_25A233C96AA647808E8C6E2D19094944_191104_3916086_Chinese_researchers_using_live_pigs_as_crash_tes_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 13:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916262</guid>
      <title>Man's ear bitten off by knife attacker outside Hong Kong mall</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> As protests in Hong Kong rage on, a Mandarin speaker who was apparently from mainland China took offence to pro-democracy protesters at a mall on November 3 using a knife and his teeth.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-s-ear-bitten-off-by-knife-attacker-outside-hong-kong-mall-3916262</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B1F/791/B1F791D1493D569AA60705CA9FCDF529.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916262/3916262_53E79B069FFE49A3AD4EE6FCB7354D65_191105_3916262_Man_s_ear_bitten_off_by_knife_attacker_outside_H_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 03:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916556</guid>
      <title>New Delhi starts car rationing in a bid to clean up toxic air pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI <br/> New Delhi is set to combat toxic smog in the city by banning cars with odd and even number plates on alternating days starting from November 4 to November 15. <br/><br/>Those who ignore the order will be fined 4,000 rupees, or roughly US$56, BBC News reports. <br/><br/>New Delhi's car rationing system was previously used in 2016 and 2017, though it's unclear if the plan successfully brought down the city's pollution levels.<br/><br/>According to Reuters, the air quality index which measures levels of PM2.5 in areas across New Delhi has surpassed 900. This has far exceeded the 500 mark which is deemed as  "severe" by the World Health Organization.<br/><br/>Authorities in New Delhi have ordered schools to be closed until November 5 and have also ordered all construction work to be halted until further notice.<br/><br/>The World Health Organization states that continual exposure to PM2.5 particles increases a person's risk of developing cardiovascular diseases, respiratory diseases and even lung cancer.<br/><br/>Factors such as farmers from nearby states burning their crop stubble before winter to clear their fields, and industrial and construction emissions all contribute to worsening pollution levels in New Delhi during wintertime, according to Reuters. <br/><br/>The issue is exacerbated as people celebrate the Hindu new year Diwali, usually at the end of October or early November, and set off fireworks.<br/><br/>The pollutants linger in the atmosphere and accumulate instead of dissipating due to the wind changing direction after the monsoon season and colder air from the Himalayas. <br/><br/>Instead of stronger winds blowing from the east and clearing the air, softer winds blow from the northwest and move the pollutants towards New Delhi and other north Indian cities. During the same time, cold air from the Himalayan mountains descends to New Delhi and other north Indian cities, essentially trapping the toxic pollutants in the cold air.<br/><br/>A report by AirVisual, a company that tracks air quality around the world, found that New Delhi was the most polluted capital city in the world in 2018, with Beijing coming in second place.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-delhi-starts-car-rationing-in-a-bid-to-clean-up-toxic-air-pollution-3916556</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/42E/190/42E190E9CC9E1DA526757F0CFC57B3E4.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916556/3916556_C61578821E754249B1FC33EEF83660D7_191105_3916556_New_Delhi_starts_car_rationing_in_a_bid_to_clean_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 11:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3916528</guid>
      <title>Chinese pilot lets woman into cockpit during flight to show off</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GUILIN, CHINA <br/> A super smooth Air Guilin pilot has been grounded for life after images took off showing a woman in the cockpit during one of his flights earlier this year. <br/>According to the SCMP, the images lifted off over Chinese censored social media over the weekend.<br/>According to a statement from the airline, the incident occurred on an Air Guilin flight on January 4 from Guilin to Yangzhou. <br/>It's a mystery how the image made its way public, but it probably has nothing to do with the picture she posted over social media with the caption, "Thanks so much for the flight captain!! I'm really happy." <br/>The SCMP reports the woman has been identified as Chen Yuying, a third-year student at Guilin Tourism University, who wants to be a flight attendant after graduation.  <br/>The plastic bimbo can be seen sitting in the pilot's seat posing for a picture<br/>no doubt taken by the pilot. <br/><br/>Some Chinese netizens with flight experience said the snap appears to have been taken while the plane was in the air.<br/>Unfortunately for Maverick, he was given the ejector seat by Air Guilin. Also for violating China's Civil Aviation Administration rules, he's been prohibited from every flying again. <br/>Other crew members from the flight have been suspended indefinitely while an investigation is launched.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-pilot-lets-woman-into-cockpit-during-flight-to-show-off-3916528</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/567/CA7/567CA7F68B38E60D9FE0288D7CAAEF4C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/05/3916528/3916528_DE0E0A0CABB746E7B6AA678B4FB33998_191105_3916528_Chinese_pilot_lets_woman_into_cockpit_during_fli_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2019 10:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917079</guid>
      <title>Chimpanzee at Chinese zoo filmed enjoying a cigarette</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HEFEI, CHINA <br/> A chimpanzee at a rundown zoo in China was caught on camera having himself a square. <br/>According to the Paper, the smoke break took place at the Hefei Wildlife Park in China's Anhui province. <br/>Apparently, some d-bag decided to toss away his lit cig directly into the chimpanzee enclosure. <br/>A video filmed by a zoo visitor shows the chimp casually pick it up and then have himself a few drags. <br/>The male chimp then quickly gets bored and drops the cancer stick onto the ground. <br/>The 11 second video has since gone viral and caused widespread anger among the public, with many worried about the animal's health. <br/>But honestly, if you solely had to stare at annoying zoo goers all day long, you'd probably want a few drags to calm the old nerves every now and then. <br/>A zoo spokeswoman responded to public criticism saying that with tens of thousands of daily visitors and a staff of only 100 people, it was impossible to keep eyes on everyone.<br/>She also added that the zoo relies on tourists visiting the center to not act like animals. Good luck with that.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chimpanzee-at-chinese-zoo-filmed-enjoying-a-cigarette-3917079</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B3A/589/B3A589DEC957EB13C1425A86D07475C8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3917079/3917079_B8D3551DB77B4CA49A0ECF3A192EBD8D_191106_3917079_Chimpanzee_at_Chinese_zoo_filmed_enjoying_a_ciga_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 11:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3917072</guid>
      <title>Chinese tourists grab seagull for photos at Kunming lake</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KUNMING, CHINA <br/> It's that time of year again when Chinese tourists are on the loose. <br/><br/>This time it's to torture black-headed seagulls at the end of their yearly migration from Siberia to the Yunnan capital of Kunming.<br/>Footage posted to Pear Video, shows one unlucky seagull being mobbed by a bunch of super annoying Chinese tourists. <br/>The group was seen at Dianchi Lake grabbing one seagull and forcefully spreading its wings just so they could take some pictures of it. <br/>What better way to reminisce than looking through your old photos of you manhandling different animals. <br/>The seagull clearly wants absolutely no part of these tourists, who apparently think that shoving some food in its mouth will somehow make it more bearable.     <br/>Thankfully some other people at the lake came over to yell at the terrorizing tourists.<br/>The geniuses apologized saying they didn't know they weren't supposed to do that, and then hightailed it out of there. <br/>Unfortunately for the migrating seagulls, this isn't the first time this kind of thing has happened. It appears to be somewhat of a tradition now with the Chinese.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-tourists-grab-seagull-for-photos-at-kunming-lake-3917072</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A0E/C0C/A0EC0C3DB24CB5EB73A71010BF8A66FC.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/06/3917072/3917072_792BE08440B5427D9D11C87A4B31CF6D_191106_3917072_Chinese_tourists_grab_seagull_for_photos_at_Kunm_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2019 11:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3918248</guid>
      <title>Wild boar frozen in fear on a Chinese glass walkway</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHUN'AN, CHINA <br/> A wild boar was found on a glass walkway frozen to the spot.<br/><br/>The pig pressed himself to the side of the walkway before lying down, likely out of fear of the 230-meter drop. <br/><br/>According to the video, officers from the local forestry bureau reached the scene and rescued the boar.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wild-boar-frozen-in-fear-on-a-chinese-glass-walkway-3918248</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B7C/25E/B7C25E173B70349640BFA687FC1FA2CA.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918248/3918248_F3D039D216BB4D8EB70D4F9FC40729F4_191108_3918248_Wild_boar_frozen_in_fear_on_a_Chinese_glass_walk_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 13:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3918242</guid>
      <title>China parking lot has super wide spaces for female drivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JIANGSU, CHINA <br/> A parking lot in China has come up with an ingenious plan to help female drivers.  <br/>According to NetEase, a parking structure in the Jiangsu city of Taizhou has unveiled a "women-only" section with super duper large spaces, because as we all know<br/>women have a really tough time when it comes to parking.   <br/>And because the spots are reserved for females, they are also painted pretty in pink.<br/>Reports say the spaces are apparently 50 percent bigger than regular parking spaces for manly men.  <br/>But of course since these parking spots are made in China, they're clearly not all the same size. <br/>Maybe the bigger ones are for the fatter female drivers?? <br/>Either way, China is clearly leaps and bounds ahead of the West when it comes to battling sexism and discrimination. <br/>The Me Too movement could stand to learn a few things from the trailblazers out in China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-parking-lot-has-super-wide-spaces-for-female-drivers-3918242</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2CC/8B1/2CC8B13393811FE163AC7B4A0B7467E0.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918242/3918242_92CDCFA7C3E5417BA8C6DCA401F4D191_191108_3918242_China_parking_lot_has_super_wide_spaces_for_fema_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 13:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3918218</guid>
      <title>Army of cockroaches found camping out in man's ear</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUIZHOU, CHINA <br/> A 24-year-old man complaining of strange scratching noises in his ear was happy to hear it was only a small gang of cockroaches. <br/>According to a report on Weibo, the guy was at home in the Guangdong city of Huizhou sleeping one night last month, when he woke up because of sharp painful scratches inside his ear. <br/>After having a family member have a quick peek into his right ear, he was suggested to immediately get his butt over to the hospital.<br/>The man rushed himself over to the emergency room at Sanhe Hospital at around 4:40 a.m., understandably looking pretty freaked out.<br/>When ENT doctors had a look inside, they were shocked to find not one, not two, not three, but a small ARMY of cockroaches taking up residence in dude's ear canal. <br/>To be exact, there was one big mother cockroach and then 10 adorable little baby roaches.   <br/>Doctors found some minor damage to the man's ear canal, but nothing serious. He was discharged the same day and sent packing with some ointment and cream.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/army-of-cockroaches-found-camping-out-in-man-s-ear-3918218</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F8/91C/8F891CDAC9559A8D3506D232932F8A25.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918218/3918218_C25373158E3541F6A7BA7DBAC5F46F83_191108_3918218_Army_of_cockroaches_found_camping_out_in_man_s_e_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 12:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3918215</guid>
      <title>China orders online gaming curfew for minors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Fun-loving Chinese officials have decided to drop the hammer on online video games for minors in an attempt to battle gaming addiction. <br/>According to the BBC, the super fun restrictions were released on Tuesday by the CCP. <br/>Gamers under 18 will now have a curfew. They'll be banned from playing online games between 10 p.m. at night until 8 a.m. in the morning.<br/>The new rules say they will also be limited to 90 minutes of gaming during the week and three hours on weekends and holidays. <br/>The BBC reports that the new guidelines also have restrictions on how much minors can spend. <br/>Gaming aficionados between 8 to 16 years old can spend up to $29 dollars a month, while 16 to 18 year olds can blow up to 57 bucks on their gaming accounts. <br/>According to NPR, Chinese officials will also require everyone to register accounts for online games using their real name and phone number, so it's easier for the government to track how much you're playing. Jesus<br/>nanny much??<br/>China is one of the world's biggest gaming markets. According to market research firm Niko Partners, digital gaming revenue in China will hit $33 billion in 2019. <br/>Will these new rules actually help cut down on gaming addiction? Or will we suddenly see an increase in parents of these gamers suddenly registering for online games?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-orders-online-gaming-curfew-for-minors-3918215</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DFD/424/DFD424955BE0A8D5042C9E8BE4C89325.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/08/3918215/3918215_678946A5C48E420ABFA5F0B6CB4A3822_191108_3918215_China_orders_online_gaming_curfew_for_minors_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2019 12:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919279</guid>
      <title>Critically endangered porpoise
found dead with bricks tied to it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YUEYANG, CHINA <br/> Chinese fishermen discovered a critically endangered Yangtze Finless Porpoise dead in a lake in the most barbaric way imaginable. <br/><br/>According to a post on Weibo by Toutiao news, fisherman of Dongting Lake in Yueyang alerted authorities when they came across the dead animal on Thursday. <br/><br/>Photo and video evidence posted by the East Dongting Ecological Protection Association documented an 18-centimeter long slash down the animal's belly, and how a rope with two bricks on the end had been tied to its tail.<br/><br/>The porpoise measured 1.52 meters in length and weighed 43 kilograms.<br/><br/>According to WWF, The Yangtze Finless Porpoise is critically endangered with an estimated population between a mere 1,000 and 1,800.<br/><br/>The Yangtze Finless Porpoise is known for its "mischievous smile" and high level of intelligence comparable to that of a gorilla.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/critically-endangered-porpoise%0Afound-dead-with-bricks-tied-to-it-3919279</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DA3/ADD/DA3ADD4FC1579A978635077F442F7AC5.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/11/3919279/3919279_88489C554FFA4B30BB6F5D690FF7C031_191111_3919279_Critically_endangered_porpoise_found_dead_with_b_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 05:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919681</guid>
      <title>Inebriated man busts jet door, delays flight in Thailand</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Thailand <br/> A "crazed" flier tore the emergency door right off the hinges moments before an airplane's scheduled takeoff, according to the Bangkok Post.<br/><br/>A drunk bubba ripped open the emergency exit of an Airbus A320 in Thailand on Thursday in a desperate bid to do we don't know what.<br/><br/>Fox News reports that other passengers saw a foreign male "explode in a bizarre outburst" on the Chiang Mai to Bangkok flight on Thursday afternoon.<br/><br/>The unnamed man then ran down to the emergency exit over the left wing and proceeded to brute force the thing, Fox News cites the airline as saying.<br/><br/>Did we say that the plane was just about to take off? Because it was.<br/><br/>The man popped the door clean off the cabin wall in a stupendous display of, well, stupid strength, causing the emergency slide to inflate and 86 sober passengers to scream in terrified chorus.<br/><br/>Thai police tackled the maniac and dragged him off the plane, but his antics delayed flight for an hour and caused over $19,700 property damage.<br/><br/>The Bangkok Post reports that Thailand's aviation authorities have yet to identify the motive behind the insane escapade.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/inebriated-man-busts-jet-door-delays-flight-in-thailand-3919681</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/991/E23/991E23E7BFDFE842029067A5BBF50025.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919681/3919681_34035883FB2648A5A0DDCF5334E402A4_191112_3919681_Inebriated_man_busts_jet_door__delays_flight_in__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 02:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3919992</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protester shot by cop at point-blank range</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> Police in Hong Kong fired three live rounds during a city-wide strike, hitting at least one pro-democracy protester.<br/><br/>RTHK reports that around 7:15 a.m. on Monday, masked protesters throwing debris onto an intersection in Hong Kong's Sai Wan Ho were confronted by a traffic policeman.<br/><br/>In a live video posted by Cupid News, a protester in a white hoodie is seen approaching the officer, who reaches for his service pistol.<br/><br/>The officer initially pointed his gun at the man at point-blank range, before putting him in a headlock.<br/><br/>When another protester approached, the policeman turned his gun on him and fired a round into his torso from a distance of less than half a meter.<br/><br/>Two more people, one in black and one in gray, came forward to grapple with the officer, who then fired two more shots. In the video, the protester in black can be seen falling to the ground.<br/><br/>Riot police soon arrived to help subdue a large crowd of angry people. They had begun demanding an explanation for the shooting, and were pepper sprayed in return.<br/><br/>According to the Hong Kong Free Press, an anonymous source told Ming Pao that two people had been shot, and that the first one, identified only as a 21-year-old man, was injured in the kidney and liver, with his renal vein crushed.<br/><br/>He had needed cardiopulmonary resuscitation after his heart stopped once, and CNN reports that he remains in critical condition according to the Hong Kong Hospital Authority.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hong-kong-protester-shot-by-cop-at-point-blank-range-3919992</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4BF/7E4/4BF7E4566A3852E140EBC77BB1B8710D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/12/3919992/3919992_63EE761E1EC8438780334489579CA0D6_191112_3919992_Hong_Kong_protester_shot_by_cop_at_point_blank_r_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 12:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920161</guid>
      <title>Chinese woman wants to give away her extra kidney</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINYU, CHINA <br/> A woman with three kidneys from the city of Xinyu in China's Jiangxi province is looking to give one away, according to Peach Video.<br/><br/>The unnamed woman had frequent urges for number one and pains in the waist that flares up if she slept for more than six hours. Ouch!<br/><br/>Having enough of this nonsense, our kind hearted heroine went to the hospital.<br/><br/>After some x-rays, the doctor told the unnamed woman that she has a triple. No, not three babies, three kidneys, with an extra on the right. <br/><br/>Although the woman volunteered to donate the surplus organ, no surgery was performed.<br/><br/>Doctors told Peach Video that they generally favor "more conservative treatment plans" and the would be good samaritan is recovering.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-woman-wants-to-give-away-her-extra-kidney-3920161</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BFE/DA1/BFEDA127D215DD895F9B03500F3DCFE0.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920161/3920161_F68F208549694CA9AF4F98962D501599_191113_3920161_Chinese_woman_wants_to_give_away_her_extra_kidne_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 02:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920417</guid>
      <title>Zoo monkey in China takes phone and goes online shopping</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHANGZHOU, CHINA <br/> A crafty little monkey in China was able to get a hold of its keeper's smartphone and did what everyone else is doing these days<br/>made a bunch of online purchases. <br/>According to a report on Jiangsu TV, the hilarious incident happened at the Yancheng Wild Animal World in the Jiangsu city of Changzhou.<br/>Looks like zoo worker Lu Mengmeng was using her phone to look at some stuff online one day while she was working with the animal, when the monkey got hungry. <br/>Lu then left the room to get some food, but forgot to bring her phone. <br/>A few days later, a bunch of packages showed up at the office addressed to Lu. She thought it was strange because she didn't remember ordering anything. <br/>She then went back to check the surveillance video and found that the monkey was the culprit. <br/>Footage shows the monkey picking up the phone before going on an online shopping spree. <br/>Lu told media that the monkey has grown up watching her play on her phone and make purchases over Chinese e-commerce site Taobao. <br/>Apparently the monkey knows how to shop too, because Lu says she plans on keeping the stuff. Guess that's what you call monkey business.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/zoo-monkey-in-china-takes-phone-and-goes-online-shopping-3920417</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F00/F8B/F00F8B0DE27C0A7C9196F5C2A283C7B8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920417/3920417_2D9C5D2B9DCE45139F5A27067C993BDA_191113_3920417_Zoo_monkey_in_China_takes_phone_and_goes_online__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920397</guid>
      <title>Chinese man crashes his car straight into a hospital</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> A BMW came crashing through a hospital waiting room on Saturday, narrowly missing a mother and her two children. <br/><br/>As the mother holds her infant, the car smashes through the door sending her and her children sliding across the floor before hitting the ground.<br/><br/>Unfortunately, a sleeping man takes the brunt of the impact and is pushed backward by the force before being flipped over and wedged in by the car. <br/><br/>After a second, a man appears from the passenger side surprisingly undisturbed, leaving with a baby in his arms.<br/><br/>The footage has since made its rounds on Chinese social media with netizens speculating the urgency of the man's need to get his baby to the hospital. <br/><br/>The accident location is so far unreported as is the reason why this happened.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-crashes-his-car-straight-into-a-hospital-3920397</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6D4/F48/6D4F4859EDDF92F0979419B94214D82C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920397/3920397_B1C210996EAA4735BABEFB05314A566E_191113_3920397_Chinese_man_crashes_his_car_straight_into_a_hosp_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 10:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3920481</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong protesters clash with police at universities</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> Ongoing protests have been taking place in Hong Kong for 24 consecutive weeks.<br/><br/>Around midday on November 12, protesters in black clothing as well as office workers took to the streets and occupied an intersection in the city's business district, Central. The police fired tear gas in the afternoon and detained roughly 12 people, CNN reports. <br/><br/>According to the Hong Kong Free Press, separate protests took place at a campus of the Chinese University of Hong Kong on the same day. Masked protesters in black had put up barricades on the university campus to prevent the police from entering in the morning.<br/><br/>This led to a clash between the protesters and the police in the afternoon as activists threw bricks and petrol bombs at the officers while the officers fired tear gas and projectiles into the campus.<br/><br/>According to CNN, this caused an empty car to catch on fire.<br/><br/>Protesters also dropped bricks from a footbridge at Hong Kong Polytechnic University while other protesters throw chairs and traffic cones at passing traffic from another footbridge near the University of Hong Kong.<br/><br/>This comes a day after a 21-year-old protester was shot in the torso by a police officer at point-blank range.<br/><br/>Protests began in June over an extradition bill that would allow suspects to be extradited for trial to mainland China.<br/><br/>Those against the bill believe that Beijing may use it as a way to extradite political activists, dissidents and other critics in the city. The protests have now snowballed into massive anti-government and pro-democracy protests.<br/><br/>The Hong Kong government has since suspended the bill, though the activists still have four other unmet demands, the BBC reports. The fifth demand, which was to suspend the bill, has already been met.<br/><br/>The four other demands include: amnesty for all the protesters who were arrested, an independent investigation into alleged police brutality; implementing complete universal suffrage across the city; and for the Hong Kong government to stop characterizing the protests as "riots."<br/><br/>The Hong Kong government has not officially suspended classes, though some schools and universities have announced cancellation of classes due to the ongoing protests, CNN reports.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hong-kong-protesters-clash-with-police-at-universities-3920481</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/485/5BF/4855BF9E749FC9AF4C178193A8048D12.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/13/3920481/3920481_AB11831A0A6A4648B8F3B9B763D5970D_191113_3920481_Hong_Kong_protesters_clash_with_police_at_univer_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 12:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3921686</guid>
      <title>Chinese student falls off Huashan mountain while taking selfie</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HUASHAN MOUNTAIN <br/>  A Chinese University student met her untimely end while taking a selfie from one of China's most famous mountains.<br/><br/>The Paper reports that at the end of October, university student Xiao Deng went up China's Huashan Mountain in Shaanxi <br/> best known for its steep cliffs and deadly, pee-your-pants plank trails.<br/><br/>The 21-year-old had been taking selfies all the way up the mountain and sharing it with classmates in a WeChat group, before suddenly going radio silent.<br/><br/>Her university in Hunan went to the cops a day later, and told her family she was missing.<br/><br/>Police checked the surveillance at Huashan, and saw that Deng had been taking a selfie on an observation deck on the western part of the mountain.<br/><br/>While framing the shot, she made a misstep that caused her to fall back past the 60-centimeter chain fence and off the edge of the cliff to her death.<br/><br/>The management at Huashan National Park said it wasn't responsible for the incident, since Deng was an adult who ignored safety warnings. Still, it said it would give the family "humanitarian aid" to the tune of 40,000 yuan, or $5,700.<br/><br/>The girl's mom, though, thinks management is fully to blame, because of the too-low fence.<br/><br/>I mean, sure, Huashan needs to step up its guardrail game and actually have one that does its job, but actions <br/> like ignoring warnings <br/> do have consequences.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-student-falls-off-huashan-mountain-while-taking-selfie-3921686</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/196/9D1/1969D19CE003AEDFDE89A9F5D82C1009.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921686/3921686_B9F31E87E4BA42EFA4B29BBAC654EF31_191115_3921686_Chinese_student_falls_off_Huashan_mountain_while_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 15:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3921595</guid>
      <title>Woman goes blind in one eye from staring at phone too much</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA <br/> A woman in China is looking at things a bit differently after losing sight in her left eye from over excessive mobile phone usage. <br/>According to a Pear Video report, a woman from Shenzhen in China's Guangdong province had spent an entire night staring into her smartphone<br/>not so smart.<br/>When she woke up the next morning, after about five minutes things started to get blurry in her left eye until she couldn't see anything.<br/>Cyclops then hightailed it over to Songgang People's Hospital where doctors quickly zeroed in on the cause. <br/>Looking at her bright mobile screen all night had caused blood vessels to burst in her eye. <br/>Doctors said images taken of her eye revealed large patches of blood on her retina, obstructing her vision. <br/>Luckily for Left Eye, physicians were able to use a laser to drill a small hole in her retina to let the blood flow from the burst vessels, which allowed her to regain her vision. <br/><br/>Reports say she's now recovering from the procedure. Hopefully someone gave her a phone to look at to pass the time.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-goes-blind-in-one-eye-from-staring-at-phone-too-much-3921595</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F6A/BCE/F6ABCECE01ABD9988C29325E1179F7F9.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/15/3921595/3921595_15ACE7FAABC4445C994970B37B73C5CF_191115_3921595_Woman_goes_blind_in_one_eye_from_staring_at_phon_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2019 12:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3922717</guid>
      <title>HK police officer shot with
arrow during university siege</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> The battle for Hong Kong's democracy has taken to new heights as a police officer was shot by an arrow during a siege of Hong Kong's Polytechnic University campus in Hung Hom, Kowloon.  <br/><br/>On Sunday, the pro-democracy protesters on campus rained Molotov cocktails down on riot police and their vehicles in one of the longest days of fighting since the demonstrations began nearly six months ago.<br/><br/>Police retaliated by pummeling front-line protesters with rounds of tear gas and water cannons.<br/><br/>According to the Hong Kong Free Press, during the skirmish, a member of the police's media liaison team, who are typically dressed in blue vests, was "struck in the calf by an arrow" at around 2 pm.<br/><br/>Police took to Facebook to warn protesters that if they continued to use petrol bombs and bows and arrows, they would respond by using minimum force and, given no other choice, live rounds.<br/><br/>Worryingly, the Hong Kong Polytechnic University issued a statement announcing that, "dangerous chemicals" had been stolen from laboratories and that they scolded the protesters for "damaging the campus."<br/><br/>Furthermore, for the first time, the Hong Kong police deployed a Long Range Acoustic Device mounted on an armored truck that emits high-pitched noises. <br/><br/>According to The City Broadcasting Channel, a news outlet run by students from the City University of Hong Kong, the sonic device was used for, "about three seconds"  at around 2:20 pm and caused slight discomfort to its reporter.<br/><br/>According to a police statement, the man shot by the arrow is conscious and was sent to the hospital for treatment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hk-police-officer-shot-with%0Aarrow-during-university-siege-3922717</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/267/EC3/267EC3FE0D054F87B8A627268B3BDAED.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/18/3922717/3922717_113D7C06069D4870A038A3E52F6A3C17_191118_3922717_HK_police_officer_shot_with_arrow_during_univers_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 08:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923273</guid>
      <title>Protesters try to escape
uni after skirmish with police</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> Protestors had started to flee the blockaded Polytechnic University on monday, with the Hong Kong police force meeting them with tear gas and rubber bullets; multiple arrests were made, with those caught being aggressively detained. <br/><br/>Protestors claim that even though they were trying to leave, they were being boxed in by the authorities.<br/><br/>A 23-year-old protestor inside the university campus told CNN by phone, "Of course, we want to leave." <br/><br/>"We are still quite safe currently in the campus, but if we try to leave ... they will arrest us." <br/><br/>"They are just everywhere surrounding the campus."<br/><br/>The protester added, "Currently, around me, we just want to escape, we don't have any equipment to help us fight."<br/><br/>He later fled unharmed and knows of roughly 50 more individuals who escaped, some by abseiling down a rope to waiting motorbikes or running along train tracks.<br/><br/>More worryingly, police confirmed to CNN that assault rifles being carried by riot police Monday afternoon, were in fact, "ready to use."<br/><br/>Demonstrators, however, will be more frightful than ever after a video surfaced on Monday of apparently detained protestors being loaded onto a train near the border of China for speculated extradition.<br/><br/>According to Taiwan News, the footage is sparking dread online that the pro-democracy protesters are in fact being sent to a detention center in communist China, similar to the so-called "reeducation camps" used to imprison innocent Uighurs.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/protesters-try-to-escape%0Auni-after-skirmish-with-police-3923273</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/2F2/CE6/2F2CE6D3D1BF69F93C86F84B2C465ACE.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/19/3923273/3923273_78E706639180483285CC3A7118BACC5F_191119_3923273_Protesters_try_to_escape_uni_after_skirmish_with_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 09:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3923781</guid>
      <title>Last few protesters hold out 
inside Hong Kong university</title>
      <description><![CDATA[#HongKong #HongKongProtests #HongKongpolice<br/>HONG KONG <br/> Few protestors remain at the Hong Kong Polytechnic University as supplies and outside support dwindle into the third day of the police siege, reports Hong Kong newspaper and TomoNews sister publication Apple Daily.<br/><br/>CNN reported on Tuesday that only around 50 or so remained at the campus.<br/><br/>About ten protestors tried to escape the campus as medics left. Riot police officers tackled runners and beat them with clubs. The police later described them as 'masked rioters' in a Facebook post.<br/><br/>Speaking at a press conference on Tuesday evening, a spokesperson for volunteer medics treating protestors told Apple Daily that they are evacuating because of the diminishing number of protesters. <br/><br/>The spokesperson added that no supplies are reaching the campus.<br/><br/>Apple Daily reports that dozens of protesters left voluntarily after displaying hypothermia symptoms. Parents told the newspaper that many of those who surrendered to police are missing.<br/><br/>Hong Kong police claim to have identified or arrested an estimated 1,100 people in the school and its surrounding areas, including 600 who left voluntarily as of Tuesday at 3pm.<br/><br/>Citing Hong Kong's Hospital Authority, Apple Daily reports that 354 people were wounded in the ten hours between midnight and 10pm yesterday.<br/><br/>A Taiwanese student told the paper that she was scared to leave because she did not know if she would be beaten or shot at despite public assurances. She was reportedly evacuated after the interview.<br/><br/>Meanwhile, Beijing hinted that it may upend Hong Kong's legal system after the autonomous territory's High Court ruled the police ban on masks as unlawful.<br/><br/>A spokesman of the National People's Congress said the issue, "can only be judged and decided by the NPC Standing Committee, and no other organ has the right to judge or decide," in a statement published by Chinese state-run Xinhua News Agency on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/last-few-protesters-hold-out-%0Ainside-hong-kong-university-3923781</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/9E7/591/9E75913E01F576FAA0E3CA36DDF236E5.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/20/3923781/3923781_7A1EDDD837804EBE840E1ABC41F76A88_191120_3923781_Last_few_protesters_hold_out__inside_Hong_Kong_u_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924603</guid>
      <title>China 'tortured' ex-British consulate worker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> A former employee of the UK consulate in Hong Kong claims he was tortured by Chinese authorities, reports CNN.<br/><br/>In a Facebook post on Wednesday, ex-UK Hong Kong consulate worker Simon Cheng says he took part in the city's protests but did not break any laws.<br/><br/>Cheng approached protesters on Telegram and other social media as part of his job to evaluate travel alerts and protect British citizens, he says in a Facebook post on Wednesday.<br/><br/>He was returning from a business trip in August in Shenzhen when police arrested him on the Chinese side of the West Hong Kong Kowloon railway station.<br/><br/>According to Cheng, he was then handed over to State Security Bureau officials and detained in Shenzhen.<br/><br/>Speaking to CNN, Britain's Foreign Secretary Dominic Raab said he summoned the Chinese Ambassador to express outrage at the brutal and disgraceful treatment of Cheng. <br/><br/>China responded on Wednesday with foreign minister Geng Shuang telling reporters that Cheng made a full confession and that the public security bureau "guaranteed all his rights and interests according to law."<br/><br/>CNN reports that Cheng fled to an unnamed third country following his detention and is currently seeking asylum.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-tortured-ex-british-consulate-worker-3924603</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/227/B35/227B351B4B70A5DD2FF80DA3FB8956A2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924603/3924603_9D15A62FDDE846C9BC706C6B0655AA55_191122_3924603_China__tortured__ex_British_consulate_worker_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 05:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924593</guid>
      <title>China 'tortured' ex-British consulate worker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> A former employee of the UK consulate in Hong Kong claims he was tortured by Chinese authorities, reports CNN.<br/><br/>In a Facebook post on Wednesday, ex-UK Hong Kong consulate worker Simon Cheng says he took part in the city's protests but did not break any laws.<br/><br/>Cheng approached protesters on Telegram and other social media as part of his job to evaluate travel alerts and protect British citizens, he says in a Facebook post on Wednesday.<br/><br/>He was returning from a business trip in August in Shenzhen when police arrested him on the Chinese side of the West Hong Kong Kowloon railway station.<br/><br/>According to Cheng, he was then handed over to State Security Bureau officials and detained in Shenzhen.<br/><br/>Speaking to CNN, Britain's Foreign Secretary Dominic Raab said he summoned the Chinese Ambassador to express outrage at the brutal and disgraceful treatment of Cheng. <br/><br/>China responded on Wednesday with foreign minister Geng Shuang telling reporters that Cheng made a full confession and that the public security bureau "guaranteed all his rights and interests according to law."<br/><br/>CNN reports that Cheng fled to an unnamed third country following his detention and is currently seeking asylum.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-tortured-ex-british-consulate-worker-3924593</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4F5/617/4F561748D4062A82C7A4B4B67276114E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924593/3924593_06401B2EF8A346F79252AF157C17B5AD_191122_3924593_China__tortured__ex_British_consulate_worker_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 04:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924584</guid>
      <title>China 'tortured' ex-British consulate worker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA<br/> A former employee of the UK consulate in Hong Kong claims he was tortured by Chinese authorities, reports CNN.<br/><br/>In a Facebook post on Wednesday, ex-UK Hong Kong consulate worker Simon Cheng says he took part in the city's protests but did not break any laws.<br/><br/>Cheng says he approached protesters on Telegram and other social media as part of his job to evaluate travel alerts and protect British citizens.<br/><br/>He was returning from a business trip in August in Shenzhen when police arrested him on the Chinese side of the West Hong Kong Kowloon railway station.<br/><br/>According to Cheng, he was then handed over to State Security Bureau officials and detained in Shenzhen.<br/><br/>Cheng says he was buckled to a tiger chair and rendered immobile during his initial interrogation, which lasted for hours.<br/><br/>He says officers took blood and urine samples and confiscated his glasses and cellphone.<br/><br/>Cheng says he was repeatedly tortured. He says, officers would hang him on a "steep X-cross" while he was handcuffed, shackled and blindfolded. This stress position causes extreme pain.<br/><br/>The interrogators forced him to perform exercises such as squatting while he was still blindfolded and restrained by cuffs and shackles.<br/><br/>If he fell from exhaustion, Cheng says, the interrogators would beat him with weapons that felt like sharpened batons.<br/><br/>Cheng says his captors also prevented sleep by making him stand still while under restraints for hours at a time.<br/><br/>If he went under, they would force him to sing the Chinese national anthem.<br/><br/>Cheng says that secret police forbade him from telling prison doctors that the bruises and wounds on his limbs were the result of torture.<br/><br/>He says they stopped applying physical torture after one week, when he became too weak to walk.<br/><br/>Cheng says he ultimately agreed to a filmed confession at the detention center under duress.<br/><br/>He says he was released after falsely confessing to soliciting prostution and betraying the motherland.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-tortured-ex-british-consulate-worker-3924584</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/67A/377/67A3777FB9296FFDAFCFF68AE138C5D4.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924584/3924584_4CE44FB30C1C4CF38194E61D4B70A567_191122_3924584_China__tortured__ex_British_consulate_worker_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 04:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924578</guid>
      <title>China 'tortured' ex-British consulate worker</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA<br/> A former employee of the UK consulate in Hong Kong claims he was tortured by Chinese authorities, reports CNN.<br/><br/>In a Facebook post on Wednesday, ex-UK Hong Kong consulate worker Simon Cheng says he took part in the city's protests but did not break any laws.<br/><br/>Cheng says he approached protesters on Telegram and other social media as part of his job to evaluate travel alerts and protect British citizens.<br/><br/>He was returning from a business trip in August in Shenzhen when police arrested him on the Chinese side of the West Hong Kong Kowloon railway station.<br/><br/>According to Cheng, he was then handed over to State Security Bureau officials and detained in Shenzhen.<br/><br/>Cheng says he was buckled to a tiger chair and rendered immobile during his initial interrogation, which lasted for hours.<br/><br/>He says officers took blood and urine samples and confiscated his glasses and cellphone.<br/><br/>Cheng says he was repeatedly tortured. He says, officers would hang him on a "steep X-cross" while he was handcuffed, shackled and blindfolded. This stress position causes extreme pain.<br/><br/>The interrogators forced him to perform exercises such as squatting while he was still blindfolded and restrained by cuffs and shackles.<br/><br/>If he fell from exhaustion, Cheng says, the interrogators would beat him with weapons that felt like sharpened batons.<br/><br/>Cheng says his captors also prevented sleep by making him stand still while under restraints for hours at a time.<br/><br/>If he went under, they would force him to sing the Chinese national anthem.<br/><br/>Cheng says that secret police forbade him from telling prison doctors that the bruises and wounds on his limbs were the result of torture.<br/><br/>He says they stopped applying physical torture after one week, when he became too weak to walk.<br/><br/>Cheng says he ultimately agreed to a filmed confession at the detention center under duress.<br/><br/>He says he was released after falsely confessing to soliciting prostution and betraying the motherland.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-tortured-ex-british-consulate-worker-3924578</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/AE9/87B/AE987BFDD0E3E1C53AA7EDCCAC67C9F7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924578/3924578_98341923E7FB41ACA3B7BA16BDBA4FAE_191122_3924578_China__tortured__ex_British_consulate_worker_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 04:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3924779</guid>
      <title>Man has over 700 tapeworms from eating undercooked meat in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HANGZHOU, CHINA <br/> A Chinese man who had been suffering from headaches and seizures was found to have a whopping 700 plus tapeworms taking up residence throughout his body. <br/>According to Pear Video, 43-year-old Zhu Zhong-fa from Hangzhou in Zhejiang province started feeling a bit funky about a month ago. <br/>Looks like he had eaten some hotpot with a few too many slices of infected and <br/>undercooked pork<br/>YUMMY.<br/>Zhu got himself over to a hospital at Zhejiang University where he was found to have a colony of around 700 tapeworms all over his body.     <br/><br/>According to doctors, the little suckers were found in Zhu's brain, lungs and chest cavity. <br/>Doctors say the worms had already caused damage to the patient's organs. <br/>According to the WHO, when tapeworms get into the central nervous system, they can cause neurological symptoms, including epileptic seizures. <br/>Well, that's good to know. Hopefully your appetite has kicked in by now. Hotpot anyone?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-has-over-700-tapeworms-from-eating-undercooked-meat-in-china-3924779</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/05C/70F/05C70F3A767868D5EE1320D7296205D7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/22/3924779/3924779_4653EDBF678546619C75C220DDE80C73_191122_3924779_Man_has_over_700_tapeworms_from_eating_undercook_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 09:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3925938</guid>
      <title>China increases coal power capacity, despite climate pledge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> A new report by Global Energy Monitor found that China has increased its coal power capacity by 42.9 gigawatts between January of 2018 and June of 2019. <br/><br/>That is enough energy to power 31 million homes, according to the BBC. The report notes that the rest of the world decreased its total coal capacity by 8.1 gigawatts during the same time period.<br/><br/>Researchers involved with the study say China would need to reduce its current coal capacity by over 40 percent, from 1,027 gigawatts to 600 gigawatts or less, by 2030 in order to keep its Paris climate agreement pledge to limit the rise in global temperatures to below 2&#176;C.<br/><br/>The report found that China is constructing 121.3 gigawatts of coal plants and is likely to revive 26.4 gigawatts of other existing coal-related projects that are currently suspended, or a total of 147.7 gigawatts of coal power capacity.<br/><br/>This is almost equivalent to the European Union's existing coal power capacity, which stands at 150 gigawatts.<br/><br/>China continues to finance a quarter of all coal plant projects around the world, in countries such as South Africa, Pakistan and Bangladesh, the BBC reports.<br/><br/>China has invested heavily in clean energy, though the country continues to invest in coal power.<br/><br/>Co-author of the study Christine Shearer from Global Energy Monitor, called China's coal power expansion plans "far out of alignment with the Paris Agreement."<br/><br/>Shearer said that China needs to make significant reductions to its coal power capacity instead of continued expansion over the coming decade.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-increases-coal-power-capacity-despite-climate-pledge-3925938</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F56/BA9/F56BA98C123A2328B6FBA504C2C45357.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3925938/3925938_B7886784A1F543648E37F7F9612E8416_191125_3925938_China_increases_coal_power_capacity__despite_cli_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 05:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926162</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong pro-democracy camp wins big in local elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> Hong Kong held its local district council elections on Sunday after almost six months of anti-government protests.<br/><br/>Voter turnout was more than 71 percent, up from 47 percent in 2015, BBC News reports. The elections are considered to be a test for the current Hong Kong government.<br/><br/>The city has a total of 18 district councils, of which the pro-democracy camp won 17, according to the South China Morning Post. District councils mainly advise the government on local issues concerning their district, such as the use of public facilities and public services.<br/><br/>Several prominent pro-democracy activists including Jimmy Sham, who was attacked by masked assailants with hammers last month in Kowloon, managed to win district council seats in the local elections.<br/><br/>The district councils may play a significant role when electing Hong Kong's chief executive in 2022.<br/><br/>This is because the city's leader is elected by a 1,200-member committee, which includes 117 members chosen by district councillors. In this system, whichever camp<br/>claims the majority of votes, has the ability to claim all 117 of these seats.<br/><br/>This could influence who is chosen to be the city's chief executive as the pro-democracy camp already held roughly 400 committee seats before the district council elections.<br/><br/>As six out of 70 seats are reserved in the city's Legislative Council for district councillors, the pro-democracy camp may also secure seats in the Legislative Council as the majority.<br/><br/>Hong Kong's Legislative Council has the ability to enact, amend, repeal laws or even start an impeachment process against the city's leader.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hong-kong-pro-democracy-camp-wins-big-in-local-elections-3926162</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926162/3926162_4153D561CCAC4A99B9CD7E09D832D4A5_191125_3926162_Hong_Kong_pro_democracy_camp_wins_big_in_local_e_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926157</guid>
      <title>Hong Kong pro-democracy camp wins big in local elections</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> Hong Kong held its local district council elections on Sunday after almost six months of anti-government protests.<br/><br/>Voter turnout was more than 71 percent, up from 47 percent in 2015, BBC News reports. The elections are considered to be a test for the current Hong Kong government.<br/><br/>The city has a total of 18 district councils, of which the pro-democracy camp won 17, according to the South China Morning Post. District councils mainly advise the government on local issues concerning their district, such as the use of public facilities and public services.<br/><br/>Several prominent pro-democracy activists including Jimmy Sham, who was attacked by masked assailants with hammers last month in Kowloon, managed to win district council seats in the local elections.<br/><br/>The district councils may play a significant role when electing Hong Kong's chief executive in 2022.<br/><br/>This is because the city's leader is elected by a 1,200-member committee, which includes 117 members chosen by district councillors. In this system, whichever camp<br/>claims the majority of votes, has the ability to claim all 117 of these seats.<br/><br/>This could influence who is chosen to be the city's chief executive as the pro-democracy camp already held roughly 400 committee seats before the district council elections.<br/><br/>As six out of 70 seats are reserved in the city's Legislative Council for district councillors, the pro-democracy camp may also secure seats in the Legislative Council as the majority.<br/><br/>Hong Kong's Legislative Council has the ability to enact, amend, repeal laws or even start an impeachment process against the city's leader.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hong-kong-pro-democracy-camp-wins-big-in-local-elections-3926157</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/67E/EB1/67EEB1F67C2192B94C688FC3862CD20E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/25/3926157/3926157_68EB60331A9640278F08B730F1D86854_191125_3926157_Hong_Kong_pro_democracy_camp_wins_big_in_local_e_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 11:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926673</guid>
      <title>High rise park views turn out to be awesome plastic lake in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHANGSHA, CHINA <br/> When you got the big bucks in China, you got to have the big baller view to go with it.<br/>According to the SCMP, lucky suckers who purchased units in a brand new residential high rise that touted "park views" were treated to that and so much more. <br/>The development located in the Hunan provincial city of Changsha promised "high vegetation cover" and a "park lifestyle."<br/>The real estate developer then translated that into the magnificent beauty of a fake blue lake created with gorgeous man-made plastic. <br/>They then topped that off with a luxuriously elaborate fake bridge that spanned the entire pretend lake. <br/>And who needs actual grass covering the larger open areas when you have grass block paving that is usually seen in driveways or parking lots instead. That counts as vegetation.     <br/><br/>If you've got your bathing suit ready so you can test out the crystal clear waters you're unfortunately out of luck. <br/>After the story went viral and complaints started rolling in, the developers ended up tearing up the fake plastic pool, leaving the crappy concrete foundations underneath. <br/>Guess we'll just have to wait and see what kind of magic the developers will put in its place.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/high-rise-park-views-turn-out-to-be-awesome-plastic-lake-in-china-3926673</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E9F/12F/E9F12F4BA8C50F520CAEEC1279276EDA.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926673/3926673_BBE9AEC7A93E43C490B1ACB0527406DB_191126_3926673_High_rise_park_views_turn_out_to_be_awesome_plas_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926655</guid>
      <title>Beijing police force just cloned 6 K-9 dogs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Beijing's boys in blue introduced six new members into the police force that you might have trouble telling apart from each other. That's just because they were all cloned.  <br/>CBS News reports that the young officers were sporting shiny new badges, uniforms and collars. <br/>The six clones are the result of work between the Beijing Municipal Bureau of Public Security's Police Dog Base and private pet-cloning company Sinogene. <br/>According to CBS, four of the doggos were born in the same litter in August. Their DNA is more than 99 percent identical to the two Belgian Malinois donor dogs. <br/>The donors were selected for their RUFF and tough performance on the police force. <br/>According to the Chinese authorities, police dogs lose some of their abilities as they get older, so naturally why not turn to cloning. <br/>The goal of the cloning program is to create a K-9 police force with greater efficiency and shorter training periods. <br/>The police dog base said it would be watching the cloned recruits closely during their training. <br/>That's all good and fine, but when are they going to start cloning humans? China needs more of those.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/beijing-police-force-just-cloned-6-k-9-dogs-3926655</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5A8/B6C/5A8B6C5637A00347498927260EC14D78.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/26/3926655/3926655_CF5AA6D2772549F1BD8D60D9C0D87C44_191126_3926655_Beijing_police_force_just_cloned_6_K_9_dogs_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 11:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926976</guid>
      <title>New leak exposes China's brainwashing camps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG / CHINA <br/> China has built a vast camp system in Xinjiang and interned about a million Uyghurs. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, or ICIJ, says that a new leak has revealed the conditions in the system.<br/><br/>The Guardian reports that the documents contain instructions for officials to "never allow escape."<br/><br/>The orders demand constant surveillance with no blindspots and establishing guard towers and layers of fences and walls, according to the Guardian.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that every aspect of life in the camps is controlled. The document shows that a detainee must take a fixed position for bed, for workshop, and for lunch queues. <br/><br/>The BBC reports that the documents include orders to enforce strict discipline for sleeping, waking, closing doors and roll calls.<br/><br/>Chinese officials claimed the camps give lessons on Chinese language and citizenship, but former detainees described them as harsh brainwashing sessions, the New York Times reports.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the camps established a points system based on the detainee's ideological transformation and compliance. <br/><br/>The Guardian reports that those who loses points could be transferred to a higher tier of security camps and see their internment increased from the required term of one year.<br/><br/>The ICIJ says the documents also revealed the extent of China's AI-powered domestic surveillance program. <br/><br/>The predictive system tracks VISAs application records, use of encrypted apps and facial recognition to flag thousands of people for searches and detention.<br/><br/>Speaking to the BBC, China's UK ambassador Liu Xiaoming dismissed latest Uyghur internment camp revelations as "fake news," in a press conference on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-leak-exposes-china-s-brainwashing-camps-3926976</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/B61/AFE/B61AFE08F1D5098818FFB0846261FD30.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3926976/3926976_C9F5107E05BB41F68AEAD52364182C94_191127_3926976_New_leak_exposes_China_s_brainwashing_camps_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 05:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3926959</guid>
      <title>New leak exposes China's brainwashing camps</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINJIANG / CHINA <br/> China has built a vast camp system in Xinjiang and interned about a million Uyghurs. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists, or ICIJ, says that a new leak has revealed the conditions in the system.<br/><br/>The Guardian reports that the documents contain instructions for officials to "never allow escape."<br/><br/>The orders demand constant surveillance with no blindspots and establishing guard towers and layers of fences and walls, according to the Guardian.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that every aspect of life in the camps is controlled. The document shows that a detainee must take a fixed position for bed, for workshop, and for lunch queues. <br/><br/>The BBC reports that the documents include orders to enforce strict discipline for sleeping, waking, closing doors and roll calls.<br/><br/>Chinese officials claimed the camps give lessons on Chinese language and citizenship, but former detainees described them as harsh brainwashing sessions, the New York Times reports.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the camps established a points system based on the detainee's ideological transformation and compliance. <br/><br/>The Guardian reports that those who loses points could be transferred to a higher tier of security camps and see their internment increased from the required term of one year.<br/><br/>The ICIJ says the documents also revealed the extent of China's AI-powered domestic surveillance program. <br/><br/>The predictive system tracks VISAs application records, use of encrypted apps and facial recognition to flag thousands of people for searches and detention.<br/><br/>Speaking to the BBC, China's UK ambassador Liu Xiaoming dismissed latest Uyghur internment camp revelations as "fake news," in a press conference on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-leak-exposes-china-s-brainwashing-camps-3926959</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/734/165/73416530712B5C0ED5D0F1A6CF8B3D2B.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/27/3926959/3926959_C986E9A29BF5445EB4FE84711E63E62B_191127_3926959_New_leak_exposes_China_s_brainwashing_camps_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 05:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927470</guid>
      <title>World's only brown panda in captivity kind of gets adopted</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANXI PROVINCE <br/> The world's only brown panda held in captivity has been adopted by a U.S.-based charity last week. <br/>According to China's fake news media Xinhua, Qizai is a 10-year-old male with a one-of-a-kind brown and white coat because of a genetic anomaly. <br/>According to Next Shark, he was adopted by Colorado-based nonprofit Pandas International founded by Suzanne Braden and Diane Rees in 2000. <br/>The group is committed to the conservation of pandas. <br/>Here's the catch, Qizai will continue crashing at the Qinling Giant Panda Research Center located in China's northwestern Shaanxi province. <br/>The arrangement is that Pandas International is granted access to him<br/>whatever that means. <br/><br/>The panda non-profit will also get regular updates about his life. UPDATES like<br/>he ate, he pooed, he slept?<br/>The Chinese breeding center allowed for the group to adopt Qizai for life to thank them for their daily work and for donating vaccines, lab instrument, baby panda crib and milk powder.   <br/><br/>Apparently there have only been five brown-and-white pandas spotted since 1985. According to World Wildlife, there are currently, 1,864 pandas living in the wild around the world.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-only-brown-panda-in-captivity-kind-of-gets-adopted-3927470</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F0/8DD/1F08DD687CDF1BE7DA0DFC125AB2327E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927470/3927470_BB487A9527AA417EA7D5C75315E2FC56_191128_3927470_World_s_only_brown_panda_in_captivity_kind_of_ge_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3927808</guid>
      <title>Dead Thai deer found with seven kg of plastic waste in stomach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN THA, THAILAND <br/> A wild deer living in a Thai national park was found to have seven kilograms of trash in its stomach.<br/><br/>Kriangsak Thanompun, a director from the Khun Sathan National Park in northern Thailand said the male deer had been eating plastic for a "long time" before it succumbed to death.<br/><br/>The deer was found on November 25, by a patrolling officer, the BBC reports. According to the Bangkok Post, the animal appeared to have some hair loss and deterioration at his hoofs and was thin in appearance.<br/><br/>An autopsy conducted on the wild deer found items such as rubber gloves, instant noodle packets, coffee packets, plastic bags and even underwear stashed in its stomach.<br/><br/>Officials believe all that trash had blocked up the poor animal's gastrointestinal tract, though a further investigation will be launched.<br/><br/>Thailand is a major producer of plastic waste due to strong demand in the nation, though it lacks an effective waste management system to recycle plastic, according to the Bangkok Post.<br/><br/>Roughly 75 billion pieces of bags are thrown away in Thailand every year, the BBC reports, citing Greenpeace. <br/><br/>Thanompun told BBC Thailand that the park plans to implement a scheme to get locals in the area to help collect discarded plastic and other waste.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dead-thai-deer-found-with-seven-kg-of-plastic-waste-in-stomach-3927808</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/97C/600/97C600375E617945169834B3F968003C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/11/28/3927808/3927808_4B725217E9DA4FC3AA6A65A253CABC06_191128_3927808_Dead_Thai_deer_found_with_seven_kg_of_plastic_wa_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 11:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
