<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 18:05:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3957950</guid>
      <title>Bird flu outbreak kills thousands of chickens in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHAOYANG, CHINA <br/> China has confirmed the latest outbreak of the highly pathogenic H5N1 bird flu in Hunan province."<br/><br/>On Sunday, China's Ministry of Agriculture and Rural Affairs reported the discovery of an H5N1 cluster on a farm in the province's city of Shaoyang[d].<br/><br/>The incident occurred on a farm with about 7,900 chicken, where 4,500 of the birds have died. Local authorities have responded by culling the infected birds.<br/><br/>According to the WHO, H5N1 is an influenza virus that is highly contagious among birds and can cause severe respiratory disease in avians.<br/><br/>The virus does not infect people easily and human to human transmission is rare.<br/><br/>However, the WHO reports that people associated with close contact with dead or live birds could contract the H5N1 and that the infection is fatal to humans 60 percent of the time.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/bird-flu-outbreak-kills-thousands-of-chickens-in-china-3957950</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957950/3957950_B3D96D1F58FD4907A9993A73A4272BB1_200203_3957950_Bird_flu_outbreak_kills_thousands_of_chickens_in_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957884</guid>
      <title>China claims herbal medicine will cure coronavirus then backtracks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> As a certain country continues to battle against you-know-what, herbal remedies are also being enlisted in the fight.  <br/><br/>Chinese state-owned speakerbox Xinhua reported on Friday that scientists in China recommended a traditional Chinese medicine called Shuanghuanglian [b]to help "alleviate fever" and "contain the progression" of the latest virus spreading across the country.<br/><br/>Apparently, the concoction is made with honeysuckle and flowering plants, which is said to "inhibit" the latest epidemic.  <br/><br/>Xinhua was encouraging the public to use traditional Chinese medicine along with western medicine to get better results.<br/><br/>Chinese people were quick to storm their nearest drugstore. Images and videos shared on social media show long lines of people geared up waiting to get a hold of the miracle drink. Shuanghuanglian quickly sold out online and in actual stores.<br/><br/>Though not everyone was thrilled about the product. Some on Weibo expressed skepticism about the effectiveness of herbal medicine.<br/><br/>In response, The China Daily and the People's Daily then began to discourage people from buying the herbal concoction as it is still in its early stages of research.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-claims-herbal-medicine-will-cure-coronavirus-then-backtracks-3957884</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957884/3957884_A711FB66DB484F219B2717764711057E_200203_3957884_China_claims_herbal_medicine_will_cure_coronavir_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958192</guid>
      <title>Man gets socked for calling out pharmacy over face mask prices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOMEWHERE <br/> A pharmacy employee is in a world of trouble after going rock 'em sock 'em at a customer complaining about face mask price gouging.<br/><br/>According to Beijing News on Miaopai, the incident happened in Donggang, in China's Liaoning province. <br/><br/>On January 27, a male customer at a Kangyi Medicine store filmed himself confronting staff about a too-expensive 35 yuan face mask. He reminded them that there were government regulations against jacking up face mask prices amid the Wuhan outbreak.<br/><br/>A female employee offers to refund his money, but the man insists he wants to buy it at its regular price.<br/><br/>Eventually, a male staff member got aggressive, telling the customer to scram and then punching him right in the moneymaker.<br/><br/>Wth China in the middle of an epidemic, raising face mask prices is about one of the worst, most shameful things anyone can do. That plus the violence, and sure enough &#8211; the Chinese internets got absolutely livid.<br/><br/>By that evening, the Donggang City Market Supervision Bureau announced in a statement that it would impose penalties on the store.<br/><br/>According to the Shanghaiist, the male employee has also been detained by the cops.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-gets-socked-for-calling-out-pharmacy-over-face-mask-prices-3958192</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958192/3958192_E3387EAB12E7413D8E5641400EAB94D7_200204_3958192_Man_gets_socked_for_calling_out_pharmacy_over_fa_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958167</guid>
      <title>Drones are being used in China to help battle Wuhan coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOMEWHERE <br/> As the you-know-what continues to spread around the country that will remain nameless, authorities are now enlisting the help of drones to make it look like they are doing something. <br/>According to video posted to Weibo, traffic police in Shuyang county in Jiangsu province have enlisted the help of drones to yell at pedestrians walking around the streets without face masks. <br/>At one point, the drone can be heard squawking at one guy, "the gentleman with a pink coat riding a motorcycle. Yeah, you! Please put on your mask."<br/>In another exchange the drone blurts out, "Hey, guy on the phone! Where is your mask? Wear your mask!"<br/><br/>And in other parts of the country that will not be named, videos from provinces like Jilin, Shandong and Zhejiang have been posted onto social media showing drones crop dusting the air with disinfectant. <br/>Apparently the unmanned aerial machines are more effective at dispersing cleaning solutions than on foot or by car.  <br/>Police in the Sichuan province were also using drones to disinfect areas harder to reach like people's roofs. But here's the thing, does your roof really need disinfecting? <br/>Can all these drones make a difference? What do you think?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/drones-are-being-used-in-china-to-help-battle-wuhan-coronavirus-3958167</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958167/3958167_D5FA7231405B4A149C71B4B1083661C0_200204_3958167_Drones_are_being_used_in_China_to_help_battle_Wu_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 01:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958161</guid>
      <title>Chinese health officials clueless on coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Chinese health officials are struggling to answer questions about recent developments in the country. <br/><br/>On January 29th, two senior health officials were asked a set of basic questions about the virus during an interview in Huanggang, a city to the east of Wuhan. State broadcaster CCTV sat down with Tang Zhihong, chief of the city's health commission, and Chen Mingxing, director of the city's Center for Disease Control and Prevention. <br/><br/>However, they either couldn't answer the questions or couldn't agree. <br/><br/>The Huanggang government announced that Tang had been dismissed from her position the following day. <br/><br/>But they're not the only ones to suffer a media mishap, Sheng Wenjun the Communist Party Secretary of quarantined Chibi City was caught wearing his surgical mask incorrectly during an inspection of his city's response to the virus.<br/><br/>Worst of all, at a press conference on the 26th of January, the governor of Hubei Province didn't even wear a mask; the Hubei secretary did, however, he too didn't cover his nose and the mayor wore his inside out. <br/><br/>On January 29th, Zeng Guang, the chief scientist of epidemiology at China's CDC, made a rare and honest admission about why Chinese officials cannot tell people the truth, saying that they, "need to think about the political angle and social stability" in order to keep their positions.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-health-officials-clueless-on-coronavirus-3958161</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958161/3958161_C1B10C6F24BB401E978D8A3B2C80F564_200204_3958161_Chinese_health_officials_clueless_on_coronavirus_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 00:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958514</guid>
      <title>Chinese man takes out 2,257 feet of guardrail with one kick</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LINFEN, CHINA <br/> Guardrails and fences around the world fear this man. <br/><br/>In an amazing testament to human strength<br/>or shoddy Chinese construction<br/>a guy in the city of Linfen in Shanxi province was caught on camera taking out a whopping 2,257 foot chunk of guardrail with just one kick.<br/>According to United Daily News, the incident happened around 2 p.m. on January 29 at the Shili Promenade, a 5 km long riverside trail.<br/><br/>That's when the two men surnamed Shi and Chang decided to film a TikTok video of them kicking a stone pillar. <br/>Unfortunately for the stone pillar<br/>it was made in China. Thankfully for us the stone pillar was<br/>made in China.    <br/>One of the guys then unleashes the kick heard round the world, which sets in motion a hilarious CHAIN of events. <br/>After the first pillar falls, because they are all connected by an iron chain, they all begin falling like a massive chain of dominos<br/>218 stone pillar dominos to be exact.  <br/>Wonder how the TikTok video turned out?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-man-takes-out-2-257-feet-of-guardrail-with-one-kick-3958514</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958514/3958514_34723C38A28B4CAFAE1A1782808911F5_200204_3958514_Chinese_man_takes_out_2_257_feet_of_guardrail_wi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958428</guid>
      <title>Claw machines in Taiwan offer masks, hand sanitizers as prizes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> Claw machines in Taiwan are now offering face masks, hand sanitizers and antibacterial hand wipes as prizes amid the latest you-know-what.<br/><br/>Local authorities have found at least 40 such claw machines in Taipei alone, reports the Liberty Times.  A Taipei city councilor has accused the claw machine vendors of violating fair trade laws by hawking and hoarding these medical supplies during this time. <br/><br/>An official from Taipei's Department of Health said that these vendors may face fines of up to $66,000 if the products inside contain a medical equipment license number. This would mean they're in violation of Taiwan's Pharmaceutical Affairs Act.<br/><br/>Face masks, hand sanitizers have been in high demand in Taiwan recently, with stores now routinely running out of supplies at record speed.<br/><br/>As a result, the government has announced plans to ration face masks. Taiwanese people will be allowed to only purchase two face masks per week while showing their national health insurance cards starting this Thursday.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/claw-machines-in-taiwan-offer-masks-hand-sanitizers-as-prizes-3958428</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958428/3958428_1B64E8D3B7E248D09AADEF9C86E449EB_200204_3958428_Claw_machines_in_Taiwan_offer_masks__hand_saniti_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958718</guid>
      <title>Fend off Chinese mask hoarders with Taiwan flag face masks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> It's trying times in China with the you-know-what causing a global pandemic and prompting everyone and their Great Aunt to wear protective face masks.<br/><br/>As folks went into a frenzy of panic buying and mask hoarding, a photo popped up on Reddit showing face masks embellished with the Taiwan flag.<br/><br/>It came with text saying: "Taiwan printed its national flag on face masks so that any mainland Chinese who buys them will have to wear the Taiwanese flag on his face."<br/><br/>Ooooh, yes please!<br/><br/>According to Taiwan News, the Japanese got wind of the photo after blogger Rie Ogasawara posted it on social media site Ameba. <br/><br/>Some commented that the presence of the dreaded flag would keep any card-carrying follower of the CCP from buying it, which only means more for the rest of us!<br/><br/>They also mistakenly assumed someone in Japan had started the trend. But eagle-eyed Taiwanese netizens were quick to claim that the manufacturer, Champ Mask, was Taiwanese, and the price in the photo couldn't be in yen.<br/><br/>It's unlikely that the face masks were made specifically to troll Chinese, but hey, if it's there why not use it?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/fend-off-chinese-mask-hoarders-with-taiwan-flag-face-masks-3958718</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958718/3958718_B2E1D18EFCB3404EB4B5ED8F2F195422_200205_3958718_Fend_off_Chinese_mask_hoarders_with_Taiwan_flag__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 03:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958942</guid>
      <title>Video shows Wuhan's new hospital looking like a prison</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> China announced the completion of a 1,000-bed hospital that will accommodate patients infected with the dreaded you-know-what.<br/><br/>The Associated Press reports that the first patients arrived Monday at Huoshenshan Hospital, which was assembled in 10 days.<br/><br/>Satellite images released by the China Aerospace Science and Technology Corporation shows a field at the site back in October 29. <br/><br/>Construction was in full swing by January 30, a mere seven days after it broke ground, and was complete by February 2.<br/><br/>A new video posted to Twitter by Himalaya Global claims to show the inside of the Huoshenshan facility. <br/><br/>The footage was supposedly shot by a contractor, who shows a sick ward with the ominous warning that "once you are in, you can't get out" and says "you'd better quarantine at home than here."<br/><br/>He then proceeds to walk around the facility, showing windows welded shut, a small window opening to deliver food, and doors that can't be opened from the inside. <br/><br/>It's supposed to be a hospital, but looks more like a prison.<br/><br/>Folks online chimed in that hospitals don't usually have doors opening just one way, and commented that this was more a "medical" internment camp than anything else &#8211; a jail for sick people, basically.<br/><br/>A second 1,500-bed "hospital" called Leishenshan began construction on January 27 and is meant to be ready this week after 12 days of construction work.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/video-shows-wuhan-s-new-hospital-looking-like-a-prison-3958942</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958942/3958942_00083AF9D3DC47A4AFE544190BD0F27B_200205_3958942_Video_shows_Wuhan_s_new_hospital_looking_like_a__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 10:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959222</guid>
      <title>63-year-old actress Chen Meifen dubbed "Taiwan's Hottest Auntie"</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> A Taiwanese actress is turning heads all across the internet for her age-defying looks.<br/><br/>If you didn't know any better, you'd think Chen Meifen was in her 30s. She's actually 63, because ladies and gentlemen, Asian don't raisin!<br/><br/>Back when she was still 36, an influential Taiwanese TV presenter called her the "hottest obasan of Taiwan", obasan being the Japanese term for aunt or older woman. 30 odd years later, she's still fresh-faced and living up to that monicker.<br/><br/>Next Shark reports she's been quoted as saying obasans don't have to look dowdy and ugly, adding that "we can grow beautiful as we age."<br/><br/>Her most recent outing was in a pre-recorded Lunar New Year show for a local broadcaster, which saw her showing off her toned physique in this revealing number.<br/><br/>Most of us can only dream about being this genetically blessed, though according to Next Shark, Chen attributes her assets to a diet of "ginger and soup", and working out.<br/><br/>Chen is a household name in Taiwan. As a 19-year-old in 1975, she was crowned Knitwear Beauty and has been in the limelight for over four decades. <br/><br/>The stunning 63-year-old is fairly active on Facebook and Instagram, where she's got over 500,000 likes and 83,000 followers respectively.<br/><br/>And in case there's any hot uncles watching this &#8211; she's also still single!]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/63-year-old-actress-chen-meifen-dubbed-taiwan-s-hottest-auntie--3959222</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959222/3959222_7D3A36AEDF834525907EFBBBF3F88041_200206_3959222_63_year_old_actress_Chen_Meifen_dubbed__Taiwan_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 03:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959444</guid>
      <title>Global Times spreads hoax that infrared cameras see your farts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> As China continues to tell the world that everything is A-okay when it's clearly not, the uber pro-government Global Times has been trying to pass off a story about infrared cameras picking up when you let one go. <br/>Using their official Twitter account, the Chinese tabloid posted a Tik Tok video from a television station in Enshi located in Hubei province on Monday. <br/>They included the caption, "Can't help farting? Well, better try harder, because infrared temperature sensors recently installed in airports and train stations to monitor temperatures of passengers amid" the latest outbreak can screen them all. <br/>Seems legit. Actually...it's fake<br/>which in China passes the test of a hard hitting news story. <br/>According to Gizmodo, the video is actually from 2016 with the noxious gas clouds digitally added.  <br/>Gimozo reports that the video was first LET GO in 2016 by an online group called Banana Factory, who later came out and said the video was a hoax. <br/>And now thanks to the Global Times, you have Chinese people worried about fevers and holding it in when they pass through security.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/global-times-spreads-hoax-that-infrared-cameras-see-your-farts-3959444</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959444/3959444_ABBCDAA5F329490EB35FEACAAA64DECB_200206_3959444_Global_Times_spreads_hoax_that_infrared_cameras__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959418</guid>
      <title>Anonymous create pro-Taiwan page on United Nations website</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN <br/> Anonymous successfully hacked into a United Nations webpage and created a page that supports Taiwan.<br/><br/>Taiwan is not a member of the United Nations because China<br/>who is one of the permanent members of the UN security council<br/>won't allow it. China also forces the U.N. to deny Taiwan membership into the WHO, which is of vital importance especially at a time like this.   <br/><br/>Hackers at Anonymous had created a UN page that had a black background with the logo of the hacking group, the words "TAIWAN NUMBAH WANNNN!!," the Taiwanese flag, the Kuomintang's party emblem and the flag of the Democratic Progressive Party, representing the two main political parties in Taiwan.<br/><br/>As we scroll further down, we see two videos. One is a video playing Taiwan's national anthem and another is a soundtrack titled, "It's Been a Long, Long Time," from the Marvel movie "Avengers Endgame."<br/><br/>The hacked page was shared via a link by a Reddit user. <br/><br/>Interestingly, 14 hours after the link was shared on Reddit, the UN had yet to take the page down, though it has since been removed.<br/><br/>Users on a Taiwanese subreddit praised the hacking group for standing up for Taiwan. One user said, "Okay, this is epic," while another said, "Awesome. Fully support taking advantage of the confusion of the virus crisis."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/anonymous-create-pro-taiwan-page-on-united-nations-website-3959418</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959418/3959418_A9A11E1AA50C48C185DC3BDFB25BFB4A_200206_3959418_Anonymous_create_pro_Taiwan_page_on_United_Natio_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 09:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959524</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's three effective responses to Wuhan virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIWAN <br/> Taiwan has drawn from lessons learned during the SARS epidemic to mount an effective and immediate response to the 2019 novel coronavirus outbreak, using three major steps. <br/><br/>According to a report by Mirror Media, Taiwan's first response to the novel coronavirus came on December 31, when China reported 27 cases of a mysterious Wuhan pneumonia to the WHO.<br/><br/>Direct flights from Wuhan became subject to onboard health screening, and passengers had to declare their health status.<br/><br/>It wasn't until January 21 that the island nation reported its first confirmed case. A 55-year-old businesswoman who returned to Taiwan from Wuhan was brought directly to the hospital upon arrival.<br/><br/>Taiwan's second step was made on January 15, when the country's Centers for Disease Control listed the Wuhan pneumonia as a Category 5 communicable disease.<br/><br/>According to Focus Taiwan, this made it mandatory to report suspected cases within 24 hours. Quarantining those who exhibited symptoms also became compulsory.<br/><br/>When a man in Kaohsiung neglected to report viral symptoms after returning from Wuhan, the government fined him NT$300,000, or about US$10,000.<br/><br/>On January 16, Taiwan's CDC raised the travel alert for Wuhan, after a Taiwanese expert team sent to the city to observe the epidemic suspected the possibility of human-to-human transmission.<br/><br/>As of February 6, Taiwan has 13 confirmed cases of the virus. According to a CDC press release, patients are being treated in isolation wards and are in a stable condition.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-s-three-effective-responses-to-wuhan-virus-outbreak-3959524</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959524/3959524_5DD19CFFED0E4511A840F5C23213CB29_200206_3959524_Taiwan_s_three_effective_responses_to_Wuhan_viru_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 12:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959696</guid>
      <title>Did Tencent just leak real data on Wuhan coronavirus epidemic?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA <br/> Tencent may have accidentally posted the real numbers of infections and deaths from the coronavirus, figures astronomically higher than what the Chinese government has been telling everyone. <br/><br/>On February 1st, Tencent's homepage, titled "Epidemic Situation Tracker" showed confirmed cases of the coronavirus in China as 154,023, ten times the official figure at the time. <br/><br/>It also listed the number of suspected cases as 79,808, four times the official figure.<br/><br/>The number of cured cases was a mere 269, well below the official claim of 300. <br/><br/>Most worryingly, however, was the death toll which stood at 24,589 which was tremendously higher than the 300 officially listed for that day.<br/><br/>Tencent then wiped the numbers and updated them to reflect the government's 'official' ones. <br/><br/>According to Taiwan News, netizens noticed that Tencent has on at least three separate occasions posted extremely high numbers, only to quickly change them to adhere to the government-approved numbers. <br/><br/>This jump or swap of numbers has led netizens to believe Tencent has two sets of data, the real data, and 'processed' data.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/did-tencent-just-leak-real-data-on-wuhan-coronavirus-epidemic--3959696</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3959696/3959696_6F6D2E72053A4069ABC24CBE6FD665B1_200207_3959696_Did_Tencent_just_leak_real_data_on_Wuhan_coronav_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 00:53:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960018</guid>
      <title>China's coronavirus containment strategy is not working</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> China continues to struggle. <br/><br/>On Thursday, China's number of confirmed novel coronavirus infections grew to 28,000 cases or a 15 percent increase over the previous day.<br/><br/>According to CNN, reported deaths have spiked, which increased the death toll to 600 fatalities.<br/><br/>The contagion continues to spread rapidly despite population control and quarantine protocols Beijing imposed in central China.<br/><br/>BBC reports that the new coronavirus has infected about 28,300 people worldwide, compared to SARS's 8,100 cases and MERS's 2,500 cases.<br/><br/>Citing an epidemiologist, BBC reports that the Wuhan pneumonia appears to have lower mortality rates than the two other viruses.<br/><br/>Al Jazeera reports that China has built hospitals at a frantic pace in Wuhan, including the Huoshenshan Hospital built over 10 days with 1,000 beds, which opened Monday.<br/><br/>CNN reports that a second new hospital named Leishenshan opened on Thursday.<br/><br/>The CNN reports that common symptoms include headache, malaise, coughing and muscle pains.<br/><br/>Complications include fever over 39 degrees Celsius, troubled breathing and pneumonia, and sepsis that could result in death.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-coronavirus-containment-strategy-is-not-working-3960018</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3960018/3960018_6EFCD80338AB4521B354F389E33D88F3_200207_3960018_China_s_coronavirus_containment_strategy_is_not__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:14:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959887</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus impacting cruise ships, airlines, car manufacturers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> As the Wuhan virus continues to spread at an alarming rate, it is starting to impact cruise ships, airlines and other international companies.<br/><br/>Two cruise ships traveling in Asia have been forced to quarantine thousands of passengers. One of the ships is anchored off of Japan while the other is in Hong Kong, Reuters reports. <br/><br/>According to Bloomberg, Japanese health workers said 61 passengers on one of the ships were found to test positive for the novel coronavirus.<br/><br/>Air travel has been disrupted, with more than 73 airlines around the world either suspending or restricting flights to China, as reported by Business Insider. This includes airlines such as Japan Airlines, Air Canada, Air France, Cathay Pacific and American Airlines.<br/><br/>Hong Kong's Cathay Pacific has gone a step further and asked staff members to take three weeks of unpaid leave to cope with the impact of the Wuhan virus. The company says that it plans to cut roughly 90 percent of its flights to China over the next two months, BBC News reports. <br/><br/>Global car manufacturing firms have been forced to shut down factories for an extended amount of time in China following the outbreak of the coronavirus. Car companies that have closed down their Chinese factories include Hyundai, Tesla, Ford and Nissan among others.<br/><br/>Airbus SE is halting one of its assembly lines in China, while Boeing and French company Safran SA are both closing plane making facilities in China in order to minimize workers' exposure to the virus, Bloomberg reports. <br/><br/>The coronavirus has already spread to 28 countries and regions outside of China. More than 31,000 people in China have been affected with the virus so far. The virus has caused 636 deaths in China, with two additional deaths from the virus in the Philippines and in Hong Kong.<br/><br/>The World Health Organization had declared the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak a global health emergency at the end of last month.<br/><br/>Symptoms of the coronavirus include severe coughing, fever and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-virus-impacting-cruise-ships-airlines-car-manufacturers-3959887</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3959887/3959887_5B8A08E41BAF4F93A26A1EF163B17A49_200207_3959887_Wuhan_virus_impacting_cruise_ships__airlines__ca_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 08:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959869</guid>
      <title>China is sealing people in their homes amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> As new cases continue on an upward climb, respect for human lives has gone right out the window as footage appears to show how some are being treated amidst the latest outbreak.    <br/><br/>In a video shared on Chinese social media, a door of a house is seen totally blocked by a massive pile of coal ash, commonly used in furnaces. It's unclear how many people live in the house, or what their condition is, but it's safe to say they won't be leaving anytime soon. <br/><br/>In another video, health officials are seen using a welding machine to seal the door of a residential house in order to prevent those under quarantine from leaving their house.<br/><br/>Chinese police officers are also seen in another disturbing video nailing in wooden planks to block the front door of an apartment with people inside who had just returned home from Wuhan.<br/><br/>Afterwards, officials are seen sticking a red sign beside the front door which reads, "The people in this house have just returned from Wuhan, don't be in contact with them." The poor people inside are heard desperately screaming, "Open the door!"<br/><br/>Chinese officials did the same to other residences as well, but this time they used metal bars instead of wooden ones.<br/><br/>How will those sealed inside their houses get access to food, medicine and other essential supplies?<br/><br/>And this comes after rumors that China has woefully underreported the number of those who have been sickened and those who have unfortunately succumbed to it.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-is-sealing-people-in-their-homes-amid-virus-outbreak-3959869</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3959869/3959869_7271EEFF25914A3186B0DDD232A9EBA8_200207_3959869_China_is_sealing_people_in_their_homes_amid_viru_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 07:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960125</guid>
      <title>China quarantines negative coronavirus news coverage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> As cases continue to skyrocket within the country, Xi Jinping and his pals in Beijing have decided to clamp down on negative coverage over news media and online.<br/>According to the failing New York Times, the Communist party is struggling to control the narrative about the crisis that has slammed the leaders like a serious case of the mexican beer thing. <br/>The party was caught off guard by the flu's ugly cousin, which handled the initial outbreak in typical fashion<br/>by shoving it under the rug.     <br/>And then when it blew up in their faces, when it was already too late, they put around 60 million people on total lockdown. <br/>Now that Chinese citizens are getting increasingly pissed off, China's leaders are once again putting the screws on information.<br/><br/>This after a short spell where news outlets were able to be quite straightforward about the tense situation, and negative comments about the clumsy official response were left uncensored online. <br/>The failing Times reports that in recent days, both state-run media and more commercially minded outlets have been ordered to focus on positive stories. <br/>Internet platforms have removed numerous articles criticizing the lazy-footed response by the Chinese government or painting the current situation in a negative light. <br/>Unfortunately less actual information and more positive propaganda isn't going to make this problem go away. <br/><br/>With thousands of new cases each day, many Chinese fear the spread is not being adequately contained<br/>and they're dead right.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-quarantines-negative-coronavirus-news-coverage-3960125</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3960125/3960125_3A5525BFE86A431A81437A5EF2AA4EC6_200207_3960125_China_quarantines_negative_coronavirus_news_cove_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 14:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960976</guid>
      <title>Driver wears 12 face masks at once during Wuhan coronavirus scare</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DONGGUAN, CHINA <br/> As China continues to struggle with all the negative news swirling around the Mexican beer sickness, stockpiles of many things are running low, especially face masks, so it's good to see people needlessly wasting them. <br/>Video footage posted to Miaopai, shows one driver from the city of Dongguan located in Guangdong province wearing a ridiculous 12 masks at one time. <br/>The clip shows the driver being pulled over by traffic cops for a quick temperature check. <br/>The police then ask the man how many masks he has on, so he starts taking them off. <br/>The guy methodically removes all 11 superfluous masks, while the police kindly wait for him. <br/>Authorities then let the man know that he only needs to wear one. <br/>What they should have told him is that if he's really that paranoid about catching the dreaded you-know-what, then you also need to protect your eyes. <br/>Great, now this guy is going to start driving around wearing 12 sets of goggles on his face.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/driver-wears-12-face-masks-at-once-during-wuhan-coronavirus-scare-3960976</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3960976/3960976_964FF076A99540C5B1883D94719AD871_200210_3960976_Driver_wears_12_face_masks_at_once_during_Wuhan__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 05:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961200</guid>
      <title>Soldier kills 29 in Thailand's deadliest ever mass shooting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NAKHON RATCHASIMA, THAILAND <br/> A Thai soldier went on a shooting rampage over the weekend, killing 29 people in the country's deadliest ever mass shooting.<br/><br/>Sergeant Major 1st Class Jakrapanth Thomma[m][n][o] made his way to his commanding officer's house in Nakhon Ratchasima, Thailand on Saturday, February 8 at 3:00 p.m. local time, where he shot his commander and a woman believed to be a relative of the commander after a dispute, Reuters reports. <br/><br/>An hour later, he went to the Surathampithak army base where he was stationed and killed an army guard before stealing assault weapons, at least one machine gun and roughly 800 rounds of ammunition.<br/><br/>The gunman drove off in a stolen Humvee and stopped at a Buddhist temple as authorities chased him. He killed around nine people before driving away. A Thai police officer was also killed during the shooting spree.<br/><br/>The shooter posted updates to Facebook during the shootings, with messages such as "No one can escape death," at 6:30 p.m.<br/><br/>The Thai soldier also live-streamed part of his shooting rampage on Facebook, though the video has since been deleted. It's unclear which part of the shooting was streamed on the social media platform.<br/><br/>Around 5:30 p.m., the soldier made his way to Terminal 21 shopping mall in Nakhon Ratchasima, where he began to open fire on frightened shoppers in the vicinity. At least 12 shoppers were shot dead, while dozens were injured.<br/><br/>Twenty minutes after the shooting, the police cordoned off two kilometers of the area around the mall. A few hours later, Thai security forces stormed the mall and helped hundreds of shoppers escape.<br/><br/>The gunman escaped to the basement of the mall at 12:30 a.m., Sunday. Authorities continued to search for the soldier throughout the night. He was located in the basement in the morning at 9:05 a.m., when he was promptly shot dead by security forces.<br/><br/>At least two victims died at the hospital during surgery, while others remain hospitalized, CNN reports, citing Narinrat Pitchayakamin, a Thai public health ministry official.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/soldier-kills-29-in-thailand-s-deadliest-ever-mass-shooting-3961200</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961200/3961200_440BF7E74F4A4CB28E5768FF014125D7_200210_3961200_Soldier_kills_29_in_Thailand_s_deadliest_ever_ma_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961190</guid>
      <title>Doctor's death sparks anger toward government in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> The passing of the Chinese doctor who tried to sound the alarm about China's grave situation has sparked public anger and grief. <br/>BBC reports that Li Wenliang is no longer around after contracting the same illness he was treating his patients for in the city where the latest incident began. <br/>Last December Li sent a text in a group chat with other physicians of a SARS-esque cousin. <br/>For his troubles he was told by police to "stop making false comments" and was put under the magnifying glass for "spreading rumors" <br/> aka telling people THE TRUTH.    <br/><br/>According to Forbes, after conflicting reports last Thursday the Li was no longer around, then critically ill, then indeed no longer around, Chinese citizens stormed onto social media voicing sorrow and extreme displeasure toward Xi and his pals.   <br/><br/>Li has become a hero to Chinese people for his attempts to warn the public about the crisis in the early days, when the government was trying to cover it up. <br/>He was hospitalized January 12, 2020 and officially diagnosed with the you-know-what on February 1, 2020, before his passing was confirmed on February 6.<br/>According to the failing New York Times, #WeWantFreedomOfSpeech had at least 2 million views and 5,500 posts before fun-loving Chinese censors completely wiped them out of existence. <br/>But in the meantime, China will continue to keep hush hush at the expense of its citizens, all because saving face remains more important than saving ACTUAL lives.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/doctor-s-death-sparks-anger-toward-government-in-china-3961190</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961190/3961190_51E997DF9ABA4C3D8D1373B2C293256B_200210_3961190_Doctor_s_death_sparks_anger_toward_government_in_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 12:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961423</guid>
      <title>Rise in sulfur dioxide could be sign of mass cremations in Wuhan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Do you smell that? <br/><br/>Data from Windy.com on Feb. 9 showed a massive increase in levels of sulfur dioxide around the city which will remain nameless, causing some to speculate it could be a sign of mass cremation. <br/>Images from Windy.com shared over Twitter appear to show unusually high levels of sulfur dioxide being released, with no other city in China showing similar levels besides Chongqing. <br/>High levels of sulfur dioxide in the air is commonly associated with the burning of organic material. <br/>According to Taiwan News, as the number of no longer living continues to rise, there have been accounts and anecdotal evidence that crematoriums have been working in overdrive. <br/>On Sunday, Intelwave shared an image showing sulfur dioxide levels as high as 1,300ug/m^3 around the city.  <br/>For reference, the WHO recommends that a dosage of 500ug/m^3 should not be exceeded for more than 10 minutes. <br/>Intelwave then went through some possible explanations for the increased emissions, with the first being a power plant. Unfortunately, none of China's other power plants were displaying such high levels. <br/>A second possibility is that a lot of refuse and animal carcasses were being burnt. Yeah ok, maybe.<br/>The third possibility? Evidence is being disposed of on the outskirts of the city so that China can keep telling everyone that the flu is worse. Hmmmmmmm.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/rise-in-sulfur-dioxide-could-be-sign-of-mass-cremations-in-wuhan-3961423</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961423/3961423_08F5EBE8A3A246CF88D7EEFEBDCB9CE7_200211_3961423_Rise_in_sulfur_dioxide_could_be_sign_of_mass_cre_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 04:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961383</guid>
      <title>China silences whistleblowers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> After the death of a whistleblower doctor that led to hundreds of thousands of Chinese netizens demanding freedom of speech, little did they know, another unsung hero was about to go quite. <br/><br/>Chen Qiushi, a citizen journalist who had been doing critical reporting from the center of China's epidemic went missing on Thursday. <br/><br/>When friends and family could not locate him, they later learned from police that Chen had been forced into quarantine. <br/><br/>Chen's disappearance didn't go unnoticed and by Sunday netizens on Weibo began pleading for his release. <br/><br/>Chen had been in the outbreak epicenter since January the 24th, a day after the city was put under lockdown. <br/><br/>Chen had visited hospitals that were overwhelmed, funeral parlors and temporary isolation wards and filmed it all. He uploaded videos of what he saw to offer us a glimpse into the reality of the situation and reveal China's struggle to control the situation.<br/><br/>Fearing he could be detained at any moment for his reporting, friends checked in with him multiple times per day; but when Chen stopped picking up his phone they began to panic. <br/><br/>The following day, a message from his mother was posted to his Twitter account pleading for help.  <br/><br/>Chen was believed to have been in perfectly good health when he was forcibly detained. CNN contacted the Wuhan city police for information about Chen, however, they claim they had no information on him. <br/><br/>The latest incident is pushing China's censoring machine into overdrive; they're desperate to shape the narrative and it is through this desperation that its methods of suppression are being forced into the light. <br/><br/>Xi Jinping's government is getting reckless and will do anything to maintain the party's rule by iron fist, they fear free speech and will silence all whistleblowers and the house arrest of a nearly 90-year-old man illustrates that. <br/><br/>This is Dr. Jiang Yanyong, an 88-year-old retired military surgeon who became a national hero when he exposed the government's cover-up of the Sars epidemic back in 2003. <br/><br/>This so-called 'national treasure' was then detained and forced to undergo brainwashing sessions, or what China calls 're-education' when he wrote a letter to the government asking them to acknowledge that the 1989 student movement was a "patriotic movement."<br/><br/>Jiang's wife said, "He is not allowed to be in contact with people outside. He is at home. He has no means of communication with the outside. His health is not good. He is not in a good mental state either. He is not very well. I am sorry, it is not convenient to say more." <br/><br/>The free flow of information is the best weapon we have to stop this, so we have to ask ourselves, what exactly is China doing?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-silences-whistleblowers-3961383</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961383/3961383_EF2E824F90D14BB4AFE5E597BC764A82_200211_3961383_China_silences_whistleblowers_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 03:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961588</guid>
      <title>China goes into further lockdown as Wuhan coronavirus spreads</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> As China continues to struggle with their grave situation, some of its biggest cities are partially hanging up the "We're Closed" sign.  <br/><br/>Taiwan News reports that according to the Beijing Daily, Chinese officials said on Sunday Feb. 9 that Beijing was being locked down under "closed off management" measures. <br/>Authorities said the city would be strictly implementing "closed community management," under which vehicles and people from outside a community will be prohibited. <br/>Those coming to Beijing from other areas are required to report their health status and register their personal information. <br/><br/>According to the new regulations, the first 14 days while in lovely Beijing, people visiting from affected areas or have a history of recent contact with those in affected areas must undergo inspection and observation in their homes. <br/><br/>People must also actively provide health status updates and cooperate with relevant authorities. Oh yeah<br/>and they are not allowed to leave their quarters.  <br/><br/>If people refuse to accept hospital confinement, home confinement and other prevention measures, they get to be FORCED to accept it. <br/>All public areas in residential communities, like recreation rooms and sports areas are now off limits, and all businesses and government agencies must constantly monitor people's temperatures. <br/>In addition, there will be checkpoints at entrances and exits of residences, where people coming and going on foot and in vehicles must be masked up and have their temps checked.  <br/>Shanghai followed Beijing's lead on Monday, Feb. 10 and also said it would be introducing similar lockdown measures across the city's 13,000 residential complexes. <br/>  <br/>Beijing is home to more than 20 million people, while Shanghai is close to more than 24 million people. Can locking these cities down slow the spread?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-goes-into-further-lockdown-as-wuhan-coronavirus-spreads-3961588</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961588/3961588_1D9A08AB699D425D9071BA82AB33EB37_200211_3961588_China_goes_into_further_lockdown_as_Wuhan_corona_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 09:20:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961910</guid>
      <title>Chinese couple suspected to have virus rounded up like strays</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> As pretty much all of China remains on edge, authorities are taking increasingly fewer chances when handling new or suspected cases. <br/>Video posted to YouTube by Epoch Times on Feb. 6 shows how one amazingly unlucky couple was rounded up because they might have been sick. <br/>The footage starts out with the couple hugging each other while the woman cries loudly. They are surrounded by Chinese officials in pink hazmat suits and some dude with an umbrella. <br/>The camera then pans toward a pickup truck with a metal box in back reminiscent of something stray animals are tossed into.<br/>The next thing we see is the couple climbing up into the pickup and getting inside the box.<br/><br/>After getting sealed in, the woman is heard screaming at the top of her lungs as the hazmat guys prepare to drive off. <br/><br/>According to the Liberty Times, last week another Chinese man suspected of having the you-know-what outside the Shanghai airport was also kindly introduced to the box.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-couple-suspected-to-have-virus-rounded-up-like-strays-3961910</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3961910/3961910_312DB473D5EB4E5688FAABD538E77B75_200212_3961910_Chinese_couple_suspected_to_have_virus_rounded_u_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961895</guid>
      <title>Whistleblower who filmed coronavirus corpses arrested</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> China continues its mission. <br/>China has silenced the whistleblower who posted the now viral video showing the not living piling up outside a local hospital.<br/><br/>The Epoch Times reports that citizen journalist Fang Bin was arrested by police officers around 3 p.m. on February 10.<br/><br/>He had refused to come out of his apartment, so officers surrounded his home and blocked possible escape routes before firefighters eventually broke down his front door.<br/><br/>Netizens suspect his phone and home wifi were cut off before his arrest, which rendered him unable to post another video.<br/><br/>Fang, a traditional clothes seller, had been spurred to citizen journalism by a lack of reliable information. He visited local you-know-where hospitals and recorded what he saw. <br/> <br/>One video, where he spots 8 no-longer-around in a span of five minutes, went viral and caught the attention of Chinese authorities. <br/><br/>Masked men in hazmat suits came to his house later that day wanting to take his temperature and possibly put him in quarantine. He refused to open the door, but they barged in anyway.<br/><br/>Fang told the LA Times in a phone interview that he was detained by police and interrogated about the videos. He was told to stop "spreading rumors" before being released.<br/><br/>But Fang continued with his crusade, and told his followers that he would be posting a video every morning so people would know he was alright.<br/><br/>Plainclothes police officers, he said, were monitoring his every move, and he speculated that the only reason they haven't broken in is because his videos were attracting the world's attention.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/whistleblower-who-filmed-coronavirus-corpses-arrested-3961895</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3961895/3961895_BC598F62AE72435A99D2BFFED347B8CC_200212_3961895_Whistleblower_who_filmed_coronavirus_corpses_arr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 03:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962134</guid>
      <title>China has a coronavirus 'close contact detector' app</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> China has apparently launched an app that allows people to check whether they have been at risk of catching you-know-what. <br/>The BBC reports that the "close contact detector" tells users if they have been near a person who has been confirmed or suspected of having the thing that will remain nameless. <br/>Those identified as being at risk are advised to seal themselves up in their homes and notify local authorities, so they can come and lock you up. <br/>The technology is just another example of how invasive the Chinese government is with its 1984-esque surveillance of its population. <br/>To see if you're about to join the land of the not living, users just scan a QR code on their smartphones. <br/>After the new app is registered with a phone number, users are asked to enter their name and ID number. Every registered phone number can then be used to check the status of up to three ID numbers. <br/>According to state-run speakerbox Xinhua, the app was designed in a fun-filled collaboration with government departments and the China Electronics Technology Group Corporation and supported by data from health and transport authorities. <br/>Here's a question though, how exactly is this app supposed to function properly when the Chinese government is obviously lying about how many people have been infected and how many are now pushing up daisies?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-has-a-coronavirus-close-contact-detector-app-3962134</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962134/3962134_CFC256C8E8944F3CA7719A6AEA451751_200212_3962134_China_has_a_coronavirus__close_contact_detector__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 10:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962410</guid>
      <title>Massive flock of crows take over Chinese city during outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[XINING, CHINA <br/> This could be the end of days as we know it<br/>no seriously. <br/><br/>Video footage posted online by Epoch Times from the city of Xining located in the fantastic Qinghai province could be a sign that the apocalypse is right around the corner.<br/>As China continues to try and get a handle on the situation, cities around the country have turned into virtual ghost towns.<br/>And now with everyone hunkered down at home and most vehicles off the roads, the birds have come out to play. All of them it seems.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/massive-flock-of-crows-take-over-chinese-city-during-outbreak-3962410</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962410/3962410_6CD040F3A5834FFEB4708A7B6930AE40_200213_3962410_Massive_flock_of_crows_take_over_Chinese_city_du_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 04:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963131</guid>
      <title>Lying about Wuhan virus will kill your social credit score</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> With all the things Chinese people are worrying about with the you-know-what<br/>that's now being called you-know-whatever-19<br/>destroying your social credit score is now another one.<br/>According to state-run Xinhua, a bunch of Chinese provinces and cities are tossing people on the social credit blacklist for lying about symptoms and sneaking out of quarantine. <br/>If you're lucky enough to live in Anhui, Jiangsu or Jilin provinces, or the cities of Shanghai, Chongqing and Hangzhou, officials there have also approved guidelines to punish those concealing travel history to key hit regions or history of contact with confirmed or suspected patients. <br/>Apparently if you're caught, not only will you have to deal with Chinese legal consequences, but you'll also be blacklisted on the local credit information platform. <br/>On February 12, Hangzhou did just that to nine completely appreciative residents for one year. <br/><br/>Those nine people also got the privilege of being publicly shamed online with their full names and part of their ID card numbers posted, along with a full list of all the trouble they'll soon be in. <br/>Some Chinese have been forced to think outside of the seat like one woman who was caught at a Shanghai highway checkpoint hiding in the trunk of a car, so she could dodge quarantine. Let's just say she was unsuccessful. <br/>Maybe it's time for China to build a really big and really long wall to keep everyone from moving around<br/>oh wait.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/lying-about-wuhan-virus-will-kill-your-social-credit-score-3963131</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963131/3963131_8310E2548F814D58AD27B7C3B854F4FB_200214_3963131_Lying_about_Wuhan_virus_will_kill_your_social_cr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:40:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963128</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus misinformation as epidemic continues to grow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> TomoNews effed up. We here at TomoNews would like to apologize for publishing two stories that after further investigation were found to be untrue. <br/>On February 7, we published a story, "Tencent may have just leaked the truth," where it said a screenshot from Tencent's "Epidemic Situation Tracker" webpage appeared to show much higher estimates of those infected and killed by the Wuhan coronavirus. <br/>According to New Bloom Magazine, upon closer examination, Tencent's epidemic tracker has a link to a public database that anyone can access. <br/><br/>New Bloom reports that hundreds of Chinese web developers have been scraping data from the Tencent website to generate their own charts, taking screenshots of the main Tencent dataset at different times, and sharing them along with their source code. <br/>A search of all available datasets did not reveal any of the inflated figures appearing in the screenshot used for the original story.  <br/>A second story published on February 11 titled, "Sulfur dioxide cloud could be sign of cremations" was also found to be incorrect. <br/>In the story, we said data from Windy.com on February 9 appeared to show high levels of sulfur dioxide, which could be a sign of mass cremations. <br/>However, Windy.com does not display real-time empirical data. It is a forecasting tool which relies on projections from datasets like those at NASA's GEOS-5 model.  <br/>Historical trends can be plugged into the underlying model, but it cannot predict individual events. <br/>Both stories have since been removed. We apologize again for not doing our proper due diligence.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-virus-misinformation-as-epidemic-continues-to-grow-3963128</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963128/3963128_E0B5E7F19DA2415983D191E3F20673E2_200214_3963128_Wuhan_virus_misinformation_as_epidemic_continues_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964022</guid>
      <title>Quarantined North Korean official executed for public bath visit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORTH KOREA  <br/> That's some swift justice. <br/>A North Korean official has been introduced to the 'land of the not living' for going to a public bath when he was supposed to be under quarantine after coming back from China.<br/><br/>The trade official was quarantined under a policy that isolates anyone who has been to China or had contact with Chinese people; the country has taken measures to almost completely shut China off, with flights being reduced and road and rail links either closing or being heavily restricted.<br/><br/>North Korea's supreme ruler, Kim Jong-un has vowed to "rule by military law" against anyone who leaves quarantine without approval.<br/><br/>According to a South Korean outlet, the trade official was promptly arrested and then immediately dealt with. <br/><br/>World Health Organisation officials based in Pyongyang have not confirmed any cases; despite this, some South Korean media outlets have reported multiple cases and even possible deaths in the North.<br/><br/>State media report that the country's Red Cross Society has been deployed to monitor people with possible symptoms. <br/><br/>North Korea's KCNA report that the Red Cross Society is conducting 'information activities' in public places to introduce common medical knowledge. They say they want to encourage people to "give fuller play to the noble moral traits of helping and leading each other forward."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/quarantined-north-korean-official-executed-for-public-bath-visit-3964022</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964022/3964022_1CA06507618D4C0AB5C3FB84CCBBDB38_200217_3964022_Quarantined_North_Korean_official_executed_for_p_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964431</guid>
      <title>China's makeshift Wuhan virus hospitals aren't even full yet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> As China's latest saga was in its early days<br/>but already out of control<br/>to take the focus off their foot-dragging, the boys in Beijing decided to slap together a few prefabbed hospitals. <br/>At first, the Chinese boasted the first one, Huoshenshan, would be finished in a mere 6 days, leaving many westerners to complain that it often took 6 years just to get a simple road built in their home countries. But then 6 days, turned into 10. <br/>According to Business Insider, Chinese state media livestreamed frantic construction efforts with a bunch of aerial drone shots of excavators everywhere pushing around a lot of dirt paired with patriotic CCP-style tunes. <br/>The second makeshift hospital, Leishenshan, was completed in 12 days. <br/>And if you're wondering what kind of quality construction went into building these facilities? Here's a little taste. <br/>Anyways, Chinese officials claimed the two hospitals would have 2,600 extra beds for a health care system clearly stretched over its limits.<br/>Official speakerbox Xinhua even went so far as to call the quick construction, "Mission Impossible made possible."<br/>However, Business Insider reports that official Chinese data shows that as of Feb. 12, the facilities were running at less than half their projected capacity.  <br/>While Huoshenshan is now full, Leishenshan only had 416 patients out of a possible 1,600 capacity.  <br/>But let's be honest folks, would you want to stay at one of these places?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-makeshift-wuhan-virus-hospitals-aren-t-even-full-yet-3964431</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964431/3964431_24A3AC0B2F394F9697B5A4FC46F8BF2B_200218_3964431_China_s_makeshift_Wuhan_virus_hospitals_aren_t_e_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 23:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964499</guid>
      <title>Big Chinese developer slashes prices in Feb, March due to virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> One of mighty China's biggest developers is offering massive sales around the country on all of its properties in February and March. <br/>Reuters reports that China Evergrande Group<br/>the third-largest builder by sales in the country<br/>announced that they were offering a 25 percent discount for the rest of February.<br/>According to Reuters, the discount will then go down to 22 percent for the month of March. <br/><br/>The SCMP reports that the scale and amount they're slashing prices makes this a much larger campaign than Evergrande carried out last year. <br/>According to Evergrande's latest annual report, the company currently has 811 projects on sale. <br/>According to the SCMP, the company is trying to get a hold of some cash to help ease their finance crunch as home sales plunge across lovely China. <br/>Citing the China Real Estate Information Corporation, the SCMP said more than 110 cities in 12 provinces have told developers to shut down property sales offices. <br/>Many developers are getting hammered by tanking home sales, shrinking cash flow and a ton of loan repayments piling up. <br/>Reuters reports that an Evergrande official, who declined to be named because he or she isn't allowed to talk to the media, said the measures, "are routine marketing and there is  no specific reason for the price cut this time."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/big-chinese-developer-slashes-prices-in-feb-march-due-to-virus-3964499</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964499/3964499_BC30B13D895A4ADF95CF4B3D8F744A7A_200218_3964499_Big_Chinese_developer_slashes_prices_in_Feb__Mar_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 04:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964441</guid>
      <title>China implements new restrictions in Hubei province</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Beijing has now tightened restrictions across Hubei province amid the growing threat of the Wuhan virus.<br/><br/>Residents of Hubei province have been ordered to stay at home and aren't allowed to leave unless there is an emergency, BBC News reports. The government will allow one person from each household to leave their house once every three days in order to purchase food and other essential products.<br/><br/>Only one entrance will be kept open in residential buildings. The buildings will be guarded and only those residing in the building will be allowed to enter or leave.<br/><br/>Pharmacies, hotels, grocery stores and medical services will be open while other businesses in Hubei province will remain closed.<br/><br/>China has also banned the use of private cars on the streets of Hubei, though delivery vehicles carrying essential goods will be exempt from the ban.<br/><br/>Separately, the New York Times reports, Beijing has now ordered everyone returning to the capital city to quarantine themselves for 14 days in an attempt to contain the novel coronavirus.<br/><br/>According to CNN, the virus has already killed 1,775 people and has infected more than 71,000 people globally. 70,548 of these cases are in China. Outside of China, only five deaths have been reported: one in Hong Kong, Taiwan, Japan, the Philippines and France.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-implements-new-restrictions-in-hubei-province-3964441</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964441/3964441_2527D2190D9D457AB7020E26B22BD179_200218_3964441_China_implements_new_restrictions_in_Hubei_provi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 01:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964434</guid>
      <title>Chinese netizens compete in 'earphone wire waist' challenge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Chinese netizens have taken to wrapping their abs in earphone wires to demonstrate their fitness in an all-new bizarre internet trend. <br/><br/>The challenge comes as people are forced to isolate themselves during quarantine over fears of COVID-19; netizens have taken to the trend to deal with being cooped up. <br/><br/>The hashtag for the new internet craze has wrapped up some 76million views and plenty of submissions.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-netizens-compete-in-earphone-wire-waist-challenge-3964434</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964434/3964434_B990F1E11F764004B0B232397C6F8B98_200218_3964434_Chinese_netizens_compete_in__earphone_wire_waist_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965002</guid>
      <title>China deploys remote tanks and drones in the fight against virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE MIDDLE COUNTRY <br/> Technology is being called up to duty as you-know-where continues to deal with its little situation.<br/><br/>According to Pear Video, officials in the Shanxi city of Taiyuan have dispatched a couple of remote controlled mini tanks to spray a bunch of disinfectant in the streets<br/>which apparently keeps the road from catching a case of the sniffles. <br/>Community workers say the mini tanks had originally been used to spray pesticides in the orchards before they got the repurposing call.<br/>Sure, the tiny tanks can roll around down the streets, but they can also climb up onto the sidewalk and make sure the walkways also stay in good health. <br/>Each tank can carry 400 liters of disinfectant spray. <br/>Officials say the little guys can cover a lot more of the city than just hoofing it. <br/>Here's the thing. It probably makes a lot more sense to be disinfecting inside homes and apartments, rather than outside. <br/><br/>But then of course, you don't get the nice photo op to show the people you're doing everything you possibly can to keep them safe.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-deploys-remote-tanks-and-drones-in-the-fight-against-virus-3965002</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965002/3965002_C72AFEA1B0C1409B8F679630239CA8DB_200219_3965002_China_deploys_remote_tanks_and_drones_in_the_fig_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 04:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964946</guid>
      <title>Uighurs detained for beards, veils and internet browsing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> A leaked document that details the lives of thousands of Muslims currently detained in so-called 're-education' camps across China is just another example of how Beijing is punishing Uighurs for their religious beliefs. <br/><br/>A 137-page PDF file was allegedly leaked by a source inside Xinjiang. According to CNN, the document included information of more than 3000 individuals and listed details such as how often they pray, how they dress, whom they engage with and even how their own family members behave. <br/><br/>CNN sent a copy of the document to both the Chinese Ministry of Foreign Affairs and the local government in Xinjiang to see if either could verify its authenticity, however, neither responded. <br/><br/>The Chinese Foreign Minister, Wang Yi said that these  "concentration camps" are "fake news" and that he would gladly welcome any "international diplomat or media" to visit Xinjiang for themselves and see how harmoniously everyone lives together.<br/><br/>CNN attempted to visit the detention centers in Xinjiang but was blocked by the local government. <br/><br/>What other information can be found on these documents?<br/><br/>One row listed the case of a 38-year-old woman who was sent to one of these camps for one main reason, she was known to have worn a veil some years ago. <br/><br/>In another, a 28-year-old man was incarcerated for, "clicking on a web-link and unintentionally landing on a foreign website."<br/><br/>One man's father is shown to have been sentenced to five years for "having a double-colored thick beard and organizing a religious studies group." <br/><br/>The BBC details how a series of rows were dedicated to a 65-year-old man. His records show that his two daughters "wore veils and burkas in 2014 and 2015." He even had a verdict,  "continued training." <br/><br/>Do we trust the document? <br/><br/>One of the world's leading experts on China's policies in Xinjiang, Dr. Adrian Zenz, believes, yes we can.<br/><br/>"This remarkable document presents the strongest evidence I've seen to date that Beijing is actively persecuting and punishing normal practices of traditional religious beliefs."<br/> <br/>The BBC claim that much of the evidence they uncovered during a tour of one of these camps last year is, in fact, corroborated by this new document. <br/><br/>What is the biggest justification for a person's internment?<br/><br/>In the eyes of communist China, having too many children is the clearest sign that Uighurs put their traditions above their absolute obedience to the Chinese state.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/uighurs-detained-for-beards-veils-and-internet-browsing-3964946</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3964946/3964946_0B63900557044EA79C0F2E3A19317FC7_200219_3964946_Uighurs_detained_for_beards__veils_and_internet__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 02:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964932</guid>
      <title>Chinese farmer uses chickens to write out message of support</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GANSU PROVINCE, CHINA <br/> A farmer in China used his chickens to send out a message of support for the fight against you-know-what.<br/><br/>Shang Yukang is relatively famous on the Chinese web, having turned into an internet star after showcasing his daily life as a chicken farmer in rural Gansu province. <br/><br/>He's also known for making his chickens come together to form various characters and patterns, such as this cute display of "I love you."<br/><br/>Shang's latest video saw him using over a thousand of his feathery buddies to spell out "Zhong guo" &#8211; China &#8211; and "jiayou", which literally means "add oil" but is used as an expression of support or encouragement. <br/><br/>Shang told pear video he didn't have enough chickens to spell out all the characters at the same time, so he did "China" one day, and "jiayou" the next day.<br/><br/>As we all know, China is going through rough times these days with the-thing-Youtube-doesn't-want-named wreaking havoc all over, so this was Shang's way of cheering people on.<br/><br/>He has also very generously donated over 3,000 eggs from his own farm to medical workers on the front line.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-farmer-uses-chickens-to-write-out-message-of-support-3964932</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3964932/3964932_CAA90648CA164A54B0B2CE211A0EB3BC_200219_3964932_Chinese_farmer_uses_chickens_to_write_out_messag_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 02:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965487</guid>
      <title>Chinese authorities humiliating people for not wearing masks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Where's your mask? <br/><br/>As China's government desperately scrambles to show the world they can manage this new threat, local police forces are implementing some ruthless and quite frankly archaic orders from Beijing.<br/><br/>Shocking videos have emerged that show local authorities within China humiliating people for not wearing face masks.  <br/><br/>In response to these videos, the editor-in-chief of China's Global Times offered a some-what audacious response by claiming the videos, "gave the public a very bad impression" and meant the "personal rights of citizens&#8230; have been severely violated."<br/><br/>While the Chinese government is attempting to suppress negative coverage of its response to the threat, the masses of content flooding the internet of videos like these can not be stopped. <br/><br/>China's control of the narrative is slipping.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-authorities-humiliating-people-for-not-wearing-masks-3965487</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965487/3965487_BA2F4E7CF42B4A45A0457B12EAEDAE3B_200220_3965487_Chinese_authorities_humiliating_people_for_not_w_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 04:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965460</guid>
      <title>Largest Chinese COVID-19 study shows elderly, sick most at risk</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> Chinese authorities have published a study of COVID-19 patients across China &#8211; the largest one done on the disease so far.<br/><br/>According to data released by the Chinese Center for Disease Control and Prevention, 80.9 percent of COVID-19 cases have been mild, with patients exhibiting only mild pneumonia or none at all.<br/><br/>Thirteen point eight percent of infections were classified as severe, and 4.7 percent as critical, with the sick and elderly found to be most at risk.<br/><br/>The study also pointed out the high risk the outbreak presented to medical workers, 1,716 of whom have been diagnosed with the disease.<br/><br/>While men are more likely than women to get infected, children and teens aged 0 to 19 are not as affected, making up just 2 percent of those who contracted COVID-19.<br/><br/>Of the 44,672 confirmed cases used in the study, 1,023 had died as of February 11, which puts the crude death rate for the virus at 2.3 percent.<br/><br/>Hubei province was found to have a much higher rate at 2.9 percent, compared to 0.4 percent for the rest of China.<br/><br/>Patients with cardiovascular disease were found most likely to die of complications from the virus, followed by those suffering from diabetes, chronic respiratory disease, and hypertension.<br/><br/>The report finds that the epidemic peaked in January, and that a 'downward trend' in the overall epidemic curve since February 11 suggests China's aggressive containment measures have paid off.<br/><br/>It's important to remember though, that the CDC is a Chinese government entity, and that with people returning home from their long holidays, there may be a possible rebound of the epidemic.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/largest-chinese-covid-19-study-shows-elderly-sick-most-at-risk-3965460</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965460/3965460_8AAA2E1B53C94684B2F6423811496A88_200220_3965460_Largest_Chinese_COVID_19_study_shows_elderly__si_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 02:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965911</guid>
      <title>India builds wall to hide poor people during Trump visit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AHMEDABAD, INDIA <br/> Ahead of President Donald Trump's visit to India next week, Indian authorities decided to build a wall to welcome the big American cheese. <br/>No just kidding. They built it to hide a bunch of poor people and slums, so Trump won't have to look at it when his motorcade wizzes by it during his visit. Oh, how thoughtful of Prime Minister Narendra Modi.<br/>The Associated Press reports that a half-kilometer (1,640-foot) brick wall was thrown up in an awful hurry in India's Gurjurat state.<br/>According to the AP, Trump plans to hop over to Ahmedabad in Gujarat during a two-day India trip to attend an event called "Namaste Trump," which translates to "Greetings Trump" at a cricket stadium.  <br/>Trump and his motorcade accompanied by Modi are planned to drive along a road next to the slum.  <br/>Apparently, the wall was originally supposed to be 6 or 7 feet tall, but was chopped down to 4 feet after the government got blasted in public after widespread media coverage. <br/>Senior government official Bijal Patel told AP that the wall was built "for security reasons" and not to hide the slum. <br/>She also said, "apart from security reasons, the wall is also part of a beautification and cleanliness drive."   <br/>Here's the most important question though. Is Mexico going to pay for this wall too?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/india-builds-wall-to-hide-poor-people-during-trump-visit-3965911</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965911/3965911_39EC2B642E46453097F0352ADCED7FBC_200221_3965911_India_builds_wall_to_hide_poor_people_during_Tru_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 23:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965988</guid>
      <title>Police force mahjong players to carry table down the street</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE BEST COUNTRY <br/> So what do you do when you're stuck in your house for a couple of weeks with nothing to do in the greatest country on earth? You play mahjong of course. <br/>The only problem is, getting caught by the authorities means some good old fashioned Cultural Revolution style public shaming. <br/>Footage from Twitter's illegitimate cousin Weibo shows four people from the town of Hexin in Chongqing prefecture having a pleasant stroll down the middle of the street. <br/>Oh yeah, they're also lugging a mahjong table over their shoulders while being followed by a police car. <br/>And to get everyone pumped up and in the proper mood, an officer is kind enough to hope on the loudspeaker and scream super annoyingly that playing mahjong and cards is a no no. <br/>Naturally people were thrilled when the footage was leaked online, so a local government worker had to explain that it was not an example of "parading through the streets" but of "disciplinary action" <br/> by parading them through the streets. <br/>The fun police have actually cracked down on mahjong all over the country amid their latest struggles. Will it work? Wouldn't bet on it.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/police-force-mahjong-players-to-carry-table-down-the-street-3965988</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965988/3965988_395F3A51EA3C42628F66C0EC75487593_200221_3965988_Police_force_mahjong_players_to_carry_table_down_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 04:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965940</guid>
      <title>Shanghai lady breaks quarantine, nabbed for boozy behavior</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> A woman in Shanghai got herself in a whole lot of trouble after not only breaking quarantine, but also getting into a boozy fight with some security guards.<br/><br/>According to a Miaopai video, the lady had been under self-isolation in her Shanghai apartment, and sneaked out one night for a drink...or seven.<br/><br/>She came back totally sloshed and sans face mask, and began to get into a skirmish with the neighborhood guards over getting her temperature checked. In footage of the incident, the lady is seen being loud and aggressive, and ends up pushing one of the guards, who was REALLY not happy with her.<br/><br/>Cops were called to the scene, and the unruly woman was arrested and hauled off.<br/><br/>The best part is that once she got her bearings back, she realized she'd been trying to get into the wrong 'hood.<br/><br/>Shoulda stayed home, lady.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/shanghai-lady-breaks-quarantine-nabbed-for-boozy-behavior-3965940</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3965940/3965940_708D2C6096274079A7EAEC8977F5FEFD_200221_3965940_Shanghai_lady_breaks_quarantine__nabbed_for_booz_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 02:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966204</guid>
      <title>China created youth anime influencers, then deleted them</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE BEST COUNTRY <br/> With everything on the up and up in the fantastic Middle Kingdom, the Communist Youth League decided to introduce a pair of patriotic anime mascots on Feb. 17. <br/>According to the failing New York Times, the youth wing unveiled the two new anime influencers, but then got so pathetically hammered and criticized online that they quickly deleted them out of existence. <br/>The Times reports that the new, super short-lived avatars were styled like Japanese anime characters and were named Hong Qi Man and Jiang Shan Jiao, names derived from fun-loving dictator Mao's poetry.<br/>Apparently Jiang Shan Jiao, whose name translates into "lovable country," and her younger brother Hong Qiman, aka "fluttering flag," were meant to encourage patriotism among younger Chinese. <br/>After introducing the tag team on Twitter's ugly cousin Weibo, netizens immediately started criticizing the pair. <br/>Reuters reports that a lot of the negative comments were getting thousands of "likes," so they had to be removed by censors during the day on the 17th. <br/>By the end of the day, the post with the avatars was given the old Beijing bye-bye. Well, better luck next time guys.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-created-youth-anime-influencers-then-deleted-them-3966204</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3966204/3966204_1B7395B96A3F42FDA5A242335ACD6FA0_200221_3966204_China_created_youth_anime_influencers__then_dele_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 09:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967399</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How North Korea uses the Internet to prop up its regime</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOMERVILLE, MASSACHUSETTS <br/> North Korea is turning to cryptocurrency as a means to circumvent sanctions. In a published report, analysts at Record Future say the regime is investing in high end machines for mining Monero and the activity has increased tenfold since May 2019.<br/><br/>Recorded Future, which has ties to the CIA, says North Korea heavily regulates internet access and allows only elite military officials to use the Web. This makes Pyongyang's cyber traffic easier to sample and analyze. <br/><br/>North Korea also engages in cyber theft and espionage, including cryptocurrency theft, hacking enabled bank theft, and financial cybercrimes. Over the past four years, those activities generated $2 billion, a sum equal to 7 percent of North Korea's annual GDP.<br/><br/>According to the report, North Korea has three main ways to connect to the Internet, which is via its normal allotted IP, China-based Unicom, or Russia's satellite company SatGate Holdings.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-how-north-korea-uses-the-internet-to-prop-up-its-regime-3967399</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967399/3967399_0BB00C01BCAB44069D3FAF83AD5B0185_200224_3967399_Explainer__How_North_Korea_uses_the_Internet_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968178</guid>
      <title>Wuhan's blood curdling screams will haunt your nightmares</title>
      <description><![CDATA[THE MIDDLE KINGDOM <br/> That doesn't sound good. <br/><br/>Video posted to Chinese social media from the city on lockdown that shall remain nameless on February 22 is pretty bone-chilling.  <br/><br/>Just listen.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-s-blood-curdling-screams-will-haunt-your-nightmares-3968178</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968178/3968178_ECDCEF6EDCB14342AD2E61BAA2541409_200226_3968178_Wuhan_s_blood_curdling_screams_will_haunt_your_n_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 05:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968075</guid>
      <title>Shanghai police now using WeChat to handle car accidents</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> Shanghai traffic police announced last Friday that they will now be using WeChat to handle car accidents. <br/>According to the Shanghai Daily, let's say you are lucky enough to be able to drive at a time like this and you happen to get into a little fender bender. <br/>The cop in charge of the accident will set up a WeChat group with everyone that was involved and their insurance agents. <br/>Traffic authorities say evidence collection, exchanging of information and compensation will all be carried out in the chat group. <br/>If the police have any questions, the head officer will get in touch with relevant parties via video call on WeChat. If you don't have WeChat, you get sent to a camp<br/>that's not true. When WeChat isn't available, the police officer will make recorded calls.   <br/>Police will then take a picture of any court decision and send it over in case anyone wants to appeal. <br/>Chinese authorities say the reason for going online is to try to discourage citizens from face-to-face gatherings. That should be pretty easy for a city of 24 million people.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/shanghai-police-now-using-wechat-to-handle-car-accidents-3968075</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968075/3968075_350E5006C0AA456D90842C513E1A9C49_200226_3968075_Shanghai_police_now_using_WeChat_to_handle_car_a_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 03:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968062</guid>
      <title>China SWAT team practices using nets to nab COVID-19 victim</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TONGBAI COUNTY, CHINA <br/> China's got a new tool to take down uncooperative citizens suspected of being infected with you-know-what: fishing nets.<br/><br/>According to Storyful, footage of a mock drill was uploaded to Weibo by the Tongbai County Municipal Public Security Bureau.<br/><br/>The staged incident starts off with a masked driver being given a temperature check at a checkpoint in Henan province.<br/><br/>After presumably failing the temp check, two SWAT team members, one of whom is carrying a riot shield, are called in. They ask the man to get out of the vehicle and cooperate with the investigation, but he refuses and begins to drive off.<br/><br/>He's subsequently stopped by a police van, and when he gets out and strips off his face mask, more SWAT team members descend and pull him in with a net over the head.<br/><br/>The man is restrained, and the net over is head quickly replaced by what appears to be a black bag. After he's taken away, those at the scene are sprayed down with disinfectant.<br/><br/>In a post accompanying the video, the Tongbai security bureau wrote that the armed exercises were conducted in order "to win the epidemic defense."<br/><br/>Since Henan borders Hubei province, whose capital Wuhan is the epicenter of the outbreak, Sky News reports that authorities are on particularly high alert.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-swat-team-practices-using-nets-to-nab-covid-19-victim-3968062</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968062/3968062_131C5C757EA347AF9EC9132D82293E9D_200226_3968062_China_SWAT_team_practices_using_nets_to_nab_COVI_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 02:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968260</guid>
      <title>China's wildlife consumption ban explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> China announced on Monday that the country has banned the consumption and trade of wildlife with immediate effect amid the ongoing Covid-19 outbreak.<br/><br/>Hunting or transporting wild animals for eating purposes will also be prohibited under the ban. <br/><br/>Scientists in China suspect that the new coronavirus has spread from wild animals to humans, but this has not been proven yet.<br/><br/>This includes wild animals protected by law, terrestrial animals and terrestrial wild animals that are being raised in breeding farms, the South China Morning Post reports, citing the People's Daily. Animals such as civet cats, wild boars, deer, blue peacocks and pigeons will all be protected under the ban.<br/><br/>According to Reuters, these wild animals can be used for medical or scientific purposes but will be subject to inspection and strict examination.<br/><br/>Aquatic animals, livestock, poultry and other animals are exempt from the ban.<br/><br/>China's wildlife protection laws, which was brought into effect in 1989, included loopholes that allowed consumption of wild animals and captive breeding of wildlife for commercial purposes, the South China Morning Post reports.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-wildlife-consumption-ban-explained-3968260</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968260/3968260_CB92BFEC74AB4DE190467D48A4CBE0DC_200226_3968260_China_s_wildlife_consumption_ban_explained_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 08:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968549</guid>
      <title>China is hunting down Wuhan coronavirus critics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA <br/> As the Middle Kingdom continues to struggle controlling the narrative behind their latest gift to the world, it's now going after critics. The more things change, the more they stay the same. <br/>According to Vice, 28-year-old Chinese entrepreneur Joshua Left, from the city that shall remain nameless, arrived in San Fran in mid-January as the you-know-what was just blowing up. <br/>Worried about his family back home, he started sharing information most likely not available in lovely China over his WeChat. <br/>Left told Vice that he then received a warning message from WeChat administrators. <br/><br/>Then he started getting really specific messages from four WeChat friends, all asking him for his location, what hotel he was staying at in S.F., what his room number was, and what his U.S. phone number was.<br/>He then said his phone got a warning message that someone in Shanghai was trying to log into his account. <br/>When he refused, the same four WeChat friends then simultaneously began telling him to immediately come back to China. <br/>According to Left, he thinks his friends were probably forced by agents from the Ministry of State Security to try and get Left to give up his location.<br/><br/>It appears to be a part of a much wider effort by Beijing to crack down on people sharing real information about the you-know-whatever-19. Well, that's comforting.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-is-hunting-down-wuhan-coronavirus-critics-3968549</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968549/3968549_DA517F35E7A84DB083C6931844523BBC_200227_3968549_China_is_hunting_down_Wuhan_coronavirus_critics_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 23:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968602</guid>
      <title>China sentences HK bookseller to 10 years in prison</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Hong Kong bookseller Gui Minhai has just been sentenced to 10 years in Chinese prison, in what some say is a warning from Beijing that acts of resistance will be strictly punished.<br/><br/>CNN reports that 55-year-old Gui was put on trial by a court in Ningbo for "providing intelligence" overseas. According to a court statement posted online, he pleaded guilty to the charge and will not appeal.<br/><br/>Back in 2015, Gui, a naturalized Swedish citizen, disappeared from his holiday home in Thailand. Around the same time, four other Hong Kong-based booksellers went missing. <br/><br/>All were connected to Mighty Current Media, which published salacious books on President Xi Jin-pooh and the rest of China's ruling elite. They later surfaced in Chinese police custody.<br/><br/>In 2016, Gui appeared on Chinese state television claiming he returned to China voluntarily to face justice over a drunk driving incident over a decade earlier. <br/><br/>Chinese police announced he'd been released from custody a year later, but was not allowed to leave the county.<br/><br/>He was taken for a second time by 10 plain clothes policemen in 2018, while traveling on a train to Beijing with two Swedish diplomats.<br/><br/>Sweden has repeatedly called on China to free Gui, on the grounds that he is a Swedish citizen. But China warned Sweden not to interfere, and despite having a law that bans dual citizenship, officials claim Gui is "a Chinese national first and foremost."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-sentences-hk-bookseller-to-10-years-in-prison-3968602</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968602/3968602_1F26F66EF3D9473C8D016082210EFE32_200227_3968602_China_sentences_HK_bookseller_to_10_years_in_pri_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 03:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968585</guid>
      <title>Why COVID-19 infections surged in South Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DAEGU, SOUTH KOREA <br/> Coronavirus infection cases have surged in South Korea, with more than half linked to a religious cult whose secretive nature is said to have helped the virus spread undetected. <br/><br/>The Korean Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported 1,146 confirmed COVID-19 infections in the country as of February 26. Majority are located in the city of Daegu and neighboring Cheongdo county, where they are centered around a hospital and the Shincheonji church of Jesus.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports that the link to many of the cases is a 61-year-old woman known as Patient No. 31. Despite presenting a fever and sore throat, she initially refused to be tested for the virus, and attended several Shincheonji church gatherings before testing positive.<br/><br/>Church members sit packed together on the floor during services and are not allowed to wear glasses or face masks. Citing South Korean health officials, the BBC reports that any gathering in such a confined space attended by Patient No. 31 would likely have led to more infections.<br/><br/>Another cluster at a hospital in Cheongo has also been associated with the church. According to the New York Times, a large number of followers attended a funeral at a hall owned by the hospital. Over 100 patients and staff have since tested positive for the virus.<br/><br/>Health officials learned that Patient No. 31 had also been in Cheongdo in early February. She told Newsis she hadn't visited the funeral or the hospital, only a public bathhouse.<br/><br/>Shincheonji is considered a cult by many in South Korea, so members typically hide their membership from non church members. This, along with the belief that being sick is a weakness, has made it more difficult for authorities to track down those who have been infected, according to the BBC.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/why-covid-19-infections-surged-in-south-korea-3968585</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968585/3968585_097E52ED5B4842FCAD453AB5831EA485_200227_3968585_Why_COVID_19_infections_surged_in_South_Korea_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Asia</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 03:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
