<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:07:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3978556</guid>
      <title>Woman licks freezer handle to protest against coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MARSHFIELD, WISCONSIN <br/> A Marshfield Wisconsin woman was caught licking the door handle of a freezer at a supermarket in what she says was a protest to the coronavirus. <br/><br/>Seems like the #coronaviruschallenge isn't just something attention-hungry millennials and Gen Z kids are doing.<br/><br/>It's not just toilet seats and door handles that are being licked. According to a police report by the Marshfield Police Department, it appears that grocery store freezer door handles are also victims of human insanity.<br/><br/>According to the report, the store manager at a Festival Foods in Marshfield, Wisconsin was going about his day, sanitizing the door handles of freezers in the store <br/> you know doing his part in fighting a global pandemic <br/> when he spotted an odd woman in the section.<br/><br/>The store manager told police the woman, who was later identified as 53-year-old Nona Lindhorst, was staring him down and then, get this, proceeded to lean over and lick the handle of one of the freezer doors.<br/><br/>Of course, cops got involved, and when questioned by the police, the woman said that she had done it in protest to the coronavirus. Yes, you heard that right.<br/><br/>Do we really have to say it people? Don't go around licking toilet seats, door knobs, freezer door handles &#8230; or anything for that matter. What part of global pandemic do people not get?!<br/><br/>Luckily, the woman told police she hadn't 'protested' anywhere else. Police told her her behavior was quote 'uncalled for.' You think?]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/woman-licks-freezer-handle-to-protest-against-coronavirus-3978556</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/23/3978556/3978556_F093D4E1C9684AA3929AA956ACC4DB7B_200323_3978556_Woman_licks_freezer_handle_to_protest_against_co_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Satire</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 07:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979273</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus challenge: Man licks toiletries in supermarket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ST. LOUIS <br/> So, another coronavirus licking-related incident has happened. And no, we are not surprised or mad ... just, disappointed.<br/><br/>The St. Louis Post-Dispatch reports yet another video of another faulty human specimen went viral after he decided he wanted to be part of the 'licking things in exchange for internet points and validation' team.<br/><br/>The young man seemed to be intoxicated when he filmed himself in the toiletries aisle of a Walmart about an hour west of St. Louis, Missouri.<br/>He then pulled down his facemask and said to the camera, 'Who's scared of the coronavirus? Don't touch your mouth?'<br/><br/>While still filming he then proceeded to lean over and run his tongue all over the products captioning his video, 'I'm a nasty moths f***er', and yes, that's how he spelled it.<br/><br/>According to St. Louis Post-Dispatch, the Warrenton Police Department said in a statement on Monday the man has been taken into custody and charges are pending. Thank God.<br/><br/>Warrenton police said they received tips from concerned citizens around the world: "We have received numerous reports about the video from locals, nearby residents, as well as people from the Netherlands, Ireland, and the United Kingdom," the statement said. "We take these complaints very seriously and would like to thank all of those who reported the video so the issue could be addressed.<br/><br/>We are at a loss of words at this point. It's because of people like Missouri Man that we are in the situation that we are in. So for your own sake and for the sake of other people, wash your hands, stay home, and keep your tongue in your mouth.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-challenge-man-licks-toiletries-in-supermarket-3979273</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/25/3979273/3979273_82713A58D1BB406E85F785F36393FA17_200325_3979273_Coronavirus_challenge__Man_licks_toiletries_in_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Satire</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 03:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
