<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 18:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3983673</guid>
      <title>Man leads cops on 100 mph chase while letting his pit bull drive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LAKEWOOD, WASHINGTON <br/> A man was detained last Sunday after he decided he'd give his dog a driver's ed class that ended up in a high-speed police chase.<br/><br/>According to CNN, police were onto the driver after they received a call about him hitting two vehicles south of Seattle and then just driving away like nothing happened.<br/><br/>Little did the police know that this would become a 109 mile an hour high-speed chase between them and a white 1996 Buick.<br/><br/>Finally, while attempting to corner the crazed driver, a police trooper caught a glimpse of who was on the driver's seat. The answer? A pit bull. <br/><br/>You'd think that's where it would all end, but no, the man did not stop until troopers put out spike strips. That's when they learned the reasoning behind the reckless driving, the man was, "trying to teach his dog how to drive." Yes. That was his excuse.<br/><br/>Comedy aside, during the chase, the man, sorry, dog, drove onto a trail for pedestrians and cyclists that is usually pretty busy so things could've ended pretty badly. Thankfully, they didn't.<br/><br/>According to AFP, the pet driving instructor was later identified as 51-year-old Alberto Tito Alejandro and apparently he has a history of driving under the influence of drugs. We're not surprised.<br/><br/>Seattle state trooper and public information officer Heather Axtman told CNN, "I've been a trooper for almost 12 years and wow, I've never heard this excuse. I've been in a lot of high-speed chases, I've stopped a lot of cars, and never have I gotten an excuse that they were teaching their dog how to drive."<br/><br/>If you're worried about the real victim of the situation here, the cute pit bull who had to be subjected to this nightmarish class, she is doing well and currently chilling at a shelter.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/man-leads-cops-on-100-mph-chase-while-letting-his-pit-bull-drive-3983673</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/06/3983673/3983673_49EC0894E94D44E38D8AF380B98AFEA5_200406_3983673_Man_leads_cops_on_100_mph_chase_while_letting_hi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Satire</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2020 05:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985449</guid>
      <title>WHO chief accuses Taiwan of racism, Taiwan denies accusations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> During a press conference on Wednesday, World Health Organization chief Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus said he had been receiving racist comments and death threats from Taiwan for months. <br/><br/>Now, what's interesting to us here at TomoNews is that he said quote, "this attack came from Taiwan." Does he mean China? We're just saying because, you know, isn't Taiwan part of China in his world? Hmmm.<br/><br/>He also made it a point to say that the whole African community had been insulted by these comments and that he would not tolerate it. Wait till he hears about the Uighur internment camps in China.<br/><br/>Taiwan's Foreign Ministry replied to the allegations on Thursday in a statement saying that Taiwan understood quote, 'how he feels given that the 23 million people of Taiwan have long experienced the serious political discrimination of the international health system' end quote.<br/><br/>But I mean, let's not forget who really is behind this brawl. Yes, we mean Winnie the Xi.<br/><br/>For those of you who don't know, although Taiwan is clearly doing something well in terms of containing the spread of the coronavirus, it is still not allowed to participate in the WHO.<br/><br/>This is because China uses its economic clout to keep Taiwan from joining the organization. According to Beijing, "Taiwan as a province of China is completely not qualified and has no right to participate in it." And, as per usual, the rest of the world kowtows to China and follows its lead. <br/><br/>But no worries, guys. Taiwan has managed to fight its way through this pandemic without the WHO's help. According to data from Taiwan's Centers for Disease Control, since January there have been 380 confirmed cases and five deaths in this country of 23 million people. Much less than predicted and far less than China. So, yeah, you can keep that spot in the WHO, Xi, Taiwan doesn't need it.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/who-chief-accuses-taiwan-of-racism-taiwan-denies-accusations-3985449</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985449/3985449_A22CC67B128142EBA2440BA50E3961D8_200410_3985449_WHO_chief_accuses_Taiwan_of_racism__Taiwan_denie_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Satire</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 09:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985445</guid>
      <title>WHO chief accuses Taiwan of racism, Taiwan denies accusations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> During a press conference on Wednesday, World Health Organization chief Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus said he had been receiving racist comments and death threats from Taiwan for months. <br/><br/>Now, what's interesting to us here at TomoNews is that he said quote, "this attack came from Taiwan." Does he mean China? We're just saying because, you know, isn't Taiwan part of China in his world? Hmmm.<br/><br/>He also made it a point to say that the whole African community had been insulted by these comments and that he would not tolerate it. Wait till he hears about the Uighur internment camps in China.<br/><br/>Taiwan's Foreign Ministry replied to the allegations on Thursday in a statement saying that Taiwan understood quote, 'how he feels given that the 23 million people of Taiwan have long experienced the serious political discrimination of the international health system' end quote.<br/><br/>But I mean, let's not forget who really is behind this brawl. Yes, we mean Winnie the Xi.<br/><br/>For those of you who don't know, although Taiwan is clearly doing something well in terms of containing the spread of the coronavirus, it is still not allowed to participate in the WHO.<br/><br/>This is because China uses its economic clout to keep Taiwan from joining the organization. According to Beijing, "Taiwan as a province of China is completely not qualified and has no right to participate in it." And, as per usual, the rest of the world kowtows to China and follows its lead. <br/><br/>But no worries, guys. Taiwan has managed to fight its way through this pandemic without the WHO's help. According to data from Taiwan's Centers for Disease Control, since January there have been 380 confirmed cases and five deaths in this country of 23 million people. Much less than predicted and far less than China. So, yeah, you can keep that spot in the WHO, Xi, Taiwan doesn't need it.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/who-chief-accuses-taiwan-of-racism-taiwan-denies-accusations-3985445</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985445/3985445_9D5CBEE1CF414D71823450C3E3E2BA6E_200410_3985445_WHO_chief_accuses_Taiwan_of_racism__Taiwan_denie_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Satire</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 09:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
