<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 18:08:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3957959</guid>
      <title>A dwarf star's giant mass twists the fabric of space and time</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA <br/> In a new study published in Science, astronomer writes that a dwarf star in the Musca constellation has so much mass that it measurably distorts space and time.<br/><br/>According to OzGrav, the dwarf star's stellar companion, an exotic pulsar, courses around the bigger star in a speedy five-hour orbit.<br/><br/>Space.com reports that the white dwarf is the size of the Earth, but according to OzGrav, the star's mass and density is hundreds of thousands of times greater than our planet.<br/><br/>According to Space.com, the pulsar is the corpse of a star that had gone supernova and the dead star crushes protons and electrons to emit neutrons.<br/><br/>The white dwarf's powerful gravity and rapid spin cause frame-dragging, or distortions in space-time.<br/><br/>Frame-dragging imparts a wobbling effect on the pulsar and makes the neutron star twirl on its axis about 30 times an hour.<br/><br/>The drift in the pulsar's orbit is then picked up by Australia's telescopes, including Parkes, which allowed astrophysicists to corroborate Einstein 's theory of general relativity.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-dwarf-star-s-giant-mass-twists-the-fabric-of-space-and-time-3957959</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957959/3957959_585D5963557946D29B1BFD46F0048D52_200203_3957959_A_dwarf_star_s_giant_mass_twists_the_fabric_of_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 11:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957876</guid>
      <title>United Nations networks targeted by hackers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> Leaked documents from the United Nations reveal that the body's networks had been compromised by hackers last year.<br/><br/>Thirty-three servers were compromised at the United Nations Geneva headquarters while at least four were infected at the agency's Vienna office. The United Nations Human Rights Geneva office also had three of its servers compromised.<br/><br/>Hackers exploited a flaw in Microsoft's SharePoint software to infiltrate the United Nations' networks, the Associated Press reports, citing the report. Hackers were able to exfiltrate roughly 400 gigabytes of data.<br/><br/>According to the New Humanitarian, which had access to the documents, hackers may have been able to access internal documents, emails and databases from the United Nations.<br/><br/>The publication says staff records, health insurance and commercial contract information were also compromised. Staff members were asked to change their passwords but were not informed of the breach.<br/><br/>A UN official told the Associated Press that it was possible the cyber attack was state-sponsored as it appeared "sophisticated."<br/><br/>Technicians isolated the agency's data center from the internet and rebuilt its infrastructure and replaced keys and credentials to ensure network systems were protected, the Associated Press reports.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/united-nations-networks-targeted-by-hackers-3957876</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957876/3957876_E3825C382D5C49EA915CB20E9A6F7DE4_200203_3957876_United_Nations_networks_targeted_by_hackers_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 09:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3957815</guid>
      <title>Wuhan coronavirus symptoms clarified in new study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> A study published in The Lancet examined 99 of the earliest cases of the 2019 novel coronavirus, which first emerged in the Chinese city of Wuhan.<br/><br/>Science News reports that coronaviruses are one of a variety of viruses that can cause the common cold, as well as deadlier infections like SARS and MERS.<br/><br/>According to the Lancet study, the average age of infected patients was 55. Sixty-eight percent were male, half already had a preexisting chronic disease, and 49 percent had a direct connection to the seafood market where the virus is believed to have originated.<br/><br/>Fever and cough were the two most prominent and consistent symptoms of the virus, with most of the infected displaying these symptoms on admission to a hospital. Other patients exhibited shortness of breath, muscle aches, and headaches.<br/><br/>According to University of East Anglia Professor of Medicine Paul Hunter, the features and epidemiology of the Wuhan virus outbreak is similar to SARS.<br/><br/>The one big difference is a lack of upper respiratory symptoms like runny nose, sore throat, and sneezing, which can spread the infection.<br/><br/>By January 25, 31 of the patients in the Lancet study had recovered and been discharged, while 11 had died from the virus.<br/><br/>Most of the deceased were over 60 with pre-existing medical conditions, and died primarily from a critical form of respiratory failure called acute respiratory distress syndrome.<br/><br/>The study also found that similar to the SARS and MERS outbreaks, the virus had a higher infection risk to men than women.<br/><br/>Scientists hypothesized that women's reduced susceptibility to the virus could be due to protection from the X chromosome and sex hormones, which play a role in immunity.<br/><br/>According to China's National Health Commission, the novel coronavirus is contagious during its incubation period, before patients start showing visible symptoms. This incubation period lasts up to 14 days.<br/><br/>A case study recently published in The Lancet describes how a family in Shenzhen became infected with the virus after travelling to visit relatives in Wuhan, which verifies person-to-person transmission. <br/><br/>A child in the family remained without symptoms despite being diagnosed with the virus, which also suggests asymptomatic transmission is possible.<br/><br/>Because of this, researchers in the family study believe that to control the outbreak, patients need to be isolated, and those they came into contact with traced and quarantined. It's likewise paramount that health workers comply with infection control, and the public be educated on proper food and personal hygiene.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-coronavirus-symptoms-clarified-in-new-study-3957815</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/03/3957815/3957815_0BAD83E960E14B21A1828D18AD89D04C_200203_3957815_Wuhan_coronavirus_symptoms_clarified_in_new_stud_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 07:24:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958520</guid>
      <title>Vampire star unleashes blazing light while eating its companion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Astronomers have spotted a strange white dwarf star that devours its captive companion and blazes intense light in a rare event called a "super-outburst."<br/><br/>NASA published the study in Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society.<br/><br/>NASA says that the retired Kepler telescope, which revolved around the sun to search for exoplanets, had captured the archival footage that made this discovery possible."<br/><br/>According to NASA's news release, the brown dwarf circles around the stellar vampire every 83 minutes at a distance of 400,000 km.<br/><br/>The white dwarf is about the size of the Earth, but its mass is equivalent to the Sun.<br/><br/>The little star's huge mass creates a powerful gravitational pull that sucks in matter from the brown dwarf which forms an accretion disk.<br/><br/>According to NASA, current theory speculates that when the accretion disk reaches a critical mass, its outer edge experiences gravitation resonance with the orbiting star.<br/><br/>The resonance heats up the accretion disk, raising the temperature from a normal high of 5,300 degrees Celcius to a peak of 11,700 degrees.<br/><br/>The study says that the enormous heat build up results in the blaze known as the super-outburst in a repetitive process."<br/><br/>NASA further states that current theory does not explain why there is a long delay between each outburst.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/vampire-star-unleashes-blazing-light-while-eating-its-companion-3958520</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958520/3958520_24C2F212571242E09D8E1D048D24F9C1_200204_3958520_Vampire_star_unleashes_blazing_light_while_eatin_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 11:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958418</guid>
      <title>How plants are slowing down global warming</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOSTON <br/> Researchers from Boston University have found that increased vegetation growth, or greening, has effectively slowed global warming. <br/><br/>Greening usually involves intensive land use for farming, planting trees at a large scale or natural reforestation of lands that have been abandoned. The study found that roughly half of Earth's vegetated land has been greened due to this technique.<br/><br/>For the study, scientists analyzed satellite images from the 1980s to the 2010s. They noticed an increase of greening in China and India over the decades due to afforestation efforts.<br/><br/>As green leaves convert sunlight to sugar, carbon dioxide in the atmosphere is replaced with water vapor which cools Earth's surface. <br/><br/>In the study, researchers explained that global greening may have slowed the rate of global warming by roughly 0.2 to 0.23 degrees Celsius.<br/><br/>Study authors Shilong Piao and Xuhui Wang, explained in a Boston University news release that this provides "credible evidence" that human activities are dramatically impacting Earth's climate.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-plants-are-slowing-down-global-warming-3958418</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/04/3958418/3958418_EB969C02445F43DEBA9CBC4B36C3D067_200204_3958418_How_plants_are_slowing_down_global_warming_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958993</guid>
      <title>Discrimination could make people feel more physical pain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CORAL GABLES, FLORIDA <br/> A study published in Nature Human Behavior suggests that discrimination can change how different ethnic groups perceive and respond to pain. <br/><br/>The University of Miami says scientists gave pain stimuli to the participants' arm, then gauged their pain via MRI.<br/><br/>Researchers learned that when the same pain is applied by a heating device, African Americans reported more pain than Hispanic or non-Hispanic white American participants.<br/><br/>Scientists found that two areas of the brain <br/> the ventral striatum and ventromedial prefrontal cortex <br/> responded to pain more strongly in African Americans.<br/><br/>Those brain areas have been linked to chronic pain."<br/><br/>Since stressful experiences are correlated to chronic pain later in life, the researchers <br/>believe that stress from racial discrimination may cause increased pain sensitivity.<br/><br/>Yet data suggests that doctors tend to believe African Americans to be more pain tolerant, which might make them less inclined to alleviate black pain.<br/><br/>The research team writes in a statement: 'Understanding why these pain biases exist, therefore, is a key step toward ... eliminating racial and ethnic disparities in pain and its treatment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/discrimination-could-make-people-feel-more-physical-pain-3958993</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958993/3958993_7FF467B461BA43D6BB10BBEC6096D9A2_200205_3958993_Discrimination_could_make_people_feel_more_physi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 11:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958901</guid>
      <title>Google admits sending users' private videos to strangers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA  <br/> Google has admitted that a few of its users had their private videos on Google Photos sent to complete strangers because of a tech glitch. <br/><br/>This is because the search giant allows its users to download their data through a service called Google Takeout, the Verge reports. <br/><br/>The problem was discovered after users who downloaded their data discovered private videos from other users that didn't belong to them. Google says 0.01 percent of users were affected. The company did not specify the exact amount of people affected by the breach.<br/><br/>Users who had their videos compromised were in for a rude shock when Google sent out an email this month informing them that some of their videos were "incorrectly exported" to other users between November 21 to November 25 last year.<br/><br/>According to 9 to 5 Google, the company asked users who downloaded their data from Google Takeout to delete their previous export and to request new ones. The search giant also stated in the email that the issue has since been identified and resolved.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/google-admits-sending-users-private-videos-to-strangers-3958901</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958901/3958901_0D4818328BF64B0B835365C321D0A9D0_200205_3958901_Google_admits_sending_users__private_videos_to_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3958890</guid>
      <title>Red and processed meat linked to heart disease, early death</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EVANSTON, ILLINOIS <br/> A new study published in the journal JAMA Internal Medicine has found that eating two servings of red meat or processed meat every week is linked to a 3 to 7 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease and premature death.<br/><br/>The study included more than 29,000 participants who were asked about their dietary habits.<br/><br/>One of the study's authors said that it's worth trying to cut down on red meat and processed meat such as pepperoni, bologna and deli meats.<br/><br/>Scientists also found those who consumed two servings of poultry a week had a 4 percent higher risk of cardiovascular disease. Though researchers noted that this might be related to the cooking method of the chicken which may have been fried or due to consumption of chicken skin rather than chicken meat itself.<br/><br/>The study did not find any association between eating fish and cardiovascular disease or early death.<br/><br/>The researchers recommended consuming fish, seafood and plant-based protein sources such as nuts, legumes, beans and peas as healthier alternatives.<br/><br/>The study's findings are in stark contrast to a meta-analysis published just a few months ago which claimed that there was no need for people to reduce their intake of red meat or processed meat for good health.<br/><br/>Nutritionists at NutriRECS said at the time that their analysis did not find "any certainty that eating red meat or processed meat causes cancer, diabetes or heart disease," CNN reports.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/red-and-processed-meat-linked-to-heart-disease-early-death-3958890</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3958890/3958890_513C686D79C54BB695D862189DF7D8F3_200205_3958890_Red_and_processed_meat_linked_to_heart_disease___2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 09:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959019</guid>
      <title>U.S. creates first ever coupled quantum dots</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GAITHERSBURG, MARYLAND <br/> Coupled quantum dots <br/> which act like artificial atoms that share an electron <br/> could potentially form a robust qubit to revolutionize computing.<br/><br/>According to a study in Physical Review B, scientists have created the first ever pair of this substance.<br/><br/>The U.S. National Institute of Standards and Technology says that classical computers are made of binary bits that store information as fix values of either one or zero.<br/><br/>Qubits can take on multiple values simultaneously, which enables quantum computers that utilize qubits to perform larger and more complex tasks.<br/><br/>To create the coupled quantum dots, NIST researchers hovered a scanning tunneling microscope above a sheet of graphene with an underlying layer of boron nitride.<br/><br/>The STM's electrical charge penetrates the graphene and releases electrons from the boron nitride, which the graphene then captured. <br/><br/>Afterward, the team applied a magnetic field on the microscope's tip and forced the electrons to take up residence in two concentric rings.<br/><br/>This process leads to the creation of the coupled system, but the research team states that they are unable to explain their success with the current state of quantum theory.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-creates-first-ever-coupled-quantum-dots-3959019</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/05/3959019/3959019_F67C9ED0F788483EB0988CFB9608F2CA_200205_3959019_U_S__creates_first_ever_coupled_quantum_dots_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 12:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959504</guid>
      <title>Pluto's frozen heart pumps out nitrogen wind</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> According to a study in the Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets, Pluto's frozen heart of nitrogen ice may be the main driver of the dwarf planet's winds. <br/><br/>Pluto's heart shaped Tombaugh Regio is a vast structure made of nitrogen ice and its left lobe Sputnik Planitia contains 1,000 km of ice sheet within its 5 km basin.<br/><br/>During the day, a thin layer of the frozen nitrogen evaporates in relative heat; at night, the gas condenses and returns to icy form.<br/><br/>The sequence pumps nitrogen wind through Pluto's atmosphere like rhythmic heartbeats.<br/><br/>As nitrogen in Tombaugh Regio vaporizes in the north and freeze into ice in the south, the process triggers a westerly wind.<br/><br/>Citing the study's authors, Phys.org says this behavior is unique in the entire solar system with perhaps the exception of Neptune's moon Triton.<br/><br/>The study's other discovery is that Sputnik Planitia's high cliffs trap winds within the basin before releasing the strengthened currents to the west.<br/><br/>The atmospheric movement is similar to certain wind patterns on Earth, such as the Kuroshio in Eastern Asia.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/pluto-s-frozen-heart-pumps-out-nitrogen-wind-3959504</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959504/3959504_3596A0D465A7460D9260DC75F095C0B8_200206_3959504_Pluto_s_frozen_heart_pumps_out_nitrogen_wind_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3959332</guid>
      <title>Fireflies threatened by artificial light, habitat loss: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEDFORD, MASSACHUSETTS <br/> A joint study by Tuft University and the International Union for the Conservation of Nature has found that fireflies are being threatened by habitat loss, light pollution and pesticide use.<br/><br/>Researchers surveyed 49 firefly experts from around the world in order to get a better understanding of prominent threats faced by roughly 2,000 different firefly species.<br/><br/>Habitat loss was believed to be the largest threat to fireflies worldwide as their habitats are shrinking due to loss of land. <br/><br/>Artificial light pollution is the second largest threat to fireflies globally as it interferes with their natural light which is used for communication and mating purposes. <br/><br/>The use of pesticides was regarded to be the third largest threat as it is harmful to insects that fireflies consume for survival.<br/><br/>Study author Sara M. Lewis, told the Washington Post that this was the first time a comprehensive list of threats, based on expert opinions, has been written about fireflies from around the world.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/fireflies-threatened-by-artificial-light-habitat-loss-study-3959332</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/06/3959332/3959332_15F5CD16E26E41CA9FC1C3B57A56075A_200206_3959332_Fireflies_threatened_by_artificial_light__habita_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 07:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3960041</guid>
      <title>Why cruise ship passengers are falling to diseases</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YOKOHAMA, JAPAN <br/> Thousands of travelers are stranded on cruise ships after coronavirus cases were discovered on board.<br/><br/>CNN reports that the World Dream cruise ship is quarantined at the port of Hong Kong, while the Diamond Princess is kept at bay in Yokohama by Japan.<br/><br/>According to Live Science, the confined spaces of a cruise ship provide almost the ideal environment for viruses that rely on person-to-person contact to thrive.<br/><br/>Coughing and sneezing, contaminated water and shared food onboard are all potential paths of infection."<br/><br/>For instance, a trace amount of feces in the food or water can infect any passenger that dined in the buffet.<br/><br/>Some pathogens can linger on surfaces that an infected person touched and transmit to the next victim.<br/><br/>Not only that crews have limited time to sterilize the ship between cruises, but certain viruses including the norovirus can survive  bleaching even by a 10 percent solution.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/why-cruise-ship-passengers-are-falling-to-diseases-3960041</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/07/3960041/3960041_11B40482D41940D79F27DE9F8F6D65C4_200207_3960041_Why_cruise_ship_passengers_are_falling_to_diseas_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 11:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961117</guid>
      <title>7-Eleven trials cashier-less convenient store</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRVING, TEXAS <br/> 7-Eleven has announced a trial of a cashier-less store in Irving, Texas starting this week. <br/><br/>During the trial period, the store will only be open to 7-Eleven employees.<br/><br/>Customers shopping at the store will need to download and sign up for an app then use it to check-in at the cashier-less store, according to a press release from the company.<br/><br/>The convenience store will offer an array of products including beverages, food, groceries and also over-the-counter drugs.<br/><br/>Once the customer has finished shopping, the app will be used to make payments and customers can view their receipt once they have exited the store.<br/><br/>7-Eleven did not mention in its press release how long the trial is expected to last.<br/><br/>The company had previously launched a Mobile Checkout feature which allowed customers to skip waiting in line and instead pay for products using their smartphones in selected stores.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/7-eleven-trials-cashier-less-convenient-store-3961117</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961117/3961117_2354B19A86F645489947631C70380159_200210_3961117_7_Eleven_trials_cashier_less_convenient_store_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 10:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961084</guid>
      <title>Asteroid will fly very close to Earth this Saturday: NASA</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA warned that asteroid 2002 PZ39 will approach Earth on Saturday.<br/><br/>This asteroid is moving at a speed of nearly 55,000 km per hour relative to Earth and has a diameter of between 440 meters to 990 meters.<br/><br/>According to NASA, should a rocky asteroid bigger than 25 meters but smaller than 1 km were to hit Earth, the meteorite would likely cause local damage to the impact area.<br/><br/>A meteorite larger than one or two kilometers in size would be capable of worldwide effects.<br/><br/>Business Insider reports that most asteroids occupy orbits between Jupiter and Mars, so they pose little danger to the Earth.<br/><br/>The outlet adds that 2002 PZ39 is one of the rare exceptions.<br/><br/>NASA considers this asteroid a near Earth object and estimates that it will miss earth by a margin of 15.2 lunar distances <br/> or 5.8 million km <br/> at 11:00 pm on February 15.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/asteroid-will-fly-very-close-to-earth-this-saturday-nasa-3961084</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/10/3961084/3961084_52EB46003B8A4382B9BDC0DEB4F89946_200210_3961084_Asteroid_will_fly_very_close_to_Earth_this_Satur_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 09:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961624</guid>
      <title>Melting Arctic ice might make Europe colder</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GREENBELT, MARYLAND <br/> A NASA study says that human caused climate change is rapidly melting arctic ice and disrupting ocean currents, which could make Western Europe cooler.<br/><br/>The new study was conducted over 12 years and published in Nature Communication."<br/><br/>"The Beaufort Gyre is a current that previously kept the Arctic waters cold and protected sea ice.<br/><br/>However, the glut of cold fresh water is making the gyre spin stronger and faster, and the natural reversal of the spin's direction has not happened for over 10 years.<br/><br/>Researchers say that if the westerly wind guiding the current should reverse its direction now, the cold water build up could be unleashed at all once.<br/><br/>The cold tide may well slow down the Atlantic currents that bring warmth to Western Europe.<br/><br/>Citing the researchers, NASA says in its news release that disruptions to the Gulf Stream would have a negative impact on ocean life and the communities that depend on them.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/melting-arctic-ice-might-make-europe-colder-3961624</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961624/3961624_B3F4B1418E06457182E12107C8C2277D_200211_3961624_Melting_Arctic_ice_might_make_Europe_colder_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 10:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3961601</guid>
      <title>Locust plague threatens Somalia and eastern Africa</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GAROWE, SOMALIA <br/> The U.N. has warned that Somalia and the rest of east Africa may soon be facing a severe locust plague.<br/><br/>A report by the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations says that young locusts are threatening pastures and crops in Somalia. The insects are said to threaten more than 10 million people in the region.<br/><br/>These young locusts are expected to mature and develop wings in the coming weeks. They are then expected to make their way to Ethiopia and Kenya.<br/><br/>Somalia has become the first country in east Africa to declare an emergency over locust infestation, BBC News reports. <br/><br/>Kenya and Ethiopia are already taking precautionary measures by using planes to spray pesticides to prevent a locust outbreak.<br/><br/>The locust outbreak follows a period of unusually heavy rains and a powerful cyclone off the coast of Somalia at the end of 2019, the Associated Press reports, citing climate experts. <br/><br/>According to the report, more rains are expected in the next few weeks. This means that the number of locusts could increase.<br/><br/>Dominique Burgeon, the Food and Agriculture Organization's emergency and resilience director, explained another generation of the insect could now even be born in regular moisture conditions due to the high density of locusts.<br/><br/>He said that without enough planes spraying to stop the locust swarms, the outbreak may even turn into a plague, which could take years to control.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/locust-plague-threatens-somalia-and-eastern-africa-3961601</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/11/3961601/3961601_384B1EF78CA9459CB18C8160505E47F3_200211_3961601_Locust_plague_threatens_Somalia_and_eastern_Afri_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 09:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962130</guid>
      <title>New MRI tracer could make cancer much easier to spot</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA <br/> Researchers claim that a new MRI contrast agent could be a "game changer" for the early detection of metastasizing cancers, especially liver cancer. This study was published in Science Advances on Feb. 5.<br/><br/>The paper focused on a form of eye cancer that can migrate to the liver during the early stages of metastasizing. Georgia State University's news release states that current tests often do not detect liver cancer before advanced stages.<br/><br/>The research team applies the metal element gadolinium to the contrast agent's protein. This allows the MRI to accurately detect overexpression of receptors called CXCR4 in cancerous organs, even during early stage metastasis.<br/><br/>According to the paper, the contrast agent has been tested in mice, but the university says that the substance can identify multiple types of cancer cells and the FDA is fast tracking human trials, which could begin in 18 months.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-mri-tracer-could-make-cancer-much-easier-to-spot-3962130</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962130/3962130_141E87384A694A1CB5E3E62B08CABA3E_200212_3962130_New_MRI_tracer_could_make_cancer_much_easier_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 10:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962035</guid>
      <title>North Korea is still making bombs</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PYONGYANG, NORTH KOREA <br/> North Korea has continued development of its nuclear and missile programs, according to a confidential United Nations report seen by Reuters.<br/><br/>The country conducted 13 missile tests last year and launched roughly 25 missiles. This included new short-range and submarine-launched ballistic missiles, according to the report. It mentioned that North Korea has continued to "develop infrastructure and capacity" to enhance its missile program.<br/><br/>The U.N. report says that the country also exported tons of commodities such as coal using Chinese barges, even though North Korea has been banned from doing so since 2017. <br/><br/>DPRK-flagged vessels would transfer over the commodities to local Chinese barges, a method known as ship-to-ship transfer, which would then deliver the goods to ports in Hangzhou Bay and the Yangtze River in China.<br/><br/>In a statement, China called the accusations "baseless," and said that it is implementing U.N. sanctions against North Korea.<br/><br/>According to the report, North Korea also continued to illegally import refined petroleum using the same method.<br/><br/>The country has been allowed to import 500,000 barrels of refined petroleum under current sanctions, but the report found that North Korea exceeded the limit "many times over," between January 1 and October 31 of last year, reports Reuters. <br/><br/>North Korea's allies, Russia and China, have both raised concerns saying that the U.N. sanctions are causing harm to civilians in North Korea, according to Reuters. The United States, France and Great Britain have all said that sanctions should not be lifted.<br/><br/>North Korea has been sanctioned by the United Nations since 2006, Reuters reports. Members of the U.N. security council have imposed harsher sanctions against the country over the years to deprive the country of funding for its nuclear and ballistic missile programs.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/north-korea-is-still-making-bombs-3962035</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/12/3962035/3962035_296F01A607184A7F8F45CC587DE4A646_200212_3962035_North_Korea_is_still_making_bombs_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 08:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962449</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus can survive on surfaces for up to 9 days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GERMANY <br/> New analysis shows that many human coronavirus strains can stay infectious on inanimate surfaces for up to 9 days.<br/><br/>The 2019 novel coronavirus is a droplet-based infection that can be spread through direct person-to-person transmission or by touching contaminated surfaces. <br/><br/>These include door knobs or handles, bedside tables and chairs, call buttons, and other objects around an infected patient.<br/><br/>A report published in the Journal of Hospital Infection looked at 22 studies on different coronaviruses and found that human coronaviruses such as SARS and MERS can survive on glass, plastic, and metal surfaces for up to 9 days.<br/><br/>According to Professor Gunter Kampf, from the Institute of Hygiene and Environmental Medicine at Germany's Greifswald University Hospital, low temperature and humidity can increase the viruses' lifespan.<br/><br/>Fortunately, the research also found that disinfectants such as ethanol, hydrogen peroxide, or sodium hypochlorite can easily kill the viruses within just one minute.<br/><br/>While the study focused on other types of coronaviruses like SARS and MERS, researchers predict the findings may also be applicable to the 2019-nCov.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-can-survive-on-surfaces-for-up-to-9-days-3962449</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962449/3962449_6334987814A849C789693D1785D3382F_200213_3962449_Coronavirus_can_survive_on_surfaces_for_up_to_9__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 05:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962635</guid>
      <title>NASA's Mars 2020 rover will sport a laser that vaporizes rocks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> First 150 characters of description should repeat as many keywords from title as possible. Do not exceed 150 characters in first graf. This is so that the subscribe link appears above the dropdown bar.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-s-mars-2020-rover-will-sport-a-laser-that-vaporizes-rocks-3962635</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962635/3962635_42709C6281A84C05B2B05FBF9655E21A_200213_3962635_NASA_s_Mars_2020_rover_will_sport_a_laser_that_v_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 10:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962601</guid>
      <title>New coronavirus might spread through sewage pipes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> A Hong Kong woman fell victim to the new coronavirus after a man residing 10 floors directly above her unit became sick. The South Morning China Post reports on Tuesday that the new cases suggest building pipes could be a path for the virus.<br/><br/>Citing the WHO, Live Science reports that the coronavirus which causes SARS could get into feces and infect people through leaky pipes because compromised sewage pipes could allow pathogens to move into the surrounding air.<br/><br/>Toilets have a u-shaped drain to trap fluids and odor. However, the Washington Post reported in 2003 that faulty plumbing can cause backwash from toilets, which led to a SARS outbreak at another residential tower in Hong Kong.<br/><br/>Citing an infectious disease expert, Live Science explains that the new virus, now named COVID-19, could in fact transmit via feces, although aerosols from coughing and sneezing are still believed to be the main infection mechanism.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-coronavirus-might-spread-through-sewage-pipes-3962601</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962601/3962601_44F4E06CB25347BABCAC7C72006A75A2_200213_3962601_New_coronavirus_might_spread_through_sewage_pipe_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 09:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962538</guid>
      <title>Global CO2 emissions plateaued last year: Report</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS <br/> A new report by the International Energy Agency has found that global carbon emissions flattened in 2019, following two years of increased emissions. The U.S. also decreased its carbon emissions by 2.9 percent last year.<br/><br/>This is because advanced economies, such as Australia, Canada, Japan and South Korea, increased their use of renewable resources such as wind and solar power, according to the report. <br/><br/>The report also found that a rise in nuclear power and a weaker demand for electricity resulted in lower carbon emissions.<br/><br/>In comparison, usage of coal-fired plants in advanced economies last year had declined by nearly 15 percent.<br/><br/>The report also found that carbon emissions rose sharply in southeast Asia due to an increased demand of coal. China and India were found to have moderate emissions growth in 2019 due to slower economic growth and an increase in usage of renewable energy.<br/><br/>In a statement, Fatih Birol, the International Energy Agency executive director, said that the halt in carbon emission growth provides optimism that climate change can be tackled this decade.<br/><br/>A separate report from the United Nations stated that global emissions would have to be reduced by 7.6 percent every year until 2030 to prevent temperatures from rising to dangerously high levels which would "increase the frequency and intensity" of climate change.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/global-co2-emissions-plateaued-last-year-report-3962538</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/13/3962538/3962538_AD8437BFCD464A94A5C9A51DC8BFEDFC_200213_3962538_Global_CO2_emissions_plateaued_last_year__Report_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 08:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3962830</guid>
      <title>Crew of Diamond Princess ship at greater risk of COVID-19 infection</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YOKOHAMA, JAPAN <br/> As quarantine on the Diamond Princess cruise ship continues, crews may be facing a greater risk of coronavirus infection.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports that at least 219 people aboard the Diamond Princess cruise ship currently docked in Yokohama port have been infected with the novel coronavirus, or COVID-19.<br/><br/>Those who tested positive for the virus have disembarked and been sent to local hospitals.<br/><br/>CNN reports that passengers and crew have been quarantined on the ship since February 4.<br/><br/>Passengers are asked to wear masks and stay in their cabins. Meals are delivered to their rooms. They are also permitted to walk the decks for a few minutes each day, but must keep a distance of at least six feet from other passengers.<br/><br/>The ship's crew, meanwhile, continue to live and work in close proximity to each other and the passengers, which can mean potential contact with those who are infected.<br/><br/>Harvard University professor of immunology Eric Rubin told CNN that keeping everyone on the ship poses a greater infection risk for the crew. 10 crew members who recently tested positive for the virus stayed in shared cabins and ate meals in the mess hall alongside other employees.<br/><br/>According to the New York Times, it isn't clear how many people on the ship have the virus, because Japanese officials have only tested 439 of the 3,700 passengers for infection, reasoning that there is a shortage of testing supplies. <br/>The current quarantine period is scheduled to end on February 19, unless there are any "unforeseen developments."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/crew-of-diamond-princess-ship-at-greater-risk-of-covid-19-infection-3962830</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3962830/3962830_7BB2FEC58A6548BC90F66B80458FD610_200214_3962830_Crew_of_Diamond_Princess_ship_at_greater_risk_of_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2020 16:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963152</guid>
      <title>Mars formation may have taken a lot longer than previously thought</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN ANTONIO, TEXAS <br/> The early solar system was a chaotic place with many large-scale collisions. A new study in Science Advances argues that such collisions involving Mars could be why scientists are underestimating the red planet's age.<br/><br/>According to the Southwest Research Institute, Martian meteorites' tungsten content are highly varied. Since tungsten migrates from a planet's mantle to its core during formation, scientists are led to believe that Mars formed rapidly in 2 to 4 million years.<br/><br/>However, the institute's researchers say Mars is known to have experienced large collisions in its early formative history. According to their models, this would have scrambled Mars's mantle and created a heterogeneous, marbled structure.<br/><br/>Subsequently, when later collisions on Mars sent meteorites to Earth, the debris would have contained an uneven quantity of tungsten. Using the new models, the paper's authors claim that Mars may have taken 20 million years to become fully formed.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mars-formation-may-have-taken-a-lot-longer-than-previously-thought-3963152</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963152/3963152_CC5C5F2521C14023A1D1A1E11ECBE940_200214_3963152_Mars_formation_may_have_taken_a_lot_longer_than__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 09:55:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3963269</guid>
      <title>Using old mattress foam to grow plants</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZAATARI, JORDAN  <br/> Researchers from the University of Sheffield have found a way to use foam from abandoned mattresses to grow plants and vegetables for those living in the Zaatari refugee camp in Jordan.<br/><br/>In a news release from the university, researcher Tony Ryan explained that the mattress foam supports the plant while water and nutrient solution are pumped into the foam to allow the plant to grow. This system is called hydroponic farming and involves plants that are supported artificially and do not use soil.<br/><br/>According to Jordanian law, refugees aren't allowed to grow plants in the ground or build permanent structures while living in these camps.<br/><br/>In order to allow large-scale farming, researchers built a plastic piping system and put it on a rack. The piping system has numerous openings in which recycling yogurt pots holding the mattress foam and plants are put inside. Nutrient solution is added and flows through to the plants, helping them to grow and produce crops.<br/><br/>This gives the refugees the opportunity to grow fresh vegetables which can be used for cooking their own meals, according to the researchers.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/using-old-mattress-foam-to-grow-plants-3963269</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/14/3963269/3963269_BC6F42CA11954BA2BE0BF325E9D86797_200214_3963269_Using_old_mattress_foam_to_grow_plants_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 12:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964033</guid>
      <title>New Horizons probe of Arrokoth reveals how planets are formed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> New Horizons' flyby of the most distant object ever visited has revealed the secrets to how planets are formed.<br/><br/>MIT Technology Review reports that there have been two theories for planet formation. The first more prominent theory, hierarchical accretion, is when smaller objects collide at high speeds until they form a larger structure.<br/><br/>The second theory, called cloud collapse, is when concentrations of matter collapse or gently clump together at low speeds.<br/><br/>NASA's New Horizons spacecraft ventured to Kuiper Belt in the outer reaches of our solar system, it conducted a flyby of an ancient planetesimal named Arrokoth.<br/><br/>Three studies published in the journal Science analyzed the high-resolution photos of Arrokoth taken by New Horizons  and found no evidence of violent impact, indicating that there was instead a gentle accumulation of matter.<br/><br/>Simulations based on the new data suggest that Arrokoth's two parts formed independently from the collapse of the same cloud, and eventually gently merged together.<br/><br/>More data collected during the Arrokoth flyby has yet to be downloaded and analyzed &#8211; a task which scientists say may take another year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-horizons-probe-of-arrokoth-reveals-how-planets-are-formed-3964033</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964033/3964033_AD45FB07B5804FEC975F6C5E2CACA2C5_200217_3964033_New_Horizons_probe_of_Arrokoth_reveals_how_plane_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 01:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964237</guid>
      <title>China says plasma of recovered patients may help treat COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Could this help?<br/>Chinese researchers say blood plasma from recovered patients may help other COVID-19 patients to survive.<br/><br/>China National Biotec Group said it is taking plasma taken from recovered COVID-19 patients to treat those who are critically ill. The state-owned pharmaceutical made those remarks in a news release dated Feb. 13.<br/><br/>The group claims a round of the treatment improved the patient's condition significantly after 12 to 24 hours, including reduced inflammation and improved blood oxygen levels, lymphocyte counts, and reduced viral load.<br/><br/>Citing an unnamed expert, the group states that this plasma contains special antibodies which were used to treat COVID-19 in the critically ill.<br/><br/>The group says the procedure was tested successfully in over 10 patients and asserts that it is the best available option for reducing mortality rates. China Daily reports the president of Wuhan's Jinyintan Hospital called for plasma donations on Feb. 13.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-says-plasma-of-recovered-patients-may-help-treat-covid-19-3964237</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964237/3964237_661FC413E76C4664AB571C0EC32DF00A_200217_3964237_China_says_plasma_of_recovered_patients_may_help_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 10:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964185</guid>
      <title>Using lasers to communicate with robotic spacecraft, astronauts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> NASA has announced that it is building a new satellite dish as part of the Deep Space Network that would be able to communicate with far away robotic spacecrafts.<br/><br/>The dish, named Deep Space Station-23, is expected to be completed in two and a half years.<br/><br/>The satellite dish will be 34 meters wide and will use advanced technology, such as lasers, to transmit data to and from space. Deep Space Station-23 will operate as a radio antenna and will also be equipped with mirrors and include a special receiver for laser beams.<br/><br/>NASA officials say this technology can be used for communicating with astronauts once they are sent to places like Mars.<br/><br/>According to Suzanne Dodd, director of the Interplanetary Network, which manages the Deep Space Network, lasers will be able to transmit roughly 10 times more data than radio antennas from Mars to Earth.<br/><br/>NASA currently has deep space networks in Goldstone, California; Madrid, Spain; and Canberra, Australia. This is to allow spacecraft to have continual contact with Earth while our planet rotates.<br/><br/>As part of the Artemis program, NASA plans to launch three lunar missions by 2024 which will eventually pave way for astronauts to make their way to Mars and make human exploration of the red planet a reality.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/using-lasers-to-communicate-with-robotic-spacecraft-astronauts-3964185</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/17/3964185/3964185_8262251AB3274ECDAB62BD9BB7ED4254_200217_3964185_Using_lasers_to_communicate_with_robotic_spacecr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 08:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964759</guid>
      <title>SETI will scour the sky for alien signatures with 27 giant scopes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA<br/> The SETI Institute says that National Radio Astronomy Observatory will turn the Very Large Array's 27 telescopes to scan for signs of alien life in 75 percent of the night sky, in a Feb. 14 news release announcing the collaboration.<br/><br/>According to the institute, the VLA's 25 meter radio telescopes are the most productive in the world. While scientists utilize scopes to study black holes and the formation of the universe, the project will be the first time the VLA is used to look for technosignatures."<br/><br/>SETI's contribution will be building and installing a system dubbed COSMIC SETI that establish Ethernet links for VLA telescopes. This system will allow the instruments to scan for alien signatures at all hours of the day.<br/><br/>According to the NRAO, COSMIC SETI will allow parallel data processing with VLA's other analytical systems in real time, enhance analytical efficiency and detecting fast radio bursts.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/seti-will-scour-the-sky-for-alien-signatures-with-27-giant-scopes-3964759</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964759/3964759_79889F38383D48BE89BB59515A5EA1F4_200218_3964759_SETI_will_scour_the_sky_for_alien_signatures_wit_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 11:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3964718</guid>
      <title>Airbus unveils prototype of futuristic plane</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LEIDEN, NETHERLANDS <br/>  Airbus unveiled a prototype for a new aircraft called MAVERICK at the Singapore Airshow on February 11.<br/><br/>MAVERICK is an acronym for Model Aircraft for Validation and Experimentation of Robust Innovative Controls.<br/><br/>The prototype is two meters long and 3.2 meters wide, according to a press release from the company. Airbus has yet to unveil the dimensions of a full-sized MAVERICK.<br/><br/>The company states in the press release that MAVERICK will have a "blended wing body design," which would allow the aircraft to potentially burn up to 20 percent less fuel in comparison to traditional planes. <br/><br/>The press release explained that MAVERICK will also have a shielded engine above its central body that will reduce aircraft noise significantly.<br/><br/>Its design would also allow the plane to utilize different types of propulsion systems, though Airbus has yet to specify what these might be.<br/><br/>Airbus explained the unique design will allow the aircraft to have a wide cabin layout, which would provide passengers with extra legroom and larger aisles.<br/><br/>According to WIRED, the aircraft may accommodate fewer window seats than traditional airplanes due to its design, though this may lead to more creative seating arrangements than what are usually present in traditional planes.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/airbus-unveils-prototype-of-futuristic-plane-3964718</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/18/3964718/3964718_318A8CF1F7F94D3BB967DCBDE9D35B92_200218_3964718_Airbus_unveils_prototype_of_futuristic_plane_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 10:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965039</guid>
      <title>SpaceX launches another 60 Starlink satellites to orbit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA <br/> SpaceX successfully launched another batch of 60 Starlink satellites with a Falcon 9 rocket. Space.com reports that the mission lifted off at an airbase in Florida at 10:05 a.m. on Friday.<br/><br/>According to SpaceX, Falcon 9 is a reusable first stage booster with nine Merlin 1D engines that put out more thrust than five Boeing 747s at full power. The payload of 60 small satellites rides atop the rocket into orbit.<br/><br/>According to SpaceX, Starlinks are telecom satellites that feature ion thrusters for maneuvering into position and articulated solar arrays. Space.com reports the latest launch brought the Starlink constellation up to nearly 300 satellites.<br/><br/>The launch marked the fourth time the company used a booster four times. This rocket's earlier missions include a satellite launch and two runs to replenish the International Space Station last year.<br/><br/>However, the rocket apparently missed the drone ship Of Course I Still Love You and made a soft landing in the seas near the robotic vessel. Space.com reports that the company is hopeful that the rocket can still be retrieved, citing SpaceX.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/spacex-launches-another-60-starlink-satellites-to-orbit-3965039</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965039/3965039_21E9E3E4AB294A9A94B23D15CDC5214D_200219_3965039_SpaceX_launches_another_60_Starlink_satellites_t_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965179</guid>
      <title>The Sun's violent death will destroy the asteroid belt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> Billions of years from now, the Sun will exhaust its hydrogen fuel and enter what astronomers call the 'giant branch' phase. The Sun will grow bigger by hundreds of times, while its luminance and radiation output increase by thousands of times.<br/><br/>Writing in the Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, researchers say this energy will heat up the asteroid belt and cause the asteroids to spin faster and faster until they are torn to pieces, which will happen in six billion years.<br/><br/>Since most big asteroids are a loose collection of rocks called rubble piles, they are susceptible to this heat induced spinning, or the YORP effect. Most asteroids will be reduced until they become small homogeneous fragments.<br/><br/>The scientists' model predicts that the Sun will collapse into a white dwarf and absorb the smashed asteroids, which pollutes the star and changes its spectra. This would explain why many white dwarfs' spectra suggest the dead stars contain asteroid elements.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-sun-s-violent-death-will-destroy-the-asteroid-belt-3965179</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965179/3965179_5049240393764684BF39E5E86F73DFB5_200219_3965179_The_Sun_s_violent_death_will_destroy_the_asteroi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 09:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965073</guid>
      <title>Iran-backed Hackers target VPN servers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEHRAN, IRAN <br/> A new report by cyber security firm ClearSky has found that hackers backed by the Iranian government have been exploiting bugs in corporate VPN servers.<br/><br/>Over the past three years this campaign has targeted numerous companies around the world ranging from the IT sector to the oil and gas, aviation, government and security sectors. In some cases, the hackers were able to exploit vulnerabilities in a short period of time.<br/><br/>The hackers developed and used infrastructure that would allow them to control and access their targets in the long-term, according to the report. They were able to use this technique to steal valuable information from targeted companies.<br/><br/>Researchers said that this could also be used to spread malware such as <br/>ZeroCleare and Dustman. Both of these malware are designed to delete as much data from hacked devices as possible, according to ZDNet. <br/><br/>ZDNet points out that the report 'dispels the notion' that Iranian cyber hackers aren't as sophisticated as hackers in Russia, China or North Korea.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/iran-backed-hackers-target-vpn-servers-3965073</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965073/3965073_8AFABEF28ED8437B8655F5BE3BB73D02_200219_3965073_Iran_backed_Hackers_target_VPN_servers_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 06:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965277</guid>
      <title>Why January 2020 was the warmest in history</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO <br/> The past month was the hottest January in weather history, according to the U.S. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration.<br/><br/>Citing climate researchers, NBC reports that a jet stream trapping cold air over the Arctic might be responsible for the warm January." <br/><br/>NOAA data shows that the US and Hawaii region, Russia, Europe, South America and Australia experienced abnormally hot weather in January. <br/><br/>Meanwhile, sea ice has retreated in the Arctics and Antarctica.<br/><br/>Citing the National Ice and Snow Data Center, NBC reports the jet stream over the Arctic is called the Arctic Oscillation. <br/><br/>The jet stream is wavy during a negative phase of this. This allows cool air to go south, taking cold temperatures and rains with it.<br/><br/>Citing the center's director Mark Serreze[d], NBC reports the AO is having a positive phase with a flat jetstream circle, which entraps the cold air over the Arctic region. Serrez says this weather phenomenon is possibly the cause of the high temperatures.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/why-january-2020-was-the-warmest-in-history-3965277</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/19/3965277/3965277_5C13A5B51B644EDA95EFD861DDB712BB_200219_3965277_Why_January_2020_was_the_warmest_in_history_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2020 12:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965744</guid>
      <title>Get ready for 3D printed chocolates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZURICH <br/> Barry Callebaut, a Swiss-based chocolate manufacturer, has announced that it will start producing 3D printed chocolate at scale in its new studio called Mona Lisa.<br/><br/>The 3D printing studio will be able to create personalized chocolates for customers, according to a news release from the company. Clients can choose which design, shape and size they want for their chocolate.<br/><br/>Once a design has been chosen, studio designers will then make a digital 3D prototype of the chocolate. The news release explained that the technology is capable of printing thousands of chocolate pieces at a time while retaining a "hand-made appearance."<br/><br/>The service could be used for desserts, confectionery or pastries.<br/><br/>The company says that the service will be available to chefs, hotels, coffee chains and restaurants in select European countries.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/get-ready-for-3d-printed-chocolates-3965744</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965744/3965744_329CFCEE10F043E2B15AD7DC1EEDB2C8_200220_3965744_Get_ready_for_3D_printed_chocolates_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 11:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965707</guid>
      <title>Coral reefs may lose nearly all habitats by 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO <br/> A new study presented to the American Geophysicists Union says that global warming and rising acidity will kill off nearly all coral reef habitats by 2100.<br/><br/>Warming and rising acidity bleach coral reefs by making corals eject their symbiotic algae.<br/><br/>Scientists expect 70 percent to 90 percent of coral reefs to disappear in the next 20 years. While some groups are trying to regrow bleached corals with transplants, the study's model shows that almost none of these projects will remain viable in 2100.<br/><br/>The study shows that small portions of Baja California and the Red Sea will be some of the last viable sites for growing reefs in 2020, but these locations are too close to rivers to be ideal habits.<br/><br/>Researchers say climate warming and rising acidity are the main culprits for shrinking coral habitats because plastic pollution is so extensive that there are few places left for plastics to affect.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coral-reefs-may-lose-nearly-all-habitats-by-2020-3965707</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965707/3965707_445C69BA53A847CB9CF8E672E2A6FFD2_200220_3965707_Coral_reefs_may_lose_nearly_all_habitats_by_2020_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3965690</guid>
      <title>MasterCard makes biometrics push for public transit users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARRISON, NEW YORK <br/> Market Watch reports CCTV and gait analysis may come to US public transit to allow commuters to pay without using cards or passes, citing MasterCard officials working on biometric technologies with transport firms.<br/><br/>Speaking to the outlet, MasterCard's cyber solutions president Ajay Bhalla said facial features and gait could be linked to databases for cardless payment. <br/><br/>Those methods are less vulnerable to hacking than password authenticated accounts.<br/><br/>MasterCard is also exploring other biometric solutions, such as using wrist bands to identify a commuter's unique heartbeat patterns, EEG, and veins on the surface of their skin to authenticate payments.<br/><br/>Bhalla is cited as saying the way a person holds a phone, which ear they use and the manner their fingers touch buttons on their devices are all potentially useful methods for authentication.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mastercard-makes-biometrics-push-for-public-transit-users-3965690</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/20/3965690/3965690_23CC845E05694392936864B6B5B67722_200220_3965690_MasterCard_makes_biometrics_push_for_public_tran_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 10:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966249</guid>
      <title>Scientists say they may figure out why the universe exists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERKELEY, CALIFORNIA <br/> Scientists may have figured out  why matter outnumbers antimatter in our universe. <br/><br/>According to the researchers, had the two substances been created in equal amounts, they would have annihilated one another and the universe would not have existed.<br/><br/>In a study published in Physical Review Letters, researchers say that after the big bang, the early universe must have gone through a phase that allowed neutrinos to create more matter than antimatter. <br/><br/>This period would also have created the cosmic strings.<br/><br/>Citing the authors, Live Science reports that cosmic strings are thin bands of energy that still thread through the universe and that the strings' formation in the early cosmos can be proven by the ripples in space time they created.<br/><br/>Although the ripples are faint, the research team says that if their models are correct, future instruments such as NASA's future Laser Interferometer Space Antenna will be able to detect the ripples and confirm their theory.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-say-they-may-figure-out-why-the-universe-exists-3966249</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3966249/3966249_E258BE4141084AC0A49E259AF0BFC49A_200221_3966249_Scientists_say_they_may_figure_out_why_the_unive_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 10:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3966318</guid>
      <title>Google just removed 500 Chrome extensions containing malware</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOUNTAIN VIEW, CALIFORNIA <br/> Google has removed hundreds of extensions for their internet browser Chrome after they were found to have malware.<br/><br/>A joint investigation by cyber security firm Duo Security, and Jamila Kaya, an independent security researcher, has identified roughly 70 chrome extensions that contained malicious codes. <br/><br/>The researchers notified Google after which the tech giant conducted its own analysis and found more than 500 chrome extensions that were infected with malware.<br/><br/>According to the report, the chrome extensions would inject malicious advertisements while users are browsing a website or lead users to specific websites such as Macys, Dell, or BestBuy.<br/><br/>In some cases, the extension would take users to a phishing page or a malware download site.<br/><br/>Researchers said that if users weren't regularly checking their chrome extensions, the plugins were able to collect extensive data and generate revenue through the user's device.<br/><br/>Google has since removed the malicious chrome extensions and deactivated them for users who had installed the extensions on their browser, according to ZDNet. The website reports that Google also marked these extensions as "malicious",  so users would know to not reactivate them and to get rid of them from their browser.<br/><br/>Google did not mention how many people had been affected by the breach.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/google-just-removed-500-chrome-extensions-containing-malware-3966318</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/21/3966318/3966318_0BBAD57DF9464AB49B4DCC4E9A9A5FF6_200221_3966318_Google_just_removed_500_Chrome_extensions_contai_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 12:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967250</guid>
      <title>Here's how endangered blue whales are coming back</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH GEORGIA <br/> Researchers from the British Antarctic Survey have found an increase of blue whales around the island of South Georgia near Antarctica.<br/><br/>The whale population in South Georgia declined due to extensive hunting in the early 20th century, according to BBC News. <br/><br/>The researchers embarked on several missions to the waters of South Georgia from January 1, 2018 to January 1, 2020 and spotted roughly 55 blue whales.<br/><br/>Researchers used advanced acoustics to locate different whales and attached satellite tags to identify them. They also collected skin samples and flew drones over the whales to assess their body conditions.<br/><br/>The report suggests that the whales may be returning to South Georgia waters for feeding purposes which is, in turn, impacting the reproductive rate of the whale population.<br/><br/>According to British Antarctic Survey's website, South Georgia may have been an important place for many whale species in the past due to its influx of Antarctic krill and immense seasonal productivity.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/here-s-how-endangered-blue-whales-are-coming-back-3967250</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967250/3967250_6C3D7E1164E341C2A453834D6B6F6EBC_200224_3967250_Here_s_how_endangered_blue_whales_are_coming_bac_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 08:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967425</guid>
      <title>Earth formed a whole lot fast than previously thought: study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COPENHAGEN, DENMARK <br/> Scientists say the early Solar System's cosmic dust gave rise to primitive Earth over just five million years. If the Solar System's existence is compressed into 24 hours, then the proto-Earth's creation did not take more than a minute.<br/><br/>According to the study published in Science Advances, the research team found that a type of meteorites known as CI chondrites are the closest iron isotope match to our planet and the bulk composition of the solar system itself.<br/><br/>In a news release, the University of Copenhagen says that the Sun once possessed an accretion disk. After the young star cooled, the CI dust in the disk was allowed to settle on proto-Earth.<br/><br/>The university says the process would not be not possible unless the earlier iron had already migrated into the proto-Earth's nascent core. That our planet's composition is similar to only one meteor type suggests it is not created from random collisions.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/earth-formed-a-whole-lot-fast-than-previously-thought-study-3967425</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967425/3967425_4A01B25AA11349928FAC0A76B5DE66E3_200224_3967425_Earth_formed_a_whole_lot_fast_than_previously_th_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 13:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967414</guid>
      <title>Increased methane emissions linked to human fossil fuel usage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ROCHESTER, NEW YORK <br/> A new study published by the University of Rochester in Nature magazine has found that human activity has been contributing significantly to the rise of methane emissions via the use of fossil fuels.<br/><br/>For this study, scientists collected ice cores from Greenland and melted them to measure the amount of carbon-14 isotopes that were trapped in the ice cores.<br/><br/>Fossil methane does not contain carbon-14 as it has been trapped underground for millions of years and the isotope has decayed. Biological methane, which comes from living sources such as animals, contains carbon-14. <br/><br/>This chemical signature allowed researchers to distinguish natural emissions from man-made emissions over a period of 200 years, from before the Industrial Revolution started in the early 18th century to the present day.<br/><br/>Researchers found that almost all methane that was emitted to earth's atmosphere until 1870 was biological in nature.<br/><br/>After 1870, researchers found a roughly 25 to 40 percent increase of human-produced methane emissions. This coincides with a sharp increase in the use of fossil fuels such as coal, oil and natural gas around the same period of time.<br/><br/>Scientists linked the study to today's climate crisis and said that a reduction in fossil fuel use could lessen the threat of global warming.<br/><br/>A separate study from Princeton University found that methane emissions are roughly 30 times more potent than carbon emissions.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/increased-methane-emissions-linked-to-human-fossil-fuel-usage-3967414</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/24/3967414/3967414_3428FC1DED2A40B7ADDD098384ADB81A_200224_3967414_Increased_methane_emissions_linked_to_human_foss_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 12:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967855</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy deploys its first laser-equipped destroyer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The U.S. Navy has put its first laser-equipped destroyer to sea. In a news release dated Feb. 20, Sea Systems Command says the Optical Dazzling Interdictor Navy, or ODIN, is designed to help ships counter enemy surveillance drones.<br/><br/>Citing the command, Military.com reports the ODIN was installed on the Arleigh Burke-class destroyer Dewey in November. An image published by the Drive shows that the laser dazzler appears to be mounted in a turret atop the deckhouse."<br/><br/>ODIN's predecessor <br/> the Laser Weapons System <br/> is a 30 kilowatt laser that had been tested but never operationally fielded.<br/><br/>Military.com reports that Iranian drones had shadowed the carrier George H.W. Bush in the Persian Gulf and the laser will stymy hostile drones' attempt to gather intelligence on U.S. warships.<br/><br/>The outlet reports that ODIN is only one of the laser weapons planned by the service. Another weapon, a 60 to 150 kW laser which has a range of five nautical miles will likely be installed on another destroyer by 2021.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-navy-deploys-its-first-laser-equipped-destroyer-3967855</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967855/3967855_B08B2EDF00B2440EB7338645F0A6DFA2_200225_3967855_U_S__Navy_deploys_its_first_laser_equipped_destr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 10:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967761</guid>
      <title>Misleading recycling labels found on plastic products: Greenpeace</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A new report by Greenpeace published on February 18 has found that several companies in the U.S. are misleading consumers by adding incorrect recycling labels onto their plastic products.<br/><br/>This includes companies such as Target, Walmart, Procter & Gamble and Nestl&#233;.<br/><br/>After surveying 367 material recovery facilities across the U.S., Greenpeace identified only two types of plastics, PET #1 and HDPE#2, that can be processed in the U.S. These are the only types of plastic allowed to be labeled as recyclable.<br/><br/>PET #1, or polyethylene terephthalate, includes plastic water bottles, soda bottles or peanut butter jars while HDPE#2, or High-Density polyethylene, refers to milk jars, shampoo bottles or laundry detergent containers.<br/><br/>Researchers noted that many PET #1 and HDPE#2 plastic bottles or other containers consist of full body shrink sleeves which makes the products non-recycle too.<br/><br/>The report found that plastics labeled PVC#3, LDPE#4, PP#5, PS#6 and others cannot be classified as recyclable as they have low acceptance by material recovery facilities and are typically sent to landfills or incinerators. These include plastics such as plastic cups, bags, plates and cutlery.<br/><br/>Greenpeace has called for companies to eliminate single-use plastics and to invest in reusable, refillable packaging or go package-free instead.<br/><br/>The organization has said that they will file a complaint with the Federal Trade Commission if the companies do not correct their labeling.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/misleading-recycling-labels-found-on-plastic-products-greenpeace-3967761</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967761/3967761_AFE0F3A2F6C74BBE856FB026D67119D9_200225_3967761_Misleading_recycling_labels_found_on_plastic_pro_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 08:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3967913</guid>
      <title>Scientists discover parasite blobs that do not breathe</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The Henneguya salminicola is a species of parasitic blob that lives inside and feeds on the flesh of fish. The creature is the first multicell animal discovered that does not breathe, according to a study in Proceedings of the Academy of Natural Sciences.<br/><br/>The parasite has no mitochondrial DNA, which enables other animals to respirate. Citing the authors, Live Science reports the parasite possibly absorbs ATP energy molecules directly from infected hosts to acquire energy without using oxygen fuel.<br/><br/>Science Live reports that H. salminicola is mostly innocuous, but related parasites have wiped out whole fisheries stocks.<br/><br/>H. salminocla is a distant relative of the jellyfish and the microscopic parasites have evolved to lose nerves, muscles and tissue. This genetic simplicity allows the creature to reproduce quickly, an evolutionary advantage for parasites.<br/><br/>Study co-author Dorothee Huchon is cited as saying the parasite's spores are the only part of H. salminocla that shows any complexity. The spores are able to swim with two tails, and their eye-shaped stingers can latch on to the host when needed.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-discover-parasite-blobs-that-do-not-breathe-3967913</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/25/3967913/3967913_3424825BF8AB4A5786ADAF4378CC1015_200225_3967913_Scientists_discover_parasite_blobs_that_do_not_b_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 13:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968387</guid>
      <title>Archeologists complete first-ever laser survey of ancient Mayan road</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COBA, MEXICO <br/> Archeologists have used laser scanning to chart an ancient 100 km long Mayan highway built 13 centuries ago. They say Coba, a powerful city-state, may have built the road to invade its neighbor Yaxuna. The study was published in the Journal of Archeological Science.<br/><br/>The University of Miami said in a news release that the study used light detection and ranging technology lasers to penetrate thick jungle vegetation and reveal the ruins beneath. The LIDAR survey mapped out the road and uncovered 8,000 structures on its path.<br/><br/>University professor Traci Ardren is cited as saying the road did not run straight as supposed. Instead, Coba's warrior queen K'awiil Ajaw may have built the winding road to control settlements across the Yucatan Peninsula and to attack Yaxuna.<br/><br/>Arden, who is a co-author, says the Mayan roads were an engineering marvel. Giant limestone boulders were utilized to fill uneven ground, then white plaster was applied to make the road surface. This substance is similar to Roman concrete and gave the road its name Sacbe, which comes from the Mayan word for "white way."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/archeologists-complete-first-ever-laser-survey-of-ancient-mayan-road-3968387</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968387/3968387_623226BBF02B4A4E865A54946B8D8E55_200226_3968387_Archeologists_complete_first_ever_laser_survey_o_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968375</guid>
      <title>Japan plans 2024 space mission to explore Martian moons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> Japan is set to launch a robotic mission to the Martian system in 2024. The MIT Technology Review reports the mission will visit Phobos and Deimos, and recover dust samples from the former Martian moon, citing Japan's space agency JAXA.<br/><br/>According to JAXA, the Martian Moon Exploration spacecraft, or MMX, will enter into a stable orbit to observe the two moons for a year. The MMX will utilize a NASA-funded neutron and gamma-ray spectrometer to determine the composition of these moons.<br/><br/>The MMX will also land on Phobos and send out a small rover. The vehicle will use its equipped geological core sampler and dig 2 cm deep into the dust to retrieve samples weighing 10 grams.<br/><br/>The mission's main goals are to investigate the two moon's origins, to find evidence that water had been present on Deimos and Phobos, and gather data on the gravitational stress that is expected to tear Phobos apart 30 to 50 million years from now.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/japan-plans-2024-space-mission-to-explore-martian-moons-3968375</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/26/3968375/3968375_C6240E662CF548858DFB1307BE835C80_200226_3968375_Japan_plans_2024_space_mission_to_explore_Martia_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 12:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3968859</guid>
      <title>Explainer: how coronaviruses spread from animals to humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> The WHO reports the COVID-19 outbreak as of February 25 has infected 80,000 people and resulted in about 2,700 deaths, mostly in China's Hubei.<br/><br/>Writing in a column for Quanta Magazine, U.S. epidemiologist Tara C. Smith says that SARS-CoV-2 probably transmitted from bats to pangolins to humans.<br/><br/>However, Smith, who is a public health professor at Kent State, notes other coronaviruses are known to jump the species barrier.<br/><br/>SARS-CoV, which caused the SARS outbreak in 2003, originated from a civet cat. A decade later, MERS-CoV would emerge from a camel to infect humans.<br/><br/>Coronaviruses rely on surface glycoproteins for binding themselves with the receptors on the cells of their hosts to cause infections.<br/><br/>The part of the protein that binds is called the S1 subunit. Coronaviruses possess highly varied S1s that allow them to bind with many mammalian cell receptors, including those found on the surface of human air passageways.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-how-coronaviruses-spread-from-animals-to-humans-3968859</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/02/27/3968859/3968859_9CEBCAC168CA47ED92A2FABC798B4D39_200227_3968859_Explainer__how_coronaviruses_spread_from_animals_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 10:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
