<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 18:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3944039</guid>
      <title>Global warming could force the North Atlantic Current to halt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRONINGEN, NETHERLANDS <br/> The North Atlantic Current is a vast flow of warm seawater from the Gulf of Mexico that makes northwestern Europe's mild climate possible.<br/><br/>According to a study in Science Reports, Netherlands-based scientists warn that global warming might temporarily halt this important current in the next century.<br/><br/>According to the British Meteorological Office, the North Atlantic Current is driven by differentials in salinity and temperature levels in the sea.<br/><br/>As the hot current flows north, the water loses salinity and heat. This cold, dense water then sinks deep into the ocean and flows back to tropical waters.<br/><br/>According to the researchers' news release, climate change-related ice melt in Greenland and excessive rains over the seas are adding freshwater to the North Atlantic.<br/><br/>The scientists say the new study's mathematical model has bolstered previous theories that freshwater inclusions would slow the current or even interrupt it.<br/><br/>A study co-author says that their simulations predict a 15 percent chance that the current would seize up temporarily in the next 100 years.<br/><br/>The scientists say that such a disruption might lead to cold spells in the northern Atlantic region.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/global-warming-could-force-the-north-atlantic-current-to-halt-3944039</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EE4/A0C/EE4A0CB25A1BDF5EF2C8C8FEA60A12F9.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3944039/3944039_FA0FB5FD57F8427F87D5882CAE109A12_200102_3944039_Global_warming_could_force_the_North_Atlantic_Cu_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 11:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943916</guid>
      <title>U.S. to investigate nuclear waste site in Marshall Islands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RUNIT DOME, MARSHALL ISLANDS <br/> The U.S. Congress is demanding an investigation into the Runit Dome in the Marshall Islands, which contains radioactive waste and is being threatened by rising sea levels.<br/><br/>The dome was built in the late 1970s during the Cold War era. It was originally built to contain radioactive waste from nuclear tests conducted by the U.S on the islands, according to CBS News.<br/><br/>The U.S. conducted 64 nuclear weapons tests at Bikini and Enewetak atolls between 1946 to 1958.<br/><br/>The tests included the "Bravo" hydrogen bomb, which was said to be 1,000 times more powerful than the atomic bomb the U.S. dropped on Hiroshima, Al Jazeera reports. <br/><br/>According to the Los Angeles Times, the site holds more than 3.1 million cubic feet of radioactive ash and soil from the nuclear explosions, which was closed with a concrete dome that is 18 inches thick.<br/><br/>This was originally meant to be a temporary solution since the bottom of the crater was never lined.<br/><br/>As part of the National Defense Authorization Act, the Department of Energy must investigate the deteriorating concrete site and submit a report about the risks the dome poses to the people, wildlife, and surrounding environment by June 2020, the Los Angeles Times reports. <br/><br/>The report must also assess how rising sea levels could affect the nuclear dome.<br/><br/>In May 2019, UN Secretary General Antonio Guterres had raised concerns about the risk of the dome's radioactive material leaking into the sea, reports BBC News. <br/><br/>According to the U.S. Department of Interior, the Marshall Islands was a UN trust territory that was administered by the U.S. from 1947 to 1978. It became a sovereign nation in 1979.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-to-investigate-nuclear-waste-site-in-marshall-islands-3943916</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3EB/BBC/3EBBBCC7C2C6D0D047CE5E974843268A.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943916/3943916_D898DF4C63F34AC98667C48BD9951EEC_200102_3943916_U_S__to_investigate_nuclear_waste_site_in_Marsha_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 08:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943882</guid>
      <title>Microsoft sues North Korean hackers for stealing user info</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REDMOND, WASHINGTON <br/> Microsoft has filed a lawsuit against two anonymous North Korean hackers for stealing user information in a hacking operation called Thallium.<br/><br/>The hackers were using 50 domains as part of their cyber operation, according to ZDNet. <br/><br/>In the court documents for the lawsuit, which was filed on December 18, Microsoft explained that hackers would send spear phishing emails to users that pretended to be from a Microsoft Account Team.<br/><br/>The emails would include a link to a host phishing page that would encourage users to enter their account credentials. Once hackers gained access gained access to a users' account, they would be able to review user emails, contact lists and other information.<br/><br/>In addition, Microsoft said the hackers were able to use misleading domains to trick users into clicking links that would result in malware such as KimJongRAT and BabyShark, which are remote access trojans, being installed on a user's computer.<br/><br/>This type of malware is able to exfiltrate information and wait to receive additional commands from the hackers who installed it, ZDNet reports. <br/><br/>Most targeted users were based in the U.S., Japan and South Korea.<br/><br/>According to ZDNet, Microsoft has since been granted a court order by U.S. authorities to take over the 50 domains used by the North Korean hackers. The tech company has since taken those websites down.<br/><br/>Microsoft had previously notified 10,000 users in July that their accounts had been targeted by hackers from North Korea, Russia and Iran over the past 12 months, CBS News reports.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/microsoft-sues-north-korean-hackers-for-stealing-user-info-3943882</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8F2/868/8F2868DA30F9400AE54B64BB3FF8202B.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943882/3943882_024C232861AA4ACD9100E7A19EFFF07A_200102_3943882_Microsoft_sues_North_Korean_hackers_for_stealing_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 07:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3943853</guid>
      <title>CDC links Vitamin E additives  to vaping related lung injuries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA <br/> U.S. health officials have linked vitamin E acetate additives to a "vast majority" of vaping illness cases.<br/><br/>The CDC made those remarks in a news conference on December 20, citing the latest papers in a series of studies the agency carried out. <br/><br/>The agency says it has been tracking the vaping cases since July and confirmed that incidents of illnesses have declined.<br/><br/>According to a study in the New England Journal of Medicine, the CDC took bronchus and lung fluid samples from a large number of vaping illness patients across 16 states.<br/><br/>Analysis found vitamin E, a substance identified in e-cigarette product samples, in 48 out of 51 patients, but not in healthy people. <br/><br/>According to the Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, the CDC studied 38 vaping illness patients who died or were rehospitalized after hospital discharge.<br/><br/>The median time for patients to go back to the hospital was three days, and the median time from hospital discharge to death was four days.<br/><br/>The CDC advises doctors to follow up on patients soon after hospital discharge.<br/><br/>According to the same report, vaping illness patients over 50 years of age are more likely to die than other patients.<br/><br/>The CDC says that vaping illness patients with heart diseases and diabetes are significantly more likely to be readmitted after their initial hospitalization.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cdc-links-vitamin-e-additives-to-vaping-related-lung-injuries-3943853</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/02/3943853/3943853_944D63BB2201423E977BA3EE694D67EE_200102_3943853_CDC_links_Vitamin_E_additives__to_vaping_related_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 06:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944253</guid>
      <title>A designer rolled out 3D printed synthetic fruits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[Jerusalem <br/> An Israel-based designer has invented 3D printed synthetic fruits that are edible and contain essential minerals and vitamins.<br/><br/>According to Dezeen, Meydan Levy created five types of artificial "neo fruits."<br/><br/>The neo fruits' structure is made of cellulose, an organic compound that forms the structure of living plants.<br/><br/>The artificial fruits' cellulose microtubes also contain the liquid mixture that gives the fruit nutrients and flavor. <br/> <br/>Citing Levy, the online outlet says the artificial fruits do not take up their final shape until liquid is injected. <br/><br/>Levy says that without the liquids, the artificial fruits could be stored for long periods and transported easily until the injections are added before consumption.<br/><br/>According to Levy, industrial agriculture will not be able to meet the nutritional needs that coincide with a global population increase. <br/> <br/>Dezeen reports that nutritionists helped Levy to create different ingredients for each type of neo fruit in order to meet the wide range of nutrition the human body requires.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-designer-rolled-out-3d-printed-synthetic-fruits-3944253</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/523/426/523426B9D9D26E1DE8E2AD1792B5204D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944253/3944253_C3B94ADBC2EC4412BFE4E674B8D720BC_200103_3944253_A_designer_rolled_out_3D_printed_synthetic_fruit_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 03:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944521</guid>
      <title>India announces plans for third lunar mission, Chandrayaan-3</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BENGALURU, INDIA <br/> The Indian Space Research Organization on Tuesday announced plans for a third lunar mission called Chandrayaan-3 and said it is most likely to be launched later this year, according to the Times of India.<br/><br/>Speaking at a press conference, the space agency's chairperson K Sivan explained that the spacecraft's configuration will be similar to its predecessor, Chandrayaan-2.<br/><br/>According to AFP, he said the agency will build a new propulsion module, lander and surface rover for the mission.<br/><br/>Sivan told the Times of India the mission will cut costs by reusing the same orbiter from India's second lunar mission as it is already orbiting the moon.<br/><br/>The aim is to land the spacecraft on the moon's south pole, the same area that the Chandrayaan-2 tried to land in but failed to do so in September of 2019.<br/><br/>If the mission is successful, this would make India the fourth nation to achieve a soft landing on the lunar surface.<br/><br/>India's second moon mission failed as the Chandrayaan-2 spacecraft had a hard landing on the moon's south pole and lost communication with Indian spacecraft operators.<br/><br/>The mission was aimed at searching for water and minerals on the moon as well as measuring moonquakes.<br/><br/>Sivan said the Indian space agency plans to launch at least 25 space missions this year as part of India's plans to become a low-cost space power.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/india-announces-plans-for-third-lunar-mission-chandrayaan-3-3944521</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/3D9/04C/3D904C70087684543F25A96519F1875E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/03/3944521/3944521_F647E9799D664472824AE8AF2AB4B055_200103_3944521_India_announces_plans_for_third_lunar_mission__C_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 10:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3944435</guid>
      <title>Global warming could force the North Atlantic Current to halt</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GRONINGEN, NETHERLANDS <br/> The North Atlantic Current is a vast flow of warm seawater from the Gulf of Mexico that makes northwestern Europe's mild climate possible.<br/><br/>According to a study in Science Reports, Netherlands-based scientists warn that global warming might temporarily halt this important current in the next century.<br/><br/>According to the British Meteorological Office, the North Atlantic Current is driven by differentials in salinity and temperature levels in the sea.<br/><br/>As the hot current flows north, the water loses salinity and heat. This cold, dense water then sinks deep into the ocean and flows back to tropical waters.<br/><br/>According to the researchers' news release, climate change-related ice melt in Greenland and excessive rains over the seas are adding freshwater to the North Atlantic.<br/><br/>The scientists say the new study's mathematical model has bolstered previous theories that freshwater inclusions would slow the current or even interrupt it.<br/><br/>A study co-author says that their simulations predict a 15 percent chance that the current would seize up temporarily in the next 100 years.<br/><br/>The scientists say that such a disruption might lead to cold spells in the northern Atlantic region.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/global-warming-could-force-the-north-atlantic-current-to-halt-3944435</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url=""/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 08:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945481</guid>
      <title>Australia's bushfires are creating freak thunderstorms</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VICTORIA, AUSTRALIA <br/> CBS News reports that bushfires in Australia are burning so fiercely that they are creating pyrocumulonimbus clouds which are then creating thunderstorms.  <br/><br/>The Bureau of Meteorology in Victoria tweeted that the bushfires in East Grippland had triggered one such storm in a warning issued on Thursday last week. <br/><br/>CBS News meteorologists say that bushfires heat the air so intensely that they could send ash upwards at a speed of 100 miles an hour or more.<br/><br/>The updrafts can then cause ash and smoke to rise miles up into the atmosphere where cooler temperature causes water to condense into clouds.<br/><br/>According to CBS News,  freak storms like this could increase as our planet continues to heat up. <br/><br/>According to CBS News, the more violent the bushfire, the faster the updraft and the more likely the clouds will form thunderstorms.<br/><br/>Unlike normal storms, bushfire-caused storms do not result in much rain since the falling raindrops are evaporated by the heat from the fires raging below.<br/><br/>CBS News warns that lightning strikes from these storms are far more likely to cause further bushfires due to the lack of rain.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/australia-s-bushfires-are-creating-freak-thunderstorms-3945481</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945481/3945481_2663BECF5AD349588E017A7FECD9301E_200106_3945481_Australia_s_bushfires_are_creating_freak_thunder_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 04:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945634</guid>
      <title>First human composting facility to open in Seattle next year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE <br/> US-based company Recompose will start the first ever funeral service that turns human bodies into compost soil next year.<br/><br/>Citing architects involved in the project, Dezeen reports that the flagship facility in Seattle will be capable of housing 75 bodies in its compost vessels.<br/><br/>According to Recompose, prosthetics and pacemakers will be removed from the cadaver to prepare the body for the natural organic reduction process.<br/><br/>Citing company founder Katrina Spade, the Washington Post reports that the vessels accelerate natural decomposition.<br/><br/>According to Recompose, the company's technology is designed for urban areas that do not have space for burials.<br/><br/>The body is interred in a vessel 4 feet wide and 8 feet tall with alfalfa, wood chips and straw and then heated to a temperature of 150 degrees Fahrenheit.<br/><br/>After 30 days, the microbes will have decomposed the body and eliminated most pathogens and residual pharmaceuticals.<br/><br/>The process creates about a cubic yard of soil from each person and the decedent's friends and family may take part of the soil for their garden.<br/><br/>Recompose claims their services save one tonne of carbon emissions per person when compared to conventional burial or cremation, which increases sustainability.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/first-human-composting-facility-to-open-in-seattle-next-year-3945634</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945634/3945634_525950EA241D471398DB896F62B96279_200106_3945634_First_human_composting_facility_to_open_in_Seatt_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 09:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3945623</guid>
      <title>This is the amount of plastic particles ingested by humans</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEWCASTLE, AUSTRALIA <br/> New research from the World Wide Fund for Nature and the University of Newcastle, Australia suggests that humans consume roughly 2,000 pieces of microplastics, or five grams of plastic, a week. <br/><br/>This is equivalent to eating a credit card a week.<br/><br/>Microplastic particles are less than five millimeters in length and are approximately the size of a sesame seed.<br/><br/>The study found that the number increases to 21 grams of plastic pieces a month, which is equivalent to the weight of a hanger or the amount of microplastics needed to fill half a rice bowl.<br/><br/>Every six months we consume 125 grams of plastic, which is enough plastic to fill an entire cereal bowl. According to the study, this turns into roughly 250 grams of microplastics in a year, or a dinner plate full of plastic.<br/><br/>The study found that we consume approximately 20 kilograms of microplastics in our lifetime, or roughly the weight of two mobile recycling bins, according to Reuters.<br/><br/>The study notes that the largest source of plastic ingestion around the world is through water consumption, either ground water, surface water, tap water or bottled water.<br/><br/>The study also estimates that a small number of microplastics may enter the body through inhalation.<br/><br/>Researchers mentioned that the long term effect of microplastics on our health is unclear and that additional studies are still needed to understand the effect of plastic on human health.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/this-is-the-amount-of-plastic-particles-ingested-by-humans-3945623</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/06/3945623/3945623_54E893A398E341C281FF2234820E5E7A_200106_3945623_This_is_the_amount_of_plastic_particles_ingested_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 09:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946122</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's endangered leopard cats saved by road culverts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAOLI, TAIWAN <br/> Taiwan is making a push to save its leopard cats.<br/><br/>Taiwan's Miaoli County passed an ordinance to protect leopard cats by rewarding eco-friendly farming and mandating impact studies for some construction projects on December 28.<br/><br/>Liberty Times reports that Miaoli is an important breeding ground for leopard cats, an endangered species in Taiwan. <br/><br/>The busy traffic on Taiwan's freeways poses a significant danger to the leopard cats and at least 21 cats were killed by cars in 2019.<br/><br/>Taiwan's government has been trying to address the problem by building culverts to help leopard cats safely cross roads.<br/><br/>Citing the Forestry Bureau, United Daily News reports that its camera detected 39 leopard cats at one culvert.<br/><br/>Last year, the government and the National Chung Hsing University unveiled a safe crossing system.<br/><br/>The system features a speedometer linked traffic sign, fences, light sound emitters to slow down cats, animal biometrics, and a safe passage culvert.<br/><br/>The Forestry Bureau says that cats have learned to use those systems and that a combination of LED lights, fences and speeding enforcement may help save the cats.<br/><br/>Liberty Times reports that Miaoli's laws would require construction of a certain size--such as roads over 1 km long--to pass an environmental impact study before they are built.<br/><br/>According to the Liberty Times, there are less than 1,000 living leopard cats in Taiwan. The government has issued repeated calls for motorists to slow down in areas that the cats inhabit.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-s-endangered-leopard-cats-saved-by-road-culverts-3946122</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3946122/3946122_6A1931EBEF584B88AAA2489B3ED29535_200107_3946122_Taiwan_s_endangered_leopard_cats_saved_by_road_c_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946041</guid>
      <title>How to protect yourself from SIM swapping</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> SIM swapping occurs when scammers gain access to your sim card number, usually by telling the cell phone service provider that the device has been lost or damaged, according to the Federal Trade Commission.<br/><br/>Once the same number is activated on a new device, the hacker receives all your text messages, calls and data.<br/><br/>According to the agency, scammers may log into your email accounts, social media accounts and change your passwords to potentially lock you out of your own accounts.<br/><br/>They could also use your login credentials to access money in your bank account. This is because once hackers have gained access to your phone number, they can receive verification codes through SMS and bypass two-factor authentication.<br/><br/>The agency urges users to limit the amount of personal information shared online, and in emails and text messages, in order to prevent becoming a victim of SIM swapping.<br/><br/>Users are also advised to set a password or a PIN on their cellular account in order to better protect their phone numbers.<br/><br/>Those who have fallen victim to SIM swapping are urged to contact their cell service provider to gain back access to their account. Once access has been restored, users should change their account passwords.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-to-protect-yourself-from-sim-swapping-3946041</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/07/3946041/3946041_FECD74FFCF5841C498CD74327D71AD90_200107_3946041_How_to_protect_yourself_from_SIM_swapping_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 07:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946383</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show the scale of Australia's wildfires</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY <br/> Australia's wildfires are so big now that satellites in space are able to spot the fires.<br/><br/>Footage captured from Japan's Himawari-8 satellite shows plumes of smoke covering eastern Australia on January 2. Another image from the same satellite pinpoints the exact location of the burning fires using near infrared light.<br/><br/>NASA released images from the International Space Station that show smoke from the fires around the Sydney area on January 3.<br/><br/>The European Space Agency's Sentinel-2 satellite also captured images of the growing wildfires in New South Wales on New Year's Eve. <br/><br/>Images captured by the Japanese satellite in the past few days show the smoke from the fires gradually drifting and slowly making its way toward New Zealand.<br/><br/>These bushfires have been fuelled by record high temperatures and severe drought over the past few months, BBC News reports. The state of New South Wales has been the worst hit, with the fires destroying more than 1,300 homes and forcing thousands of people to evacuate.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the fires have been worse than usual. Since July 1, roughly 5 million hectares have already been burned down in New South Wales. In comparison, the Amazon rainforest fires in 2019 burned down approximately 900,000 hectares of land.<br/><br/>According to CNN, the fires aren't likely to end anytime soon as it is just the beginning of summer in Australia, and temperatures tend to soar in the months of January and February.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/satellite-images-show-the-scale-of-australia-s-wildfires-3946383</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946383/3946383_EA6249915D8A4AA3BA966993A2C08A68_200108_3946383_Satellite_images_show_the_scale_of_Australia_s_w_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 02:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946695</guid>
      <title>Deepfake videos banned on Facebook</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA <br/> Facebook has put forth a new policy that would ban all videos that are "edited or synthesized" using AI technology in a way that would be difficult for average Facebook users to spot, reports the Washington Post. <br/><br/>This would include a ban on videos that use techniques to make a subject say words that he or she never said.<br/><br/>Though the company said in a news release that they will allow manipulated videos as long as they are for satire or parody purposes.<br/><br/>In this case, the Washington Post points out that under the policy, a doctored video showing Speaker of the House Nancy Pelosi drunkenly giving a speech last year would still be allowed on Facebook.<br/><br/>Last year, the company declined to remove the video even though fact-checkers had determined that the video was fake. A Facebook spokesperson explained to the Washington Post that this is because the company doesn't have a policy that says that the information you post on their platform must be true.<br/><br/>Facebook's new policy would also not restrict simpler forms of video deception. This includes mislabeled footage, or trimming a video to make something a person says sound out of context.<br/><br/>Another Facebook spokesperson said in a statement that the company would remove political ads if they include highly manipulated videos.<br/><br/>A digital forensics expert from UC Berkeley told the Washington Post in an email that the social media giant should focus on the issue of removing misleading videos in general instead of just deepfake videos.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/deepfake-videos-banned-on-facebook-3946695</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946695/3946695_DA12A5AC75DF4AC79C8C5FFFCA16DED9_200108_3946695_Deepfake_videos_banned_on_Facebook_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 11:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946656</guid>
      <title>How the moon lost its magnetic field one billion years ago</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS <br/> Billions of years ago, the ancient moon had a powerful dynamo at its core that produced a strong global magnetic field.<br/><br/>Scientists at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology say that they have pinned down when that dynamo stopped, leading to the field's dissipation.<br/><br/>In a study published in Science Advances, researchers say that the Apollo mission collected lunar rocks that preserve a record of the moon's ancient magnetic field.<br/><br/>However, most of these rocks dated to between 3 and 4 billion years, or too long ago for studying the end of the moon's internal dynamo. <br/><br/>To research the moon's later magnetic history, the scientists tested two samples that were 1 billion years old and found them to record a weak lunar magnetic field. <br/><br/>As the rocks were left by a meteor impact, scientists reheated the rocks and obtained the same readings to make sure the impact's heat did not interfere with the rocks' magnetic records.<br/><br/>According to the MIT news release, the moon used to be much closer to earth, and the gravitational effect caused the liquid lunar core to wobble, which created the magnetic field.<br/><br/>The weak magnetism recorded by the two rocks suggests the gravitational effects had begun to seize up one billion years ago.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-moon-lost-its-magnetic-field-one-billion-years-ago-3946656</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946656/3946656_A62F51F7F75541D1A2EF25EF40E40FCA_200108_3946656_How_the_moon_lost_its_magnetic_field_one_billion_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 10:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3946538</guid>
      <title>Mysterious virus sickens dozens in central China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> A mysterious strain of viral pneumonia has affected 59 people in Wuhan, China since mid-December 2019, China Daily reports. <br/><br/>The cause of the infection has yet to be determined.<br/><br/>According to the Wuhan Municipal Health Commission, some of the victims were sellers at a local seafood market, sparking fear that the virus may have been transmitted from animals to humans. The market has since been temporarily shut down for disinfection, and patients placed in quarantine.<br/><br/>Symptoms of the virus include fever, with a few of the patients having breathing difficulties. Chest X-rays from the victims show invasive lesions on both lungs.<br/><br/>Wuhan's health commission said that they have eliminated the possibility of the virus being SARS, MERS or bird flu.<br/><br/>Although a preliminary analysis found no clear evidence of the virus being transmitted from one human to another, at least 163 others were placed under medical observation for coming into close contact with the infected.<br/><br/>Asian nations such as Singapore and Hong Kong have taken precautionary measures to prevent the spread of the virus by conducting temperature screenings at airports for visitors from China, as reported by BBC News. <br/><br/>The World Health Organization said on its website that it "does not recommend any specific measure for travelers." They said that they are closely monitoring the situation and are in close contact with authorities in China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mysterious-virus-sickens-dozens-in-central-china-3946538</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/08/3946538/3946538_07DEB296BB5A44E3AC477D058897D84A_200108_3946538_Mysterious_virus_sickens_dozens_in_central_China_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 07:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947135</guid>
      <title>SpaceX just put 60 satellites in orbit with one rocket</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAPE CANAVERAL, FLORIDA <br/>   SpaceX launched its third batch of Starlink satellites into orbit from a U.S. Air Force base in Florida on Monday evening.<br/><br/>Space.com reports that a Falcon 9 rocket carried the satellites in its first stage and that the launch marked the second time SpaceX reused a booster four times.<br/><br/>Citing SpaceX, AFP reports that after deployment, the satellites would utilize ion thrusters to reach an orbit of 550 km to avoid collisions at higher, more congested space.<br/><br/>MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX now operates 180 Starlinks, making the company the owner of the world's largest constellation of commercial satellites.<br/><br/>According to the publication, the reusable first stage booster was successfully recovered by a drone ship in the Atlantic Ocean, but not the payload fairing.<br/><br/>The lost component is worth an estimated US$3 million.<br/><br/>However, the program has come under criticism because the satellites reflect glare that interferes with astronomical observatories.<br/><br/>The MIT Technology Review reports that SpaceX has applied a light absorbing coating to the new satellites to address those concerns.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/spacex-just-put-60-satellites-in-orbit-with-one-rocket-3947135</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947135/3947135_92C9C1CA406B410DA7698CA373989AB8_200109_3947135_SpaceX_just_put_60_satellites_in_orbit_with_one__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 11:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947004</guid>
      <title>NASA finds Earth-size world in habitable-zone</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON  <br/>  NASA's Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite, or 'TESS' mission, devised to specifically find Earth-sized planets orbiting nearby stars has identified TOI 700 d as a potential candidate occupying a star's habitable zone where conditions may be just right to allow the presence of liquid water on the surface.<br/><br/>NASA explains that TESS observes large regions of the sky known as sectors for 27 days at a time. TESS identifies and tracks changes in stellar brightness caused by an orbiting planet passing in front of its star.<br/><br/>During recent observations, TESS tracked a total of three planets.<br/><br/>The closest to the star, TOI 700 b is Earth-sized, rocky and has an orbit of ten days. The middle planet, TOI 700 c, is 2.6 times larger than Earth, likely gas-dominated and orbits every 16 days. TOI 700 d, the only one in the habitable zone, measures 20 percent larger than Earth and orbits every 37 days.<br/><br/>While the exact conditions on TOI 700 d are unknown, researchers at NASA's Goddard Space Flight Center created models to explore its potential conditions to help narrow future predictions of the planet's atmosphere. One model showed a water-covered world and the other, a completely dry version of today's earth. <br/><br/>NASA says that future missions, "may be able to identify whether the planets have atmospheres and, if so, even determine their compositions."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-finds-earth-size-world-in-habitable-zone-3947004</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/09/3947004/3947004_03B7BD50AE614C91AB9FBCB5B4D8BA79_200109_3947004_NASA_finds_Earth_size_world_in_habitable_zone_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 07:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947345</guid>
      <title>Toyota to transform site at Mt. Fuji base into a futuristic city</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> Danish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group has been commissioned by Toyota to build a prototype futuristic city called Woven City at the base of Mt. Fuji in Japan.<br/><br/>In a press release, Toyota said the city will be built on a 175-acre site and will be used to test futuristic vehicles, AI robots and smart homes in a "real-world environment."<br/><br/>Designs of the city were unveiled at the Consumer Electronic Show in Las Vegas on January 7.<br/><br/>Woven City will include buildings made mostly of wood for sustainability, with its rooftops covered with solar panels to produce energy. In addition to solar power, the city will also be powered by hydrogen fuel cells.<br/><br/>Homes will be equipped with AI robots and sensors to take care of residents' basic needs and to monitor their health.<br/><br/>The futuristic city's main roads will only allow fully-autonomous vehicles, such as the Toyota e-Palettes, to operate. There will be separate roads for pedestrians and those using personal mobility vehicles such as bicycles.<br/><br/>A central plaza, neighborhood parks and a large central park will be included for social gatherings among residents.<br/><br/>Toyota explained in its press release that it plans to populate the city with company employees, families, retired couples, visiting scientists and others.<br/><br/>The city will initially be populated with 2,000 people. The company plans to break ground by early 2021.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/toyota-to-transform-site-at-mt-fuji-base-into-a-futuristic-city-3947345</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947345/3947345_B4556CFCD5DC4F1384B00F27E40362FB_200110_3947345_Toyota_to_transform_site_at_Mt__Fuji_base_into_a_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 02:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947575</guid>
      <title>Israel claims breakthrough in anti-missile laser weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEL AVIV, ISRAEL <br/> Israel's Defense Ministry says in a news release that it made a technological breakthrough in a defensive laser weapon that intercepts aerial threats.<br/><br/>Israel-based Defense Update reports that the laser can shoot down range rockets fired at close range and other threats that are too costly for the Iron Dome to engage.<br/><br/>Defense Update reports that Israeli air defense batteries, armored vehicles and aerial drones will be outfitted with the lasers to bolster defense systems already in use.<br/><br/>The Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon is electrically powered and that it combines multiple beams into one beam capable of overcoming atmospheric conditions. <br/><br/>The active defense system is precise and the laser has successfully intercepted various projectiles in tests, including mortar shells and anti-tank missiles.<br/><br/>Citing a military researcher, the Jerusalem Post reports that the weapon could fire a beam the diameter of a coin from Tel Aviv to Herzliya, which "provides a dramatic solution to rocket fire."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/israel-claims-breakthrough-in-anti-missile-laser-weapons-3947575</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947575/3947575_9FD81847F7004CAC8669A5ECAF2A744A_200110_3947575_Israel_claims_breakthrough_in_anti_missile_laser_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 09:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3947741</guid>
      <title>Sky Green towers built in Taichung, Taiwan</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAICHUNG, TAIWAN <br/> Singaporean architectural firm WOHA has designed a sustainable, mixed-use building called Sky Green, in Taichung, Taiwan.<br/><br/>According to the company's project website, the development features two towers with sky gardens and terraces filled with lush greenery.<br/><br/>One of the tower's facades is lined with mesh screens with vegetation on it, while the other consists of balconies with plants and other flora.<br/><br/>The first three floors of the structure includes retail stores, while the rest of the building consists of residential apartments stacked on top of one another.<br/><br/>The tower's interior offers open spaces with green vegetation for residents to relax in.<br/><br/>According to Arch Daily, the design of the structure was chosen to adapt to Taiwan's local culture and climate.<br/><br/>Construction on the building was completed in November of 2019.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sky-green-towers-built-in-taichung-taiwan-3947741</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/10/3947741/3947741_7400DFD523F8433896C18AE9E5F752A9_200110_3947741_Sky_Green_towers_built_in_Taichung__Taiwan_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 13:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948711</guid>
      <title>Vulnerabilities found in video-sharing app TikTok</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN CARLOS, CALIFORNIA <br/> Cybersecurity firm Check Point has conducted an investigation into video-sharing app TikTok and found major vulnerabilities within the app.<br/><br/>In a report, researchers from the company explained that hackers could access a person's account by using a function on TikTok's website that allows users to enter their phone number, which will text them a link to download the app.<br/><br/>Hackers could use this flaw to change the download url and send a fraudulent SMS link containing a malicious link created by the attacker. This allowed attackers to access a user's account and to send requests on their behalf.<br/><br/>Attackers could use this to manipulate a user's content feed by deleting videos from their feed and uploading unauthorized videos onto their feed instead. Hackers would also have the authority to change a user's video privacy settings from hidden, or private, to public.<br/><br/>Researchers found that attackers could also execute JavaScript code in order to retrieve sensitive information about the user. This includes emails, payment information or birthdates.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, Check Point said they informed TikTok's parent company ByteDance about the vulnerabilities in November.<br/><br/>TikTok says the security flaws have since been fixed in their latest app version.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/vulnerabilities-found-in-video-sharing-app-tiktok-3948711</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948711/3948711_C335D815DCF940CCA8D0DF01CA17FF2C_200113_3948711_Vulnerabilities_found_in_video_sharing_app_TikTo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 04:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948923</guid>
      <title>U.S. Army is retooling to fight in the Indo-Pacific Region</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The U.S. Army will deploy two task forces with the ability to fight across the information, electronic, cyber and missile domains in the Pacific to counter China.<br/><br/>Reuters reports that Army Secretary Ryan McCarthy said at a Brookings Institute event on Friday that the multi-domain task forces will be established in two years.<br/><br/>Although McCarthy did not specify any locations, Bloomberg News speculates that those units will likely be based on islands east of Taiwan and the Philippines.<br/><br/>Citing McCarthy, Reuters reports the U.S. Army intends to "neutralize all the investments China and Russia have made."<br/><br/>China's military strategy calls for blocking U.S. naval forces from entering the Pacific through the first and second island chains.<br/><br/>The People's Liberation Army intends to achieve this by utilizing surveillance satellites and building up its arsenal of anti-ship ballistic missiles.<br/><br/>The task forces would potentially be armed with hypersonic missiles and other weapons capable of attacking land and sea based targets.<br/><br/>Reuters reports that these units will help neutralize the capabilities China and Russia now possess.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-army-is-retooling-to-fight-in-the-indo-pacific-region-3948923</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948923/3948923_E43ACBACC8CE4A508C5278116E70CEB4_200113_3948923_U_S__Army_is_retooling_to_fight_in_the_Indo_Paci_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948902</guid>
      <title>NASA completes the booster for its 'mega-rocket'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW ORLEANS <br/> NASA rolled out the core stage of the Space Launch System 'mega-rocket' from a New Orleans factory on Wednesday.<br/><br/>BBC reports that the core stage was loaded onto the Pegasus barge to sail down the Mississippi River for testing at the Stennis Space Center.<br/><br/>According to NASA, the SLS rocket is the backbone of U.S. plans to land on the moon again by 2024 and to explore Mars. It has a top speed of Mach 23.<br/><br/>NASA states that the rocket's core stage is 212 feet tall and 27.6 feet wide, making it the largest booster ever built.<br/><br/>The core stage features a forward skirt for housing avionics, a liquid oxygen fuel tank, an intertank that joins the boosters' tanks, a liquid hydrogen fuel tank and quadruple RS-24 engines.<br/><br/>The four engines create more than 2 million pounds of combined thrust.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that the SLS will deliver the Orion spacecraft<br/>which is undergoing testing<br/>to Luna for the uncrewed Artemis 1 mission planned for the next year.<br/><br/>According to European Space Agency, the Orion spacecraft will feature foldable solar panels and it will orbit the moon for the Artemis 1 mission.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-completes-the-booster-for-its-mega-rocket--3948902</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948902/3948902_55C0B65D79264A84A2F3FE9B2BAFEC05_200113_3948902_NASA_completes_the_booster_for_its__mega_rocket__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 11:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3948777</guid>
      <title>The Chinese paddlefish is extinct</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANGTZE, CHINA <br/> The Chinese paddlefish has been declared extinct. But what was it and why has this happened?<br/><br/>The Chinese paddlefish was thought to be the world's largest freshwater fish with an average length of 10 feet. Some reports recorded them reaching 23 feet and weighing half a ton.<br/><br/>The Chinese paddlefish had a long, silver-gray body and their name derived from their protruding snout that resembled a paddle.<br/><br/>The fish were prominent in many parts of the Yangtze, Asia's largest river flowing 3914 miles from the Tibetan Plateau to the East China Sea.<br/><br/>They used their special sword-like snout to sense electrical activity to find prey, such as crustaceans and fish, however, they haven't been spotted since 2003.<br/><br/>In the journal Science of The Total Environment, a team of researchers at the Chinese Academy of Fishery Sciences in Wuhan declared the paddlefish as extinct. <br/><br/>They believe overfishing in the 1970s, which harvested 25 tons of paddlefish per year on average was the root cause of the gradual decline in paddlefish.<br/><br/>However, the main contributor which led to extinction was the loss of habitat through the construction of the Gezhouba Dam, built on the main stem of the Yangtze.<br/><br/>The dam was constructed without a fish ladder or bypass, cutting off the paddlefish from their only spawning grounds upstream.<br/><br/>The team tried to locate the paddlefish at hundreds of locations along the Yangtze using nets, sonar and electro-fishing gear.<br/><br/>Researchers even monitored fish markets around the country but found nothing.<br/><br/>Based on the previous population size and the intervals between sightings, the researchers used a mathematical model to determine the likelihood that the species is, in fact, extinct and most likely went extinct between 2005 and 2010.<br/><br/>The researchers believe that this is a hard lesson in conservation. Sadly, efforts to save the paddlefish did not begin until the fish had already gone.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-chinese-paddlefish-is-extinct-3948777</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/13/3948777/3948777_BEE653C905874F2481A0E87663FCA42E_200113_3948777_The_Chinese_paddlefish_is_extinct_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 07:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949152</guid>
      <title>Water on Mars is evaporating faster than expected</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS <br/> New research by France's National Center for Scientific Research suggests that water on Mars is evaporating faster than previously thought.<br/><br/>Scientists analyzed data from the Trace Gas Orbiter, which orbits around Mars, and found seasonal changes affect how water vapor is distributed around the atmosphere.<br/><br/>As the sun warms up the red planet's ice poles, water molecules, in the form of water vapor, are released into the atmosphere. The molecules are then carried by the wind to higher altitudes.<br/><br/>During the warmest parts of the year, Mars' atmosphere becomes "supersaturated" with 10 to 100 times more water vapor than its frigid cold temperatures typically allow. This allows the water to reach the planet's upper atmosphere.<br/><br/>As water molecules make their way to Mars' upper atmosphere, ultraviolet rays from the sun breaks them down into hydrogen and oxygen atoms where the atoms are able to escape into space.<br/><br/>The researchers were surprised at their findings, as they expected that the water vapor would be limited by Mars' cold temperatures and would condense into clouds, according to Space.com.<br/><br/>Franck Montmessin, one of the scientists involved with the study, told the publication that further research would be needed to find out how much water exactly is making its way to Mars' upper atmosphere and escaping so that scientists can get a better understanding of the process.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/water-on-mars-is-evaporating-faster-than-expected-3949152</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949152/3949152_2D49B0F5DAF8449AB1818AEC15B36F6A_200114_3949152_Water_on_Mars_is_evaporating_faster_than_expecte_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 03:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949364</guid>
      <title>Japan will upgrade air defense missiles to counter North Korea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> Japan's Type-03 Air Defense System is a surface to air missile system that utilizes a truck-mounted launcher to shoot interceptor missiles, according to Missile Advocacy.<br/><br/>Citing unnamed defense officials, Japan Forward reports the Japanese military will give the missile an anti-ballistic capability to respond to the North Korean threat.<br/><br/>According to Global Security, the Chu-SAM is 490 cm long, 30 cm wide, and weighs 580 kg.<br/><br/>Missile Advocacy states that the current version of the missile has a top speed of Mach 2.5.<br/><br/>According to Global Defense, the rocket uses a single stage solid fuel design and includes an active radar homing system.<br/><br/>Japan Forward reports that the Defense Agency is testing technologies that will improve both components of the projectile.<br/><br/>North Korea's new ballistic missile, which was tested last year and is based on Russia's Iskander missile, flies in an erratic trajectory that Japan's other air defense missiles cannot track.<br/><br/>According to Japan Forward, the upgraded the Chu-SAM will be able to predict the irregular trajectory and achieve a shootdown of the enemy missile.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/japan-will-upgrade-air-defense-missiles-to-counter-north-korea-3949364</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949364/3949364_EEA2985530AF4A4F81E88C94353E11BB_200114_3949364_Japan_will_upgrade_air_defense_missiles_to_count_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 11:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949347</guid>
      <title>Philippines Taal volcano could be about ready to blow</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANILA, PHILIPPINES <br/> Philippine officials have urged a "total evacuation" of millions of people close to Manila, after a volcano spewed ash up to nine miles into the air on Sunday, prompting warnings of a possible "explosive eruption," CNN reports. <br/>The BBC reports that early Monday, a weak flow of lava began seeping out of Taal volcano, which is located around 45 miles south of Manila. <br/>According to the BBC, Taal had earlier emitted a huge plume of ash, triggering the mass evacuation of 8,000 people from the immediate area. <br/>The BBC cites that Taal is the country's second most active volcano, located in the middle of a lake. <br/>CNN reports that the Philippine Institute of Volcanology and Seismology<br/>PHIVOLCS<br/>has raised the alert lever to four, meaning an "explosive eruption" could happen in the coming hours or days. The highest alert level is five, indicating that an eruption is taking place. <br/>According to CNN, in explosive eruptions, magma is fragmented and violently released from the volcano as opposed to thick lava flowing out. <br/>PHIVOLCS has requested a "total evacuation" of citizens within a 10.5 mile radius around the volcano.    <br/>The BBC reports that Taal is also one of the world's smallest volcanoes and has recorded at least 34 eruptions in the past 450 years.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/philippines-taal-volcano-could-be-about-ready-to-blow-3949347</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/14/3949347/3949347_8B27B8FFF9A54326905289AA91A8FF42_200114_3949347_Philippines_Taal_volcano_could_be_about_ready_to_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2020 10:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949580</guid>
      <title>New artificial trees to absorb pollution in London</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> German startup Green City Solutions has installed artificial trees called CityTrees across London to absorb urban pollution.<br/><br/>According to the company's website, the CityTree is the world's first bio-tech filter that has been able to considerably improve air quality.<br/><br/>The CityTree is a tower filled with different types of moss which collect toxins such as particulate matters such as PM 10 and nitrogen dioxide from the air while giving off oxygen. Each artificial tree is able to produce as much clean air as 275 real trees, according to Dezeen.<br/><br/>The structure is powered by solar panels and collects rainwater which is evenly distributed using a fully automated irrigation system.<br/><br/>Green City Solutions explains on their website that the CityTrees also contain Internet-of-Things technology to gather environmental data about the trees' surrounding as well as data about its own performance. <br/><br/>The artificial trees also have the ability to create an immense cooling effect in its surrounding atmosphere as mosses can store large amounts of moisture.<br/><br/>CityTrees were previously trialled in London in 2018 as a trial. The current project is a permanent installation.<br/><br/>The structures have previously been installed in Oslo, Paris, Brussels and Hong Kong,  according to CNN.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-artificial-trees-to-absorb-pollution-in-london-3949580</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949580/3949580_312EEF18DFAC405B99858A11C3566630_200115_3949580_New_artificial_trees_to_absorb_pollution_in_Lond_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 02:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3949809</guid>
      <title>EU, Russia to launch ExoMars mission in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZURICH, SWITZERLAND <br/> The EU and Russia are collaborating on a mission to Mars to try and answer the question of whether life has ever existed on the Red Planet.<br/><br/>According to the European Space Agency, the ExoMars programme is comprised of two missions. The first <br/> the Trace Gas Orbiter <br/> launched in 2016 to orbit Mars and examined its atmosphere.<br/><br/>The Schiaparelli lander had been deployed with the Trace Gas Orbiter to the surface but crashed during a touchdown attempt.<br/><br/>The second mission, slated for July 2020, will launch Roscosmos' Kazachok surface platform and the ESA's Rosalind Franklin rover to Mars via a Proton rocket.<br/><br/>After a nine-month journey, a descent module will separate from the carrier and perform a controlled landing on the surface of the Red Planet, at a site called the Oxia Planum.<br/><br/>Space reports that the Oxia Planum is a plain in the planet's northern hemisphere that is rich in clay deposits, indicating ancient water activity.<br/><br/>After touchdown, the Kazachok platform will remain at the landing site to study the surface environment. Instruments on board will be used to take images of the landing point, study subsurface water distribution, as well as the planet's atmosphere and internal structure.<br/><br/>The rover, meanwhile, will travel across the planet's surface, using stereo cameras to build navigation maps and collision avoidance cameras to navigate the terrain. It will drill up to 2 meters down to retrieve underground samples that may contain preserved biomarkers, which will be subject to chemical, physical, and spectral analysis.<br/><br/>New Atlas reports that the mission has had trouble in the past with the parachutes, which tore in high-altitude tests.<br/><br/>The team has since worked with NASA to iron out the issues, and have announced that the previous problems have been eliminated. But to be sure, further tests will be conducted ahead of the official launch later in the year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/eu-russia-to-launch-exomars-mission-in-2020-3949809</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/15/3949809/3949809_F798EF2EB06445038E23332BBFAB685F_200115_3949809_EU__Russia_to_launch_ExoMars_mission_in_2020_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 10:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950362</guid>
      <title>Satellite images show Philippines Taal volcano erupting</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TALISAY, PHILIPPINES <br/> The eruption of Taal volcano in the Philippines was so big that it was visible from space.<br/><br/>Japanese satellite Himawari-8 captured a series of images from space showing plumes of smoke from the volcano that erupted on January 12, according to Live Science. <br/><br/>The images were put together to create an animation and were released by NASA's Earth Observatory. In the satellite images, the volcano is seen spreading its volcanic plumes across the surrounding area from January 12 to 13.<br/><br/>On Sunday, ash spewed out of the volcano as high as nine miles up into the air, CNN reports. Taal continues to create dark gray plumes that rise up to 0.6 miles high since the eruption began a couple of days ago. <br/><br/>The Philippine Institute of Volcanology and Seismology has said that the volcano may continue to erupt in the next few days.<br/><br/>Authorities ordered a total evacuation for those who live within 8.7 miles of the volcano, while those who live within 10.6 miles were advised to leave. Images show houses near the volcano buried in volcanic ash while animals that were left behind were captured with their fur and feathers covered with ash, according to CNN. <br/><br/>Philippine's Institute of Volcanology and Seismology has raised the alert level for Taal volcano to a level 4. This means that the volcano may have an "explosive eruption" very soon, either in a few hours or in the coming days.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/satellite-images-show-philippines-taal-volcano-erupting-3950362</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950362/3950362_B2F65B3B50DB4B428BF05B52C240E09C_200116_3950362_Satellite_images_show_Philippines_Taal_volcano_e_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950341</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy's new missiles will be strike anyway in an hour</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ARLINGTON, VIRGINIA <br/> The U.S. Navy plans to arm the fleet's newest destroyers with a classified hypersonic missile.<br/><br/>Citing a naval officer's remarks at the Surface Naval Association's annual symposium, Fox News reports that the Zumwalt class may obtain the Conventional Prompt Strike weapon.<br/><br/>The Zumwalts are stealthy warships that feature two advanced 155mm guns, vertical launching systems, advanced radars in the deckhouse, and electric drive propulsion. <br/><br/>No details about the prompt strike weapons are available, but Fox reports that the missile combines a conventional warhead with a ballistic missile.<br/><br/>This allows the U.S. to launch conventional strikes with the speed and range of nuclear weapons.<br/><br/>According to Fox, the stealthy warships will be able to deliver missiles to any target in the world in an hour and some targets could be struck within minutes.<br/><br/>The outlet reports that the missiles will potentially allow the U.S. to launch attacks rapidly and without giving away time or the element of surprise.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-navy-s-new-missiles-will-be-strike-anyway-in-an-hour-3950341</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950341/3950341_8CAC082E99784027BF9A2DC558403653_200116_3950341_U_S__Navy_s_new_missiles_will_be_strike_anyway_i_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950335</guid>
      <title>The solar system's 'Great Divide' explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO  <br/> A separation known as the Great Divide splits the rocky planets and the gas planets in our solar system.<br/><br/>According to the latest paper published in Nature Astronomy, researchers can now explain how the divide came to exist.<br/><br/>Citing the researchers, University of Colorado's news release says that rocky planets in the sunward side of the divide are poor in carbon and other organic materials.<br/><br/>The opposite is true for the gas planets beyond the divide, such as Jupiter, which is rich in carbon.<br/><br/>The paper theorizes that billions of years ago, the sun may have once had a massive ring structure with alternating high and low pressure bands.<br/><br/>Those bands would separate matter into distinct sinks, one forming Jupiter and Saturn, and another Earth and Mars. This results in the Great Divide.<br/><br/>A paper co-author says that the pressure barrier was not impenetrable, as enough materials from outer space have likely crossed over.<br/><br/>The carbon rich material that had climbed the divide would then play a role in the evolution of life on Earth.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-solar-system-s-great-divide-explained-3950335</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950335/3950335_1C629C1431834449B4A64A11D28973F4_200116_3950335_The_solar_system_s__Great_Divide__explained_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950324</guid>
      <title>NASA's Journey to Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> NASA's road to Mars is via the moon.<br/><br/>NASA's Moon to Mars exploration program first proposed in 2015 consists of three phases.<br/><br/>The first, called 'Earth Reliant', involves using the International Space Station until 2024 to research deep space technologies, and study the effects of long-term space missions on the human body.<br/><br/>It also covers the development of the Orion spacecraft and the Space Launch System super heavy lift launch vehicle, or SLS.<br/><br/>The second phase, 'Proving Grounds', involves the creation of infrastructure in cislunar space such as the Lunar Orbital Platform Gateway, to help the agency learn how to conduct operations in a deep space environment.<br/><br/>The Gateway space station is slated for completion in the mid-2020s. According to Space.com, NASA's 2019 fiscal budget request calls for a 2022 launch of the power and propulsion module. Two additional launches by 2025 will add habitation, logistics, and airlock functions.<br/><br/>According to the ESA, Gateway will serve as a staging post where astronauts can dock and leave their spacecraft, then travel to the lunar surface in a lander.<br/><br/>It will also provide them shelter, a place to stock up on fuel and supplies and relay communications, and a base to dispatch crew and robots to the moon.<br/><br/>Missions to Mars and its moons would begin during 'Earth Independent', the third and final phase, which could see NASA using the Lunar Gateway and a spacecraft such as the Deep Space Transport.<br/><br/>According to Universe Today, a station in the Red Planet's orbit, like Lockheed Martin's proposed Mars Base Camp, could also be built to allow crewed missions to journey to the Martian surface.<br/><br/>Based on a White House directive, NASA will be aiming to land astronauts on the moon by 2024, and then on Mars by the 2030s.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-s-journey-to-mars-3950324</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/16/3950324/3950324_685084D0601C47FDB1478429F352CEC3_200116_3950324_NASA_s_Journey_to_Mars_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 10:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950604</guid>
      <title>Golden tower planned for Toronto</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TORONTO <br/> Canadian architectural firm Giannone Petricone Associates has unveiled plans to build a 79-story golden tower in Toronto. The skyscraper would be 266 meters in height.<br/><br/>The building's exterior resembles a pleated curtain which reflects sunlight from different angles to create a sense of movement, according to Urban Toronto. The development would cover a gross floor area of roughly 121,965 square meters.<br/><br/>It would include three levels of retail space at the bottom of the building, while the rest of the tower would be residential.<br/><br/>The building's main lobby would include escalators to the tower's shopping areas, while elevators would be available for residents looking to return home or visit the building's sky lobby.<br/><br/>Architects have also proposed a five-level underground garage and 500 bicycle parking spaces, reports Urban Toronto.  Once completed, the building would be connected to Toronto's Bay subway station.<br/><br/>According to Urban Toronto, if the building was completed today, it would be the fifth tallest building in the city.<br/><br/>Toronto is expected to surpass Chicago as home to the second highest number of skyscrapers in North America, Bloomberg reports , citing data from the Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitat. <br/><br/>The city is currently home to 67 skyscrapers. Toronto currently has 31 skyscrapers under construction and has proposed an additional 59 towers.<br/><br/>Chicago now has 126 skyscrapers and 19 other skyscrapers that are either under construction or have been proposed.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/golden-tower-planned-for-toronto-3950604</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950604/3950604_29EEBC7893D44633B566A14DA3777134_200117_3950604_Golden_tower_planned_for_Toronto_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 02:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950838</guid>
      <title>Scientists found weird celestial objects near the galactic core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> Scientists identified a new class of celestial bodies near the Sagittarius A, the Milky Way Galaxy's supermassive black hole.<br/><br/>According to the paper in Nature Astronomy, the six strange objects, named G1 through G6, orbit around Sagittarius A in circuits that range from 100 to 1,000 years.<br/><br/>Citing the authors, the University of California Los Angeles says that as the objects are close to Sagittarius A, the black hole stretches them out of shape and strip away their outer gas shell.<br/><br/>Observing one of the objects G2, the researchers found that even after the black hole dramatically elongates its gas shell, the object retains a relatively coherent dust core.<br/><br/>This suggests G2--and by inference, the rest of the G-class objects--had stellar objects inside the core.<br/><br/>Co-author and UCLA professor Andrea Ghez speculates that all six G objects were formerly binary stars that fell under the black hole's influence.<br/><br/>Ghez says that Sagittarius A's powerful gravity may have caused the binary stars to merge and to give rise to the weird G-class objects.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-found-weird-celestial-objects-near-the-galactic-core-3950838</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950838/3950838_AC11AF0DC35F4E04A2B2F595BFC49188_200117_3950838_Scientists_found_weird_celestial_objects_near_th_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950821</guid>
      <title>This skyscraper is set to become the tallest building in Canada</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TORONTO <br/> Supertall skyscraper "The One" is set to become the tallest building in Canada at 309 meters once it is completed in Toronto later this year.<br/><br/>The mixed-use development is designed by British architecture firm Foster + Partners and Canadian design firm Core Architects.<br/><br/>The skyscraper's exterior consists of multiple champagne-hued rectangular blocks stacked on top of one another. The tower's facade has two diagonal columns with diagonal bracing on each side of the building.<br/><br/>Residents will be able to see the diagonal bracing through their window as they look out to the city.<br/><br/>The top of the skyscraper will feature a green space with trees, according to Urban Toronto. The 85-story tower will include retail stores, restaurants, hotels and apartments.<br/><br/>Toronto currently has 67 skyscrapers and is set to add 31 more to its skyline. An additional 59 skyscrapers have been proposed by architects and design firms. <br/><br/>According to data from the Council on Tall Buildings and Urban Habitat, this will make Toronto home to the second highest number of skyscrapers in North America.<br/><br/>Chicago currently has 126 skyscrapers while 19 other skyscrapers are either under construction or have been proposed for the city.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/this-skyscraper-is-set-to-become-the-tallest-building-in-canada-3950821</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950821/3950821_A34EC53EC0394B08A447D1FE3B137124_200117_3950821_This_skyscraper_is_set_to_become_the_tallest_bui_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 09:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3950962</guid>
      <title>Sepsis causes one in five deaths around the world: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE <br/> A study in The Lancet estimates that sepsis is associated with one in five deaths around the world, or more deaths than cancer.<br/><br/>Citing the authors, the University of Washington says in a news release that the study's figure doubled the previous estimates of global sepsis deaths.<br/><br/>Sepsis is triggered by diarrhoeal infections or lung diseases that cause the immune system to overreact.<br/><br/>The immune cells attack the patient's own body and can lead to organ failure followed by death.<br/> <br/>In adults, sepsis symptoms include passing little urine, shivering, extreme shivering or muscle pain, and mottled or discolored skin.<br/><br/>According to the paper, low and middle income countries are overwhelmingly more affected by sepsis cases.<br/><br/>Those deaths could have been prevented by better sanitation, clean water, and access to vaccines.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sepsis-causes-one-in-five-deaths-around-the-world-study-3950962</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/17/3950962/3950962_6ABFD04EF5F642AEBE8B5601A812DE4B_200117_3950962_Sepsis_causes_one_in_five_deaths_around_the_worl_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2020 12:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952136</guid>
      <title>China's virus outbreak may be a lot worse than Beijing reported</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> Citing Chinese officials, the BBC reports that the coronavirus outbreak in China's city of Wuhan has killed three people and infected over 200 as of Monday.<br/><br/>The news comes days after researchers at London Imperial College's MRC Centre for Global Infectious Disease Analysis warned that there may be far more infection cases than what Beijing had reported.<br/><br/>Citing the MRC GIDA, the BBC reports that the China-based virus outbreak has infected two people in Thailand and one in Japan.<br/><br/>The researchers say that their model, based on the virus, Wuhan's population and flight data, estimates that more than 1,700 people have been infected.<br/><br/>Chinese authorities speculate that the virus likely crossed the species barrier from infected animals to people at a seafood and wildlife market in Wuhan.<br/><br/>Citing an MRC-GIDA researcher, the BBC says that the authorities should seriously consider the possibility of "substantial human-to-human transmission."<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the new coronavirus more closely resembles SARs than any other viral strain.<br/><br/>Coronavirus is a large family of viruses and only seven are known to infect humans, including the new one discovered in China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-virus-outbreak-may-be-a-lot-worse-than-beijing-reported-3952136</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952136/3952136_1CF60CABF68F4976930718A7029DF9B1_200120_3952136_China_s_virus_outbreak_may_be_a_lot_worse_than_B_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 11:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952093</guid>
      <title>British fish species projected to decline over the next 30 years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> A new report by the Marine Climate Change Impacts Partnership has predicted that cold-water fish species in British waters may be replaced with warm-water species as sea temperatures continue to rise in the next 30 years.<br/><br/>Researchers explained that local fish such as cod may decline and be replaced with fish that are typically found in warmer waters, such as the European anchovy.<br/><br/>The study also pointed out that the number of Atlantic bluefin tuna has been increasing in British waters, and that this may be partially related to rising temperatures.<br/><br/>Likewise, warming waters has caused mackerel to become the dominant fish off of Scotland's west coast over the past 30 years, while the Northern hake has repopulated in the northern part of the North Sea after being largely absent for more than 50 years.<br/><br/>The study also predicts that fish may evolve to have smaller bodies as oxygen levels decrease in the warming waters, and fish have to swim farther to find food.<br/><br/>Researchers involved in the study explained that this could be bad news for the British fishing industry, which could face a limited quota allocation, and may have to make their livelihood with tinier fish.<br/><br/>They projected the net value of the British fishing industry to decrease by 10 percent by 2050 under a "high-emissions scenario."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/british-fish-species-projected-to-decline-over-the-next-30-years-3952093</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3952093/3952093_8E1E3198A8ED4544941D78D743757046_200120_3952093_British_fish_species_projected_to_decline_over_t_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 10:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3951939</guid>
      <title>How sugar addiction impacts the brain</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AARHUS, DENMARK <br/> New research from the journal Scientific Reports has found that sugar has the ability to transform our brain chemistry.<br/><br/>Scientists from Denmark's Aarhus University performed their experiment on seven pigs to test out their theory. These pigs were fed two liters of sugar water on a daily basis over a 12-day period.<br/><br/>The pigs' brains were imaged using a brain scanner prior to the experiment, after the first day of the experiment and after the last day of the experiment.<br/><br/>Researchers found significant changes in the pigs' brains' dopamine and opioid systems.<br/><br/>Michael Witherdahl, one the researchers involved in the study, said in a Aarhus University press release that the pigs' opioid system, which is associated with well-being and pleasure, had been activated after the pig's first sugar intake.<br/><br/>Witherdahl explained both natural stimuli and artificial stimuli have the ability to activate the brain to release dopamine and opioids.<br/><br/>He said humans may end up replacing natural stimuli, such as socializing, with artificial stimuli, such as sugar, in order to get a rush of dopamine and opioids to the brain.<br/><br/>As part of the bigger picture, the study was looking to see how palatable food, such as sugar, is addicting and how it affects the human body.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-sugar-addiction-impacts-the-brain-3951939</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/20/3951939/3951939_7441A7CF7B934E8ABCA5A9BD5AD037D0_200120_3951939_How_sugar_addiction_impacts_the_brain_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 07:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3952618</guid>
      <title>Novel coronavirus infection just tripled in China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Cases of novel coronavirus infection in China have tripled over the weekend, sparking global concerns about an outbreak.<br/><br/>China's state-run Xinhua News reports that there are 218 confirmed cases, mostly in the city of Wuhan. The BBC reports that three have died and nine are in critical condition.<br/><br/>China Daily yesterday reported that a fourth fatality occurred in Wuhan, where 15 medical workers have caught the disease as they try to help the patients.<br/><br/>Millions of Chinese are traveling in the country to celebrate the Lunar New Year vacation, which will begin on Friday.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that the virus has spread, with five cases in Beijing, one in Shanghai and one in Shenzhen.<br/><br/>Outside of China, four cases have been confirmed, two in Thailand, one in Japan and a new case in South Korea.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that in each case, the infected person had recently visited Wuhan before falling ill.<br/><br/>Scientists believe the infection's main source is animal-based and have advised people not to handle live chickens without protection and to thoroughly cook meat and eggs.<br/><br/>However, China's state-run Xinhua News Agency reports that health officials have confirmed that human to human transmission has occurred in two cases.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, genetic analysis has identified the pathogen as a SARS-like coronavirus strain and one of the seven coronaviruses capable of infecting humans.<br/><br/>According to the WHO, scientists are calling the pathogen 2019-nCoV.<br/><br/>The pneumonia-like infection causes coughing, shortness of breath, breathing difficulties and fever.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/novel-coronavirus-infection-just-tripled-in-china-3952618</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/21/3952618/3952618_D294583881D54B25A8D3AF5A4C2D8B13_200121_3952618_Novel_coronavirus_infection_just_tripled_in_Chin_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2020 11:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953234</guid>
      <title>A huge 'ghost net' is haunting Hawaii's seas</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WAILUKU, HAWAII <br/> Ghost nets are commercial fishing nets discarded by fishers or lost in the ocean.<br/><br/>The Maui News reports that local authorities are asking for the public's help to recover a very large ghost net floating in Hawaii's near seas.<br/><br/>According to the paper, the giant net is 50 feet long, 70 feet wide and drifting at a depth of about 50 feet. It is also believed to have a yellow floater bucket.<br/><br/>The massive net could ensnare whales and potentially inflict serious damage to boats.<br/><br/>According to CNN, the net has not been found as of January 18, although the debris is possibly in the area of Maui, Kahoolawe, Lanai, and Molokai.<br/><br/>According to the institute, the ghost net may have collected up to 18 tons of plastic trash.<br/><br/>The network reports that ocean nonprofits are hoping to retrieve the ghost net before it sank, or rescuers would have to remove net carefully to avoid harming the reefs.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-huge-ghost-net-is-haunting-hawaii-s-seas-3953234</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953234/3953234_B198DD7FA5064A2395916188D7580469_200122_3953234_A_huge__ghost_net__is_haunting_Hawaii_s_seas_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 13:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953221</guid>
      <title>Scientists found clues for making universal cancer cure</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CARDIFF, BRITAIN <br/> Cardiff University researchers have identified a mechanism in our immune system that could be utilized to treat most cancers.<br/><br/>According to the study published in Nature Immunology, certain T-cells can be engineered to kill prostate, breast, lung and other cancers, albeit only in lab settings."<br/><br/>T-cells are a type of lymphocytes found in the blood that searches and destroys threats to the body that include infections to cancers.<br/><br/>Cardiff University says in a press statement that one type of T-cells was found to possess a unique receptor that allows them to detect almost all cancer cells.<br/><br/>The BBC reports that scientists may be able to take blood from a cancer patient and isolate their T-cells.<br/><br/>The T-cells could then be reprogrammed by a harmless virus to grow the special receptor and cultured before the immune cells are reintroduced to fight the patient's cancer cells.<br/><br/>T-cells with the special receptors are able to ignore healthy cells and attack the cancerous tissue, including tumors, which normal T-cells cannot.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-found-clues-for-making-universal-cancer-cure-3953221</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/22/3953221/3953221_8123C5D985DD4EC28176323BE2E4BFC2_200122_3953221_Scientists_found_clues_for_making_universal_canc_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 13:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953201</guid>
      <title>Update: Wuhuan virus is spreading fast out of China</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> A new virus from the Chinese city of Wuhan has made 440 people sick, at least nine of whom have died, as of Wednesday, Reuters reports, citing China's National Health Commission.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The state-run Xinhua news agency on Monday reported that the commission confirmed the virus is capable of human-to-human transmission.<br/><br/><br/><br/>According to NBC, a man who recently visited Wuhan and lives alone near Seattle became the first case of the virus in the U.S.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The man fell ill and read about the outbreak online before he contacted his doctor.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Citing U.S. officials, the network reports that he was sequestered but is doing well.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Taiwan's Liberty Times reports that a Taiwanese woman working in Wuhan got sick and decided to return to Taiwan because she did not trust Chinese hospitals.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The woman informed the flight crew of her condition and was sent to a hospital upon landing. She is confirmed to have been infected.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The novel coronavirus's rapid spread from across China to Thailand, Japan, South Korea and Taiwan has sparked fears of a larger epidemic.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The Wuhan Municipal Health Commission states that the novel coronavirus' symptoms include fever, respiratory difficulties, coughing and invasive lesions on both lungs."<br/><br/><br/><br/>China's state-run CCTV reports that scientists identified the pathogen as a coronavirus by its microscopic appearance and its novel strain by genetic analysis.<br/><br/><br/><br/>According to the BBC, the new virus resembles SARS and is one of the seven coronaviruses that prey on humans.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/update-wuhuan-virus-is-spreading-fast-out-of-china-3953201</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/763/20/01/22/3953199/3953199_481C526CB6314ABDAC3516D1E14345BF_200122_3953199_Update__Wuhuan_virus_is_spreading_fast_out_of_Ch_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2020 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953756</guid>
      <title>Wuhan suspends public transport amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Authorities in the Chinese city of Wuhan have shut down public transport to stop the spread of a new strain of coronavirus.<br/><br/>All flight and passenger train services in and out of Wuhan have temporarily been stopped as of Thursday, January 23, BBC News reports. Public buses, subways and ferry services have also been shut down starting from Thursday, 10:00 a.m. local time.<br/><br/>In addition, those residing in Wuhan have already been advised to avoid crowds and to minimize public gatherings. Large-scale activities that were planned at tourist attractions throughout the city have also been suspended ahead of the Lunar New Year holidays.<br/><br/>According to CNN, Wuhan has already made it mandatory for everyone in the city to wear face masks in public after the city confirmed more than 500 coronavirus cases.<br/><br/>The virus is now known as 2019-nCOV and is believed to be a new strain of coronavirus that had not been previously identified in humans, reports BBC News. <br/><br/>Chinese officials believe that the virus was spread from a local seafood market in Wuhan. The coronavirus originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there is now evidence that the virus can be transmitted between people.<br/><br/>The seafood market has since been closed for disinfection.<br/><br/>Symptoms of the virus include fever, with some experiencing difficulty breathing. Chest X-rays from the victims show invasive lesions on both lungs.<br/><br/>According to CNN, there have already been 555 confirmed cases of the Wuhan coronavirus, out of which there have been 17 deaths.<br/><br/>The virus has since spread to countries such as Thailand, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan and the United States.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-suspends-public-transport-amid-virus-outbreak-3953756</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953756/3953756_9399DDDC88684A0B8B30CC2D1A1531F5_200123_3953756_Wuhan_suspends_public_transport_amid_virus_outbr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 10:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3953639</guid>
      <title>Scientists use x-ray 'light echoes' to scope out black holes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, BRITAIN <br/> Astronomers have found a novel way to explore the regions around a black hole.<br/><br/>In a paper published in Nature Astronomy, researchers say that they were able to use x-ray echoes around a black hole to map the celestial body's surroundings.<br/><br/>According to the University of Cambridge's news release that black hole's gravitational force is extremely powerful and causes massive spatial distortions around itself.<br/><br/>As objects caught in the black hole pull are drawn to the event horizon, they heat up and radiate x-rays that "echo and reverberate" against nearby gas.<br/><br/>Using the European Space Agency's XMM x-ray observatory, the team was able to observe x-ray echoes of a black hole at the heart of a distant galaxy.<br/><br/>The echoes allowed the team to determine the spin and mass of the black hole.<br/><br/>The team also made the unexpected discovery that a black hole's the corona--or hot electrons above the accretion disk--changed its size often and quickly.<br/><br/>By raising and lowering the roof of the comic echo chamber, the corona's shift in size affected the light echoes and changed their quality.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-use-x-ray-light-echoes-to-scope-out-black-holes-3953639</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/23/3953639/3953639_441CA66447C84328A753A9357E53AE1B_200123_3953639_Scientists_use_x_ray__light_echoes__to_scope_out_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 08:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954293</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus spreads amid Lunar New Years celebrations</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Lunar New Years' festivities pose a great challenge for the Chinese government as it tries to contain the Wuhan coronavirus. <br/><br/>According to Reuters, the coronavirus death toll has now risen to 18, after the death of an 80-year-old victim in Hebei province. The South China Morning Post, citing Hebei Daily, reported the victim had spent more than two months in Wuhan visiting relatives.<br/><br/>This is the first death due to coronavirus infection outside of Hubei province. The number of infected individuals has risen to 650 worldwide.<br/><br/>So far, the virus has been detected in 23 Chinese provinces, four municipalities, Hong Kong, Macau, Thailand, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, Singapore, Vietnam and the United States. <br/><br/>According to the South China Morning Post, local governments have issued travel bans in eight cities in Hubei which include Wuhan, Huanggang, Ezhou, Chibi, Xiantao, Qianjiang, Zhijiang and Lichuan.<br/><br/>BBC News reports, the city of Wuhan has halted all flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city as of Thursday, January 23. <br/><br/>The travel ban includes ride-sharing services. Wuhan authorities asked Didi, a Chinese company similar to Uber or Lyft, to stop all ride services starting Friday at noon. <br/><br/>The coronavirus originally spread from wild animals to humans, though there is now evidence that human to human transmission of the virus is possible.<br/><br/>Chinese officials believe that the virus originated from a local seafood market in Wuhan. The market has since been closed for disinfection.<br/><br/>The virus has an incubation period of 5 days.Symptoms of the virus include fever, with some experiencing difficulty breathing. Chest x-rays from infected patients show invasive lesions on both lungs.<br/><br/>However, despite the virus's spread and rising death toll, the World Health Organization said on Thursday that the coronavirus is not an international public health emergency.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-virus-spreads-amid-lunar-new-years-celebrations-3954293</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954293/3954293_6BD609FD610841D2B966246D3ABCBFD0_200124_3954293_Wuhan_virus_spreads_amid_Lunar_New_Years_celebra_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 11:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954224</guid>
      <title>Rise in greenhouse gas emissions linked to China, India: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CHINA / INDIA <br/> New research from the University of Bristol has found that atmospheric levels of hydrofluorocarbon gas, or HFC-23, have continued to rise despite China and India saying they had stopped emissions.<br/><br/>Scientists involved with the study said they expected to find a roughly 90 percent decline in greenhouse gas emissions as part of the Montreal Protocol, an international treaty signed by countries around the world to protect the ozone layer from greenhouse gas emissions.<br/><br/>Researchers gathered data from the Advanced Global Atmospheric Gas Experiment network baseline stations and created model simulations for data between 2015 to 2018. Their research linked HFC-23 emissions to China and India, even though both countries were said to have almost completely halted emissions in 2017.<br/><br/>According to a news release from the University of Bristol, HFC-23 is an extremely potent greenhouse gas, with one ton of HFC-23 emissions being equivalent to more than 12,000 tons of carbon dioxide emissions.<br/><br/>HFC-23 is typically used in cooling systems such as refrigerators and air conditioners, the Guardian reports.<br/><br/>Lead author of the study Kieran Stanley explained in the news release that it is very likely that China wasn't as successful in its endeavor to reduce HFC-23 emissions as was previously reported.<br/><br/>As for India, Stanley said that without additional measurements, the team can't be sure whether or not India was able to implement an emissions reduction program.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/rise-in-greenhouse-gas-emissions-linked-to-china-india-study-3954224</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954224/3954224_231546DB8D6D4AB2899C798F40053ECC_200124_3954224_Rise_in_greenhouse_gas_emissions_linked_to_China_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 09:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3954143</guid>
      <title>Four leaks found in Japan's Fukushima Nuclear Plant</title>
      <description><![CDATA[FUKUSHIMA, JAPAN <br/> After surviving a massive earthquake, tsunami and nuclear meltdowns in 2011, Japan's Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Plant is now dealing with four different leaks in its walls. <br/><br/>According to NHK Japan, there are four coolant leaks at four different locations of the Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Power Station. <br/><br/>According to Tokyo Electric Power Company Holdings, also known as TEPCO, the coolant has been found seeping through pipes located in the nuclear station's underground wall of frozen soil. This wall surrounds the facility's reactor and turbine buildings.<br/><br/>The leaks are specifically located in the pipes between the plant's No. 2 and 3 reactor buildings.<br/><br/>TEPCO found the leaks in late 2019 after noticing a reduction in coolant liquids in its tanks. The company estimates it has lost a total of 20 cubic meters of coolant due to the leak.<br/><br/>The cooling liquid is an important tool in disaster prevention for the plant. As it circulates through the underground pipes, it freezes the soil surrounding the reactor buildings, this keeps groundwater from flowing into the nuclear station.<br/><br/>Although a leak at a major nuclear station sounds alarming, TEPCO assures that the chemical composition of the cooling liquid is commonly found in snow-melting agents and therefore is not harmful to the environment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/four-leaks-found-in-japan-s-fukushima-nuclear-plant-3954143</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/24/3954143/3954143_90A4C8CD24F74CF29914A1007460F646_200124_3954143_Four_leaks_found_in_Japan_s_Fukushima_Nuclear_Pl_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 07:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955123</guid>
      <title>Do masks prevent the spread of the coronavirus outbreak?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> The rapid spread of the Coronavirus in cities in China has everyone wearing surgical masks out on the streets. <br/><br/>But does wearing surgical masks actually protect us from catching deadly diseases?<br/><br/>According to BBC News, more than 80 million masks were sold on Chinese online retailer, Taobao, on January 20 and 21 following the outbreak of the deadly coronavirus.<br/><br/>However, wearing facemasks alone is not the most efficient way to avoid transmission of viruses or prevent the contraction of them.<br/><br/>Talking to BBC News, Dr. David Carrington of St George's, University of London explained that surgical masks do not provide sufficient protection from airborne viruses as they have no filter and do not shield the wearer's eyes.<br/><br/>They do however protect against and prevent the spray of coughing and sneezing. They also provide limited protection against hand-to-mouth viral transmission.<br/><br/>According to the Centers for Disease Control, the best way to prevent the current coronavirus outbreak is to compound wearing a facemask with the following actions:<br/>covering your mouth when coughing or sneezing, washing hands often for at least 20 seconds, avoid touching eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands, avoid sharing items that could be infected and consistently monitoring for coronavirus symptoms.<br/><br/>So far there have been 18 deaths in China and over 600 cases of coronaviruses detected globally. So mask up and wash up people.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/do-masks-prevent-the-spread-of-the-coronavirus-outbreak--3955123</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955123/3955123_76C88C3FCE9746EF94B2374794EAFEC0_200127_3955123_Do_masks_prevent_the_spread_of_the_coronavirus_o_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 09:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955202</guid>
      <title>Wuhan coronavirus contagious even during incubation period</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/>  Chinese authorities believe the coronavirus is contagious even when symptoms are not visible.  <br/><br/>Citing China's National Health Commission, the South China Morning Post reports that the new strain of coronavirus is contagious during its incubation period, that is before patients start showing visible symptoms. The incubation period of the coronavirus lasts up to 14 days.<br/><br/>Symptoms of the virus include fever and cough with some experiencing difficulty breathing.<br/><br/>National Health Commission Minister Ma Xiaowei, told media during a press conference on January 26 that 1,350 doctors had been sent to Hubei province with 1,000 more to come in the following days.<br/><br/>According to the South China Morning Post, so far there are 2,510 cases of coronavirus infections around the world. The death toll has risen to 80.<br/><br/>The virus is believed to have originated from a wet market in Wuhan.<br/><br/>In an effort to contain the virus, the city of Wuhan has halted all flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city as of Thursday, January 23. Other transportation systems have been curtailed.<br/><br/>According to Reuters, China announced it was temporarily banning the sale of wildlife in markets, restaurants, and online retailers throughout the whole country.<br/><br/>The best way to prevent the spread of the virus is to compound wearing masks with other sanitary measures such as washing hands thoroughly and frequently as well as avoiding hand to mouth and eye contact.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-coronavirus-contagious-even-during-incubation-period-3955202</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/27/3955202/3955202_8313607AB275487A9565192C93454FFE_200127_3955202_Wuhan_coronavirus_contagious_even_during_incubat_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 13:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955448</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus continues to spread, its origins are still being debated</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> The number of confirmed cases and deaths from the novel coronavirus infection continues to rise with more than 4,000 confirmed cases in China and a death toll of 106 as of January 28, according to Al Jazeera. <br/><br/>The death toll includes its first fatality in Beijing.<br/><br/>The virus was believed to have originated from a seafood market in Wuhan, however, according to a report published in The Lancet by a group of Chinese researchers, the earliest patient that contracted the virus had not visited the seafood market.<br/><br/>The report also notes that the first cases of coronavirus occurred on December 1, 2019. This means the viral disease first began spreading in November 2019, during its incubation period.<br/><br/>According to Deutsche Welle, the virus has now reached Germany. The Bavarian Health Ministry reported its first case of coronavirus in Starnberg, a town located 30 kilometers southwest of Munich.<br/><br/>The man is in medical isolation and, according to the Bavarian Health Ministry, there is a low risk of infection.<br/><br/>The symptoms of the novel coronavirus include severe coughing, fever, and difficulty breathing. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.<br/><br/>The city of Wuhan's transportation has been on lockdown since January 27. All flight and passenger train services coming in and out of the city have been canceled.<br/><br/>In an effort to aid overcrowded hospitals in Wuhan, National Health Commission Minister Ma Xiaowei told media during a press conference on January 26 that 1,350 doctors had been sent to Hubei province with 1,000 more to come in the following days.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-virus-continues-to-spread-its-origins-are-still-being-debated-3955448</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955448/3955448_B1143E722E3C4847BA446617A0D906B6_200128_3955448_Wuhan_virus_continues_to_spread__its_origins_are_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955442</guid>
      <title>Rolls-Royce unveils plans to build mini nuclear reactors in the U.K.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> Rolls-Royce has announced that it plans to build small modular reactors, or SMRs, and install them in old nuclear sites across the United Kingdom by 2029.<br/><br/>The company said they will build approximately 10 to 15 mini nuclear stations. These are expected to last for 60 years.<br/><br/>Rolls-Royce explained that these modular reactors will be mass produced while prefabricated components will be delivered onsite in order to reduce costs.<br/><br/>Chief technology officer at Rolls-Royce, Paul Stein, told the BBC that lower reactor building costs would eventually lead to cheaper electricity for the public.<br/><br/>These nuclear reactors will be roughly 1.5 acres in size, BBC News reports. This is 16 times smaller than the size of Hinkley Point, a major nuclear power station in the United Kingdom.<br/><br/>A press release by the company states that one reactor will be able to provide roughly 220 to 440 megawatts of energy which is equivalent to up to 150 onshore wind turbines.<br/><br/>Roll-Royce said that it also plans to sell these tiny modular reactors to other foreign countries such as Canada, the U.S. and China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/rolls-royce-unveils-plans-to-build-mini-nuclear-reactors-in-the-u-k--3955442</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/28/3955442/3955442_9C619001F855435EB8E6EBC23494F60B_200128_3955442_Rolls_Royce_unveils_plans_to_build_mini_nuclear__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 08:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3955867</guid>
      <title>Japan and U.S. evacuate citizens in Wuhan amid virus outbreak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> According to Bloomberg, China has confirmed over 5,900 cases of coronavirus nationwide and at least 132 deaths.<br/><br/>About 60 thousand patients are being monitored. The number of confirmed cases now surpasses the number of SARS epidemic in China in 2003.<br/><br/>Channel News Asia reports, Japan successfully evacuated 206 of its citizens from Wuhan on Wednesday. All passengers will be tested for the virus and will be asked to stay home until test results are ready.<br/><br/>According to CNN, the U.S. has also evacuated 240 American citizens from Wuhan on a flight chartered by the U.S. State Department. There are roughly 1,000 Americans currently trapped in the city of Wuhan.<br/><br/>BBC News reports Chinese authorities in Beijing and Shanghai are implementing a 14-day monitoring period for individuals entering the cities from Hubei province, where Wuhan is located.<br/><br/>A report published in The Lancet by a group of Chinese researchers states that the earliest patient that contracted the virus had not visited Wuhan's seafood market.<br/><br/>The symptoms of the novel coronavirus include severe coughing, fever, and shortness of breath. Complications from the virus can lead to pneumonia.<br/><br/>According to the Centers for Disease Control, the best way to prevent spreading or catching the virus is to wear a facemask, cover your mouth when coughing or sneezing, washing your hands often for at least 20 seconds, avoid touching eyes, nose, and mouth with unwashed hands, avoid sharing items that could be infected and consistently monitoring for coronavirus symptoms.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/japan-and-u-s-evacuate-citizens-in-wuhan-amid-virus-outbreak-3955867</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/29/3955867/3955867_FB6335129E5A4B18AC9BC4F15D383C99_200129_3955867_Japan_and_U_S__evacuate_citizens_in_Wuhan_amid_v_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 10:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956062</guid>
      <title>Smart campus conceptualized for new Tencent headquarters</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHENZHEN, CHINA <br/> Dutch architectural firm MVRDV has proposed a smart green campus for Tencent's next headquarters in Shenzhen, China.<br/><br/>The campus is expected to have a total floor space of 2 million square meters. <br/><br/>Sloped buildings throughout the campus will be topped with solar panel roofs, while green terraces would also be present around the smart campus, according to a news release by the architectural firm. The campus' primary means of transport will include autonomous cars and a shuttle bus loop.<br/><br/>The smart campus will also feature a conference center in the shape of a rock as well as a spherical information plaza that would display messages for Tencent employees.<br/><br/>The futuristic campus is expected to include office space for 80,000 to 100,000 employees and houses for up to 19,000 Tencent employees. The campus will also include amenities such as schools, sports centers and a waterfront park.<br/><br/>Designers explained that there would also be metro lines and bus lines that connect the Tencent campus to the rest of Shenzhen.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/smart-campus-conceptualized-for-new-tencent-headquarters-3956062</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956062/3956062_47A881E32B7A494C84B7C475CE649336_200130_3956062_Smart_campus_conceptualized_for_new_Tencent_head_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 02:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956367</guid>
      <title>Wuhan virus vaccine might take months to create</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AN ARBOR, MICHIGAN <br/> Researchers say previous work on the closely related MERS and SARS could benefit the vaccine development strategy to fight the Wuhan coronavirus outbreak.<br/><br/>The University of Michigan's Aubree Gordon and Icahn School of Medicine's Florian Kramer say that nucleic acid vaccine technology, which utilizes viral DNA or RNA material, might lead to a viable vaccine.<br/><br/>Writing in an op-ed published in Live Science, the authors explain that making a vaccine involves creating a construct, such as an antigen, that the body's immune system could use to target and attack the virus.<br/><br/>A vaccine has to be tested in animal and human trials before it is judged safe and effective.<br/><br/>According to the authors, scientists do not have isolated virus samples or enough antibodies for testing the vaccine, and they have not established the animal species suitable for animal trials.<br/><br/>The vaccine development process will likely take months to complete.<br/><br/>The authors state that better global surveillance of viruses would be important to mitigate future epidemics, as coronavirus, Zika, Ebola and influenza outbreaks have shown.<br/><br/>They say novel vaccine technologies that could be quickly adapted to different strains are needed as part of a proactive approach to combating pathogens.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/wuhan-virus-vaccine-might-take-months-to-create-3956367</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956367/3956367_FC7429089DBC4E7BA3822F90AE3C2C65_200130_3956367_Wuhan_virus_vaccine_might_take_months_to_create_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 11:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956272</guid>
      <title>Chinese villagers build wall to keep coronavirus out</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> The Wuhan coronavirus is spreading in China like wildfire and with it the paranoia of Chinese citizens. Aaaand they've gotten quite creative with their viral contention methods.<br/><br/>According to Skynews, villagers from different towns in China's Hebei province have taken the viral battle into their own hands. Some have built DIY brick walls to keep out coronavirus zombies from infecting their people.<br/><br/>Others have written eery warning signs on street entrances that read: "No outsiders allowed in." Heard that coronavirus? Ya can't come in!<br/><br/>UK's Daily Star reports poor hotel staffers in a quarantined hotel in Hangzhou China have had to deal with waves of passengers being screened for the virus.<br/><br/>They've taken a more&#8230; technological approach by sending robots to feed and sing? For the possibly infected guests.<br/><br/>Hopefully the robot doesn't go all terminator on them.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/chinese-villagers-build-wall-to-keep-coronavirus-out-3956272</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/30/3956272/3956272_2B2E0F67A5C240CE8A2EB5DBC76E333A_200130_3956272_Chinese_villagers_build_wall_to_keep_coronavirus_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 09:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3956917</guid>
      <title>SpinLaunch will slingshot rockets into space with giant centrifuge</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONG BEACH, CALIFORNIA <br/> A U.S. aerospace company is building a huge centrifuge to launch spacecraft into orbit.<br/><br/>Wired.com reports that the SpinLaunch's centrifuge, or the kinetic launch system, has an internal vacuum chamber with a diameter of 100 meters.<br/><br/>The SpinLaunch rocket is about the size of an SUV and the vehicle's design will allow it to carry a satellite payload of about 200 pounds.<br/><br/>The centrifuge's electric motor will spin the tethered rocket for an hour to build up speed.<br/><br/>Once the rocket is ratcheted up to a speed of over 5,000 miles per hour, the release mechanism will cut the vehicle loose and let it fly through the 35 degree launch tunnel.<br/><br/>When the vehicle reaches the edge of the stratosphere, the rocket's internal propulsion will fire and push the spacecraft through the final stretch to space.<br/><br/>Citing SpinLaunch, Wired reports that the centrifuge could launch up to five small satellites a day and reduce launch costs by a factor of almost 20.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/spinlaunch-will-slingshot-rockets-into-space-with-giant-centrifuge-3956917</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/01/31/3956917/3956917_C49F0D50BB174D7295F8F6B6231588AF_200131_3956917_SpinLaunch_will_slingshot_rockets_into_space_wit_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
