<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 18:08:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3929442</guid>
      <title>Amazon forest fires could make glaciers melt faster in the Andes</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTH AMERICA <br/> The fires burning in the Amazon rainforests are accelerating the melting of Andean glaciers, according to a study Nature published on November 28.<br/><br/>Brazilian scientists at the Rio de Janeiro State University report that smoke from the fires are carrying black carbon as far as the Zongo Glacier in Bolivia.<br/><br/>The study focused on the Zongo Glacier between 2007 and 2010, when more fires occurred in the rainforests than normally seen.<br/><br/>The researchers said satellite LiDAR imagery confirm black carbon particles are carried to and deposited on the Zongo, or at an altitude between three and five kilometers.<br/><br/>Lead researcher Dr. de Magalh&#227;es Neto talking to the BBC said that the black carbon then darkens glacial ice and snow.<br/><br/>The research team said that tropical glaciers supply water to millions of people in South America.<br/><br/>According to the paper, snow and ice infused with black carbon is less able to deflect sunlight, resulting in a significantly higher rate of melting.<br/><br/>Dr. Magalh&#227;es Neto tells the BBC that forest fires in Bolivia, Peru and Brazil may have vast social implications for the continent, as glacier loss could lead to a water crisis.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-forest-fires-could-make-glaciers-melt-faster-in-the-andes-3929442</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/1F9/7D1/1F97D1C5FAA88BA3583573D9FC7560C4.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929442/3929442_4E884F3BB1FC47688CE9DEC999AEC6F4_191202_3929442_Amazon_forest_fires_could_make_glaciers_melt_fas_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 09:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929614</guid>
      <title>Researchers have discovered a 'monster black hole'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> Researchers have discovered a massive black hole 15,000 light years from Earth in the Milky Way Galaxy.<br/><br/>Professor Liu Jinfeng at the Chinese Academy of Sciences said in a press release that the stellar black hole named LB-1 is so large that "it should not even exist in our galaxy."<br/><br/>According to the international research team, the "monster black hole" has a mass that is 70 times greater than the mass of the sun.<br/><br/>The discovery comes as a surprise as scientists had previously estimated the mass of most stellar black holes in our galaxy at less than 20 times the sun's mass.<br/><br/>Scientists spotted LB-1 by looking for stars that circle a black hole. LB-1's companion has eight times the mass of the sun and circles the black hole every 79 days.<br/><br/>The international team credits China's Large Sky Area Multi-Object Fiber Spectroscopic Telescope for making the discovery.<br/><br/>The Gran Telescopio Canarias in Spain and the Keck I telescope in the U.S. then determined the physical parameters of LB-1 and its companion star.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-have-discovered-a-monster-black-hole--3929614</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EB9/241/EB924193826C79F6B8AA5D55ABADEC77.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929614/3929614_97D4AE8E39A34F3894261E91CECCD29F_191202_3929614_Researchers_have_discovered_a__monster_black_hol_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 14:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929517</guid>
      <title>NASA unveils lunar lander for future missions</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA has unveiled designs for a medium-sized lunar lander that would be able to carry payloads that weigh up to 300 kilograms to the moon's polar regions.<br/><br/>Payloads may include scientific instruments, a robotic rover and even a ramp for the rover.<br/><br/>The lander will include a thermal control system, an electrical power subsystem and a navigation system with Terrain-Relative Navigation.<br/><br/>Its metal structure will house a solid rocket motor to allow the lander to brake on arrival to the moon and a liquid propulsion system to facilitate landing on the moon's surface.<br/><br/>The lander will take three to six days to reach the moon and will be sent via a commercial launch vehicle.<br/><br/>As the lander makes its way to the moon, solar panels on its surface will supply power to batteries on the lander. This will help power the rover once the lander has descended to the moon's surface, and allow it to explore the lunar environment for up to six hours. <br/><br/>The mission is part of NASA's plan to establish a permanent base on the moon.<br/><br/>The ultimate goal is to prepare humans to make their way from the moon to the red planet in order to make human exploration of Mars a reality.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-unveils-lunar-lander-for-future-missions-3929517</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/933/3BA/9333BA6633F02F0B68E3B500260BF9E3.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/02/3929517/3929517_62906788F4A24774A52900620F9808A0_191202_3929517_NASA_unveils_lunar_lander_for_future_missions_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 12:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929931</guid>
      <title>Banana stumps turned into biodegradable plastics</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KENSINGTON, AUSTRALIA <br/>According to researchers at Australia's University of South Wales, banana growing can be a highly wasteful process with 88 percent of the plant being discarded after fruit harvesting.<br/><br/>The scientists have designed a new method that reduces this waste by reusing the pseudostem, or the banana's trunk, and turning it into biodegradable packaging.<br/><br/>According to the university's press release, the team cut the pseudostem, then dry heated the pieces at low temperatures to remove water.<br/><br/>The process extracts cellulose from banana plant cells in powdered form, which is then chemically treated to become the packaging material.<br/><br/>According to the researchers, the finished product is a baking paper like polymer that may replace plastic bags and single use commercial containers for meat and fruit.<br/><br/>They claimed that tests conducted at the university found the material to be nontoxic and can be recycled up to three times.<br/><br/>According to one of the professors involved in the study, bananas are annual plants and could potentially provide a round the year supply of sustainable packaging material.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/banana-stumps-turned-into-biodegradable-plastics-3929931</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6F0/241/6F0241BF0E00A8CE6AC4CA5AA52685E3.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929931/3929931_0F5C7957FA544BFAB29B3D0BCD80F831_191203_3929931_Banana_stumps_turned_into_biodegradable_plastics_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 08:22:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3929897</guid>
      <title>Underwater loudspeakers could help boost coral reef recovery</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EXETER, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> New research has found that deploying underwater loudspeakers to play the sounds of healthy coral reef could help restore damaged reefs.<br/><br/>In a joint study by two British universities and two Australian universities, scientists recorded sounds of healthy reefs and then played these sounds via a loudspeaker for 40 days on Australia's northern Great Barrier Reef.<br/><br/>One of the authors of the study explained that healthy coral reefs are noisy, with shrimp and fish living in the area creating noise. Once coral reefs start to degrade or are damaged, reefs turn eerily quiet. This results in fish in the reefs leaving to find a new home. <br/><br/>At the end of the experiment, scientists found that the degraded coral reefs had a 50 percent increase in the number of juvenile fish.<br/><br/>Lead author of the study, Tim Gordon, explained in a news release that the growth of fish population choosing to stay in the damaged reefs could help to kick-start the natural recovery process for the coral reefs.<br/><br/>Co-author of the study, Andy Radford, from the University of Bristol, said that this technique could be combined with other coral restoration techniques to help accelerate ecosystem recovery.<br/><br/>Though Radford added that we need to combat other threats such as climate change, water pollution and overfishing in order to better protect these ecosystems in the first place.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/underwater-loudspeakers-could-help-boost-coral-reef-recovery-3929897</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C12/932/C12932F2C0E66B2690E258E8F2B4F5B7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3929897/3929897_BF9827165BAD49128BF19E59928222FE_191203_3929897_Underwater_loudspeakers_could_help_boost_coral_r_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 07:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930149</guid>
      <title>Australia uses smart cameras to spot texting drivers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MELBOURNE, AUSTRALIA <br/> The Australian government has rolled out a smart traffic camera system to catch drivers who use cell phones on the road.<br/><br/>Transport for New South Wales officially activated the mobile phone detection system on Monday after the testing the technology from January to June this year.<br/><br/>According to NSW Transport, the system features high definition cameras with infrared flash. The cameras are linked to an artificial intelligence program.<br/><br/>The optics allow the system to see into the front cabinet of road vehicles and capture clear images during day or night and in all weather conditions. <br/><br/>The system's software then analyzes the images to spot drivers who are using mobile phones.<br/><br/>The algorithm excludes images of legal phone use but passes the suspicious ones to authorized reviewers, who checks the images before issuing penalties and fines.<br/><br/>NSW Transport says it expects to install 45 cameras across its jurisdiction by 2023.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/australia-uses-smart-cameras-to-spot-texting-drivers-3930149</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/411/0E7/4110E7687EDC613119198572E6888494.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3930149/3930149_DB64F5E49DBE4F89BEBA381EAC10DB49_191203_3930149_Australia_uses_smart_cameras_to_spot_texting_dri_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 14:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930122</guid>
      <title>NASA &amp; ESA plan to crash into an asteroid and explore its properties</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> NASA and the European Space Agency are joining hands for a planetary defense mission in order to learn how to protect Earth from a possible asteroid collision.<br/><br/>The ESA is preparing for the Hera mission that will gather data from Didymoon, the accompanying moonlet of a binary asteroid system called Didymos, years after NASA crashes a spacecraft into it through its Double Asteroid Redirection Test, or DART.<br/><br/>According to NASA, the binary asteroid system is located roughly 11 million kilometers from Earth. NASA's DART spacecraft will be guided by an onboard camera and an autonomous real-time navigation system as it makes its way to the binary asteroid. <br/><br/>By 2022, NASA aims to crash onto the surface of Didymoon at a speed of roughly 6 kilometers per second in order to change the speed and direction of the asteroid.<br/><br/>Didymoon is 160 meters in width. This is roughly the width of the Great Pyramid of Giza, according to the American space agency. <br/><br/>The Hera spacecraft will then research the crater formed by the DART experiment in 2026.<br/><br/>According to an ESA news release, the spacecraft will collect surface samples, as well as data about the shape and dimensions of the crater.<br/><br/>Hera will also use thermal imaging technology to examine the asteroid's structure. <br/><br/>The European Space Agency says the experiment will provide "valuable insights" into the history and origins of our solar system.<br/><br/>The agency explained in a news release that the study would provide information on whether or not this technique would work to deflect an asteroid if one ever heads our way.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa--esa-plan-to-crash-into-an-asteroid-and-explore-its-properties-3930122</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/A5B/F67/A5BF67A2FE9FFDA55404343A7EAAE87E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/03/3930122/3930122_958940575C314A399604567469E46B11_191203_3930122_NASA___ESA_plan_to_crash_into_an_asteroid_and_ex_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 13:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930537</guid>
      <title>NASA's astronaut dummies will test new vests around the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA will send astronaut dummies around the moon in the Orion spacecraft for the uncrewed Artemis I mission scheduled for next year, Space.com reports.  <br/><br/>According to the outlet, NASA says the goal of the mission is to test a new piece of equipment designed to protect female astronauts from space radiation called the AstroRed. <br/><br/>According to the European Space Agency, the pair of phantom dummies named Zohar and Helga are fitted with over 5,600 radiation sensors.<br/><br/>Zohar will wear the AstroRad protective vest and Helgo will not, which will help researchers evaluate the effectiveness of the vest. <br/><br/>Makers of the radiation vest, a company called StemRad, say the vest protects the breasts, bone marrow, stomach, ovaries and other vulnerable organs that contain stem cells via its variable thickness shielding.<br/><br/>According to the Tel-Aviv based contractor, the contoured shields are solid polymer shielding elements that are arrayed in a scale like structure. <br/><br/>According to the German Aerospace Center's Thomas Berger, though the vest is designed for women, the garment could be adjusted for males.<br/><br/>StemRad claims its vest could allow astronauts to leave the Orioin's solar storm shelters to perform important tasks during a solar storm.<br/><br/>According to the company, the vest significantly reduces cancer and other fatal radiation exposure risks for astronauts.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-s-astronaut-dummies-will-test-new-vests-around-the-moon-3930537</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/349/504/349504D61FA4932646F5AB4ABB56ED69.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/04/3930537/3930537_B4833DD56D7A45F7B7B56CC63DFF4103_191204_3930537_NASA_s_astronaut_dummies_will_test_new_vests_aro_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 10:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930401</guid>
      <title>Your Smart TV could spying on you: FBI</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON <br/> The FBI warned consumers this week that their smart TVs may be collecting extensive data about them.<br/><br/>In a message to Christmas shoppers, the agency warned that smart TVs are vulnerable to cyberattacks. This is because they are connected to the internet and include features such as microphones and cameras.<br/><br/>The FBI said that if a device is hacked, hackers could use these features to cyberstalk someone. <br/><br/>The bureau urged owners of smart TVs to take preventive actions against this by learning their devices' privacy settings and how to turn off its microphones and cameras.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/your-smart-tv-could-spying-on-you-fbi-3930401</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/8D7/FB3/8D7FB34C29884E7AF6BA7840F73BC137.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/04/3930401/3930401_7F62A0FB7FC946939C139DF0919E33E8_191204_3930401_Your_Smart_TV_could_spying_on_you__FBI_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 07:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930855</guid>
      <title>U.S. may implement mandatory facial scans across airports</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The U.S. Department of Homeland Security has proposed a new regulation that would require all travelers <br/> including U.S. citizens and green card holders <br/> to undergo mandatory facial scans when entering and leaving the country.<br/><br/>Facial recognition technology typically matches an image of a person from a photo or video with a still image of them in a database. It has become increasingly used in airports throughout the world, according to CNN. <br/><br/>The proposed regulation would be part of a broader system to track travelers as they enter and exit the United States.<br/><br/>According to Reuters, the Trump Administration contends the face scan requirement will combat the fraudulent use of U.S. travel documents and aid the identification of criminals and suspected terrorists.<br/><br/>The U.S. Customs and Border Protection has already conducted pilot programs that collect photographs and fingerprints from foreign travelers, but until now, U.S. citizens had been exempt, Reuters reports.   <br/><br/>In 2017, President Trump signed an executive order to accelerate a full roll out of airport biometrics for all domestic and international travelers.<br/><br/>According to a statement by a senior policy analyst from American Liberties Union Jay Stanley, travelers shouldn't have to submit to "invasive biometric scans" just because they want to travel.<br/><br/>The U.S. government has been using facial recognition technology for the past 20 years, though the government has only recently started pushing for use of this technology across U.S. airports, CNN reports.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-may-implement-mandatory-facial-scans-across-airports-3930855</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/750/38D/75038D531BC45BE8E8FFE880F02093AE.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3930855/3930855_03FAB6B904BE4671808EA0559C87D870_191205_3930855_U_S__may_implement_mandatory_facial_scans_across_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 04:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3930938</guid>
      <title>NASA to attach 'robot hotel' to International Space Station</title>
      <description><![CDATA[INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION <br/> NASA plans to launch a storage space for robotic tools called the Robotic Tool Stowage, or RiTS, to the International Space Station.<br/><br/>In a news release, NASA explained that the robot hotel will be launched aboard a SpaceX Falcon 9 rocket, during its 19th commercial resupply mission, on December 4.<br/><br/>Two robotic tools called Robotic External Leak Locators, or RELL, that are currently onboard the International Space Station, will be the first residents of the storage space. <br/><br/>These robotic tools are capable of detecting gases such as ammonia and are used to find leaks in the station.<br/><br/>NASA says the storage unit will protect the tools from space radiation, tiny meteoroids, or other high-speed objects traveling through space.<br/><br/>The Robotic Tool Stowage's thermal system will be able to maintain a constant temperature to help the space station's robotic equipment stay functional. The location of the storage space will also make it easily accessible for the International Space Station's robotic arm called Dextre to get a hold of these tools.<br/><br/>Once the robot hotel makes its way to the space station, astronauts will perform a spacewalk to install the storage space to the station's exterior.<br/><br/>NASA says this type of technology could potentially be used in future space missions to the Moon, Mars, or beyond.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-to-attach-robot-hotel-to-international-space-station-3930938</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/57B/733/57B733767E03D880F94A3E7D65778C4F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/05/3930938/3930938_58C29F7D59584856B2C9E21AC32E0163_191205_3930938_NASA_to_attach__robot_hotel__to_International_Sp_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 07:37:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931317</guid>
      <title>Doctors successfully 'reanimate' heart from deceased donor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA <br/> For the first time in the U.S, doctors have successfully "reanimated" a heart from a deceased donor, prior to the heart being transplanted to an adult recipient.<br/><br/>This procedure is known as donation after circulatory death or DCD.<br/><br/>Donor hearts usually come from those who have been declared as brain dead but still have a beating heart. The beating heart is then transplanted into a recipient, CNN reports. <br/><br/>Jacob Schroder, one of the doctors involved in the heart transplant procedure, told CNN <br/>that the donor heart was doused with a cold solution and removed five minutes after the person's death was announced and after heartbeat and circulation had stopped.<br/><br/>Physicians from Duke University Medical Center then placed the heart in the TransMedics Organ Care System. The system pumps warm blood and allows the non-beating heart to be preserved and resuscitated for a transplant.<br/><br/>Once the heart and the heart recipient is ready, the donor heart is then transplanted into the recipient via standard heart transplant procedure.<br/><br/>Schroder explained that the procedure could increase the donor pool and the number of transplants performed by 30 percent. This would decrease wait time and the number of deaths of those waiting for a transplant.<br/><br/>The procedure has previously been performed in medical centers in the United <br/>Kingdom and Australia.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/doctors-successfully-reanimate-heart-from-deceased-donor-3931317</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0C7/FCA/0C7FCABA14697A685E2EC9E65A1ECAE7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/06/3931317/3931317_22B827FD7AB74E188390A49A52F35C36_191206_3931317_Doctors_successfully__reanimate__heart_from_dece_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 03:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3931961</guid>
      <title>North American birds are shrinking</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANN ARBOR, MICHIGAN <br/> New research has found that tens of thousands of North American birds have become smaller in size since 1978.<br/><br/>Scientists examined 70, 716 dead birds <br/> 52 bird species in total <br/> that crashed into skyscrapers in Chicago.<br/><br/>The study, published in the journal Ecology Letters, found that 49 of these bird species had a reduction in the length of their lower leg bone by 2.4 percent.<br/><br/>Meanwhile, the average wing length of birds saw an increase of roughly 1.3 percent.<br/><br/>The authors of the study suggested that a change in the birds' size may be a response to rising temperatures caused by climate change.<br/><br/>They added that the birds may have evolved to have a wider wingspan to compensate for their smaller bodies and to help them migrate long distances.<br/><br/>Scientists said that animal species tend to be smaller in warmer regions and larger in colder regions. This is to help animals carry less heat in hot areas while those in colder areas need a larger body size to conserve warmth.<br/><br/>The researchers plan to use the data to look at the mechanics of how a birds' body changes in shape and size, according to CNN. <br/><br/>They also plan to examine whether the change is a result of developmental plasticity <br/> an animal's ability to change its own development as a response to the changing environment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/north-american-birds-are-shrinking-3931961</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/0C4/01F/0C401F212847610EC910EF95848BAD03.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/07/3931961/3931961_9F36CDFD1F3C4D7EB538F3DF35B20D0F_191207_3931961_North_American_birds_are_shrinking_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 08:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932528</guid>
      <title>Over 500k crabs TRAPPED by plastic waste on remote islands</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HOBART, AUSTRALIA <br/> A new study led by the University of Tasmania has found that more than 560,000 hermit crabs have died from being trapped in plastic waste on the remote Cocos Keeling and Henderson Islands.<br/><br/>Scientists surveyed sites on both the islands for plastic debris and found open plastic containers across the islands. The study also accounted for the number of trapped crabs, both dead and alive, found inside the plastic containers.<br/><br/>Researchers said that the piles of plastic waste present on the island beaches create physical obstacles as well as traps for the hermit crabs.<br/><br/>The problem is exacerbated as hermit crabs don't have shells of their own, which means that they need to track down other dead crabs via their odor in order to acquire them.<br/><br/>In one example, researchers found that this led to 526 crabs being trapped in a single plastic container.<br/><br/>In a University of Tasmania news release scientists said that these hermit crabs are important as they help disperse seeds, fertilize the soil in tropical environments and form an integral part of the marine ecosystem.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/over-500k-crabs-trapped-by-plastic-waste-on-remote-islands-3932528</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/166/2EF/1662EFD4B921FB919ACBD47AC6816C3E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932528/3932528_231D509177414C25ADD55E02DE6EE57E_191209_3932528_Over_500k_crabs_TRAPPED_by_plastic_waste_on_remo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 04:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932768</guid>
      <title>Two piglets containing monkey DNA born in Chinese laboratory</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> These little piggies had some crazy scientists genetically engineer them with a bunch of monkey DNA in China.<br/><br/>According to New Scientist, pig-primate chimeras were created by a team in China. The two piglets resembled normal pigs on the outside, but they also had a proportion of their cells derived from cynomolgus monkeys. <br/>According to Tang Hai at the State Key Laboratory of Stem Cell and Reproductive Biology in Beijing, "this is the first report of full-term pig-monkey chimeras." <br/>The goal of the mad scientists is to grow human organs in animals for transplantation.<br/>Unfortunately, the research has a long way to go as both little piggies died within a week. <br/>The Chinese researchers genetically modified cynomolgus monkey cells growing in culture so they made a fluorescent protein called GFP, allowing them to track the cells and their descendents. <br/><br/>The team then derived embryonic stem cells from the modified cells and jammed them into pig embryos five days after fertilization. <br/>Over 4000 embryos were implanted into sows with ten piglets born as a result of which two where chimeras. All became bacon within a week. <br/><br/>The Chinese scientists now say they are trying to engineer healthier animals with a higher proportion of monkey cells. <br/><br/>But in the meantime, might as well just continue harvesting organs from the totally unwilling.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/two-piglets-containing-monkey-dna-born-in-chinese-laboratory-3932768</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7D1/152/7D1152D55AE1921F9BE5C44EFD9D11B6.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932768/3932768_918B0D49DBB34EAB81F72F93DC300BAA_191209_3932768_Two_piglets_containing_monkey_DNA_born_in_Chines_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932750</guid>
      <title>Stranded sperm whale had 100 kg of garbage in it stomach</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HARRIS, SCOTLAND <br/> A sperm whale that became stranded and died on a Scottish beach had 100kg of garbage in its stomach, according to the Scottish Marine Animal Strandings Scheme (SMASS).<br/><br/>According to an SMASS Facebook post on December 1, the animal had been dead for two days by the time workers examined the carcass.  <br/><br/>According to SMASS, the juvenile whale measured 14 meters long. Approximately 100 kilograms of garbage was found in its stomach, including nets, ropes, plastic cups and bags, gloves and packaging.<br/><br/>SMASS said that debris in the whale originated from both fishing and land sectors and that the animal had been eating litter for quite some time.<br/><br/>The whale could have swallowed the debris between the Azores to Norway and efforts to explain why this whale ingested so much garbage is still ongoing.<br/><br/>While the garbage did not appear to block the whale's intestines, SMASS said the debris caused indigestion and may have played a role in the stranding that resulted in the whale's demise.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/stranded-sperm-whale-had-100-kg-of-garbage-in-it-stomach-3932750</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/09/3932750/3932750_97116C9179694875A875D186540C0E99_191209_3932750_Stranded_sperm_whale_had_100_kg_of_garbage_in_it_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 10:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3932995</guid>
      <title>Architects propose 'vertical city' of the future</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ITALY <br/> The Italian firm, Luca Curci Architects have proposed 'Vertical City', a project involving a self-sustaining, zero energy building that intends to house 25,000 people. The futuristic city proposes to be settled into the sea bed close to the mainland, accessible by land, sea, and air.<br/><br/>The cylindrical residential building would be clad in photovoltaic glazing, a technology that produces electricity from sunlight. Natural light and ventilation will be promoted through hexagonal openings in the building.<br/><br/>The 'Vertical City' targets low poverty, no noise, no pollution, desalinization of seawater and producing 1,144,500 KWh of daily solar energy.<br/><br/>According to the Italian firm, this new interpretation of urban development would allow its residents to be apart of a "healthier lifestyle" through the connection with the surrounding natural elements; it would also allow residents to re-think the traditional concept of community and society.<br/><br/>According to Luca Curci Architects, the 750-meter-tall residential skyscraper would consist of 10 modular layers, each layer consisting of 18 floors, including a mixture of homes, offices, stores and other facilities. The building would also offer more than 200,000 square meters of green space, which includes the public garden at the top of the building.<br/><br/>In addition to the 25,000 people housed within the central residential tower, the Vertical City as a whole, including the three adjacent towers that house offices, government departments, healthcare facilities, and educational institutions, would service over 100,000 people who would travel to the city for work, school and medical care."<br/><br/>Luca Curci described the plans as a "new way of living." He said the proposal would be more sustainable, more interconnected and most importantly reduce poverty.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/architects-propose-vertical-city-of-the-future-3932995</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/F1C/6C1/F1C6C16DD904BC4C9E434AA846A97BCD.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3932995/3932995_9C50FAFD4956490DB41AAA3DBC14A8D4_191210_3932995_Architects_propose__vertical_city__of_the_future_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 03:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933196</guid>
      <title>Oceans are running out of oxygen because of climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRID <br/> The International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN), warns that climate change and nutrient pollution are depleting the oceans of oxygen in a report published in December. <br/><br/>The report states that nitrogen and phosphorus runoffs from sewage, agricultural waste and industrial pollution are the main cause of oxygen deletion, especially in coastal seas.<br/><br/>According to the BBC, the study also found that climate change is heating the oceans and reducing the amount of oxygen they can hold. <br/><br/>The study found the oxygen dissolved in the ocean has dropped two percent globally and as much as 40 percent in parts of the tropics.<br/><br/>The study warns that the combined effects of warmer oceans and run offs could affect the top 1,000 meter of the water column, which is richest in biodiversity.<br/><br/>The IUCN states that deoxygenation harms bigger fish that are oxygen sensitive, such as tuna, marlin and sharks, but favors microbes and jellyfish that are not.<br/><br/>The report suggests that the lack of oxygen would force the fish to live closer to the surface, where they are vulnerable to overfishing.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/oceans-are-running-out-of-oxygen-because-of-climate-change-3933196</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC7/64B/DC764B7F10CECF6C1336F79396CA76A3.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933196/3933196_EDFE5F674416485E9A18A39ABA2F4006_191210_3933196_Oceans_are_running_out_of_oxygen_because_of_clim_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 09:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933159</guid>
      <title>'Seahorse hotels' planned for endangered species in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY <br/> New artificial habitats could help save the endangered White's seahorse species in Australia.<br/><br/>SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium is working with the University of Technology Sydney and the New South Wales Department of Primary Industries Fisheries on a new breeding and conservation project for Australia's White's seahorse, one of only two endangered seahorse species worldwide.<br/><br/>The Department of Primary Industries Fisheries states on its website that the main cause for the decline of White's seahorse, also known as the Sydney seahorse, is the loss of its natural habitats.<br/><br/>In the project's first phase, researchers collected breeding pairs of White's seahorses from Sydney Harbor. Their offspring are being kept at a custom built facility at SEA LIFE Sydney Aquarium and will eventually be released into the wild.<br/><br/>For the second phase of the project, the team will begin constructing "seahorse hotels," or artificial habitats for seahorses, in Sydney Harbor this month.<br/><br/>Researchers say the seahorse hotels will provide a habitat for the project's seahorses when they are released into the wild. Monitoring of the seahorses will continue after their release.<br/><br/>These artificial habitats will be transformed into natural habitats for White's seahorses as they are grown over by sponges, algae and other marine creatures.<br/><br/>Researchers say the artificial habitats were previously trialled in Port Stephens in New South Wales, Australia in 2018 and earlier this year.<br/><br/>Trials were found to be extremely successful as they attracted seahorses, leading to mating and breeding.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-seahorse-hotels-planned-for-endangered-species-in-australia-3933159</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/114/F49/114F490C1D5DE5DBA154D1085B19943E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933159/3933159_A78C359848AE443C92B00FE77CA9494F_191210_3933159__Seahorse_hotels__planned_for_endangered_species_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 08:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933112</guid>
      <title>Project Orca: Luxury superyacht inspired by killer whales</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RAVENNA, ITALY <br/> Italian shipyard Rosetti Superyachts has unveiled its new luxury yacht that is designed to look like an orca.<br/><br/>Project Orca will be 65 meters long and consist of four decks, SuperYacht Times reports. The ship will have a range of 5,000 miles and will be able to travel at a cruising speed of 12 knots.<br/><br/>The yacht itself comes with several deck configurations. In its standard configuration, the vessel will have an open deck, a touch-and-go helipad, and snow sledges.<br/><br/>The superyacht may also be modified to include an infinity pool, or a raised helipad with a pool and spa area in its interior.<br/><br/>Project Orca's interior includes six cabins, which can accommodate up to 12 people along with a crew of 12. The lower deck will also be equipped with a garage to store equipment like jet skis.<br/><br/>Fulvio Dodich, CEO and chairman of Rosetti Superyachts, said that the yacht will take approximately 36 months to be built.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/project-orca-luxury-superyacht-inspired-by-killer-whales-3933112</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/207/983/207983CD95F24E8EC06E3A8BE92E94AD.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/10/3933112/3933112_292EBA6009B74C1B81C309732A97E02C_191210_3933112_Project_Orca__Luxury_superyacht_inspired_by_kill_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 07:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933391</guid>
      <title>White Island volcanic eruption explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WHITE ISLAND / NEW ZEALAND<br/>The sudden eruption of New Zealand's White Island volcano has left 5 people dead and injured dozens of others, reports CNN.<br/><br/>According to the University of Otago, White Island straddles the Australian and Pacific tectonic plates.<br/><br/>Magma is created beneath the island when the Pacific plate pushes against the Australian plate and sinks beneath it.<br/><br/>The Guardian reports that White Island magma is shallow and heats groundwater to form pockets of extremely hot steam. This causes high pressure in surrounding rocks.<br/><br/>The expansion of water into steam can be supersonic and its energy can shatter the rockbed, resulting in a steam-driven eruption, also known as hydrothermal eruption.<br/><br/>The Guardian reports that White Island's steam-driven eruption blasted hot volcanic rocks, ash and coarse particles that can inflict impact trauma, burns and respiratory injuries.<br/><br/>Authorities fear as many as 13 people could be dead.<br/><br/>CNN reports that five tourists on the island have been killed, while 27 have suffered serious burns and eight are still missing as of Tuesday.<br/><br/>The Guardian reports that steam-driven eruptions can happen quickly and without warning because their triggers are not well understood.<br/><br/>Volcanologists at GeoNet says the White Island volcano erupted with enough force that its plumes rose to a height of three kilometers.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/white-island-volcanic-eruption-explained-3933391</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/44C/564/44C56472EF8ED9663BAC2B099799AE6D.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933391/3933391_19CEF64E3B9F487C8A4437865C12B756_191211_3933391_White_Island_volcanic_eruption_explained_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 16:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933589</guid>
      <title>LED fishing nets save turtles and dolphins</title>
      <description><![CDATA[UNITED KINGDOM / PERU <br/> Researchers at the University of Exeter and Peruvian NGO ProDelphinus have found that by putting LED lights on top of floating commercial fishing nets, the number of critically endangered species caught in them, can be reduced by 70 percent or more<br/><br/>The research published in the journal Biological Conservation looked at small-scale vessels departing from three Peruvian ports between 2015 and 2018. LEDs were placed every 30 feet along the float line of 864 illuminated gillnets.<br/><br/>Lead author Alessandra Bielli explained that gillnet fisheries often have high bycatch rates of threatened marine species such as sea turtles, whales, dolphins, and seabirds.<br/><br/>Saying, "Sensory cues &#8211; in this case, LED lights &#8211; are one way we might alert such species to the presence of fishing gear in the water."<br/><br/>Each gillnet was paired with an unlit gillnet to compare the results. Eighty-six percent of the turtles caught in the unlit nets were green turtles, however, loggerhead and olive ridley turtles were also found in the nets.<br/><br/>Among the small cetaceans captured, 47 percent were long-beaked common dolphins, 26 percent were dusky dolphins and 24 percent were Burmeister's porpoises.<br/><br/>The findings also support previous research which suggested LED lights reduce bycatch of seabirds in gillnets by about 85 percent.<br/><br/>Just as warning lights warn us of danger, the intelligent animals were able to see the illuminated nets, furthermore, the light modification made no change to the amount of commercial catch fisherman caught.<br/><br/>Researchers hope the cost-effective nets are promptly adopted by fishermen as more than one-third of the marine mammals and nearly one-third of sharks and fish are currently threatened with extinction due to the consequences of fishing and other human activity.<br/><br/>University of Exeter Professor Brendan Godley said, "this work has further shown the usefulness of lights on nets to save wildlife. We now need lights that are ever more robust and affordable."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/led-fishing-nets-save-turtles-and-dolphins-3933589</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/119/D32/119D3281DB09F0A33B98F422136CC2B4.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933589/3933589_E4EB52C8A48041DB8972ACC014F32595_191211_3933589_LED_fishing_nets_save_turtles_and_dolphins_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 06:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3933742</guid>
      <title>Mystery stripes on Saturn's ice moon Enceladus finally explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> Scientists may have finally solved the mystery of the 'tiger stripes' on Saturn's moon Enceladus.<br/><br/>According to a study published in Nature Astronomy, the Cassini probe first detected the four strange fractures on the moon's north pole when the spacecraft orbited around Saturn 15 years ago.<br/><br/>According to the researchers, the 'tiger stripes' are about 130 kilometers long, with fracture lines running parallel to one another, spaced at 35 kilometers apart.<br/><br/>Lead author Doug Hemingway at the Carnegie Institute for Science says that the fissures constantly blow out water and ice, unlike any other formation known to exist on icy moons.<br/><br/>According to the research team, the tiger stripes and the formation's strange behavior is caused by the moon's 'eccentric' orbit around Saturn.<br/><br/>Because Enceladus' distance to Saturn fluctuates, planetary gravity stretches and flexes the moon. This effect generates the heat that keeps Enceladus from freezing solid.<br/><br/>The gravitational force is so powerful that it changes the shape of the moon, with the resulting stress creating the first tiger stripe on Enceladus.<br/><br/>As the moon's surface ocean erupts through the fissure, the jets of water then freeze and fall back on the moon." <br/><br/>The weight of the accumulated ice and snow puts pressure on the nearby ice sheet and breaks the crust on parallel lines. Those fractures become the moon's stripes.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mystery-stripes-on-saturn-s-ice-moon-enceladus-finally-explained-3933742</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/27F/4AB/27F4AB6DA2C3DBD1C9F90B8A6C684500.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/11/3933742/3933742_BA23F72CF92C48C2A37E666EEEDEB0FD_191211_3933742_Mystery_stripes_on_Saturn_s_ice_moon_Enceladus_f_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2019 10:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934038</guid>
      <title>Ozone layer recovery has slowed climate change</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY <br/> A new study from the University of New South Wales has found that in addition to allowing the ozone layer to recover, the Montreal Protocol has also slowed the rate of climate change by up to 25 percent.<br/><br/>The Montreal Protocol is an international agreement signed by countries around the world in 1987 to stop the import and production of chemicals such as chlorofluorocarbons that are harmful to the earth's ozone layer, after an "ozone hole" was found over Antarctica.<br/><br/>The ozone layer protects our planet by deflecting harmful radiation from the sun.<br/><br/>Researchers tested out two different scenarios: one in which the Montreal Protocol was brought into effect and another in which the agreement wasn't.<br/><br/>Using an estimated 3 percent increase of CFC emissions per year starting from 1987, scientists estimate the Montreal Protocol has likely already helped our planet avoid 0.5 degrees Celsius to 1 degree Celsius of temperature rise over some land areas and 3 degrees Celsius to 4 degrees Celsius of temperature rise across much of the Arctic, as of 2019.<br/><br/>The study, published in the journal Environmental Research Letters, estimates that our planet will be at least 1&#176;C cooler by 2050 than it would have been had the agreement not been enacted.<br/><br/>Researchers also found that the Arctic summer sea ice extent is roughly 25 percent higher today than it would have been otherwise.<br/><br/>The study also suggests that Greenland's melting ice sheet and subsequent sea level rise is happening at a slower speed. <br/><br/>Lead author of the paper, Rishav Goyal, said in a University of New South Wales news release that the agreement saved the ozone layer as well as reduced a "substantial fraction" of global warming as CFCs are a thousand times more potent than carbon dioxide.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ozone-layer-recovery-has-slowed-climate-change-3934038</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/EEC/7A4/EEC7A4F765A4BF137916CD2D49003BB8.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934038/3934038_69DB59CE68D44CC5AC0765C41BB6C6E5_191212_3934038_Ozone_layer_recovery_has_slowed_climate_change_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 04:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934023</guid>
      <title>Cell phones to blame for mom's eye disorder</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WAKE FOREST, NORTH CAROLINA <br/> "I'm blind in the morning, basically," said Gretta Nance, a mom from Wake Forest, who can blame her mobile device habits for her eye disorder. <br/><br/>Gretta Nance is a brand manager and she spends hours every day switching between her iPhone, Macbook, and television. She, like so many, had perfect vision her entire life, but now, unsurprisingly, is part of a troubling trend that optometrists are seeing.<br/><br/>Nance told ABC11 that she essentially wakes up blind, she also stated that by the evenings she can't even watch television because her eyes just want to close. She said that she now keeps bottles of eye drops and several pairs of glasses distributed about her home. <br/><br/>She was recently diagnosed with, Meibomian Gland Dysfunction, more commonly known as MGD. Doctors said the condition is common among the older generation, but they are starting to see more cases and younger patients. Optometrists think it's because of our dependence on mobile devices.<br/><br/>According to EMarketer.com, people are spending more time staring at their smartphones than watching TV. They say the average American is spending more than three hours every day on their mobile devices, and doctors believe when we're using these devices, our eyes are alert and glued.<br/><br/>Dr. Amorette Hanna of Stonehenge Vision Source explained that when we're using digital devices, we blink about 60 percent less. The blink is what triggers the eyelid to secrete oils. Those oils coat the eye and allow us to see clearly without irritation.<br/><br/>If you don't blink, the oils are not being replenished and the glands dry out, resulting in permanent damage.<br/><br/>Hanna said, "When those glands are lost, unfortunately, there's no way to get them back."<br/><br/>X-rays of Wake Forest mum Nance's eyelid, show that her oils have evaporated.<br/><br/>So, what're the symptoms of MGD?<br/><br/>Dryness. A sandy or gritty feeling. Burning sensation. Eye and lid irritation. Contact lens intolerance. Eyelids sticking together in the morning and or blurry vision.<br/><br/>How can you prevent getting MGD?<br/><br/>Doctors recommend the 20-20-20 rule. For every 20 minutes you spend on the phone, look away for 20 seconds to something 20 feet away.<br/><br/>Nance is now visiting her doctor every six weeks, she said, "This is something I'll have to deal with for the rest of my life. That was probably one of the most shocking things of it: learning I can't get those glands back."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cell-phones-to-blame-for-mom-s-eye-disorder-3934023</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/447/A4C/447A4C3EC8D5E5D08470B2C1A2194195.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934023/3934023_9F1934A0512B497BAB4238DFF3812F49_191212_3934023_Cell_phones_to_blame_for_mom_s_eye_disorder_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 03:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934155</guid>
      <title>Hackers can access personal data via smart home devices</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PORTLAND, OREGON <br/> The FBI issued a statement earlier this month warning consumers about smart home devices that could be vulnerable to hacks.<br/><br/>This includes smart digital assistants, smart watches, smart refrigerators, home security devices, and gaming systems.<br/><br/>FBI officials explained in the statement that these Internet of Things devices are continuously sending and receiving data, but users are typically unaware of how the data is being collected or where exactly it is being transmitted.<br/><br/>The agency warned that hackers may be able to conduct a "virtual drive-by" of users' digital lives if they gain access via unsecured devices. This, in turn, gives them access to a user's router and everything connected to their home network.<br/><br/>The bureau urged users to change the default password and set unique passwords for every smart home device, as well as store sensitive and private data on a network system separate from the IoT devices.<br/><br/>The FBI also recommended updating smart home devices regularly, and checking permissions on mobile apps linked to the smart devices.<br/><br/>The agency further encouraged users to turn on automatic updates for software, hardware and operating systems on their smart devices for the latest updates.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/hackers-can-access-personal-data-via-smart-home-devices-3934155</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/66D/D7E/66DD7E62F95B621586AE74C84B8D25D7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934155/3934155_6377439C71A44ECA8F67C91071435A1E_191212_3934155_Hackers_can_access_personal_data_via_smart_home__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 07:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934375</guid>
      <title>ESA's spacecraft will take out orbital debris in 2025</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS <br/> The European Space Agency has commissioned the world's first mission to capture a piece of space debris from Earth's orbit in 2025.<br/><br/>The ESA says that the Swiss startup ClearSpace was awarded with the contract for ClearSpace-1, a spacecraft that will sport four robotic arms for grabbing debris.<br/><br/>ClearSpace CEO Luc Piguet says the spacecraft will be a "tow truck" that clears space debris to make room for satellites.<br/><br/>According to the ESA, ClearSpace-1 will recover the VESPA, a secondary payload adapter that has been left adrift since it helped deliver the Proba-V satellite to space in 2013.<br/><br/>The VESPA is close in size to a small satellite, and its simple shape and sturdy construction makes the adaptor a prime candidate for the experiment.<br/><br/>ClearSpace-1 will be launched into a 500-kilometer orbit to undergo testing before it moves up to VESPA's higher orbit, which sits at an altitude of 660 by 800 kilometers.<br/><br/>Once in position, ClearSpace-1 will utilize its quartet of arms to catch Vespa under the ESA's supervision.<br/><br/>After ClearSpace-1 captures the target, it will return to the Earth's atmosphere and burn up with the VESPA.<br/><br/>The ESA says it will refine the chaser's capabilities with the goal of launching follow up missions in the future, including capturing multiple objects.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/esa-s-spacecraft-will-take-out-orbital-debris-in-2025-3934375</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E4E/4E0/E4E4E0B15F74AC69FF77392F86ED35A1.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/12/3934375/3934375_90D4A5532BF84119A1B4621C471D4ABF_191212_3934375_ESA_s_spacecraft_will_take_out_orbital_debris_in_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 12:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3934818</guid>
      <title>New recluse spider species discovered in Mexico</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY <br/> Biologists at the National Autonomous University of Mexico said they have discovered a new species of recluse spiders named Loxosceles tenochtitlan in Mexico Valley.<br/><br/>Quoting a researcher, El Universal reports that the spider has a distinctive dark brown coloring and a clear violin pattern on its dorsal section.<br/><br/>According to the university's press release, the spider is set apart from other recluse spiders by its sensing appendages and sexual organs of its females.<br/><br/>The spider also possesses a venomous bite that it utilizes as a defense mechanism.<br/><br/>The bite causes a blue-purple ulcer on the victim that could be hard to identify clinically because it is not painful and symptoms could be confused with a common rash or infection.<br/><br/>Biologist Valdez-Mondragon told El Universal that the spider lives in urban homes because the environment provides suitable humidity, heat and prey.<br/><br/>The spider favors hiding in tight spots and eats cockroaches, so they could be encountered in trash cans.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-recluse-spider-species-discovered-in-mexico-3934818</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E3E/FA9/E3EFA988B81E84EED873FD71F3881523.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/13/3934818/3934818_3C2B73D101E64B9C9ECF5A0197894768_191213_3934818_New_recluse_spider_species_discovered_in_Mexico_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2019 09:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935172</guid>
      <title>Using sunlight to convert plastic into green fuel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE <br/>  Researchers at the Nanyang Technological University this week said they have found a way to use sunlight to turn consumer plastic into a valuable chemical that could generate clean power. <br/><br/>They reported their findings in the journal Advanced Science.<br/><br/>Speaking in a university news release, the team said dissolved polyethylene in a solution that contained a vanadium-based catalyst.<br/><br/>Vanadium is a metal commonly used in steel and aluminum alloys for vehicles and aircraft.<br/><br/>The researchers exposed the solution to artificial sunlight, which breaks the carbon bonds in polyethylene and transforms the substance into formic acid.<br/><br/>While other conversion methods exist, the scientists said their process does not use high heat or toxic substances to produce formic acid from plastics.<br/><br/>They explained that formic acid is utilized for power generation in hydrogen fuel cells which could be a low-emissions source of clean energy.<br/><br/>The researchers say they are working to scale up the technology to help Singapore to turn its plastic waste into energy resources without harming the environment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/using-sunlight-to-convert-plastic-into-green-fuel-3935172</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/989/4C8/9894C81E6317F88B945E0C89957CEFDA.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/14/3935172/3935172_0D61302A75314E6FAD3C091DA898183B_191214_3935172_Using_sunlight_to_convert_plastic_into_green_fue_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 03:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935281</guid>
      <title>Greenland's glaciers are melting at worst-case scenario rates</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GREENLAND <br/> A new study using satellite images finds that Greenland's glacier melt is accelerating, the study's authors wrote in an article published in the journal Nature. <br/><br/>The study says the pace of melting matches the worse climate warming and sea-level scenarios predicted by the U.N.<br/><br/>The Guardian reports that according to the data, Greenland has lost 3.8 trillion tonnes of ice since 1992 and that the current rate of melting is seven times faster than compared to the nineties. <br/><br/>Study co-author Andrew Shepard says that Greenland has raised the sea level by one centimeter since the 1990s, enough to bring annual and seasonal floods to six million people.<br/><br/>He tells the Washington Post that the U.N.'s worst-case scenarios predict that  Greenland will contribute another 16 centimeters of sea-level rise by 2100.<br/><br/>While seawater normally erodes the glaciers, the study finds that rising summer temperatures are turning exposed ice to meltwater, which makes the shelf melt faster.<br/><br/>The study additionally finds that glaciers are flowing faster into the deep waters of Greenland's fjords and that this makes the ice shelf break into pieces in the ocean.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/greenland-s-glaciers-are-melting-at-worst-case-scenario-rates-3935281</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/14/3935281/3935281_48186F235F00457A92E5FFBDC3887E72_191214_3935281_Greenland_s_glaciers_are_melting_at_worst_case_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 08:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935269</guid>
      <title>Using sunlight to convert plastic into green fuel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE <br/>  Researchers at the Nanyang Technological University this week said they have found a way to use sunlight to turn consumer plastic into a valuable chemical that could generate clean power. <br/><br/>They reported their findings in the journal Advanced Science.<br/><br/>Speaking in a university news release, the team said dissolved polyethylene in a solution that contained a vanadium-based catalyst.<br/><br/>Vanadium is a metal commonly used in steel and aluminum alloys for vehicles and aircraft.<br/><br/>The researchers exposed the solution to artificial sunlight, which breaks the carbon bonds in polyethylene and transforms the substance into formic acid.<br/><br/>While other conversion methods exist, the scientists said their process does not use high heat or toxic substances to produce formic acid from plastics.<br/><br/>They explained that formic acid is utilized for power generation in hydrogen fuel cells which could be a low-emissions source of clean energy.<br/><br/>The researchers say they are working to scale up the technology to help Singapore to turn its plastic waste into energy resources without harming the environment.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/using-sunlight-to-convert-plastic-into-green-fuel-3935269</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4D3/A9C/4D3A9C8D429C192E78D54942B9A65369.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/14/3935269/3935269_9CA41691B3DE4AEFA2F8BA7CEBB6B2FB_191214_3935269_Using_sunlight_to_convert_plastic_into_green_fue_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 08:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3935825</guid>
      <title>How plants make noise when stressed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TEL AVIV, ISRAEL <br/> New research from Tel Aviv University has found that plants make noise when stressed.<br/><br/>For the study, scientists focused on tomato and tobacco plants.<br/><br/>They placed plants into three groups. These were drought-stressed plants, plants cut at the stem and control plants. These were placed in an acoustic box for an hour.<br/><br/>Each plant was recorded with two microphones placed 10 centimeters away.<br/><br/>On average, drought-stressed tomato plants emitted roughly 35 ultrasonic sounds per hour, while tobacco plants produced 11 per hour. Cut tomato plants created roughly 25 sounds per hour, while tobacco plants generated 15.<br/><br/>The study found that all control plants produced, on average, less than one sound per hour.<br/><br/>The scientists explained in the study that these sounds could potentially be heard by other organisms up to several meters away.<br/><br/>The tomato plants were also placed in a greenhouse setting to test whether or not sounds emitted by plants would be identified outdoors. The results matched researchers' findings from the plants in the acoustic box in that plants produce more sounds as they become dehydrated.<br/><br/>Machine learning classifiers were able to distinguish distinct noises produced by the different plants in both the acoustic box and the greenhouse setting.<br/><br/>Researchers suggested that in the future, farmers may be able to use this type of technology to listen out for drought-stressed crops to better assess their crops.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-plants-make-noise-when-stressed-3935825</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/ACF/09C/ACF09C60D771D9428EF68569AD6EE48F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3935825/3935825_D0CF564CEDF14532A890B604BBA9B699_191216_3935825_How_plants_make_noise_when_stressed_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 02:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936201</guid>
      <title>'Monster black hole' might not be so monster after all</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SPACE <br/> Two new studies have called into question the size of the "impossibly big" black hole named LB-1, according to the papers published independently to the arXiv database.<br/><br/>A team led by Chinese astronomer Liu Jinfeng claimed that LB-1 is 70 times the mass of the sun, bigger than the 20-solar-mass models predicted for black holes in our galaxy.'<br/><br/>The papers found the same basic problem with the Chinese researchers claim: it relied on evidence that the unseen black hole was wiggling very slightly as its heavy companion star wheeled around it." <br/><br/>The new studies claim that the initial team misinterpreted what they were seeing in the light from the distant system.<br/><br/>Movements from LB-1 create spectral light via doppler effect called H alpha line emissions."<br/><br/>The Chinese team used China's powerful LAMOST telescope to detect H alpha line emissions, then used the black hole's movements to infer its mass."<br/><br/>The authors of the new studies argue that the original team did not properly adjust for the emissions from LB1's star, which also emits H alpha, according to Live Science.<br/><br/>Astrophysicists El-Badry and Quataert write in their paper that after factoring in the star, the data suggests LB1 is far more likely to be a sun-sized black hole.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-monster-black-hole-might-not-be-so-monster-after-all-3936201</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/906/FE8/906FE83E3CBF92ABB37CBA1DADA015CA.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/16/3936201/3936201_E03E02B6E4E84F6197F8DDE0C06754FB_191216_3936201__Monster_black_hole__might_not_be_so_monster_aft_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 13:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936387</guid>
      <title>Facebook serves ads based on your offline shopping habits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MENLO PARK, CALIFORNIA <br/> Facebook is able to gather data about user shopping habits, both online and offline, in order to serve targeted ads on its platform, according to a new report by Business Insider.<br/><br/>The report says that Facebook acquires information about user purchases via its partnerships with retailers.<br/><br/>It explains that when a consumer buys a product from a physical or online store, the retailer can retain purchase details and user information such as name, email, or phone number.<br/><br/>This could be sent to Facebook if they want to display targeted ads to the consumer.<br/><br/>Facebook then matches the information to a user's profile and starts displaying ads from the retail stores directly to the consumer.<br/><br/>The company says this allows them to create a custom audience from the acquired information, allowing them to show targeted ads to Facebook users that have shopped at the store.<br/><br/>According to Business Insider, retailers such as Macy's and Dick's Sporting Goods are using these advertising techniques to increase sales.<br/><br/>The report mentioned that Facebook users have the option of opting out of targeted ads, by clicking the 'Not allowed' option on their Facebook ad setting page.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/facebook-serves-ads-based-on-your-offline-shopping-habits-3936387</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/803/834/80383414BAB39853B7CB3C423125C29E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936387/3936387_1DA9C3940E1742F5B944A8C4A2A5A713_191217_3936387_Facebook_serves_ads_based_on_your_offline_shoppi_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 02:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936609</guid>
      <title>There are a million times more microplastics in the ocean: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO <br/> A new study from the Scripps Institution of Oceanography at the University of California San Diego suggests that the ocean could potentially contain a million times more microplastic particles than previously thought.<br/><br/>Researchers say that past methods used for collecting microplastic samples, such as net tows, were inadequate as smaller plastic particles are able to escape through the holes of the net.<br/><br/>For the study, the team developed a new technique to gather microplastics from the ocean surface.<br/><br/>Researchers took three different cruises during three different time periods between 2009 to 2015 to gather surface seawater samples in metal buckets from the open ocean and near the shore. The samples were promptly filtered with polycarbonate filters and then frozen.<br/><br/>Scientists also gathered 100 salp samples from the sea in 2009, 2013, 2014, 2015 and 2017 using mesh bongo nets. Salps are gelatinous creatures that suck in seawater for food as well as to propel themselves in the ocean.<br/><br/>The study found that nearshore samples of seawater had a higher concentration of plastic than samples obtained from the open sea. Researchers then analysed the salps via epifluorescence microscopy and found that every single salp sample contained tiny microplastic pieces in their gut.<br/><br/>Scientists estimated that the sea is contaminated by roughly 8.3 million pieces of <br/>"mini-microplastics," or the smallest microplastics, per cubic meter of water.<br/><br/>Lead author of the study, Jennifer Brandon, explained in a news release from the university that even though salps are low in the ocean's food chain, these microplastic particles could eventually make their way up the food chain and one day end up in the human body.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/there-are-a-million-times-more-microplastics-in-the-ocean-study-3936609</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/638/382/6383823863CE87603582987CCCDFBFE3.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936609/3936609_6DFF4D46AA5D436E909E8952D3A784E3_191217_3936609_There_are_a_million_times_more_microplastics_in__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 09:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936794</guid>
      <title>NASA hones in on asteroid sample site</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANSICO, CALIFORNIA <br/> NASA has selected a target site for the spacecraft  OSIRIS[i]-REx[j] to gather samples on the asteroid Bennu, according to the mission's principal investigator.<br/><br/>In a statement made at the American Geophysical Union annual conference last week, principal investigator Dante Lauretta said the spacecraft has been orbiting Bennu since December 2018.<br/><br/>Lauretta says that Nightingale lies far to the asteroid's north, with cooler temperatures than other possible sites.<br/><br/>This means Nightingale's surface would preserve more materials dated back to Bennu's formation for the probe to collect.<br/><br/>Citing Lauretta, Science News reports that Nightingale is a 20-meter wide crater contained in a larger crater and that parking the six-meter wide spacecraft could be a 'tight fit'." <br/><br/>The New York Times reports that Bennu is one of the oldest rocks in the solar system and that the asteroid is rich in carbon and organic substances like hydrated minerals."<br/><br/>The spacecraft will touch down on Bennu for only a split-second next year and deploy its robotic arm to gather a sample.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-hones-in-on-asteroid-sample-site-3936794</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/029/561/0295613F3F44136DCDCC9ACB4916CA21.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936794/3936794_8BC5064CC29E47E7B361B2AC46212C1C_191217_3936794_NASA_hones_in_on_asteroid_sample_site_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3936777</guid>
      <title>NASA wants to put antennas on the far side of the moon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Space researchers have proposed building a network of radio antennas on the far side of the moon, according to a NASA funded report.<br/><br/>NASA says that the array<br/>named the Farside antennas<br/>will allow the agency to monitor the closest stellar systems more easily.<br/><br/>The paper's lead authors professors Jack Burns and Gregg Hallinan suggest deploying 128 antennas by using a lunar rover.<br/><br/>The antennas will be tethered to a base station that supplies central data processing, power and communications across the array's 10 kilometer span.<br/><br/>The Farside base then will use NASA's proposed Gateway Station to transmit signals back to Earth.<br/><br/>Habitable exoplanets closest to the solar system would possess magnetospheres that the antennas will be able to detect from the moon's far side, where there is limited sky noise.<br/><br/>The study states that the antennas could also sound the moon's subsurface.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-wants-to-put-antennas-on-the-far-side-of-the-moon-3936777</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/64E/660/64E66091625E65979106B1755CA1ED90.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/17/3936777/3936777_0646EB5DB72B4CB69BCDE25E5E237BD7_191217_3936777_NASA_wants_to_put_antennas_on_the_far_side_of_th_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 13:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937359</guid>
      <title>NASA, Lockheed Martin to build 'quiet' jet for supersonic air travel</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA has cleared the final assembly of Lockheed Martin's quiet supersonic jet prototype, the agency says in a news release on Tuesday.<br/><br/>Lockheed Martin says that X-59 aircraft will be a model for quiet, faster-than-sound passenger jets.<br/><br/>Lockheed Martin states that the X-59 will be able to cruise at an altitude of 55,000 feet and achieve an airspeed of 940 miles per hour.<br/><br/>The corporation claims technology derived from the jet will cut air travel time by half.<br/><br/>According to NASA, the X-59's shape is specially designed to mitigate sonic boom by reducing the noise that reaches the ground.<br/><br/>Lockheed Martin says that the airplane makes 75 Perceived Level decibels, or about as loud as a closing car door.<br/><br/>According to NASA, the jet will feature cameras and sensors that allow safe flying without a forward-facing window.<br/><br/>NASA says the finished jet will fly over select US communities to create instrument readings and to measure the public's opinion.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-lockheed-martin-to-build-quiet-jet-for-supersonic-air-travel-3937359</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/85A/964/85A9645A7955438A4B670FB281DC3049.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/18/3937359/3937359_62FD4AA1ADC04ED8A4FD60671E4CC744_191218_3937359_NASA__Lockheed_Martin_to_build__quiet__jet_for_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2019 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937705</guid>
      <title>Easter Island Moai statues may have helped ancient farmers</title>
      <description><![CDATA[EASTER ISLAND / CHILE <br/> Easter Island's Moai[e] stone monoliths might have been created out of the belief they would make crops more fertile, according to new research by the University of California, Los Angeles.<br/><br/>According to a UCLA press release, ancient Easter Islanders built over 1,000 Moai statues under the direction of the ruling elite in a remarkable feat of human engineering.<br/><br/>According to the study, published in the Journal of Archeological Sciences, Rano Raraku quarry is the origin point for over 95 percent of all Moai statues.<br/><br/>Researchers studied two monoliths found in the quarry and took extensive soil samples from the surrounding areas.<br/><br/>Analysis by the researchers found that quarrying would have helped in releasing clay soil that is rich in phosphorus and calcium.<br/><br/>Those elements would have helped the growth of bananas, sweet potatoes and taro that Easter Islanders grew extensively near the quarry.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/easter-island-moai-statues-may-have-helped-ancient-farmers-3937705</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/D70/F6F/D70F6F82D92A07483509A5014DC4AD90.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937705/3937705_4ADB29922DF045E7AACF7C48855A6048_191219_3937705_Easter_Island_Moai_statues_may_have_helped_ancie_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 09:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937672</guid>
      <title>Company unveils new slanted toilets to reduce bathroom breaks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STAFFORD, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> British company StandardToilet has unveiled a new design in which the toilet is tilted downwards at a 13 degree angle in a bid to reduce the amount of time spent in the bathroom.<br/><br/>The design has been approved by the British Toilet Association, an organization that advocates for better toilet facilities across the United Kingdom.<br/><br/>Founder of the StandardToilet, Mahabir Gill, explained to Wired that the toilet is designed to cause strain on the legs, like squat thrusts, and make you want to get up after about five minutes of use.<br/><br/>The company says the toilet provides health benefits such as reducing haemorrhoids, musculoskeletal disorder and improving a person's posture.<br/><br/>The company's website states that the toilet uses a water saving dual-flush system and includes specially designed slots in the toilet's rim that would allow for a quieter, more uniform flush.<br/><br/>In a press release from the British Toilet Association, StandardToilet explains that the toilet would reduce long lines for public bathrooms in shopping malls, train stations and other public spaces.<br/><br/>The company also says the toilet's new design would minimize the amount of time employees spend in the restroom during bathroom breaks. In the press release, StandardToilet noted that the workplace bathroom has become a space for texting and using social media.<br/><br/>The company's founder told Wired that the toilet would mainly benefit employers not employees, with a primary focus on reducing the amount of time spent by employees on their phone while working.<br/><br/>The toilet is currently being sold for &#163;150 to &#163;500, or roughly US$196 to US$655.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/company-unveils-new-slanted-toilets-to-reduce-bathroom-breaks-3937672</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/DC2/28B/DC228B876411AB652C81876EC0344C35.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/19/3937672/3937672_489EE64169A34DE3B7A46B777C152BF0_191219_3937672_Company_unveils_new_slanted_toilets_to_reduce_ba_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 08:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937999</guid>
      <title>Volcanic climate change may have contributed to dinosaur extinction</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANN ARBOR, MICHIGAN <br/> Massive volcanic eruptions in India may have contributed to the extinction of the dinosaurs, which has long been believed to be the result of a massive asteroid impact.<br/><br/>According to a timeline assembled by University of Texas at Austin researchers, the Chicxulub asteroid struck a shallow ocean some 66 million years ago, hitting it with the force of 10 billion atomic bombs. The blast set the land ablaze, igniting trees and plants up to thousands of miles away.<br/><br/>Although the asteroid caused destruction at the regional level when it hit, the impact itself was not what killed off the dinosaurs.<br/><br/>Instead, scientists say sulfur-bearing rocks were vaporized at the site, releasing an estimated 325 million metric tons of sulfur  into the atmosphere, where it reflected sunlight away from the planet and caused global cooling.<br/><br/>Researchers believe the global climate change that followed was responsible for the mass extinction of the dinosaurs.<br/><br/>Global cooling disrupted photosynthesis, which killed the plants and caused the food chain to collapse.<br/><br/>Now, a new study published in Nature Communications has found evidence that another event may have contributed to the extinction.<br/><br/>The University of Michigan-led research collected and analyzed ancient fossilized shells from around the world, finding evidence of both ocean warming and high mercury concentrations when they were formed 66 million years ago.<br/><br/>These measurements are both symptoms of volcanic eruptions. They align with the onset of a series of violent eruptions that created India's Deccan Traps formations, starting before the extinction, and lasting on and off for about a million years.<br/><br/>Mercury is toxic to humans, fish, and wildlife. The levels researchers found in the ancient shells were found to be roughly equivalent to those in modern shells from mercury-polluted industrial sites. <br/><br/>Scientists believe that such a level of global mercury contamination indicates a volcanic climate change was already present before the extinction, and may have merely been accelerated by the impact event.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/volcanic-climate-change-may-have-contributed-to-dinosaur-extinction-3937999</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3937999/3937999_0E80629A83AA4DD1BF63071F809DE5CC_191220_3937999_Volcanic_climate_change_may_have_contributed_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937992</guid>
      <title>Turkey vs Greece: Fighter jets spar in Greek airspace row</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TURKEY / GREECE <br/> Turkish and Greek fighter jets engaged in 16 mock dogfights after Greece's airspace was violated by Turkish jets on December 17 over territorial claims in the Aegean Sea, according to Stars and Stripes.<br/><br/>Greek air force pilots rushed to intercept the Turkish jets as they entered the country's airspace a total of 40 times on Tuesday, Stars and Stripes reports. <br/><br/>The two nations are at odds over issues including the delimitation of territorial waters, airspace, exclusion zones and Turkey's claims over small islands in the Aegean Sea.<br/><br/>Turkey said it could send in military forces into the eastern Mediterranean and add armed drones to northern Cyprus over the two countries' territorial disputes, Stars and Stripes reports, citing Turkish Vice President Fuat Oktay.<br/><br/>Greek Defense Minister Nikos Panagiotopoulos had previously said that the disputed area is controlled by the Greek military.<br/><br/>According to Greek City Times, the country plans to purchase drones from the U.S. and Israel. The technology could be used to surveil Turkey's military moves in the Mediterranean.<br/><br/>The move comes amid growing tensions between Greece and Turkey as the U.S. has increased its military ties with Greece while the U.S. could move ahead to sanction Turkey over its military invasion in northern Syria.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/turkey-vs-greece-fighter-jets-spar-in-greek-airspace-row-3937992</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/879/E51/879E51366D83D07596A0F7E2C312AC4C.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3937992/3937992_74CEAAAF20C04EE7BC06289CE6F4E5E1_191220_3937992_Turkey_vs_Greece__Fighter_jets_spar_in_Greek_air_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 02:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3937978</guid>
      <title>500-year-old anchors believed to be from Conquistador ships</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MEXICO <br/> Archaeologists believe that they may have just discovered ship anchors from Hern&#225;n Cort&#233;s, the conqueror of the Aztec empire. <br/><br/>Mexico's National Institute of Anthropology and History have announced that two 500-year-old iron ship anchors have been discovered on Mexico's Gulf Coast. These anchors could belong to the ships of Spanish conquistador, Hern&#225;n Cort&#233;s, thus potentially offering an insight into the Spanish invasion.<br/><br/>Divers discovered the anchors 10 to 15 meters below the sea, under a thick layer of sediment. In 2018, just 1,000 feet away from the site, another anchor was found and dated back to the 15th century via its wood. The date is significant as it would fit with that of Hern&#225;n Cort&#233;s as records show he landed in Veracruz, Mexico in April 1519.<br/><br/>All three anchors were found on the coast just north of the port city of Veracruz.<br/><br/>Head of the Underwater Archeology Office, Dr. Roberto Junco details the most voluminous of the three anchors as 3.68 meters long and 1.55 meters wide between its tips.<br/><br/>Both anchors are well preserved as a result of being protected beneath the sediment of the ocean. For this reason, after documentation and measurement, they will be returned to adhere to the archaeological protocols of conservation.<br/><br/>Marine archaeologist Frederick Hanselmann explains why this is so important, <br/><br/>"The Conquest of Mexico was a seminal event in human history, and these shipwrecks, if we can find them, will be symbols of the cultural collision that led to what is now the West."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/500-year-old-anchors-believed-to-be-from-conquistador-ships-3937978</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/CD2/DDB/CD2DDBD470D8132041AF1CC60EB74EC7.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3937978/3937978_00450419BA5E4B74B27B6BDF184A0F97_191220_3937978_500_year_old_anchors_believed_to_be_from_Conquis_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 01:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3938221</guid>
      <title>NASA's Mars 2020 rover conducts its first test drive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA <br/> As part of NASA's preparation for next year's Mars mission, the Mars 2020 rover took its first driving test at the Jet Propulsion Laboratory in California on December 17.<br/><br/>The rover was able to roll forward, backward and perform a pirouette in the laboratory over a period of 10 hours, according to NASA. <br/><br/>The Mars 2020 rover was also able to drive over small ramps in the lab.<br/><br/>The rover is equipped with an autonomous navigation system, which uses high-resolution navigation cameras and image processing software. Its wheels have been redesigned for added durability.<br/><br/>NASA says the technology will allow to rover to drive roughly 200 meters per Martian day. The Mars 2020 rover will also carry a radar imager to gather data about Mars' surface.<br/><br/>The rover will be launched in July or August of 2020. It is scheduled to land on Mars' Jerozo Crater on February of 2021.<br/><br/>The Mars mission is part of a larger project that includes lunar missions to prepare humans to eventually explore the red planet.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-s-mars-2020-rover-conducts-its-first-test-drive-3938221</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/6C2/F38/6C2F38E7F4E3DD1E5FF90104242CFA09.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938221/3938221_AE51DB2129F34B808B1712F206B00902_191220_3938221_NASA_s_Mars_2020_rover_conducts_its_first_test_d_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 09:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3938438</guid>
      <title>Older Japanese workers powering up in exoskeleton suits</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JAPAN <br/> Older people in Japan are suiting up in exoskeletons to help them get through the daily grind and to stay in the workforce longer. <br/><br/>According to New Scientist, The Land of the Rising Sun isn't getting any younger, with a whopping 28 percent of the population 65 or older. <br/>The problem is, the country now has fewer and fewer young people which has led to a shortage of workers, especially in manual labor industries like construction, manufacturing and farming. <br/>To help them stay in the game, Japan has no choice but to have its aging workforce remain working as long as possible. That's not depressing at all.  <br/>Enter good OLD Japanese technology. Several tech firms in Japan are developing exoskeleton suits to give workers added support so they can keep on working. <br/>One of these firms is Innophys, which has designed several exosuits that you wear like a backpack. <br/>By squeezing the hand pump 30 times, you pump air into the air-powered 'muscles' which then allows the person to lift up to 55 pounds. <br/>They ain't cheap though. Just one suit costs 1300 bones. <br/>At this rate, it should only be a matter of time before Japan goes real Gundam style.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/older-japanese-workers-powering-up-in-exoskeleton-suits-3938438</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E10/664/E10664A30997E3820AA46F2686CB75C5.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/20/3938438/3938438_8A46FCF173C7423BBA736A883371A32F_191220_3938438_Older_Japanese_workers_powering_up_in_exoskeleto_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 14:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939251</guid>
      <title>Twin skyscrapers proposed for Brooklyn waterfront development</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> Danish architectural firm Bjarke Ingels Group and New York-based landscape architecture firm James Corner Field Operations have unveiled plans for a mixed-use development on the waterfront in Brooklyn, New York.<br/><br/>The River Street Waterfront Master Plan would consist of two sandy beaches to improve coastal resiliency as sea levels continue to rise.<br/><br/>The project plans to transform the area into a waterfront park with a circular walkway raised on stilts where visitors can stroll or take part in outdoor activities such as boating, Dezeen reports. <br/><br/>To protect against heavy flooding, the seabed underneath the park will be stepped, so it can fill up with water in an emergency.<br/><br/>The redesigned waterfront site would also include nature trails and bird watching sites for the public.<br/><br/>The two companies also want to construct two skyscrapers beside the park. These towers would include residential units and office space as well as retail stores. The buildings would also include a YMCA gym and a swimming pool.<br/><br/>The structures would make use of sustainable design elements such as passive solar shading.<br/><br/>Lead designer Lisa Switkin from James Corner Field Operations explained to Dezeen that the project would provide a better wildlife environment and allow the public to live in harmony with the surrounding water.<br/><br/>The project is currently waiting for approval from New York's City Hall, the Department of City Planning and other relevant authorities such as the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers. <br/><br/>This process is expected to take two years. If approved, construction of the new waterfront could take up to five years.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/twin-skyscrapers-proposed-for-brooklyn-waterfront-development-3939251</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/E5B/4EE/E5B4EEF89A5143A1F3815E0FFD736941.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939251/3939251_0286A7B0D7CB4A96A53D75C18D4CEF69_191223_3939251_Twin_skyscrapers_proposed_for_Brooklyn_waterfron_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 03:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939482</guid>
      <title>U.S. Navy's submarine drones may be getting offensive weapons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANNAPOLIS, MARYLAND <br/>  A retired commander has proposed using the U.S. Navy's Boeing Orca underwater drone offensively in future conflicts. <br/><br/>According to Forbes, the Orca autonomous drone is a diesel-electric submarine with a payload bay<br/>that could carry mines<br/>and a control unit located in the forward section."<br/><br/>In a post on the US Naval Institute blog, Commander Brian Dulla says the "moorpedo" is a smart weapon that is both a torpedo and a moored or bottom mine.<br/><br/>The design includes an antenna, electric power propulsion, a temporary anchor, and a shaped explosive warhead with contact and proximity triggers.<br/><br/>The Orca drone or other platforms could lay inactive moorpedos in international waters during peacetime, which is legal under international law.<br/><br/>The underwater offensive drone would use its anchor to lay in wait and its antenna for receiving commands.<br/><br/>If the autonomous weapon receives the command to actuate, it would engage the propulsion system to redeploy against an enemy port.<br/><br/>The drone would also be able to attack enemy warships entering or leaving port as a mine or strike at moored ships as a slow-moving torpedo.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-navy-s-submarine-drones-may-be-getting-offensive-weapons-3939482</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/4F4/050/4F4050F090ECFE92DD620575FA9E2AFF.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/23/3939482/3939482_63601DAC612A4BF297EBA08BCBC8E03A_191223_3939482_U_S__Navy_s_submarine_drones_may_be_getting_offe_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 10:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3939764</guid>
      <title>Tesla may soon unveil a secret new vehicle from its 'Master Plan'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PALO ALTO, CALIFORNIA <br/> Tesla has yet to unveil one of its vehicles, a high passenger-density urban transport vehicle, according to the second part of the company's Master Plan. <br/><br/>Tesla recently unveiled a new vehicle, the Tesla Semi, which was also mentioned in the plan.<br/><br/>In the Master Plan, the automotive company stated that the new electric vehicle would include self-driving technology.<br/><br/>The plan mentions that center aisles inside the vehicle would be eliminated in order to increase passenger area density. Seats would instead be added to the vehicle's current entryways.<br/><br/>Tesla explains that the vehicle would be able to take passengers all the way to their destination and would improve overall traffic congestion.<br/><br/>The plan was released in 2016, in which the automotive company explained that the vehicle is currently at its early stages of development and should soon be ready for unveiling.<br/><br/>Tesla had previously released its first Master Plan over a decade ago, in 2006, and has since launched the Model S, Model 3 and the Roadster as part of the plan.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tesla-may-soon-unveil-a-secret-new-vehicle-from-its-master-plan--3939764</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/853/971/8539717CA340622628C2A55D984F17FC.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3939764/3939764_B99F1B21BD7D4E9E9639CFB68BB07A37_191224_3939764_Tesla_may_soon_unveil_a_secret_new_vehicle_from__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 04:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940003</guid>
      <title>Taiwan's Taipei City will test driverless night shuttles in 2020</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI, TAIWAN <br/> Taiwan's capital city of Taipei will test driverless shuttles in the second quarter next year, the Taipei Times reports.<br/><br/>According to the shuttle's designer and operator Turing Drive Inc, the vehicle features an NVIDIA DRIVE PX2 processor, a top-mounted LIDAR and front and rear cameras.<br/><br/>The shuttle is controlled by an AI that uses a deep learning algorithm to drive and has lower carbon emissions.<br/><br/>Citing the city's transportation director Chen Hsueh-tai, the Liberty Times reports that sensors will be installed at intersections to help the shuttle recognize traffic signs.<br/><br/>The Taipei Times reports that the pilot program will run on the part of the city's Xinyi road between the East Gate and the Keelung Road intersection at 30 kilometers per hour.<br/><br/>Officials told the Liberty Times that a safety operator will be present on the shuttle to intervene if necessary.<br/><br/>The shuttle line is to run during the closed hours of the city's mass transit system, or between midnight and 5:00 a.m.<br/>Chen told the paper while the technology is not yet ready for daytime, running the shuttle at night will help residents commuting at late hours.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-s-taipei-city-will-test-driverless-night-shuttles-in-2020-3940003</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C18/F24/C18F2467779FFA4A23C82D3249739AFB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/24/3940003/3940003_4EE1F1F0D21D4983B48FE6F879B17FF5_191224_3940003_Taiwan_s_Taipei_City_will_test_driverless_night__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 10:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3940272</guid>
      <title>Supergiant red star Betelgeuse is becoming dimmer and dimmer</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VILLANOVA, PENNSYLVANIA <br/> Astronomers from Villanova University recently published an article noting that Betelgeuse in the constellation Orion has been significantly dimmer in recent months, leading some to speculate it could go supernova.<br/><br/>According to CNet, one possible explanation for the dimming is that Betelgeuse is out of fuel and has begun to collapse on itself resulting in a supernova explosion. Once the star explodes, the explosion would be visible during daylight and could even be brighter than the moon at night for a few weeks or even months.<br/><br/>However, astronomers say this is unlikely.<br/><br/>The other likely explanation is that because Betelgeuse is a variable star that has been dimming and brightening for a millennia, the dimming could just be the most significant dip in the past 50 years or so, which is a very short amount of time in the star's lifespan.  <br/>NASA's website states that Betelgeuse is over 1,000 times larger than our sun.<br/><br/>The star's radius is also big enough to encompass Jupiter and all four planets in our inner solar system: Mercury, Venus, Earth and Mars, CNet reports.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/supergiant-red-star-betelgeuse-is-becoming-dimmer-and-dimmer-3940272</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/893/F5F/893F5F9F9358A85FE77CC0221D37F4F2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/25/3940272/3940272_A84E09711ABA4FBE87DCFB1F3D84184A_191225_3940272_Supergiant_red_star_Betelgeuse_is_becoming_dimme_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 05:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941391</guid>
      <title>Laser telescope can now spot small space debris from Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> China-based scientists have developed a way to use laser telescopes and neural network analysis to locate space debris.<br/><br/>According to a study in the Journal of Laser Applications, the team tested the method at the Beijing Fangshen laser range telescope station.<br/><br/>Citing the team leader Ma Tianming, the American Institute of Physics says the technology allows laser scopes to detect reflected laser light from small space debris with greater accuracy than before.<br/><br/>It can detect space junk with a cross-section of one square meter and a distance of 1,500 kilometers from earth.<br/><br/>According to the news release, neural networks are algorithms based on the human brain's sensory inputs, processing and outputs.<br/><br/>Using the neural network to fine-tune telescope readings, the team says their technology is the first to have significantly augmented laser ranging accuracy.<br/><br/>Researchers say refining the technology will enable telescopes to pinpoint orbital debris.<br/><br/>The paper states that locating the debris would then allow spacecraft to chart a safer course to avoid space junk.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/laser-telescope-can-now-spot-small-space-debris-from-earth-3941391</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/288/BE8/288BE880E23522969C86FA1F2B4DF5BE.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941391/3941391_B51625600A474D0A88B287A9BBDBAB46_191227_3941391_Laser_telescope_can_now_spot_small_space_debris__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3941366</guid>
      <title>World's largest 3D-printed building completed in Dubai</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES <br/> Apis Cor, an American construction firm that specializes in 3D printing, completed the world's largest 3D-printed building in Dubai at the end of October.<br/><br/>The building stands at 9.5 meters and covers an area of 640 square meters, according to the company's project website. <br/><br/>The structure was built using a mobile 3D printer onsite. It was moved around by a crane at the construction site. The 3D printer used a gypsum-based mixture developed by the company.<br/><br/>Apis Cor said the printer was able to withstand Dubai's harsh weather conditions as the entire process took place outdoors, without temperature or humidity control.<br/><br/>According to design magazine Dwell, the building was completed in three weeks.<br/><br/>Traditional construction methods were used to lay the building's foundation and install the structure's roof, windows and insulation. Manual labor was used to fill the building's columns with heavy concrete and rebar.<br/><br/>The building will provide offices for a government agency in Dubai, according to Dwell. <br/><br/>Apis Cor said on their website that they plan to improve their 3D printing technology and develop a new version of the printer that would be twice as fast.<br/><br/>The company plans to build affordable 3D-printed houses in the states of California and Louisiana.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/world-s-largest-3d-printed-building-completed-in-dubai-3941366</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/7DA/F67/7DAF67E13E316F368255F3F96963ABD2.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/27/3941366/3941366_18DC3748CB744127ABFB70137133C948_191227_3941366_World_s_largest_3D_printed_building_completed_in_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 10:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942498</guid>
      <title>Russia's floating nuclear power plant now produces electricity</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PEVEK, RUSSIA <br/>  The floating nuclear power plant Akademik Lomonosov has been connected to the electricity grid and successfully produced power for the first time in the Russian town of Pevek.<br/><br/>Back in August, the vessel had set out on a three-week journey from the port of Murmansk, as reported by the Associated Press.<br/><br/>As it is not self-propelled, the floating power unit was towed by a fleet of tugboats to the Russian town when it arrived on September 14.<br/><br/>The vessel is 144 meters long and 30 meters wide, according to a news release from Rosatom, the company that designed the floating plant.<br/><br/>The Akademik Lomonosov is equipped with two reactor systems, each with a 35-megawatt capacity. The reactors produce steam for a turbine that will then generate electricity.<br/><br/>The vessel is designed to provide energy to port cities and offshore gas and oil-extracting platforms.<br/><br/>It is capable of producing enough to power a city of 100,000 inhabitants.<br/><br/>Rosatom claims that the floating nuclear plant is designed with a great margin of safety that exceeds all possible threats, which makes nuclear reactors "invincible" against tsunamis and other natural disasters.<br/><br/>The Associated Press points out environmentalists have criticized the floating nuclear plant as "inherently dangerous" adding that it threatens the clean Arctic region.<br/><br/>But Russia has dismissed these concerns, insisting that a floating nuclear power plant is completely safe.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/russia-s-floating-nuclear-power-plant-now-produces-electricity-3942498</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/5C3/F4A/5C3F4A50135848F24F2643E798C0D24F.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/30/3942498/3942498_F4A513A87BE84EE8A9C05C7351CE2E80_191230_3942498_Russia_s_floating_nuclear_power_plant_now_produc_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 10:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942795</guid>
      <title>Geologists discover 'iron snow' in Earth's core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[AUSTIN, TEXAS <br/>It is snowing iron at the Earth's core because molten iron crystalizes in the outer core before the substance sinking downwards, a study published in JGR Solid Earth says.<br/><br/>The University of Texas at Austin said in a press release that these iron particles form a 300 kilometer layer above the Earth's solid inner core.<br/><br/>The study said that the team led by Sichuan University associate professor Zhang Youjun analyzed seismic wave signals to infer the composition of the Earth's core.<br/><br/>The university says that scientists found seismic waves propagating slowly in the outer core's base, but quickly in the eastern hemisphere of the top inner core.<br/><br/>The researchers believe that the varying thickness of the iron slurry layer is the cause of the speed difference.<br/><br/>They theorize that the iron particles have the effect of slowing seismic wave travel and that the substance is thinner on the inner core's eastern hemisphere.<br/><br/>According to the researchers, the Earth's core drives tectonic plate movement with its heat and generates the magnetic field around the planet.<br/><br/>The researchers say that understanding the composition of the Earth's core may shed light on those larger processes.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/geologists-discover-iron-snow-in-earth-s-core-3942795</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/808/92F/80892F5944C31DAD37D60B798974B881.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942795/3942795_4B285AFA4178413FBEC94D3423ECF6A9_191231_3942795_Geologists_discover__iron_snow__in_Earth_s_core_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 05:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942735</guid>
      <title>FAA proposes remote ID system to track drones across the U.S.</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The Federal Aviation Administration has proposed using remote identification for unmanned aircraft systems in the U.S.<br/><br/>The agency proposes that drones in U.S. airspace would have to meet one of three remote identification requirements: the standard remote identification; limited remote identification; or those without any remote identification.<br/><br/>The system would allow the government to track drones across the country and could also make it possible for third parties to track the vehicles as well, CNBC reports. <br/><br/>The agency says that the remote ID of drones is necessary "to ensure public safety and the safety and efficiency of the airspace of the United States."<br/><br/>A standard remote identification drone includes equipment that is able to connect to the internet and transmit remote identification messages to a Remote ID unmanned service supplier as well as broadcast these messages directly while in the sky.<br/><br/>A limited remote identification drone is an unmanned vehicle that is capable of connecting to the internet and transmitting remote identification messages to a Remote ID USS, though it is unable to broadcast these messages directly. This type of drone is restricted in operating higher than 400 feet from its control station.<br/><br/>According to an unpublished proposal by the FAA, the Remote ID USS would be required to have the ability to share these messages in near real-time with the FAA, and secure access to such information.<br/><br/>Drones such as amateur built vehicles and previously manufactured aerial vehicles that may not have remote identification capabilities would be required to fly within the visual line of sight and only in FAA-recognized identification areas.<br/><br/>The FAA states in the proposal that all drones in U.S. airspace would be required to comply with the new regulations within three years.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/faa-proposes-remote-id-system-to-track-drones-across-the-u-s--3942735</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/C7C/4BD/C7C4BDDFB594B53D05572E492B77558E.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942735/3942735_F95F2AF8D44245EA942EB449BCEADD37_191231_3942735_FAA_proposes_remote_ID_system_to_track_drones_ac_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 03:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942716</guid>
      <title>How predatory whales are able to hunt down tiny fish</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA <br/> New research has found that the rorqual whale species, particularly humpback whales, are able to use stealth and deception to prey on tiny fish.<br/><br/>In a Stanford University news release, scientists said they were curious as to why the small fish weren't able to escape from their predator.<br/><br/>The study, published in the journal Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, suggests that the precise timing of the whale opening its mouth to engulf the fish allows it to avoid triggering an escape response in them.<br/><br/>When researchers monitored anchovies' escape reaction to a virtual whale, they found that by the time the fish responded to the whale's predatory behavior, it had already expanded its jaw to capture them.<br/><br/>The study suggests that humpback whales wait to open their jaws until they are extremely close to tiny fish in order to engulf them, a method called lunge-feeding.<br/><br/>When whales lunge after tiny fish, their jaws expand to consume a volume of water larger than their own bodies. They then filter out the excess water before swallowing the fish they caught. <br/><br/>This technique allows humpback whales to capture 30 to 60 percent of the school of fish at once.  <br/><br/>Scientists did not see the whales doing the same when pursuing other prey such as krill. According to the news release, this is due to krill being less responsive to predators.<br/><br/>David Cade, a researcher involved in the study, explained in the news release that in terms of evolution, lunge-feeding is a comparatively new eating technique for the whales.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-predatory-whales-are-able-to-hunt-down-tiny-fish-3942716</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/BB8/BB7/BB8BB76315B4D80539833F0053EB22EB.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942716/3942716_C4943570693F4515AFE3DB2B929D74B2_191231_3942716_How_predatory_whales_are_able_to_hunt_down_tiny__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 02:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942825</guid>
      <title>China's very own navigation system, Beidou, near completion</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> China announced on December 27 that it is only a few months away from completing its own satellite-based position system called Beidou.<br/><br/>China has already launched 53 satellites, including those that are longer in operation, for the navigational system since 2000, reports Nikkei Asian Review.  <br/><br/>The final two satellites will be launched by June 2020. This will complete the network at 35 satellites. <br/><br/>In comparison, the U.S.'s Global Positioning System, or GPS, uses approximately 30 satellites in space.<br/><br/>China is developing a navigation system independent of the GPS in a bid to protect its own interests, Nikkei Asian Review reports. <br/><br/>The satellite's level of location accuracy is currently within 5 meters, though Beidou Navigation Satellite System spokesperson Ran Chengqi said that the system's accuracy will improve to within centimeters by the end of next year.<br/><br/>The company said this will help in search and rescue missions in the future.<br/><br/>Beidou's navigation system will also be used to improve technology for self-driving vehicles and cell phones in China.<br/><br/>According to the Nikkei Asian Review, Beidou will also include a text messaging service so that users can communicate with one another.<br/><br/>Ran said that Beidou already has plans to export its products to roughly 120 trading partners through China's Belt and Road initiative.<br/><br/>The country also plans to open up its navigational system to Southeast Asia, South Asia, Africa and eastern Europe.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-very-own-navigation-system-beidou-near-completion-3942825</link>
      <thumbnail url="https://sa-mcp.s3.amazonaws.com/up-image/tmp20180606/87D/025/87D025329BB661D77DF88DF05337C7BC.jpg"/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942825/3942825_86CE274B119A495CBC34C574DEA032FE_191231_3942825_China_s_very_own_navigation_system__Beidou__near_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 06:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3942813</guid>
      <title>Mealworms can eat styrofoam without being poisoned</title>
      <description><![CDATA[STANFORD, CALIFORNIA <br/> Scientists say that plastic eating mealworms maybe even more useful than previously thought.<br/><br/>Previous Stanford studies determined that mealworms' guts contain microbes that allow them to digest styrofoam."<br/><br/>New research published in Environmental Science & Technology has found that mealworms can potentially consume toxic plastic additives in Styrofoam without any ill effects. These worms can then be used as a safe feed supplement.<br/><br/>According to the university's news release, HBCD is a chemical added to styrofoam and other polymers as a flame retardant, but the substance is toxic.<br/><br/>Mealworms in the experiment were able to excrete 90 percent of the HBCD they ingested 24 hours after eating the plastic and expel the remaining 10 percent within 48 hours.<br/><br/>This means the mealworms are uncontaminated even if they substituted on styrofoam.<br/><br/>Stanford University says that the results have significant implications, as the worms are used as feed for various livestock, including chickens.<br/><br/>The experiment suggests worms used to consume plastic could still be used as a source of agricultural feed.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mealworms-can-eat-styrofoam-without-being-poisoned-3942813</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="http://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/19/12/31/3942813/3942813_22F1012796BC48AFAC0AF9F545D57446_191231_3942813_Mealworms_can_eat_styrofoam_without_being_poison_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 06:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
