<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 04:08:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>4014810</guid>
      <title>NASA Proposes Steam-Powered Bot for Exploring Icy Moons</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA says it might use a steam-powered hopping robot to explore the icy terrain of Jupiter's moon Europa and Saturn's moon Enceladus.<br/><br/>According to the agency's news release, the conceptual robot called SPARROW will feature avionics, instruments and thrusters inside a spherical protective shell, which is about the size of a soccer ball.<br/><br/>SPARROW stands for Steam Propelled Autonomous Retrieval Robot for Ocean Worlds.<br/><br/>The lander will transfer ice to the robot in situ, then the hopper will heat the substance into steam and use the gas to jump over great distances of the surface crust."<br/><br/>The SPARROW concept will navigate Europa's meter-high blades of ice that would stop other robots cold. After taking samples, the robot will then return to the lander for collection."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-proposes-steam-powered-bot-for-exploring-icy-moons-4014810</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/01/4014810/4014810_AAAECC2247794682A25F7F5DBE4AAAA5_200701_4014810_NASA_Proposes_Steam_Powered_Bot_for_Exploring_Ic_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 07:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4015147</guid>
      <title>Asteroid Single-Handedly Killed Off the Dinosaurs: New Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> Asteroid impact gets sole credit for wiping out the dinosaurs 66 million years ago, according to new research. Scientists from the UK say the 10-km wide asteroid that made the Chicxulub crater caused dinosaur extinction without help from volcanoes.<br/><br/>According to the study in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, the research team modeled the Chicxulub impact, Deccan volcanism and combinations of the two. The results suggest the asteroid impact was catastrophic enough to have destroyed the dinosaurs on its own."<br/><br/>According to the models, Deccan volcanism would have reduced sunlight by just 5 percent at maximum.<br/><br/>In comparison, estimates for the asteroid impact's effect is that fallout would have diminished sunlight by 15 to 20 percent. This figure is enough to have guaranteed the complete eradication of the non-avian dinosaurs."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/asteroid-single-handedly-killed-off-the-dinosaurs-new-study-4015147</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/02/4015147/4015147_827485579BE34657A4C21F3BE8C85B04_200702_4015147_Asteroid_Single_Handedly_Killed_Off_the_Dinosaur_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 05:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4015326</guid>
      <title>Explainer: What Is Remdesivir and How Does It Treat COVID-19?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE <br/> SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, is an RNA virus. This means the coronavirus uses nucleosides as the building blocks of its genetic material, according to University of Maryland, Baltimore County biochemist Katherine Seley-Radtke.<br/><br/>Writing for media outlet The Conversation, Seley-Radtke says the virus relies on an enzyme called polymerase to replicate its RNA nucleoside by nucleoside, so that it can make more copies of itself.<br/><br/>Gilead's remdesivir is an antiviral and a nucleoside analogue, or a chemical compound that is structurally similar to naturally occurring nucleosides. During replication, remdesivir could trick the polymerase into mistaking the antiviral drug, which resembles adenosine, for the genuine article.<br/><br/>After this happens, the antiviral is taken into the new RNA strand and stops the polymerase from replicating more of the RNA, which should suppress the virus. Preliminary results from May suggest the drug improved patient survival rate and time recovery.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-what-is-remdesivir-and-how-does-it-treat-covid-19--4015326</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/02/4015326/4015326_D616A9A644314435855727F618753CE8_200702_4015326_Explainer__What_Is_Remdesivir_and_How_Does_It_Tr_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:43:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4015493</guid>
      <title>Researchers Map Underwater 'Lost Continent' of Zealandia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LOWER HUTT, NEW ZEALAND <br/> The hidden continent of Zealandia has fascinated scientists ever since the mid-1990s. Now, researchers from GNS Science in New Zealand have mapped the submerged land mass in great detail, showing how tectonic and seismic activity have shaped its evolution.<br/><br/>The islands of New Zealand and New Caledonia are the only visible remnants of Zealandia, which was declared a distinct geological continent in a 2017 paper published in the Geological Society of America's journal.<br/><br/>Zealandia is a fragment of the supercontinent Gondwana, which began to separate from the northern supercontinent Laurasia around 180 million years when the Atlantic Ocean formed between what are now North America and Africa.<br/><br/>Zealandia separated from Gondwana beginning in the Late Cretaceous period. It is argued that it is a continent because it possesses a distinct and well-defined area and is composed of continental crust, not oceanic crust.<br/><br/>However, as it began its journey eastward, most of it slid beneath the ocean. Today, 94 percent of Zealandia is submerged. Its highest point is Aoraki, or Mount Cook, in New Zealand, at 3,724 meters, or 12,218 feet.<br/><br/>GNS Science is a geoscience research and consultancy organization owned by the government of New Zealand.<br/><br/>In a statement, Nick Mortimer, a geologist and lead author of the maps, said:<br/><br/>"We've made these maps to provide an accurate, complete and up-to-date picture of the geology of the New Zealand and southwest Pacific area <br/> better than we have had before," he said. "Their value is that they provide a fresh context in which to explain and understand the setting of New Zealand's volcanoes, plate boundary and sedimentary basins."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-map-underwater-lost-continent-of-zealandia-4015493</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/03/4015493/4015493_D0AC6E8EBD3045C5B483722AEB24E2C2_200703_4015493_Researchers_Map_Underwater__Lost_Continent__of_Z_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 03:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4016451</guid>
      <title>CERN Discovers First-Ever Particle of Four 'Charm' Quarks</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> A team of scientists made the first-ever sighting of an exotic particle by using the Large Hadron Collider at Europe's CERN. According to the study in the Arxiv preprint server, the particle is made of two charm quarks and two charm antiquarks.<br/><br/>The Large Hadron Collider's superconductors accelerate protons to crash them together at near-light speeds. Writing in a news release, CERN says the team then filtered out ordinary background collisions and looked for "bumps," or excess collisions, which led to the particle.<br/><br/>Quarks are elementary particles that serve as the building blocks of all matter, but most naturally existing matter, such as protons and neutrons, is made of three quarks or fewer. A particle formed by four heavy quarks of the same type has never been seen before.<br/><br/>CERN cautions that it is not known if the exotic particle is a pair of charm quarks held together by a weak bond, or a system of four quarks held together by strong bonds known as a true tetraquark.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cern-discovers-first-ever-particle-of-four-charm-quarks-4016451</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/06/4016451/4016451_2DC231DB4B2F45CC860CC6E5553C7FBF_200706_4016451_CERN_Discovers_First_Ever_Particle_of_Four__Char_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 05:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4016562</guid>
      <title>Contradicting the WHO, Scientists Say COVID Is an Airborne Disease</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW YORK <br/> Some 239 scientists in 32 countries say the coronavirus is an airborne disease that can linger in tiny droplets to infect people indoors, according to a report dated July 4 in the New York Times.<br/><br/>The report states that a scientific journal will publish the researchers' open letter in the coming days.<br/><br/>According to the WHO's guidelines, COVID spreads mainly by contact and airborne transmission of the virus only happens during medical procedures that create aerosols.<br/><br/>Yet, dissenting experts believe the virus could transmit via much smaller droplets that could carry the virus to longer distances.<br/><br/>The letter's co-signer Lindsey Marr told the New York Times that the WHO's guidelines are based on experiments at hospital rooms where good airflow and lower virus volumes prevailed.<br/><br/>According to the Guardian, documented outbreaks at meatpacking plants suggest these studies underestimate the virus's ability to survive in typical indoor conditions.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports that the new study would mean institutions should use powerful air filters, virus-killing UV lights, and face masks to prevent indoor transmission.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/contradicting-the-who-scientists-say-covid-is-an-airborne-disease-4016562</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/06/4016562/4016562_044FED7306844C2B8151BE006C5FFD06_200706_4016562_Contradicting_the_WHO__Scientists_Say_COVID_Is_a_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 10:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4016765</guid>
      <title>3D-Printed Steak Mimics Texture and Appearance of Real Steak</title>
      <description><![CDATA[REHOVOT, ISRAEL <br/> An Israeli start-up claims to have invented the world's first realistic, 3D-printed steak made from non-meat products, according to information provided by the company to Reuters and the Media Line.<br/><br/>Redefine Meat's "Alt-Steak" is made out of a combination of soy and pea proteins, coconut fat and sunflower oil, along with natural colors and flavors.<br/><br/>The company, based in Rehovot, south of Tel Aviv, says it worked with butchers and other experts to digitally mapped more than 70 sensorial parameters <br/> including the cut's texture, juiciness, fat distribution, and mouthfeel.<br/><br/>Instead of printing a single minced meat, the company's 3D food printer uses separate formulations for the fat, muscle and blood to mimic the flavor, texture and appearance of a real steak.<br/><br/>"This is the world's first 3D-printed steak that can really pass the test of what is a steak," Redefine Meat CEO and co-founder Eshchar Ben-Shitrit told The Media Line.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/3d-printed-steak-mimics-texture-and-appearance-of-real-steak-4016765</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/07/07/4016765/4016765_446ABD91F71B4BAFA37C7C6949E7AB91_200707_4016765_3D_Printed_Steak_Mimics_Texture_and_Appearance_o_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 03:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
