<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 22:08:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>4004252</guid>
      <title>Stool Tests May Help Spot COVID-19 Transmission</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ZHUHAI, CHINA <br/> Health authorities might be able to detect COVID-19's spread by testing the sewers of a community for the coronavirus's RNA.<br/><br/>Citing a new study in Gastroenterology, British Columbia Centre of Disease Control told the CBC that wastewater testing could be an early warning system for community transmission.<br/><br/>According to a research team from China's Guangdong Province, traces of SARS-CoV-2's RNA have been found in the stool samples of hospitalized patients. <br/><br/>The study involved 73 patients of both genders whose ages ranged from 10 months to 78 years old. Stool samples of 39 patients, or 53 percent, tested positive for the coronavirus RNA."<br/><br/>Additionally, some patients started testing negative for the virus in respiratory samples, even as their stool samples continued to show positive results. Endoscopy indicated that the 17 patients, or 23 percent of the total, were still infected and that they may have been able to infect others via fecal-oral transmission.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/stool-tests-may-help-spot-covid-19-transmission-4004252</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/01/4004252/4004252_87932E8142D84DFAA6FB8AEC51DE82C3_200601_4004252_Stool_Tests_May_Help_Spot_COVID_19_Transmission_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 09:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004210</guid>
      <title>Mysterious Anomaly in Earth's Magnetic Field Is Spreading</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS <br/> A mysterious anomaly in the Earth's magnetic field that stretches from South America to Africa is spreading and scientists do not understand why.<br/><br/>New data from the European Space Agency's SWARM constellation of satellites show that a weak spot in the Earth's magnetic field known as the South Atlantic Anomaly has been growing in size since 1970 and may possibly be developing a second cell centered above the coast of southwest Africa.<br/><br/>The Earth's magnetic field, which is generated by the dynamo action of its molten metal core, protects the planet from the full impact of solar and cosmic radiation. According to the ESA, over the last two centuries, the global magnetic field has lost 9 percent of its strength on a global average.<br/><br/>For now, the most significant effect of the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly is interference with satellites and spacecraft that pass over the region. However, the Earth's magnetic field destabilizes and reconstitutes itself over geological time, with sometimes even the north and south magnetic poles trading places.<br/><br/>It is not clear what is causing the weakening of the South Atlantic Anomaly, but it could be related to the African Large Low Shear Velocity Province, one of two giant underground masses of rock that float like hidden continents where the Earth's mantle meets the outer core.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mysterious-anomaly-in-earth-s-magnetic-field-is-spreading-4004210</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/01/4004210/4004210_D565CBDD97894AE79B86A9268F401068_200601_4004210_Mysterious_Anomaly_in_Earth_s_Magnetic_Field_Is__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004450</guid>
      <title>E-cigarettes May Be Triggering Gum Inflammation in Users</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLUMBUS, OHIO <br/> A team of researchers has found unhealthy bacteria and inflammation in the gums of e-cigarette smokers that could lead to more severe gum diseases. <br/><br/>Research published in the journal Science Advances found that the gums of healthy individuals who used e-cigarettes contained damaging bacteria and showed signs of gum disease.<br/><br/>The team of specialists studied the gums of 123 individuals. 25 of them were smokers, another 25 were non-smokers, 20 used e-cigarettes, 25 were former smokers who used e-cigarettes and 28 were both cigarette and e-cigarette smokers.<br/><br/>Results showed that e-cigarette use causes a change in the microbial landscape of the gums, making its healthy bacteria unrecognizable to our immune system. This then triggers an inflammatory response in the gums and coats healthy bacteria with a layer of slime.<br/><br/>This phenomenon was observed even in those using non-nicotine e-cigarettes. This caused the team of researchers to believe that the liquid in electronic cigarettes could be triggering this phenomenon.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/e-cigarettes-may-be-triggering-gum-inflammation-in-users-4004450</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/02/4004450/4004450_9D777DBB4992442589C4EBCC21F02C1B_200602_4004450_E_cigarettes_May_Be_Triggering_Gum_Inflammation__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 03:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004605</guid>
      <title>ESA's Solar Orbiter to Pass Through Tails of Comet ATLAS</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS <br/> The European Space Agency's Solar Orbiter has been given the rare opportunity to conduct some "bonus science" in a serendipitous rendezvous with the tails of the comet ATLAS during the next few days, the space agency detailed in an article on its website.<br/><br/>The Solar Orbiter was launched on February 10, 2020 and is en route to the inner solar system to study the Sun and inner heliosphere. The encounter with ATLAS had not been planned. In May, Geraint Jones of the UK's Mullard Space Science Laboratory discovered that the spacecraft would pass through the comet's tails as early as May 31, according to an article on UCL's website.<br/><br/>The instruments used to study ATLAS were not scheduled to be fully functional until the probe's first solar observation on June 15. ESA scientists moved that timeline forward to begin collecting data when the probe passed through ATLAS's ion tail on May 31 and June 1. The Solar Orbiter will cross ATLAS's dust tail on June 6.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/esa-s-solar-orbiter-to-pass-through-tails-of-comet-atlas-4004605</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/02/4004605/4004605_20AE8D4D0F424015816F920B4D8653D3_200602_4004605_ESA_s_Solar_Orbiter_to_Pass_Through_Tails_of_Com_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 09:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4004883</guid>
      <title>The Closest Exoplanet to Our Earth Has Been Confirmed</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> A team of specialists from the University of Geneva has confirmed the existence of an exoplanet orbiting in the habitable zone of a neighboring sun. <br/><br/>Researchers have confirmed the presence of Proxima Centauri B, an exoplanet that orbits in the habitable zone of the star closest to our sun, Proxima Centauri, according to a report published in the journal Astronomy and Astrophysics.<br/><br/>Researchers from the University of Geneva were able to confirm its existence by using a new generation spectrograph located in Chile called ESPRESSO.<br/><br/>Their observations showed that Proxima B is 1.17 times the mass of Earth and orbits its sun in 11.2 days.<br/><br/>Proxima B receives similar energy from its sun and could, therefore, harbor life. However, this exoplanet's sun is an active red dwarf and it hits the exoplanet with roughly 400 times the amount of X-rays that Earth receives.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-closest-exoplanet-to-our-earth-has-been-confirmed-4004883</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4004883/4004883_DDD7A687098C4AB0BE6751BB38B7A059_200603_4004883_The_Closest_Exoplanet_to_Our_Earth_Has_Been_Conf_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 05:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005042</guid>
      <title>SARS-CoV-2 Could be a Hybrid of Bat and Pangolin Viruses: Study</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA <br/> SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, could be a hybrid that descended from different clades of bat and pangolin viruses, according to new research in Science Advances.<br/><br/>Writing in a news release, the team says the bat virus RaTG13 is the closest genetic relative to SARS-CoV-2, with a 96.3 percent RNA similarity. However, the bat virus does not have the spike protein parts used by SARS-CoV-2 for infecting humans.<br/><br/>Yet another close relative, a clade of SARS-like pangolin virus from China, has receptor-binding domains that closely match the corresponding parts of the novel coronavirus.<br/><br/>The bat and pangolin viruses likely recombined to form SARS-CoV-2. Recombining may occur when two similar viruses infect the same cell. When this happens, molecules that made up the distinct viruses are reshuffled into a new pathogen.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/sars-cov-2-could-be-a-hybrid-of-bat-and-pangolin-viruses-study-4005042</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4005042/4005042_813D34934D8840C3BD69712AF01D1F61_200603_4005042_SARS_CoV_2_Could_be_a_Hybrid_of_Bat_and_Pangolin_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005016</guid>
      <title>Scientists Found the World's Biggest Volcano</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANOA, HAWAII <br/> Researchers have found the Earth's largest and hottest volcano northwest of Honolulu in the central northern Pacific.<br/><br/>The shield volcano Puhahonu is mostly submerged, with only a third of its volume above the sea level as atolls named the Gardner Pinnacles. Puhahonu means "turtle surfacing for air" in Hawaiin. <br/><br/>Writing in Earth and Planetary Science Letters, scientists say the research vessel Falkor charted the ocean with sonar and gravity mapping technology.<br/><br/>According to the survey, Puhahonu is 90 km wide and 275 km long, or twice the size of Mauna Loa, formerly the world's largest known volcano.<br/><br/>Scientists say the shield volcano's size was probably the result of abundant magma flowing from a very hot spot in the mantle. The temperature of the magma that created the Puhahonu is suggested by the forsterite content that is the highest among Hawaii's volcanoes.<br/> <br/>According to the study, Puhahonu is so massive that the Earth's crust and mantle buckled under its weight, which sank the bulk of the volcano under the sea.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-found-the-world-s-biggest-volcano-4005016</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/03/4005016/4005016_65C4F5729A394BD186F950CF527EE0CA_200603_4005016_Scientists_Found_the_World_s_Biggest_Volcano_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 10:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005326</guid>
      <title>New Ebola Outbreak in the Democratic Republic of the Congo</title>
      <description><![CDATA[KINSHASA, DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF THE CONGO <br/> The Government of the Democratic Republic of the Congo has confirmed the deaths of five individuals who were infected with Ebola.<br/><br/>Citing authorities in the Democratic Republic of Congo, the United Nations Children's Fund reports that a new Ebola outbreak has occurred in the country's city of Mbandaka. This is the eleventh outbreak in the country since the virus's discovery in 1976.<br/><br/>Nine individuals are reported to have been infected. Five of them have died. The individuals died between the 18th and 30th of May but were confirmed to be Ebola-related yesterday.<br/><br/>The virus's incubation period lasts from 2 to 21 days. Symptoms of the Ebola virus include fever, headache, muscle pain and fatigue. These symptoms are followed up by vomiting and diarrhea.<br/><br/>Ebola is passed on by human-to-human transmission. Individuals can be infected if they come in contact with sweat, mucous, saliva, blood, or other body fluids of infected people.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-ebola-outbreak-in-the-democratic-republic-of-the-congo-4005326</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/04/4005326/4005326_1AFD8F53A17A44CC85178B11FBE03E95_200604_4005326_New_Ebola_Outbreak_in_the_Democratic_Republic_of_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 06:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005728</guid>
      <title>A Rare Dino Related to T-Rexes Has Been Discovered in Australia</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VICTORIA, AUSTRALIA <br/> Five years after the discovery of a pterosaur fossil, a PhD student in Australia noticed that it had been mislabeled and that it actually belonged to a rare dinosaur called Elaphrosaurus. <br/><br/>Paleontologists at Australia's Swinburne University of Technology discovered they had mistakenly identified a fossil as the bone of an ancient flying reptile called pterosaur, but it actually belonged to a rare dinosaur called elaphrosaur. This is the first elaphrosaur found in Australia.<br/><br/>Citing Stephen Poropat, the lead author of the study, The Guardian reports that only three other elaphrosaurs species have been found in Tanzania, China and Argentina.<br/><br/>The elaphrosaur was part of the theropod family, which includes predators like the Tyrannosaurus Rex and velociraptors. It was roughly as tall as a small Emu and measures 2 meters from its head to the end of its tail."<br/><br/>According to the research published in the journal Gondwana Research, the elaphrosaur the team discovered lived during the cretaceous period. At this time, Australia's land was located in the Arctic Circle.<br/><br/>Researchers believe that the elaphrosaurs may have lived in a habitat containing a diverse variety of plants and trees such as conifers, gingkos, ferns, horsetails, conifers, and flowering plants.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/a-rare-dino-related-to-t-rexes-has-been-discovered-in-australia-4005728</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/05/4005728/4005728_3FC383ED67484297934B58E108C0C351_200605_4005728_A_Rare_Dino_Related_to_T_Rexes_Has_Been_Discover_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 05:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4005778</guid>
      <title>Scientists Designs Squid-Like Transparent Human Cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IRVINE, CALIFORNIA <br/> Scientists have engineered color-shifting abilities into human cells. Researchers say their project is inspired by female opalescent inshore squids that evade predators by changing their colors from translucent to opaque white.<br/><br/>According to the study in Nature Communications, squids and octopuses can cloak because their skin contains leucophore cells, which includes protein molecules called reflectins. This substance scatters light and creates an iridescent camouflage.<br/><br/>In a news release, the scientists say they took human embryonic kidney cells and introduced genes that express reflectin. These cells are then cultured and examined under a microscope.<br/><br/>The study's co-author was cited as saying the cells grew ball-shaped nanostructures throughout the cell bodies, and the spheres contain reflectin molecules. This means the reflectins behaved optically as if they were in squids.<br/> <br/>Thumbnail credit: PEXELS / MARTIN]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-designs-squid-like-transparent-human-cells-4005778</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/05/4005778/4005778_72D753EE1E4C46BC8970E736D7E294A3_200605_4005778_Scientists_Designs_Squid_Like_Transparent_Human__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 07:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006628</guid>
      <title>How Maize Turned Into a Staple Ancient Mesoamerican Crop</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ALBUQUERQUE, NEW MEXICO <br/> Archeologists may have found out when cave-dwelling prehistoric Mesoamericans began eating maize as a staple, according to a new study in Science Advances.<br/><br/>Researchers examined the carbon isotope content of 52 skeletons from various rock shelters in Belize. The bones belonged to a representative sample of men, women and children, and evidence showed they were consuming more and more maize.<br/><br/>Writing in a news release, researchers say pre-maize hunter-gatherers from around 9,000 years ago ate wild animals and plants. Then, about 4,700 years ago, the population began to consume maize, which made up 30 percent of their diet.<br/><br/>In the following millenia, Mesoamericans adopted sedentary farming and maize consumption increased to 70 percent of the food they ate.<br/><br/>The authors speculated that human selection and spontaneous genetic changes to the plants then led to maize crops to grow bigger cobs, bigger seeds and more seed rows.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-maize-turned-into-a-staple-ancient-mesoamerican-crop-4006628</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006628/4006628_8F0A0BE39E114A8189822350A8D8734A_200608_4006628_How_Maize_Turned_Into_a_Staple_Ancient_Mesoameri_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 06:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006776</guid>
      <title>Explainer: What Young Great White Sharks Eat</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SYDNEY <br/> Scientists from Australia say the most detailed study to date showed that great white sharks hunted more seabed-dwelling prey than they expected. This paper is published in Frontiers in Marine Science.<br/><br/>Researchers from the University of Sydney studied the stomach content of 50 juvenile great white sharks caught by the New South Wales Shark Mesh Program, according to a news release from the university.<br/><br/>Scientists found mid-water fish like salmon made up 32 percent of the sharks' diet, bottom-dwelling fish such as stargazers made 17 percent, reef fish like Eastern Blue gropers 5 percent, and batoid fish like rays made 15 percent. <br/><br/>Sharks also eat cephalopods, and they usually begin feeding on marine mammals and other sharks after growing larger in size.<br/><br/>The study tracked the seasonal migration of Australia's great white sharks and found that they ranged from the coastal seas of southern New Queensland to northern Tasmania. Sharks range further as they mature.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-what-young-great-white-sharks-eat-4006776</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/08/4006776/4006776_DF9A18A50A024CA79ED177674A7DBCD7_200608_4006776_Explainer__What_Young_Great_White_Sharks_Eat_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 12:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4006956</guid>
      <title>Human mini-liver transplanted into rats are fully-functional</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PITTSBURGH <br/> Researchers created a functioning mini-human liver and successfully transplanted it into rats. <br/><br/>According to a report published in Cell Reports, experts from the University of Pittsburgh successfully developed and transplanted functioning human mini-livers into rats.<br/><br/>Scientists created the mini livers by using human skin cells and then reverting them into a stem cell state. These cells are called induced pluripotent stem cells and other types of cells can derive from them.<br/><br/>They then used chemicals and hormones to induce differentiation. This pushed the induced pluripotent stem cells into becoming liver cells. The newly created liver cells were then seeded on mini-liver bioreactors.<br/><br/>The lab-grown livers were then transplanted into five immunosuppressed mice or mice whose immune system would be less likely to reject the organ. Four days after the transplant, the mice were dissected in order to examine how well the  implanted organ functioned.<br/><br/>After dissecting the rats, researchers found all five rats had blood circulation issues around the graft of the mini-liver. However, the rats had human liver proteins in their blood serum indicating that the livers were working properly.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/human-mini-liver-transplanted-into-rats-are-fully-functional-4006956</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/09/4006956/4006956_78DAF2AE83CD48C58863FFBA0E2CB538_200609_4006956_Human_mini_liver_transplanted_into_rats_are_full_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 04:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007264</guid>
      <title>Ex-astronaut Kathy Sullivan dives to deepest known point on Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ISLE OF MAN, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Undersea explorer Victor Vescovo and Kathy Sullivan, the first American woman to walk in space, dived into the Challenger Deep last Sunday, according to a report in the New York Times.<br/><br/>The Challenger Deep is the deepest known spot on Earth. It is roughly 10,902 to 10,929 meters deep.<br/><br/>Sullivan and Vescovo captured images of the deep sea while aboard the Limiting Factor, a deep-sea research submersible that can withstand 2,200 tonnes of pressure. It is designed to travel into the deep oceanic trenches of the ocean called the hadal zone.<br/><br/>Once the pair ascended back into their ship, they called a group of astronauts in the International Space Station, which at the time was located around 409 kilometers above Earth.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ex-astronaut-kathy-sullivan-dives-to-deepest-known-point-on-earth-4007264</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007264/4007264_CC8C659AACCD4C49A3A798D46F92E12B_200610_4007264_Ex_astronaut_Kathy_Sullivan_dives_to_deepest_kno_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 03:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007417</guid>
      <title>Virus Outbreak in China May Have Started Far Earlier Than Reported</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS <br/> Satellite imagery of vehicle traffic around hospitals in Wuhan suggests the coronavirus may have struck the city months before the outbreak was acknowledged, according to Harvard University researchers.<br/><br/>The manuscript of the study has yet to be peer reviewed.<br/><br/>According to the paper, the team reviewed satellite traffic images at the parking lots of six hospitals in the autumn of 2019. The researchers found a surge in the number of parked cars after comparing the data to the same period in the previous year.<br/><br/>At the Wuhan Tianyou Hospital, which is one of the city's largest, the team counted 285 cars and trucks. This traffic volume is viewed as a proxy for respiratory patient intake and the count marked a 67 percent increase over 2018.<br/><br/>Additionally, the team analyzed internet search terms in China and found a significant uptick in searches for the words "cough" and "diarrhoea."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/virus-outbreak-in-china-may-have-started-far-earlier-than-reported-4007417</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/10/4007417/4007417_DEE97567655249B391FD68266B333525_200610_4007417_Virus_Outbreak_in_China_May_Have_Started_Far_Ear_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 09:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4007811</guid>
      <title>Amazon Halts Police Use of Its Facial Recognition Technology</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE <br/> Amazon announced that it will ban police use of the company's facial recognition tool Rekognition for a year, in a blogpost dated Wednesday.<br/><br/>Earlier this year, an Amazon executive told PBS that not even Amazon knows the exact number of police departments that utilize Rekognition.<br/><br/>According to a 2018 study by MIT Media Lab, facial recognition tools were more prone to errors when identifying people of color, and products from major tech corporations misgendered dark-skinned women 35 percent of the time.<br/><br/>A 2019 study by the same institution further states that Amazon's Rekognition mislabelled women of color as men 31 percent of the time, while Microsoft's technology made the error only 1.5 percent of the time.<br/><br/>Citing a statement from Clearview AI, The Verge reports that Amazon, Google and IBM have exited the law enforcement facial recognition market, which left the field to Clearview. In the statement, Clearview asserts that its product "actually works."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/amazon-halts-police-use-of-its-facial-recognition-technology-4007811</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/11/4007811/4007811_5EBCFD0707434C62B5449E5E5BF864CE_200611_4007811_Amazon_Halts_Police_Use_of_Its_Facial_Recognitio_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 10:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008049</guid>
      <title>New Ancient Roman City Found Without Excavating</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Researchers from the University of Cambridge and Ghent University in Belgium have discovered the remains of Falerii Novi, an ancient Roman city just 50 kilometers away from Rome that has been buried for roughly 13 centuries. Their research was published in the journal Antiquity.<br/><br/>The team of archaeologists discovered Falerii Novi by attaching a ground-penetrating radar or GPR to an all-terrain vehicle and then using it to map the buried city. A GPR sends radio pulses into the ground and then analyzes the waves that bounce off objects underground.<br/><br/>The resulting 3D images put together by the team showed that Falerii Novi had a theatre, a market, a bath complex and temples as well as shops, monuments and atrium houses.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-ancient-roman-city-found-without-excavating-4008049</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008049/4008049_562BE7703EC34F478A1955E90C58FD3B_200612_4008049_New_Ancient_Roman_City_Found_Without_Excavating_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 05:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008318</guid>
      <title>Anti-Protest Weapons, Explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MINNEAPOLIS <br/>   American police officers have been using a variety of crowd-control weapons against black lives matter demonstrators. These weapons can cause serious injuries and, in some instances, even death.<br/><br/>Chemical irritants used as crowd control weapons such as pepper spray and tear gas contain a chemical commonly known as CS gas which can cause a burning sensation and inflammation in the eyes, mouth, throat and lungs, Reuters reports.<br/><br/>Flashbangs, also known as stun grenades, are considered disorientation devices. The sound and bright light flashbangs emit when they explode stun those standing around their explosion. However, Reuters reports that they can severely burn bystanders if fired at close range.<br/><br/>The flash and sound emitted by flashbangs can cause temporary loss of hearing and sight as well as loss of balance.<br/><br/>Sting-ball grenades contain pellets that deploy once the grenade explodes. Some also contain chemical compounds and others also emit bright lights and sounds upon explosion.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/anti-protest-weapons-explained-4008318</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008318/4008318_C8FCDA9241D241FA8F5FDB89998C3447_200612_4008318_Anti_Protest_Weapons__Explained_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 14:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4008305</guid>
      <title>Explainer: What is Teargas?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Tear gas is a chemical weapon used for crowd control that causes irritation to the eyes, mouth, throat, lungs and skin, thus incapacitating individuals.<br/><br/>The most common chemicals found in a tear gas canister are 2-chlorobenzalmalononitrile, commonly known as CS gas, and chloroacetophenone, a component that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention describes as having a "sharp irritating odor."<br/><br/>Individuals exposed to tear gas may experience wheezing, shortness of breath and vomiting along with a burning sensation in their eyes, nose and skin.<br/><br/>If exposed to the anti-riot agent for a prolonged time, individuals can develop serious eye illnesses such as scarring, cataracts and glaucoma. It may also lead to respiratory issues such as asthma.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-what-is-teargas--4008305</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/12/4008305/4008305_B800B2F2301241F1B7DFA8E1F33595E0_200612_4008305_Explainer__What_is_Teargas__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 13:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009307</guid>
      <title>Scientists Have Found Anomalous Structures Around Earth's Core</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLLEGE PARK, MARYLAND <br/> Geophysicists from the University of Maryland analyzed seismic waves around the world and found large unusual structures near the Earth's core. The study was published on June 12 in the journal Science.<br/><br/>The team of researchers analyzed 7,000 seismograms from earthquakes of 6.5 magnitude or greater that occurred from 1990 to 2018 using Sequencer, a machine learning algorithm.<br/><br/>They specifically searched for echoes of seismic waves known as shear waves, or S waves, beneath the Pacific Ocean Basin.<br/><br/>Their results uncovered an anomalous structure under the volcanic Marquesas Islands in the South Pacific. The results also showed that a previously known structure beneath the Hawaiian Islands is much larger than had been thought.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-have-found-anomalous-structures-around-earth-s-core-4009307</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/16/4009307/4009307_0C167240861641E4AD0CAAD1AC9CFF13_200616_4009307_Scientists_Have_Found_Anomalous_Structures_Aroun_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 02:50:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009499</guid>
      <title>Ancient Crocodiles May Have Walked on Two Feet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[JINJU, SOUTH KOREA <br/> Experts have found evidence which indicates that ancient crocodiles could have been bipedal.<br/><br/>Experts from South Korea's Chinju National University of Education discovered many fossilized animal tracks in 2019 that they now believe could belong to an ancient crocodile that walked on two feet. Their research was published in the journal Scientific Reports.<br/><br/>The team found the fossilized footprints at a site located west of Sacheon City in South Korea's South Gyeongsang Province. The team has named the animal Batrachopus grandis.<br/><br/>The footprints measure up to 24 centimeters in length and the heel print, digits and impressions of the pads look very similar to those of crocodile track marks, the BBC reports, citing Professor Martin Lockley from the University of Colorado at Denver, a co-author of the study.<br/><br/>The Batrachopus grandis legs were about the same height as a human adults' legs. The fact that there are no tracks of the ancient crocodiles' tails dragging behind them and the closeness of the footprints suggests this animal could have been bipedal.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ancient-crocodiles-may-have-walked-on-two-feet-4009499</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/16/4009499/4009499_01FC3867EA1043BA8AD04B4A006D7517_200616_4009499_Ancient_Crocodiles_May_Have_Walked_on_Two_Feet_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2020 09:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009855</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus Could Infect the Brain: Scientists</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BALTIMORE <br/> A new study from Johns Hopkins University suggests the coronavirus may infect the brain and replicate in brain cells.<br/><br/>The Financial Times reports the journal Altex is in the process of reviewing this paper.<br/><br/>Scientists used tiny balls of cultured brain tissue called mini-brains to simulate the virus's effect on human brain tissue.<br/><br/>The mini-brains called Brainsphere are utilized for pharmaceutical testing and virus research.<br/><br/>Microscopy of the mini-brains shows SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, can infect neurons and multiply tenfold in three days.<br/><br/>Since mini-brains do not have the blood-brain barrier found in real brains, it is not known if the virus is able to penetrate into the brain on its own.<br/><br/>However, severe inflammation <br/> which is observed in COVID patients <br/> can break down the barrier.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-could-infect-the-brain-scientists-4009855</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/17/4009855/4009855_97412E9908D84A729835F9033B9D5AF9_200617_4009855_Coronavirus_Could_Infect_the_Brain__Scientists_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 08:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4009780</guid>
      <title>Highly Magnetized Star Detected as Source of Fast Radio Bursts</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA <br/> The first fast radio burst to be discovered in the Milky Way has been traced back to a magnetar known as SGR 1935+2154 located 32,616 light-years away from Earth, astronomers researching the phenomena told Nature magazine.<br/><br/>The burst was detected by satellites including NASA's Neil Gehrels Swift Observatory, and radio telescopes operated by the Canadian Hydrogen Intensity Mapping Experiment, or CHIME, and by the Survey for Transient Astronomical Radio Emission 2, or STARE2, in the U.S.<br/><br/>Fast radio bursts are brief but cataclysmic high-energy blasts that flare for just milliseconds but release as much energy as our Sun generates in 80 years, according to previous findings published in Nature.<br/><br/>A magnetar is described in the Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics as a kind of highly magnetized neutron star, the compressed core of a star that exploded in a supernova and collapsed in on itself.<br/><br/>Citing University of Toronto astronomer and CHIME member Paul Scholz, Nature magazine explains that because they spin so quickly, magnetars build up huge reservoirs of energy that could produce powerful cosmic blasts.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/highly-magnetized-star-detected-as-source-of-fast-radio-bursts-4009780</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/17/4009780/4009780_B8DEE2DA60A147C3B5D6264E14CAE9BB_200617_4009780_Highly_Magnetized_Star_Detected_as_Source_of_Fas_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 05:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4010418</guid>
      <title>Over 600 New Covid-19 Cases Detected in Germany</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BERLIN <br/> More than 600 people at a slaughterhouse located in Rheda-Wiedenbruck, Germany, have tested positive for coronavirus, according to Deutsche Welle. The slaughterhouse is run by the Tonnies Group, the leading meat processing company in Germany.<br/><br/>Local authorities have called for the plant to shut down and for the suspension of school and preschool activities in the area until June 29. Roughly 7,000 people in the region have been asked to quarantine to prevent the spread of the virus.<br/><br/>The conditions inside slaughterhouse worker dormitories may have exacerbated the spread of the virus. The Guardian quotes a migrant worker as saying that up to five people would live in the same room and that a dorm they lived in had mice and cockroaches.<br/><br/>A large percentage of employees at meat processing facilities in Germany are not German. In fact, Deutsche Welle reports that according to trade unions, up to 80 percent of those employed in these factories are migrant workers.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/over-600-new-covid-19-cases-detected-in-germany-4010418</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/18/4010418/4010418_1A7E51224EC0482A871743C2E6E01026_200618_4010418_Over_600_New_Covid_19_Cases_Detected_in_Germany_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2020 11:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011066</guid>
      <title>Fossilised Egg Could be Linked to Ancient Marine Reptile</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEYMOUR ISLAND, ANTARCTICA <br/> Nine years ago, scientists discovered a 68-million-year-old fossilised egg on Seymour Island in Antarctica. New research published in the journal Nature suggests the egg may have belonged to an ancient marine reptile called a mosasaur.<br/><br/>The fossilised egg has a soft shell and measures 29 centimeters in length and 20 centimeters in width. It is the second-largest egg recorded to date. That is roughly five times the size of a medium-sized chicken egg.<br/><br/>Mosasaurs were marine reptiles that lived during the dinosaur era. Evidence suggests that mosasaurus gave birth to live young. However, the egg could have hatched right after being laid. This mode of reproduction is called ovoviviparity.<br/><br/>Mosasaurs belong to an order of reptiles called squamates or scaled reptiles whose ancestors split from the ancestors of dinosaurs, birds and crocodiles roughly 240 million years ago. Lizards and snakes also belong to this group.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/fossilised-egg-could-be-linked-to-ancient-marine-reptile-4011066</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/20/4011066/4011066_5C06B8A008CF47E3BE72650E0D5BDD0B_200620_4011066_Fossilised_Egg_Could_be_Linked_to_Ancient_Marine_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 03:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011229</guid>
      <title>Tourists could be sent to space using a giant balloon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, FLORIDA <br/> A new company called Space Perspective wants to send tourists and research payloads up into the stratosphere in a pressurized capsule elevated by a large balloon, according to Space.com.<br/><br/>The capsule is called the Spaceship Neptune and it can hold up to 9 people, including the pilot. The capsule has large windows from which passengers will be able to observe Earth's curvature. It will also contain a bathroom and a bar.<br/><br/>It will take the Spaceship Neptune roughly two hours to reach its maximum altitude of 30,000 meters or about 100,000 feet after taking off from the old Shuttle Landing Facility at NASA's Kennedy Space Center on Florida's Space Coast. The capsule will be suspended by a large hydrogen-filled balloon.<br/><br/>Passengers will spend two hours suspended in the stratosphere. Their descent back into Earth will take another two hours. The passengers would then be picked up by a recovery boat waiting for them at sea.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/tourists-could-be-sent-to-space-using-a-giant-balloon-4011229</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/20/4011229/4011229_58ED76DB9D3845ADB544CB4A3C4A9259_200620_4011229_Tourists_could_be_sent_to_space_using_a_giant_ba_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 14:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011775</guid>
      <title>Why you should shut the toilet lid to prevent the spread of COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[YANGZHOU, CHINA <br/> Researchers from China's Yangzhou University have used computer simulations to show that water flushed in an uncovered toilet can eject infected aerosol droplets up to three feet, or one meter, in the air, according to a study published on June 16 in the journal Physics of Fluids. <br/><br/>Up to 60 percent of the particles reach above the toilet seat and these droplets can remain airborne for up to a minute, the researchers found.<br/><br/>The virus could then infect others who inhale the aerosols or come into contact with infected surfaces, such as by touching door handles or toilet seats where the droplets have landed.<br/><br/>In the journal the researchers noted that more attention needs to be paid to toilets as potential sources of infection and even toilet design, writing, "According to the characteristics of fecal-oral transmission, there will be a large amount of viruses within a toilet when a confirmed case uses it. Thus, toilets should be regarded as one of the infection sources."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/why-you-should-shut-the-toilet-lid-to-prevent-the-spread-of-covid-19-4011775</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/22/4011775/4011775_B8B0A883C6B647F6A7E5A970D5E2632B_200622_4011775_Why_you_should_shut_the_toilet_lid_to_prevent_th_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 09:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4011734</guid>
      <title>CERN Approves Plan for 
Gigantic New Particle Collider</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> The CERN Council in Geneva, Switzerland on June 19 approved the construction of a new 100-kilometer circular supercollider called the Future Circular Collider.<br/><br/>This new collider is 73 kilometers larger than the Large Hadron Collider. The construction is expected to begin in 2038 and cost at least &#8364;21 billion.<br/><br/>According to Nature, the new collider will be developed in two stages. In the first stage, CERN will create an electron-positron collider with the goal of creating and studying Higgs boson particles.<br/><br/>In the second stage, the collider will be turned into a proton-proton smasher with capabilities of reaching collision energies of 100 teraelectronvolts. Currently, the Large Hadron Collider can reach 16 teraelectronvolts. This collider would be used to look for and study new particles.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/cern-approves-plan-for-%0Agigantic-new-particle-collider-4011734</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/22/4011734/4011734_30229520614C46909EAD1C38D8364EAA_200622_4011734_CERN_Approves_Plan_for__Gigantic_New_Particle_Co_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 08:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012046</guid>
      <title>Astronomers Discover Youngest Known Kagnetar</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN BASILIO, ITALY <br/> Astronomers at NASA and the ESA have discovered a neutron star that is the youngest known magnetar ever recorded.<br/><br/>Swift J1818.0&#8722;1607 was born in a supernova that would have been visible from Earth 240 years ago.<br/><br/>A magnetar is a kind of highly magnetized neutron star, the most powerful magnetic objects in the universe. Only 30 magnetars in the Milky Way have been found.<br/><br/>The star is located 16,000 light-years away from Earth in the constellation Sagittarius and  is 16,240 years old.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/astronomers-discover-youngest-known-kagnetar-4012046</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/23/4012046/4012046_5FBADA43477C4F57A910EECC6AF10653_200623_4012046_Astronomers_Discover_Youngest_Known_Kagnetar_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 04:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4012443</guid>
      <title>New Study Suggests Pluto Started Out With a Liquid Ocean</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA CRUZ, CALIFORNIA <br/> New research published in the journal Nature Geoscience suggests Pluto started out with a liquid ocean that has been slowly freezing over time.<br/><br/>The findings are based on an analysis of pictures of Pluto's surface taken by NASA's New Horizons mission. These show extensive ridges and troughs consistent with the planet expanding as its ocean froze.<br/><br/>Pluto is thought to possess a liquid ocean beneath a thin icy surface and a mantle of watery ice, according to the paper, which was published on June 22.<br/><br/>The study suggests the heat energy that allowed for a liquid ocean came from rocks colliding with and raining down on Pluto as the planet formed. Heat may also have been generated by radioactive elements in the rocks.<br/><br/>The new research suggests Pluto may be more capable of supporting alien life than we had previously thought.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-study-suggests-pluto-started-out-with-a-liquid-ocean-4012443</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/24/4012443/4012443_E2938AA40A8D402B927B977D53E8B19D_200624_4012443_New_Study_Suggests_Pluto_Started_Out_With_a_Liqu_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2020 07:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4014021</guid>
      <title>Did a Volcano in Alaska Bring Down the Roman Republic?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RENO, NEVADA <br/> According to new research, a powerful volcanic eruption in modern-day Alaska around 44 B.C. may have contributed to the Roman Republic's downfall on the other side of the globe.<br/><br/>This study was published in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.<br/><br/>The eruption left a 10 km wide crater in Mount Okmok that survives to this day, the research team led by Joe McConnell of Desert Research Institute said in a news release.<br/><br/>The event likely caused destabilizing environmental changes that paved the way for the imperial system after Julius Caesar was killed.<br/><br/>According to the team, the estimated time of the volcano's eruption, which would have led to climate-altering levels of fallout, coincided with a period of extreme cold, crop failures and famines in the written records.<br/><br/>Scientists used various materials to date the eruption including tree ring-based climate records from Scandinavia and volcanic remains called tephra from the Arctic ice.<br/><br/>The climate records and tephra both supported the hypothesis of an eruption in Alaska.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/did-a-volcano-in-alaska-bring-down-the-roman-republic--4014021</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/29/4014021/4014021_368EDE00E7184C21ADA5E6802B424905_200629_4014021_Did_a_Volcano_in_Alaska_Bring_Down_the_Roman_Rep_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 08:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4014274</guid>
      <title>Penumbral Lunar Eclipse Will Happen on July Fourth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A penumbral eclipse will occur over the Americas between July 4 and July 5, according to NASA. <br/><br/>Penumbral eclipses occur when the Moon moves across the Earth's lesser shadow, or the penumbra.<br/><br/>EarthSky.com reports a full moon visible in the evening of July 4, Eastern Daylight Time. The next night, a barely perceptible eclipse will take place at 11:44 p.m., with Saturn and Jupiter also visible in the evening sky.<br/><br/>Most people in the Americas will be able to observe the eclipse, but only a small part of Northwest Africa will be able to see the event, because morning twilight will obscure the Moon.<br/><br/>According to NASA, a full lunar eclipse occurs when the Moon enters Earth's greater shadow, or the Umbra. Sometimes, the Earth's atmosphere filters out blue light and bounces red light on the Moon. This results in the Blood Moon, the next of which will occur in 2021.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/penumbral-lunar-eclipse-will-happen-on-july-fourth-4014274</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/30/4014274/4014274_8A995C6A8D57455FABCF3055B91448BF_200630_4014274_Penumbral_Lunar_Eclipse_Will_Happen_on_July_Four_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 02:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4014336</guid>
      <title>Mystery Astronomical Object May Be a 'Black Neutron Star'</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA <br/> Astronomers have long wondered what lies within the so-called mass gap between black holes and neutron stars. The largest known neutron star is 2.5 times the size of our Sun, while the smallest known balck hole is five solar masses. <br/><br/>In a new study from the National Science Foundation's Laser Interferometer Gravitational-Wave Observatory, or LIGO, and the Virgo detector in Europe, scientists have announced the discovery of an object of 2.6 solar masses.<br/><br/>This object, which some are calling a "black neutron star," existed about 800 million light-years away from Earth in a binary pairing with a large black hole of 23 solar masses.<br/><br/>These two interstellar bodies collided in an event called GW190814, creating a huge splash of gravitational waves.<br/><br/>LIGO and Virgo detected the black neutron star in August of 2019, as it merged with the black hole, leaving a newly formed black hole about 25 times the size of our Sun.<br/><br/>A paper about the detection has been accepted for publication in The Astrophysical Journal Letters.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mystery-astronomical-object-may-be-a-black-neutron-star--4014336</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/30/4014336/4014336_0141676ADFAC42DBBAB65400BE73E118_200630_4014336_Mystery_Astronomical_Object_May_Be_a__Black_Neut_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 05:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>4014517</guid>
      <title>This New Virus Could Spark the Next Global Pandemic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> Scientists from China have found a virus with "pandemic potential" that is related to the swine flu, according to a study in Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences. The new virus is dubbed EA H1N1 G4.<br/><br/>Science Magazine reports the G4 variant virus has genes from three types of H1N1: the Eurasian Avian flu; the strain that caused the 2009 pandemic; and a North American strain that has genes from pig viruses.<br/><br/>Swab tests on 31,000 pigs found H1N1 spreading among farmed pigs in at least 10 provinces in China, and most of the 178 confirmed cases are of the new virus.<br/><br/>According to a previous study, two people in China were infected by the new swine flu, although the virus did not transmit to others. The study notes that the virus appears to attack the human respiratory system.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/this-new-virus-could-spark-the-next-global-pandemic-4014517</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/06/30/4014517/4014517_5AA1048BBB984BE88ABB1AC8345A21BE_200630_4014517_This_New_Virus_Could_Spark_the_Next_Global_Pande_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2020 10:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
