<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 18:08:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3970177</guid>
      <title>New research center begins construction in Antarctica</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ANTARCTICA <br/> A British architectural firm has designed a research center called the Discovery Building for the British Arctic Survey research team in Antarctica.  <br/><br/>Construction began on January 30, 2020.<br/><br/>The building's exterior will be made with metal panels that are pale blue in color to prevent high ultraviolet rays from causing degradation to the structure, according to a press release from the architectural firm. The color is also a reference to the Antarctic sky.<br/><br/>The Discovery Building will also have a wind deflector along its roofline that will be used to deflect cold air in the Antarctic so that the wind will travel down the structure's facade. This will help to minimize snow accumulation around the building.<br/><br/>The structure also consists of a control tower from its roof. The tower will provide a 360&#176; view of the area.<br/><br/>The Discovery Building will also contain a medical facility, offices and recreational spaces among other facilities.<br/><br/>The structure is expected to be completed in 2023.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-research-center-begins-construction-in-antarctica-3970177</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/02/3970177/3970177_D1472DDE99604FD39ADF935B41718EC9_200302_3970177_New_research_center_begins_construction_in_Antar_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 03:24:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970171</guid>
      <title>Doomsday Vault: Norwegian seed facility gets biggest ever deposit</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SVALBARD, NORWAY<br/> The Svalbard[f] Global Seed Vault is a repository that houses a collection of seeds from around the world in order to safeguard plant genealogy amid the growing threat of climate change.<br/><br/>According to a press release from Crop Trust, the vault received a new deposit of seeds consisting of several hundred plant species on February 25 from different institutions around the world. This is said to be the largest deposit it has ever received.<br/><br/>These contents include common staple crops, vegetables, herbs and even wild plant relatives.<br/><br/>Global Seed Vault's website explains that it has previously received large varieties of rice, wheat and barley crops among others.<br/><br/>The vault is located on the tectonically inactive Norwegian island of Spitsbergen.<br/><br/>It has been constructed 130 meters above sea level in order to keep the seeds dry and to allow easy maintenance in the event of a power failure.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/doomsday-vault-norwegian-seed-facility-gets-biggest-ever-deposit-3970171</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/02/3970171/3970171_C985756F823F472F8ED0FB355D164E84_200302_3970171_Doomsday_Vault__Norwegian_seed_facility_gets_big_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 03:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970161</guid>
      <title>China's Chang'e 4 reveals what's underneath the moon's far side</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MOON <br/> China's Chang'e 4 lunar mission has provided a glimpse into what lies beneath the far side of the moon.<br/><br/>On January 3, 2019, the Chang'e 4 lunar probe landed on the floor of the Von Karman crater, on the moon's south pole. CNN reports that several hours after touchdown, the Chang'e 4 deployed the Yutu-2 to roam and explore the surface.<br/><br/>According to a paper published in Science Advances, the rover used its Lunar Penetrating Radar to send radio signals to the lunar subsurface, up to a depth of 40 meters.<br/><br/>Paper author Li Chunlai says this is three times the depth that the Chang'e 3, China's previous mission, was able to measure.<br/><br/>After combining the radar image with tomographic data and quantitative analysis, researchers found that the subsurface was made primarily of highly porous, granular material, embedded with boulders of different sizes.<br/><br/>According to CNN, this is likely due to the moon being frequently hit by meteors and other space debris during the early days of the solar system.<br/><br/>When an object strikes the moon, the impact ejects a wave of material. The cratered surface becomes the top layer over time, with layers of boulder and fine debris buried beneath.<br/><br/>Researchers say the findings could shed more light on the geological evolution of the moon's dark side. And as Yutu-2 continues to explore the area, the team is also looking into the possibility of returning samples to Earth.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/china-s-chang-e-4-reveals-what-s-underneath-the-moon-s-far-side-3970161</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/02/3970161/3970161_674B7C686F4C492A9D7DACC3EFD49AC6_200302_3970161_China_s_Chang_e_4_reveals_what_s_underneath_the__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 03:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970306</guid>
      <title>Astronomers sights probable 'minimoon' orbiting Earth</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TUCSON, ARIZONA <br/> The Earth's busy orbit is occupied by space junk, nearly 5,000 artificial satellites, the Moon and now a possible temporary resident 'minimoon' called 2020 CD3. Live Science reports that the University of Arizona's Steward Observatory first spotted the captive space rock.<br/><br/>Citing a NASA astronomer working with the university, the outlet reports that the space rock is 1.9 meters to 3.5 meters in diameter. Light reflection from the possible minimoon is consistent with carbon-rich asteroids. Other observatories have yet to confirm the sighting.<br/><br/>It is not uncommon for Earth to capture temporary natural satellites, but most are too small to be detected. This minimoon has been orbiting our planet for close to three years and it is expected to leave in April to continue its journey around the Sun.<br/><br/>Citing a study published in Arxiv.org, the outlet reports there is a possibility that the minimoon would be recaptured by the moon's gravity well and become a natural lunar satellite, which is a theoretical class of objects astronomers think might exist.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/astronomers-sights-probable-minimoon-orbiting-earth-3970306</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/02/3970306/3970306_9C0C7ECED2F247B0ADECACA9AB271520_200302_3970306_Astronomers_sights_probable__minimoon__orbiting__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3970598</guid>
      <title>Superyacht designed using same technique as satellites in space</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NOORDWIJK, NETHERLANDS <br/> Dutch shipyard Royal Huisman has designed the superyacht Sea Eagle II using the same engineering techniques typically reserved for space missions for the European Space Agency.<br/><br/>The ship will be built in separate stages instead of the traditional approach in which ships are built from start to finish.<br/><br/>The ship will be 81 meters long and will have three masted schooners, according to a news release from the ESA. <br/><br/>Sea Eagle II will sport aluminum panels on its exterior. The panels will have holes and support structures added to them to cut down on construction time and accommodate features such as hatches for the yacht.<br/><br/>According to a new release from European Space Agency dated February 27, the ship features a "desirable, luxurious interior."<br/><br/>The superyacht is set to become the world's largest aluminum sailing ship once it is completed and delivered to its owners this spring.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/superyacht-designed-using-same-technique-as-satellites-in-space-3970598</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/03/3970598/3970598_42CEDB2762854404BB3B7B8C1CED4EB6_200303_3970598_Superyacht_designed_using_same_technique_as_sate_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 03:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971052</guid>
      <title>Covid-19 symptoms and precautions explained</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> Here's a list of symptoms of the virus and precautions people can take in order to better protect themselves as the novel coronavirus continues to spread around the world. <br/><br/>Initial symptoms of the coronavirus diseases, or Covid-19, include fever followed by a dry cough, according to BBC News. Patients suffering from Covid-19 could develop shortness of breath after a week. This may lead some to be hospitalized for further treatment.<br/><br/>The BBC noted that symptoms are similar to those of common viruses such as the cold or the flu.<br/><br/>The World Health Organization states that the incubation period for coronavirus diseases lasts up to 14 days. The incubation period may be longer and could last up to 24 days, BBC News reports, citing researchers. <br/><br/>It's unclear how exactly the virus that causes Covid-19 spreads, though similar viruses are typically spread through droplets that are produced when a person who has contracted the virus sneezes or coughs.<br/><br/>The United Kingdom's National Health Service advised the public to wash hands frequently with soap or use hand sanitizer, sneeze or cough into a tissue or into your sleeve and avoid touching the face with unwashed hands.<br/><br/>In more severe cases, Covid-19 could lead to pneumonia, severe acute respiratory syndrome, organ failure or even death.<br/><br/>The virus, which is officially known as severe acute respiratory syndrome coronavirus 2, or SARS-CoV-2, originated in China. It has since spread to 60 countries, with especially severe outbreaks in Italy, Iran and South Korea.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/covid-19-symptoms-and-precautions-explained-3971052</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/04/3971052/3971052_BCCDD22FDCC046A7B8E5C23DEFE0C782_200304_3971052_Covid_19_symptoms_and_precautions_explained_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 03:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971040</guid>
      <title>DNA found in 75 million year-old dinosaur bones</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RALEIGH, NORTH CAROLINA / BEIJING, CHINA <br/> Researchers have discovered DNA inside 75 million-year-old dinosaur fossils,  according to the National Science Review.<br/><br/>According to the Science China Press writing on Phys.org, scientists from the U.S. and China made the discovery while investigating skull fragments of Hypacrosaurus nestlings. In addition to DNA, researchers also found proteins, chromosomes and cartilage cells among the fossils.<br/><br/>According to the British Natural History Museum, these dinosaurs were herbivores and lived 70 million years ago in Canada and the USA during the Late Cretaceous period.<br/><br/>Researchers suggest that their findings could mean that DNA can exist longer than currently thought and may, in fact, be preserved in fossils that are millions of years old. <br/><br/>THUMBNAIL VIA WIKIMEDIA COMMONS / DEBIVORT  https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/cd/Hypacrosaurus-v2.jpg]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dna-found-in-75-million-year-old-dinosaur-bones-3971040</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/04/3971040/3971040_1F07902FD3694535B0492F94EF6FB56B_200304_3971040_DNA_found_in_75_million_year_old_dinosaur_bones_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 03:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3971519</guid>
      <title>Galactic collision may be bending our galaxy out of shape</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PARIS <br/> The European Space Agency's space observatory Gaia may have found an explanation for the warped shape of the Milky Way Galaxy, which is bent into an S shape. This warp rotates with the galaxy's stars instead of standing still.<br/><br/>A study published in Nature Astronomy says that an ongoing collision with another galaxy, most likely the dwarf satellite galaxy Sagittarius, has disrupted the dish shape of our galaxy.<br/><br/>The European Space Agency launched Gaia in 2013 to render a 3D map of the Milky Way.<br/><br/>The agency says the survey will eventually take a spatial census of 1 billion stars in our galaxy, or 1 percent of its constituents. <br/><br/>Citing the authors, the European Space Agency says that Gaia mapped out the motions, velocity and distance of our galaxy's stars. The researchers then worked backward to determine when and how collisions with Sagittarius deformed our galactic dish.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/galactic-collision-may-be-bending-our-galaxy-out-of-shape-3971519</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/05/3971519/3971519_8D5C57F954164BCBBE41033E0C388A8E_200305_3971519_Galactic_collision_may_be_bending_our_galaxy_out_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 05:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3972031</guid>
      <title>Scientists are making a black hole based quantum teleporter</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PASADENA, CALIFORNIA <br/> Scientists have proposed to build a functional wormhole tunnel by simulating quantum entangled black holes in a lab. Quanta Magazine reports the linked black holes are theoretically able to teleport quantum information via the tunnel.<br/><br/>Black holes were thought to totally obliterate the objects they consume. However, the experiment will test a new idea in physics that evaporating black holes actually send information about subsumed objects back to the universe via Hawking radiation.<br/><br/>Citing California Institute of Technology physicist Sepehr Nezami, the outlet reports the research team believes a black hole could be forced to disgorge intact information after it is entangled with another black hole on a quantum level.<br/><br/>Stanford University's Adam Brown is cited as saying quantum circuitry could make a functional analog for entangled black holes. If the theory is correct, this circuitry would be able to instantly transmit and decrypt qubits, also known as quantum teleportation.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-are-making-a-black-hole-based-quantum-teleporter-3972031</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/06/3972031/3972031_8DD356D9499F4187AD216B7EDC420DC9_200306_3972031_Scientists_are_making_a_black_hole_based_quantum_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 06:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3972258</guid>
      <title>Innovative bridge built vertically, unfolds like an umbrella</title>
      <description><![CDATA[VIENNA <br/> Researchers have demonstrated a futuristic bridge-building technique that allows the structure to unfold like an umbrella to the length of its span. <br/><br/>This new technique is cost-effective, time-saving and has less impact on the natural landscape, according to a news release from Vienna University of Technology.<br/><br/>The Lafnitz Bridge in Austria was built vertically instead of horizontally with scaffolding, like traditional bridges.<br/><br/>Using this technique, engineers erected two vertical concrete piers and attached steel girders on both sides. As the piers are then slowly lowered using hydraulic systems, the steel girders unfold.<br/><br/>Once the bridge has opened up to reach a horizontal position, concrete is added to the structure.<br/><br/>The 116-meter Lafnitz Bridge was "unfolded" over the Lafnitz River on February 27, 2020.<br/><br/>Johann Kollegger, a professor at the Vienna University of Technology, explained in the news release that traditional bridges erected using scaffolding can take months to be completed.<br/><br/>Using this new technique, the elements for the lowering method can be set up in two to three days while the lowering process itself takes roughly three hours.<br/><br/>Kollegger noted that the technique could be used to build bridges in difficult terrain or "terrain that should be not disturbed," such as nature reserves.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/innovative-bridge-built-vertically-unfolds-like-an-umbrella-3972258</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/06/3972258/3972258_E68D7984F898451F8F446A2EB1E5D9A2_200306_3972258_Innovative_bridge_built_vertically__unfolds_like_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 13:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973055</guid>
      <title>Ultra-rare Nintendo PlayStation sells for $300,000</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. <br/>  The ultra-rare prototype 'Nintendo PlayStation', which was rediscovered in an attic in 2015, has sold at auction for $300,000.  <br/><br/>The console was initially constructed as part of a doomed collaboration between Japanese juggernauts, Sony and Nintendo. <br/><br/>The project came to an end when Nintendo suddenly announced a partnership with Sony rival, Philips; which led Sony to make the PlayStation One. <br/><br/>Around 200 prototypes for the Nintendo PlayStation are believed to have been made, but most were eventually scrapped, and only one is publicly known to still exist.<br/><br/>According to Eurogamer, the functioning Nintendo PlayStation toured the world but was eventually put up for auction last month through Heritage Auctions. The bidding process came to an end on the 6th of March with the final bid reaching $300,000.<br/><br/>Despite wanting to keep his identity secret at first, 51-year-old real estate and tech entrepreneur, Greg McLemore had been identified as the buyer. McLemore is most notable for founding Toys.com and Pets.com. <br/><br/>McLemore told Forbes, "I'm looking to not have this machine just buried in a closet somewhere." <br/><br/>He said that he wants to take his collection<br/>which he estimates includes over 800 coin-operated machines and countless other smaller games, trade magazines and original art<br/>and build a permanent museum.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ultra-rare-nintendo-playstation-sells-for-300-000-3973055</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/09/3973055/3973055_1D0EBA0C4D58451F86F026974EF4FE79_200309_3973055_Ultra_rare_Nintendo_PlayStation_sells_for__300_0_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 04:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973083</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How the COVID-19 virus invades human cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Researchers from China have used cryo-electron microscopy to show how SARS-CoV-2 infects humans. The study published in Science says the virus targets a type of receptor found on human cells in the lungs, heart, kidneys and intestines.<br/><br/>A previous study published in Science found the virus' spike protein has two receptor binding domains, or RBDs, facing downward and another facing upward. These allow the virus to bind with and invade human cells.<br/><br/>According to the new study, the virus targets a human ACE2 receptor that has bonded with an amino acid transporter. This subtype of ACE2 structure has never been discovered before.<br/><br/>The virus uses the spike protein's 'up' RBD to bind with the ACE2 structure, which enables the virus to enter and infect the cell. According to the researchers, their discovery may help in developing a cure or vaccine that prevents infection by targeting ACE2.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-how-the-covid-19-virus-invades-human-cells-3973083</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/09/3973083/3973083_EE9B1B0F83304828BD929D641475EE28_200309_3973083_Explainer__How_the_COVID_19_virus_invades_human__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 06:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973249</guid>
      <title>NASA will be unable to command Voyager 2  for almost one year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CANBERRA, AUSTRALIA <br/> Starting early this month, Voyager 2 will stop receiving commands from NASA, the space agency announced in a news release on March 5.<br/><br/>This is because the transmitter that sends commands to Voyager 2, the DSS43 radio antenna near Canberra, Australia, will undergo "critical upgrades" over the next 11 months.<br/><br/>As Voyager 2 travels in space, the radio antenna won't be able to send commands to the space probe while it is being updated. The spacecraft is currently flying in a downward direction relative to our planet's orbital plane, which means it can only be in contact with the radio antenna site in Australia.<br/><br/>During this time, the Voyager team will put the spacecraft into a state of inactivity, which will still allow the spacecraft to send back scientific data to the team during the next 11 months.<br/><br/>NASA said in the news release that the radio antenna's transmitters and other parts need to be replaced and upgraded as they are 40 years old and are "increasingly unreliable."<br/><br/>The DSS43 antenna is part of the U.S. space agency's deep space network, which is used to communicate and receive information from faraway spacecraft.<br/><br/>NASA said the upgrades will also benefit future space missions such as the Artemis lunar missions and Mars 2020 rover mission.<br/><br/>The upgrades on the DSS43 radio antenna are expected to be complete by January of 2021.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-will-be-unable-to-command-voyager-2-for-almost-one-year-3973249</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/09/3973249/3973249_D17D19FC45424BC2A4600A36C3A707A1_200309_3973249_NASA_will_be_unable_to_command_Voyager_2__for_al_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 12:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973610</guid>
      <title>Curiosity rover spots potential clue for life on early Mars</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW ROCHELLE, NEW YORK <br/> In a study published in Astrobiology, astrobiologists at Washington State University and Technische Universitat in Berlin, say NASA's Curiosity rover found organic compounds called thiophenes in soil samples that may have been produced by bacteria.<br/><br/>The rover's instruments break down larger molecules and scientists can only examine chemical fragments. This means they cannot rule out a non-biological origin for the thiophenes, according to a press release from Washington State University.<br/><br/>On Earth, thiophenes are found in coal, crude oil and white truffles.<br/><br/>A thiophene molecule has four carbon atoms and a sulfur atom that make up a ring. Carbon and sulfur are essential elements to living organisms. The thiophene could be non-biological or bacterial in origin, but the evidence is not conclusive for either case.<br/><br/>The study's authors say that bacteria may have existed when Mars was hotter and wetter three billion years ago. Some of those bacteria may have played a role in the sulfate reduction that transforms sulfur to thiophenes.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/curiosity-rover-spots-potential-clue-for-life-on-early-mars-3973610</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/10/3973610/3973610_E54A1C723B8E4B7B956768D619A2ECFD_200310_3973610_Curiosity_rover_spots_potential_clue_for_life_on_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 10:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3973833</guid>
      <title>Dubai plans to build sky transportation system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES <br/>  Dubai's Roads & Transport Authority has announced it is working in collaboration with British company Beemcar to construct a driverless cable-car network that would operate above the city streets.<br/><br/>According to CNN, each electric pod would have four individual seats. The pods are set to travel at 50 kilometers per hour and stand at 7.5 meters above the city streets, supported by carbon composite beams.<br/><br/>According to Beemcar, the electric pod system would be able to transport roughly 20,000 passengers per hour along routes that are designed to cover the busiest areas of the city.<br/><br/>Beemcar isn't the first foreign company to collaborate with Dubai in developing aerial transportation systems. American SkyTran and Belarusian company Skyway are also collaborating with the city's transportation authorities.<br/><br/>These collaborations are part of the city's effort to reach its goal of making 25 percent of its urban transportation driverless by 2030.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/dubai-plans-to-build-sky-transportation-system-3973833</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/11/3973833/3973833_35C6C6DC84EA4C5182EBF93821F42E3F_200311_3973833_Dubai_plans_to_build_sky_transportation_system_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 04:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974634</guid>
      <title>Turtles think ocean plastic smells like food, study finds</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GAINESVILLE, FLORIDA <br/> New evidence suggests that sea turtles are drawn to the smell of plastic debris found in the ocean, according to a report published in Current Biology.<br/><br/>The research team conducted experiments on 15 five-month-old captive loggerhead turtles.<br/><br/>They placed each of the turtles into an isolated container where they would be exposed to the odor of four different items in random order: turtle food, clean plastic debris, deionized water, and plastic that was purposely exposed to a marine environment for five weeks so it would become coated with marine microbes.<br/><br/>The turtles were given roughly one minute inside the container before being exposed to the odor of the items. The airborne particles were supplied into the container through a pipe and a fan outside of the isolated tank for two minutes. Researchers observed the turtles' behavior for four minutes after being exposed to the odors.<br/><br/>Results showed that turtles were attracted by the scent of turtle food and bio-fouled plastic equally. When exposed to these two items, turtles kept their nares above the water three times longer than they did when exposed to clean plastics and deionized water.<br/><br/>Co-author of the study Joseph Pfaller of the University of Florida, Gainesville told the BBC that it's not so much that the plastics look like turtle food but that quote, 'anything out there can grow bacteria and animals on it that turtles want to eat and so it smells to them like something they should go check out and possibly consume, which can lead to their death.'"<br/><br/>According to 2015 data published in the journal Science, between 4.8 and 12.7 million tonnes of plastic enter the ocean each year.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/turtles-think-ocean-plastic-smells-like-food-study-finds-3974634</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/13/3974634/3974634_E43376537C584CFEB11BBA4B27CC312E_200313_3974634_Turtles_think_ocean_plastic_smells_like_food__st_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 03:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974602</guid>
      <title>Plastic-eating caterpillars could help tackle pollution</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MANITOBA, CANADA <br/> In 2017, small caterpillars were found to be dining on plastic garbage. <br/>According to CNN, the little caterpillars can munch through plastic, even polyethylene, a common and non-biodegradable plastic found pretty much all over the planet now filling up landfills and oceans around the world. <br/>According to findings published in the journal Proceedings of the Royal Society B, scientists now understand how the grubs are able to eat the plastic.<br/>Apparently it's because of its amazing gut bacteria or microbiome. <br/>Associate professor and chair of biology at Brandon University in Canada Christophe LeMoine said, "We found that waxworm caterpillars are endowed with gut microbes that are essential in the plastic biodegradation process."<br/>"This process seems reliant on a synergy between the caterpillars and their gut bacteria to accelerate polyethylene degradation."<br/>LeMoine did add that the waxworms were not an immediate fix to the world's horrible plastic garbage problem, and that more work still needs to be done to unlock how the caterpillars and their microbiome work together before it can be adapted and replicated on a large scale. <br/>Well, in the meantime...just keep tossing everything into the garbage or the oceans.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/plastic-eating-caterpillars-could-help-tackle-pollution-3974602</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/13/3974602/3974602_EA25D0A82D3341869C9304A1E9D1914D_200313_3974602_Plastic_eating_caterpillars_could_help_tackle_po_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 02:15:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3974719</guid>
      <title>Molten IRON RAIN discovered on massive exoplanet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[GENEVA <br/> Scientists have found evidence of molten iron rain driven by extreme heat on an exoplanet 640 lightyears from Earth, according to new research.<br/><br/>Exoplanet WASP-76b is found in the Gemini constellation where its close orbit to a star causes extreme temperatures on one side of the planet, while the other side is cooler.<br/><br/>According to Physics World, the conditions are hot enough to break down molecules into atoms on the side exposed to the star. On the darker side these can recombine into molecules.<br/><br/>The exoplanet orbits the star differently to how Earth orbits the Sun. Earth rotates as it circles the sun. The exoplanet does not. <br/><br/>The Guardian reports that, similar to Earth's moon, the exoplanet is "tidally locked". <br/>This means that only one side of the planet is continually exposed to the star, while the other is locked in darkness. <br/><br/>It's these conditions that are believed to create the exoplanet's extreme weather conditions and iron rain.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/molten-iron-rain-discovered-on-massive-exoplanet-3974719</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/13/3974719/3974719_4D6A8989180A4A7983573BE9CDFCF704_200313_3974719_Molten_IRON_RAIN_discovered_on_massive_exoplanet_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 07:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975639</guid>
      <title>COVID-19 can survive on some surfaces for up to three days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> New research by American health officials and experts published in medRxiv shows that the novel coronavirus can survive in air particles for several hours and on some surfaces for up to three days.<br/><br/>Researchers used a nebulizer machine to spread the coronavirus in the air and on several surfaces in a controlled environment. The device was used to emulate how the coronavirus would disperse if an infected individual coughed. <br/><br/>Results showed that the virus was still detectable in the air three hours after it was spread.<br/><br/>It was also detectable on copper surfaces for up to four hours, on cardboard surfaces for up to 24 hours and on plastic and stainless steel surfaces for up to two to three days.<br/><br/>An important side note is that this new evidence does not confirm that people have been infected through air particles but that it is plausible that the virus could spread through aerosol and surface contamination.<br/><br/>So what can you do? Sanitize your hands regularly, don't touch your face, watch out for symptoms in yourself and others and mainly DO NOT PANIC. That ain't going to help anyone.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/covid-19-can-survive-on-some-surfaces-for-up-to-three-days-3975639</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/16/3975639/3975639_4C9B0BEFE7534B0D9224D7DC793B720D_200316_3975639_COVID_19_can_survive_on_some_surfaces_for_up_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 02:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975778</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How the Wuhan virus infects human cells</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Researchers from China have used cryo-electron microscopy to show how SARS-CoV-2 infects humans. The study published in Science says the virus targets a type of receptor found on human cells in the lungs, heart, kidneys and intestines.<br/><br/>Citing Kingston University microbiologist Mark Fielder, Sky News reports that the virus seems to attack two types of lung cells: goblet cells that coat the respiratory tract with mucus, and ciliated cells that usually filter out pathogens.<br/><br/>A previous study published in Science found the virus' spike protein has two receptor binding domains, or RBDs, facing downward and another facing upward. These allow the virus to bind with and invade human cells.<br/><br/>According to the new study, the virus targets a human ACE2 receptor that has bonded with an amino acid transporter. This subtype of ACE2 structure has never been discovered before.<br/><br/>The virus uses the spike protein's 'up' RBD to penetrate the cell. The virus then dissolves its own protein shell and releases its RNA payload inside the cell, according to the British Society for Immunology.<br/><br/>A study in Frontiers in Microbiology says a coronavirus hijacks the cell's structure to reproduce. The viral RNA takes over the host cell's endoplasmic reticulum to replicate itself and to manufacture the protein parts to make new viruses."<br/><br/>According to the Society for Immunology, the hijacked cell's Golgi bodies then package viral RNA and proteins in a viral protein shell. This leads to the creation of new viruses that leave the infected cell via the membrane.<br/><br/>The study in Frontiers in Microbiology says coronavirus takeover imposes stress on the host cell. Cell death, or apoptosis, is the result when the infection overwhelms the host cell's ability to maintain homeostasis.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-how-the-wuhan-virus-infects-human-cells-3975778</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/16/3975778/3975778_7602A3DB91474C3889F80896DC8E20FC_200316_3975778_Explainer__How_the_Wuhan_virus_infects_human_cel_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 08:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3975739</guid>
      <title>Researchers blame toxic additive for vaping related lung injuries</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DUBLIN <br/> Medical researchers from Ireland have linked vitamin E acetate to vaping illness. According to new research published in PANAS, the substance is commonly found in illegal THC-based vaping cartridges.<br/><br/>The Royal College of Surgeons in Ireland's research team says in a news release that heating the normally harmless substance through vaping produces ketene, a highly toxic gas.<br/><br/>The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention sounded the alarm on vaping illness after detecting a rash of lung injury cases that appear to be related to e-cigarette use that began in August 2019.<br/><br/>The researchers say ketene can cause severe lung damage up to 24 hours after exposure. Citing doctors at the Mayo Clinic, the New York Times reports the lung injuries of vaping illness patients resembled those of industrial accident-related chemical burns.<br/><br/>According to a report in the New England Journal of Medicine, vitamin E acetate was in the lung liquid samples taken from 48 out of 51 cases of vaping illness, or close to 94 percent.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/researchers-blame-toxic-additive-for-vaping-related-lung-injuries-3975739</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/16/3975739/3975739_6B9B2AB80D5C4EA1BF016CBFAD6AC7FD_200316_3975739_Researchers_blame_toxic_additive_for_vaping_rela_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 06:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976173</guid>
      <title>Futuristic green house allows residents to grow crops indoors</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SHANGHAI <br/> An architectural firm based in Shanghai has unveiled a futuristic, zero-waste house that allows residents to power their own homes and grow their own produce in a living space of 150 square meters. <br/><br/>Yang Design's Green Concept House features solar panels and wind turbines that would be used to provide power to the house. Spare energy from electricity consumption would then be used to convert water vapor from the air into water drops using condensation panels on the roof of the house.<br/><br/>Circular incubators present throughout the green house would allow residents to grow plants and vegetables indoors. Water drops created from the condensation panels would be deposited to a circular pool which would regulate water flow to each circular incubator.<br/><br/>This system would be connected via a smartphone app, allowing residents to monitor their in-home garden using the app even if they are away from home. The app would alert homeowners with an alarm if one of the plants is in need of specific care or send out a notification if a vegetable or a plant is ready to be picked.<br/><br/>The architectural firm explained on its website that this futuristic design could create a new means of communication between separated individuals and allow them to bond over the vegetable garden as well as redefine the concept of agriculture.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/futuristic-green-house-allows-residents-to-grow-crops-indoors-3976173</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/17/3976173/3976173_82999E650C614EA7AAFB5B4A5EA33D10_200317_3976173_Futuristic_green_house_allows_residents_to_grow__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 07:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976529</guid>
      <title>Microfibers found to change fish' reproductive, respiratory systems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[DURHAM, NORTH CAROLINA <br/> A new study from Duke University has found that microplastic fibers can cause damage to the respiratory and reproductive systems of the Japanese medaka fish.<br/><br/>For the study, researchers placed 27 pairs of the fish in a water tank with large amounts of suspended microplastic fibers.<br/><br/>On a weekly basis, scientists monitored egg production, weight and the amount of fiber that was ingested and excreted out by the medaka fish.<br/><br/>After 21 days, researchers examined the tissue of the Japanese medaka fish and found that those exposed to larger amounts of microplastic fibers had developed fused membranes and increased mucus production in their gills. <br/><br/>The microfibers had also caused damage to the epithelial cells lining the fish gills. <br/><br/>Female fish exposed to the microfibers had been found to produce more eggs over this period of time.<br/><br/>The study also found that microplastic fibers residing in fish guts may release harmful chemical coatings that could leak into the bloodstream of the fish.<br/><br/>Melissa Chernick, a researcher involved with the study, explained in a Duke University news release from March 16 that if wild fish swimming in the ocean damage their gills, it would make the fish less competitive while looking for food and less able to guard against potential predators in the sea.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/microfibers-found-to-change-fish-reproductive-respiratory-systems-3976529</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976529/3976529_255C204779CD4C05B3BE9A60BA91E5D5_200318_3976529_Microfibers_found_to_change_fish__reproductive___2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 03:33:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976657</guid>
      <title>Explainer: What is a virus?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A virus is made of nucleic acids surrounded by a protein shell. There are many types of viruses; some like the coronavirus have RNA-based genetic material, while others contain a DNA-based genome. <br/><br/>According to the National Human Genome Research Institute, viruses straddle the definition of being living and nonliving. This is because viruses can only move or reproduce by infecting living cells, according to a study published in PubMed Central.<br/><br/>The PubMed study explains the human immune system can fight off viruses by deploying B-cells. These white blood cells produce antibodies that eradicate viruses before they get into cells.<br/><br/>The British Society of Immunology reports that another way the immune system fights viruses is to send killer T-cells to search and destroy infected cells. Since the immune response is attacking the body itself, it also causes stress to the patient.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-what-is-a-virus--3976657</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976657/3976657_217A35E44C4A40309C96BA46D24F4FCE_200318_3976657_Explainer__What_is_a_virus__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 08:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3976814</guid>
      <title>New information on how the COVID-19 spreads</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WORLD <br/> The coronavirus has officially taken over the world and information about how the virus works, spreads and affects humans seems to be changing by the minute. Here is what we know so far.<br/><br/>According to a report by the Associated Press, the coronavirus spreads when a healthy individual breathes in respiratory droplets that are expelled by infected individuals.<br/><br/>Research by American health officials and experts published in medRxiv shows that the novel coronavirus can survive in air particles for three hours.<br/><br/>It was also detectable on copper surfaces for up to four hours, on cardboard surfaces for up to 24 hours and on plastic and stainless steel surfaces for up to two to three days.<br/><br/>An individual carrying the virus can infect around two to three other people, making it more contagious than the flu. However, coronavirus spreads less easily than measles and tuberculosis.<br/><br/>Early symptoms include a fever, a dry cough and difficulty breathing. Recovery takes about two weeks.<br/><br/>People carrying the virus seem to be the most contagious a few days before showing symptoms. Older adults and individuals with underlying health conditions are at higher risk of experiencing more severe symptoms of the virus.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/new-information-on-how-the-covid-19-spreads-3976814</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/18/3976814/3976814_40A417660FF64004B47C6C19448F4BCE_200318_3976814_New_information_on_how_the_COVID_19_spreads_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 13:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977246</guid>
      <title>How coronavirus symptoms progress from day to day</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN, CHINA <br/> Chinese scientists have identified a pattern of day-to-day symptoms typical of patients with coronavirus in a new study.<br/><br/>The study, published in the journal JAMA, looked at 138 patients hospitalized with novel coronavirus-infected pneumonia at the Zhongnan Hospital of Wuhan University. <br/><br/>Fever is typically the first symptom experienced by those infected with SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes coronavirus disease 2019, according to the study of patients in Wuhan. <br/><br/>Some COVID-19 patients may also experience fatigue, muscle pain and a dry cough.<br/><br/>By day five, this transitions into breathing difficulties, especially for the elderly or those with preexisting health conditions. The study found it took patients an average of seven days after running a fever before they were admitted to a hospital.<br/><br/>By day eight, those with severe symptoms had developed acute respiratory distress syndrome, or ARDS, which can be fatal. This is when fluid builds up in the lungs.<br/><br/>Patients with worsening symptoms are typically admitted to the intensive care unit by day 10. These patients are probably experiencing more abdominal pain and loss of appetite than those with milder symptoms.<br/><br/>On average, it took patients with COVID-19 roughly two and a half weeks to recover from the illness and be discharged from the hospital.<br/><br/>According to CNN, as of March 19 there were 215,000 coronavirus cases globally. The death toll has surpassed 8,000.<br/><br/>Countries such as Argentina, Canada and Taiwan as well as the European Union have shut their borders in order to slow the spread of the disease.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-coronavirus-symptoms-progress-from-day-to-day-3977246</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/19/3977246/3977246_CD59F8E5F45B45748512E26F59079C41_200319_3977246_How_coronavirus_symptoms_progress_from_day_to_da_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 11:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977185</guid>
      <title>U.S. woman takes first COVID-19 vaccine shot in clinical trial</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SEATTLE <br/> A U.S. volunteer became the first person to receive an experimental COVID-19 vaccine as part of the first phase of humans trial on March 16, the Associated Press reports.<br/><br/>According to Kaiser Permanente, which is funded by the National Institutes of Health to conduct the project, the vaccine eschews dead or inert viruses and instead utilizes messenger RNA, or mRNA.<br/><br/>A previous study in Molecular Theory suggests engineered mRNA could cause ribosomes in human cells to manufacture artificially designed proteins.<br/><br/>According to Kaiser Permanente, their vaccine would make cells produce a protein that is found in the outer coating of SARS-CoV-2, which triggers an immune response.<br/><br/>If a person who received the vaccine is later infected with COVID-19, their prior immune response may help their body mount a stronger reaction to the real virus infection.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/u-s-woman-takes-first-covid-19-vaccine-shot-in-clinical-trial-3977185</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/19/3977185/3977185_DB2436CBA97240A5ABC6A6FD233CDA22_200319_3977185_U_S__woman_takes_first_COVID_19_vaccine_shot_in__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 09:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3977645</guid>
      <title>Mercury's scorching heat may help the planet form ice</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA <br/> Mercury's close orbit around the sun and extreme heat may have helped the planet to generate ice. Writing in the Astrophysical Journal Letters, scientists say solar wind may contribute to a chemical process that forms ice in Mercury's poles.<br/><br/>While much of Mercury is very hot, the planet lacks an atmosphere to dissipate the heat. According to Space.com, this allows pockets of cold to exist in the shadows of polar craters, which preserve the ice that exists on Mercury.<br/><br/>In a news release from Georgia Institute of Technology, researchers say Mercury's soil contains hydroxyl [e]groups, or bonded hydrogen and oxygen. After solar winds bombard the substance to 400 degrees Celsius, the oxygen and hydrogen break free to form water.<br/><br/>The scientists say that according to their model, some of the water molecules would break down into their constituent atoms, but the remainder would escape and land on Mercury's poles. This creates ice deposits in the craters.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/mercury-s-scorching-heat-may-help-the-planet-form-ice-3977645</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/20/3977645/3977645_BAB65E2C1A394BC1A2C9E380739DC101_200320_3977645_Mercury_s_scorching_heat_may_help_the_planet_for_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 09:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978522</guid>
      <title>Japan's space probe fires shell at asteroid to study its composition</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TOKYO <br/> Launched in late 2012, Japan's spacecraft Hayabusa2 was sent to investigate asteroid Ryugu by lobbing a copper shell into the space rock. Japan's space agency JAXA published the probe's findings in the journal Science on March 19.<br/><br/>According to JAXA, the Hayabusa is 0.6m across the front, 0.4m from prow to stern, and has four ion thrusters. The spacecraft is equipped with X- and Ka-band antennas for communication and its sensors include optics, LIDAR and spectrometers.<br/><br/>According to the study, the Small Carry-on Impactor shell blasted a semicircular crater 14m wide and 0.6m deep, with the shock apparently absorbed by boulders. This confirms that Ruygu is indeed a rubble-pile, or boulders loosely held together by sandy materials.<br/><br/>The impact experiment suggests the most ancient materials of the asteroid are up to 4.6 billion years old, but the substance coalesced with other asteroids' remains only 10 million years ago to form Ryugu.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/japan-s-space-probe-fires-shell-at-asteroid-to-study-its-composition-3978522</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/23/3978522/3978522_68FF04783707400EA6540DBF1E497882_200323_3978522_Japan_s_space_probe_fires_shell_at_asteroid_to_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 06:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3978909</guid>
      <title>Comet ATLAS might become the  brightest to grace the sky in years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Comet ATLAS, also known as C/2019 Y4, is growing brighter at a surprising rate as it hurtles toward the Sun. <br/><br/>Space.com reports that as of March 17, the newly discovered comet's magnitude, a measure of its brightness, was +8.5, 600 times brighter than forecasts. It may well become the brightest comet in years.<br/><br/>Comets are made of dust, frozen water, ammonia, methane and carbon dioxide. <br/><br/>Citing Karl Battams of the U.S. Naval Research Laboratory, Space Weather Archive reports ATLAS is shedding huge amounts of gas and it may yet disintegrate before reaching the Sun.<br/><br/>The comet ATLAS is named after the Asteroid Terrestrial-impact Last Alert System, a pair of observatories in Hawaii that first discovered the comet on Dec. 18, 2019.<br/><br/>Space Weather Archive reports ATLAS began heating up two months before reaching the Perihelion, or the nearest approach to the Sun. <br/><br/>Should it withstand the sun's heat, the comet will loop inside Mercury's orbit and become visible to the naked eye on Earth in April.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/comet-atlas-might-become-the-brightest-to-grace-the-sky-in-years-3978909</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/24/3978909/3978909_5556623197EA4BA4A62C7830FE232C15_200324_3978909_Comet_ATLAS_might_become_the__brightest_to_grace_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2020 06:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979446</guid>
      <title>This worm from 555 million years ago is probably your ancestor</title>
      <description><![CDATA[RIVERSIDE, CALIFORNIA <br/> Geologists examining fossil impressions from South Australia have found evidence of the earliest relative of most animal life on Earth, a tiny, wormlike creature that lived 555 million years ago, according to a study published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.<br/><br/><br/><br/>Writing in a news release, scientists at the University of California, Riverside say laser scans suggest the Ikaria wariootia was about the size of a grain of rice, 7mm long and 2.5mm wide at the largest. They were wide in the head, narrow in the rear, and possessed bilateral symmetry. This suggests they had a mouth, anus and gut.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The wormlike creatures are the oldest animals ever found to possess bilateral symmetry. This suggests they may be the first common ancestors to animals organized along the bilateral body plan, including dinosaurs, insects and humans.<br/><br/><br/><br/>According to the news release, bilateral symmetrical was a crucial evolutionary step that gave animals an efficient way to organize their body and to move purposefully.<br/><br/><br/><br/>The ocean floor-dwelling creatures lived during the Ediacaran Period. Scientists say the worms likely possessed senses that allowed them to navigate the well-oxygenated sands and search for organic matter to consume.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/this-worm-from-555-million-years-ago-is-probably-your-ancestor-3979446</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/25/3979446/3979446_A96F13F7A6FB429687A3D731E2EC67EB_200325_3979446_This_worm_from_555_million_years_ago_is_probably_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3979537</guid>
      <title>UPDATE: Coronavirus can last up to 17 days on surfaces</title>
      <description><![CDATA[ATLANTA <br/> According to the latest report by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, RNA material from the coronavirus can last on some surfaces for longer than previous research has shown.<br/><br/>Experts analyzed the interior of the Diamond Princess cruise ship, which was quarantined off Yokohama, Japan, and found RNA material from the coronavirus in the cabins of both symptomatic and asymptomatic passengers that had been infected with SARS-CoV-2 up to 17 days after they had left the cruise.<br/><br/>This evidence was found prior to disinfection of the rooms.<br/><br/>The CDC specified in their report that although RNA of the virus was present, it does not mean live virus was still on the surfaces. It is also unclear whether or not this RNA is infectious.<br/><br/>Commenting on the report, the MIT Technology Review says proper disinfection of surfaces kills traces of the coronavirus on all surfaces.<br/><br/>According to the CDC, cruise ships facilitate viral outbreaks due to the close contact of passengers in close quarters.<br/><br/>The CDC report states that altogether, the Diamond Princess and Grand Princess cruises carried more than 800 COVID-19 cases that resulted in 10 deaths.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/update-coronavirus-can-last-up-to-17-days-on-surfaces-3979537</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/25/3979537/3979537_440B6474E2594A3AAD77F8A54158D2F9_200325_3979537_UPDATE__Coronavirus_can_last_up_to_17_days_on_su_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 12:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3980291</guid>
      <title>Ozone layer's recovery is protecting wind systems</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BOULDER, COLORADO <br/> The ozone layer's recovery is stopping changes in the atmospheric circulation systems of the Southern Hemisphere, according to new research.<br/><br/>Writing in a study published in Nature, researchers say the Montreal Protocol is curbing ozone depletion, a phenomenon responsible for Antarctica's ozone hole. This hole has disrupted atmospheric circulation in the southern hemisphere, including shifting the mid-latitude jet stream poleward. <br/><br/>The Montreal Protocol was signed in 1987 to phase out chlorofluorocarbons, or CFCs, from air conditioning, refrigerators and packaging. According to the study, the international accord's removal of CFC pollution has halted the jet stream's drift to the south.<br/><br/>Writing in a news release, the University of Colorado Boulder says its researchers believe climate warming is driving the jet stream to the Southern Pole. Ozone layer recovery exerts an opposite effect that has paused the shift.<br/><br/>According to the university, ozone depletion is also linked to the southward expansion of the Southern Hemisphere's tropical dry region, which affects rainfall in South America, East Africa and Australia.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/ozone-layer-s-recovery-is-protecting-wind-systems-3980291</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/27/3980291/3980291_954A013C57ED4D458074399D4411CD3D_200327_3980291_Ozone_layer_s_recovery_is_protecting_wind_system_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2020 08:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981312</guid>
      <title>Quasars literally blasts stars away before they can be born</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BLACKSBURG, VIRGINIA <br/> Quasar black holes emit radiation so powerful that they can prevent star formation in the surrounding galaxy, according to a study in the Astrophysical Journal Supplementary Letters.<br/><br/>Writing on behalf of co-author Nahum Arav, a Virginia Tech press release says quasar outflows rip through interstellar space to generate intense light and heat. The quasar radiation blasts away matter that is needed for birthing stars. <br/><br/>The radiation emissions dubbed quasar winds blow hundreds of solar masses of material away each year. According to Science Alert, quasars spend billions of years in this violent state before maturing into more conventional black holes.<br/><br/>According to the research team, it is a scientific puzzle that the universe does not have bigger galaxies or more numerous stars than it actually possesses. They say quasars at the core of elliptical galaxies could be part of the answer.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/quasars-literally-blasts-stars-away-before-they-can-be-born-3981312</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/30/3981312/3981312_3DB0D46BFFAB445CAF39076CA1539F1A_200330_3981312_Quasars_literally_blasts_stars_away_before_they__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 09:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3981630</guid>
      <title>Why the novel coronavirus did not come from a lab</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN DIEGO <br/> The novel coronavirus did not originate from a research laboratory, according to a study published in Nature Medicine. <br/><br/>Researchers say the novel coronavirus was not made in a lab, after comparing its RNA sequence to SARS, MERS and other coronaviruses including the HKU1, which is known to cause mild symptoms in humans. <br/><br/>Citing the authors, Live Science reports the study focuses on the novel coronavirus's spike protein.<br/><br/>The protein consists of receptor binding domains, also known as RBDs, and a cleavage site.<br/><br/>The RBD hooks on to an ACE2 receptor on the surface of human cells, then the cleavage site opens the receptor for the virus to enter.<br/><br/>The spike protein design is deemed so effective that it could only have resulted from natural selection and not human engineering.<br/><br/>When scientists simulated the virus in computer models, they found computers to underate COVID-19's infectiousness by a significant margin.<br/><br/>Study co-author Kristian Andersen of Scripps Research was cited as saying if scientists designed the virus, they would not have chosen the spike protein mutations that seemed ineffective.<br/><br/>Additionally, biological weapons were usually created from deadly viruses, but SARS-CoV-2's close relatives are bat and pangolin viruses that are largely innocuous.<br/><br/>The virus is speculated to have spread from bats to pangolins to humans. According to the researchers, they are working to determine at what point SARS-CoV-2 developed the cleavage site mutations that increased its infectiousness.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/why-the-novel-coronavirus-did-not-come-from-a-lab-3981630</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/03/31/3981630/3981630_EA23B54E8F75431DAB31FA134BA09702_200331_3981630_Why_the_novel_coronavirus_did_not_come_from_a_la_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 07:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
