<?php xml version="1.0" encoding="ascii"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:metadata="http://www.w3.org/Metadata" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <link>http://us.tomonews.com/</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 18:08:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <guid>3981975</guid>
      <title>COVID-19 can survive on medical masks for seven days</title>
      <description><![CDATA[HONG KONG <br/> New research shows SARS-CoV-2 can survive on the outer layer of a surgical mask for seven days.<br/><br/>New research published in medRxive by medical specialists in Hong Kong shows how long SARS-CoV-2 can survive on different surfaces and in different environments.<br/><br/>The researchers pipetted a droplet of virus culture on several surfaces including paper, tissue paper, wood, cloth, glass, a banknote, stainless steel, plastic, the inner layer of a surgical mask and the outer layer of a surgical mask.<br/><br/>Results showed that there was no trace of the infectious virus on printing and tissue paper three hours after incubation.<br/><br/>The infectious virus stopped being present on wood and cloth by Day 2 after incubation. Glass surfaces and banknotes had no trace of the virus by Day 4. Stainless steel and plastic surfaces had no detectable virus on their surfaces by Day 7.<br/><br/>However, the infectious virus could still be detected on the outer layer of a surgical mask by Day 7.<br/><br/>The research concludes that although the virus is stable in a wide range of environments, it is still vulnerable to standard disinfection methods.<br/><br/>Previous research by American health officials and experts published in medRxiv showed that the novel coronavirus can survive in air particles for several hours and on some surfaces for up to three days.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/covid-19-can-survive-on-medical-masks-for-seven-days-3981975</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/01/3981975/3981975_E8A0FC59E75041FD83CB810DE536F5DF_200401_3981975_COVID_19_can_survive_on_medical_masks_for_seven__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 05:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3982006</guid>
      <title>Washing your hands correctly with soap destroys coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> Washing your hands thoroughly and often with soap and water for at least 20 to 30 seconds is one of the most effective ways to eliminate the coronavirus from your skin.<br/><br/>Soap molecules have a hydrophilic head which is attracted to water and a hydrophobic tail that seeks to bond with lipids such as oils and fats.<br/><br/>Coronaviruses are enveloped RNA viruses. Their key components are RNA, the virus's genetic material; proteins that allow the virus to infect cells; and a lipid envelope that coats the virus. This lipid membrane has two rings of hydrophilic heads surrounding two layers of hydrophobic tails.<br/><br/>Soap molecules destabilize a coronavirus because their hydrophobic tails are attracted to lipids in the virus's lipid bilayer. The soap molecules stick to lipids in the bilayer and pry them apart, encapsulating them in bubbles called micelles that wash away in the lather.<br/><br/>In addition to disrupting the lipid membrane of the virus, soap molecules also disrupt the bonds that hold the proteins, lipids and viral RNA together. They effectively pull the virus apart, and the viral particles are rinsed away in water.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/washing-your-hands-correctly-with-soap-destroys-coronavirus-3982006</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/01/3982006/3982006_91DE0D2ABF4041EDA0F5EFBD0FB818C0_200401_3982006_Washing_your_hands_correctly_with_soap_destroys__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2020 06:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3982354</guid>
      <title>How the coronavirus infects and damages the human body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> The COVID-19 coronavirus, or SARS-CoV-2, spreads through droplets that people make when we talk, cough or sneeze. The virus can be carried for up to 27 feet and land on the respiratory system, according to a study in the Journal of American Medical Association.<br/><br/>A gene sequence study published in Frontiers in Medicine showed that the coronavirus targets human cells with ACE2 receptors. This means the epithelial cells in the lungs and other organs are vulnerable to the coronavirus.<br/><br/>The coronavirus has mutations in the spike proteins on its surface. The mutations to the receptor binding domains, or RBDs, allow the virus to use human ACE2 receptors as entry points for getting into the cell.<br/><br/>According to the British Society for Immunology, the virus hijacks the cell and commandeers the structures inside the cell to make more copies of itself. The infected cell's ribosomes are directed to create viral RNA and proteins.<br/><br/>After that, the cell's Golgi apparatus puts the proteins and RNA together and coats them in protein, which creates new copies of the coronavirus.<br/><br/>The biochemical distress of being hijacked by the virus eventually kills the cell, which causes damage to the infected tissue.<br/><br/>At the same time, the body tries to fight off the infection by sending killer T-cells. The killer cells search and destroy compromised cells. The immune system's attack on the infected part of the body leads to more tissue damage and inflammation.<br/><br/>Speaking to the Guardian, John Wilson, president-elect of the Royal Australasian College of Physicians and a respiratory physician, said the coronavirus infection spreads down the respiratory system and may reach the alveoli at the bottom of the lungs. This fills the lungs with liquids and inflammatory materials.<br/><br/>Symptoms of COVID-19 include fever, breathing difficulties and muscle pains. Citing doctors, the New York Times reports the virus may move in the blood to attack the heart, the kidneys, and the liver. Lung damage would also deprive patients of blood oxygen.<br/><br/>George Washington University Hospital reports that 20 percent of COVID-19 patients are symptomatic. A portion of these develop severe symptoms and become unable to breathe without using ventilators or other medical devices.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/how-the-coronavirus-infects-and-damages-the-human-body-3982354</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/02/3982354/3982354_8A3B32953A524E1B9B9067E594229069_200402_3982354_How_the_coronavirus_infects_and_damages_the_huma_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 03:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3982786</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus animation: How COVID19 attacks the body</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> The COVID-19 coronavirus, or SARS-CoV-2, spreads through droplets that people make when we talk, cough or sneeze. The virus can be carried for up to 27 feet and land on the respiratory system, according to a study in the Journal of American Medical Association.<br/><br/>A gene sequence study published in Frontiers in Medicine showed that the coronavirus targets human cells with ACE2 receptors. This means the epithelial cells in the lungs and other organs are vulnerable to the coronavirus.<br/><br/>The coronavirus has mutations in the spike proteins on its surface. The mutations to the receptor binding domains, or RBDs, allow the virus to use human ACE2 receptors as entry points for getting into the cell.<br/><br/>According to the British Society for Immunology, the virus hijacks the cell and commandeers the structures inside the cell to make more copies of itself. The infected cell's ribosomes are directed to create viral RNA and proteins.<br/><br/>After that, the cell's Golgi apparatus puts the proteins and RNA together and coats them in protein, which creates new copies of the coronavirus.<br/><br/>The biochemical distress of being hijacked by the virus eventually kills the cell, which causes damage to the infected tissue.<br/><br/>At the same time, the body tries to fight off the infection by sending killer T-cells. The killer cells search and destroy compromised cells. The immune system's attack on the infected part of the body leads to more tissue damage and inflammation.<br/><br/>Speaking to the Guardian, John Wilson, president-elect of the Royal Australasian College of Physicians and a respiratory physician, said the coronavirus infection spreads down the respiratory system and may reach the alveoli at the bottom of the lungs. This fills the lungs with liquids and inflammatory materials.<br/><br/>Symptoms of COVID-19 include fever, breathing difficulties and muscle pains. Citing doctors, the New York Times reports the virus may move in the blood to attack the heart, the kidneys, and the liver. Lung damage would also deprive patients of blood oxygen.<br/><br/>George Washington University Hospital reports that 20 percent of COVID-19 patients are symptomatic. A portion of these develop severe symptoms and become unable to breathe without using ventilators or other medical devices.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-animation-how-covid19-attacks-the-body-3982786</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/03/3982786/3982786_42954D4678794203830E8C2742ACF15A_200403_3982786_Coronavirus_animation__How_COVID19_attacks_the_b_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 05:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984033</guid>
      <title>Asymptomatic people also responsible for virus spread</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SINGAPORE <br/> New research by health specialists from Singapore shows evidence that asymptomatic individuals infected with SARS-CoV-2 can inadvertently spread the virus.<br/><br/>According to a new study from Singapore published in the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Morbidity and Mortality Weekly Report, medical researchers studied 243 cases of coronavirus infections that occurred in Singapore from January 23 to March 16.<br/><br/>Out of these 243 cases, researchers detected seven clusters of cases that showed possible presymptomatic transmission of the virus. The researchers determined that 10 cases from these seven clusters were due to presymptomatic transmission.<br/><br/>For example, a man in Cluster E had traveled to Japan from February 29 to March 8 where he may have been infected. The man later infected his housemate before showing any symptoms. Both developed symptoms on March 11.<br/><br/>A woman in Cluster B, named Patient B1 in the paper, attended an event on February 15 where she likely came into contact with a confirmed COVID-19 patient. Nine days later she attended singing classes with another woman, Patient B2. Two days later Patient B1 developed symptoms. Patient B2 developed symptoms on February 29.<br/><br/>So, what can we do? Well, while wearing facemasks is not a guarantee that you won't get the virus, it is a good tool in preventing potentially contaminated droplets of saliva from others (and yourself) from spreading[d].<br/><br/>The U.S. Centers for Disease Prevention and Control recommends, quote, 'wearing cloth face coverings in public settings where other social distancing measures are difficult to maintain especially in areas of significant community-based transmission.'[e]<br/><br/>However, this does not mean you have a green light to go and stock up on medical-grade surgical masks, leave those for the professionals. They truly need them now.[f] What you can do is buy a washable cloth mask, or make one yourself.<br/><br/>And it goes without saying. Wash your hands and practice social distancing protocol people.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/asymptomatic-people-also-responsible-for-virus-spread-3984033</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/07/3984033/3984033_5E42F0DB2EC0492B84A28C52826B57CB_200407_3984033_Asymptomatic_people_also_responsible_for_virus_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 03:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984450</guid>
      <title>Evidence suggests coronavirus transmission through breathing</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A message to the White House from the National Academies of Science, Engineering and Medicine found strong evidence in the existing scientific literature that the novel coronavirus may be spread through normal breathing. <br/><br/>The report, issued on April 1, buttresses the argument that asymptomatic people should wear masks to reduce inadvertent transmission of the virus. <br/><br/>In an email to Science Insider, Kimberly Prather, an aerosol chemist at the University of California, San Diego, said she was "relieved to see aerosolization is accepted."<br/><br/>"This added airborne pathway helps explain why it is spreading so fast," she said.<br/><br/>As late as March 27, a scientific brief from the World Health Organization stated that an analysis of more than 75,000 COVID-19 cases in China found no cases of the virus spreading through aerosols. <br/><br/>On April 3, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reversed its previous advice on wearing masks in public, and recommended that everyone wear cloth face coverings while in public during the pandemic.<br/><br/>In its announcement, the CDC stressed that surgical masks or N-95 respirators must be reserved for healthcare workers and other first responders.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/evidence-suggests-coronavirus-transmission-through-breathing-3984450</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/08/3984450/3984450_9DC65E1317C34E668E2356C50C4CEA31_200408_3984450_Evidence_suggests_coronavirus_transmission_throu_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 04:37:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984408</guid>
      <title>The biggest and brightest moon of 2020: The Pink Supermoon</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The moon will reach its closest point to Earth in 2020 on April 7, getting as close as 356,907 kilometers from Earth. This phenomenon is popularly known as the Super Pink Moon.<br/><br/>According to NASA, the full moon will appear on Tuesday night. It will emerge on the opposite side of the sun, according to earth-based longitude, at 10:35 p.m. Eastern Daylight Time.<br/><br/>The closeness between Earth and a supermoon makes the moon seem around  7 percent larger than the average full moon and 14 percent brighter than when the moon is at apogee.<br/><br/>NASA explains that the Super Pink Moon receives its name from the herb moss pink, also known as 'wild ground phlox' which blooms in eastern United States during spring.<br/><br/>Unfortunately, with all the lockdowns and self-isolation regulations imposed in countries around the world, not many people will be out moon-gazing."<br/><br/>But hey, if you have a window, or porch or any access to the outside world, take a moment to go out, look up at the sky and forget the corona craze for just a while[b].]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-biggest-and-brightest-moon-of-2020-the-pink-supermoon-3984408</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/08/3984408/3984408_561ADF2CED9B4B6EB97AC394E1E838B3_200408_3984408_The_biggest_and_brightest_moon_of_2020__The_Pink_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2020 02:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3984893</guid>
      <title>Explainer: How bacteria give the rain its unique smell</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NORFOLK, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> New research may explain why rainfall on the soil creates a unique scent in the air. According to the study published in Nature, the smell of rain is caused by geosmin, a chemical secreted by a genus of soil-dwelling bacteria called streptomyces.<br/><br/>Writing a news release from John Innes Centre, researchers say the scent is bait for springtails, tiny 1.5mm-long arthropods.<br/><br/>The tiny six-legged animals sport antennas to detect geosmin. As springtails are attracted to the substance, they follow the scent and eat the bacteria.<br/><br/>By encouraging springtails to eat them, streptomyces get their spores on the arthropods and in their feces, which allows the bacteria to spread and reproduce. This mutually beneficial relationship may have endured for 450 million years.<br/><br/>Streptomyces produce antibiotics that kill nematodes and fruit flies, but not springtails. According to the scientists, this is evidence that springtails have evolved to privilege the bacteria as a food source, which the springtails help to spread.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/explainer-how-bacteria-give-the-rain-its-unique-smell-3984893</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/09/3984893/3984893_CBCB905D304844FDA3E44BC63CA4EA4E_200409_3984893_Explainer__How_bacteria_give_the_rain_its_unique_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 06:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985395</guid>
      <title>NASA reveals plans for base camp near the Moon's South Pole</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA submitted its plans for a lunar base camp to the National Space Council in a 13-page report entitled "NASA's Plan for Sustained Lunar Exploration and Development" on April 2.<br/><br/>The plans are part of NASA's Artemis program to send humans back to the Moon as early as 2024.<br/><br/>NASA plans to build its Artemis Base Camp near the Moon's South Pole. The base camp will provide a fixed outpost for exploration and in the long term would include a landing pad and infrastructure for power, radiation shielding, and waste disposal and storage.<br/><br/>Core elements for a sustained presence on the Moon would include a lunar terrain vehicle for mobility around the base camp, a habitable mobility platform that would allow for longer excursions on the Moon for up to 45 days, and a fixed lunar foundation surface habitat that could house as many as four astronauts for shorter periods of time.<br/><br/>NASA's planned Gateway outpost in lunar orbit would serve as a command and control center for operations on the Moon's surface, a rendez-vous point for spacecraft traveling to and from Earth, as well as provide living quarters and space to conduct scientific research.<br/><br/>In an April 3 article on its website, NASA said it envisions sending four astronauts to the Gateway for a multi-month stay to simulate a trip to Mars. <br/><br/>Later, two crew members would travel to the lunar surface and explore with the habitable mobility platform.<br/><br/>The four astronauts would then be reunited aboard the Gateway for another multi-month stay to simulate the return trip to Earth.<br/><br/>NASA said: "These missions will be by far the longest duration human deep-space missions in history."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-reveals-plans-for-base-camp-near-the-moon-s-south-pole-3985395</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985395/3985395_E5A0D39921DB4CA88811DB2371DDF830_200410_3985395_NASA_reveals_plans_for_base_camp_near_the_Moon_s_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 07:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3985384</guid>
      <title>Scientists are deciphering the coronavirus's sugar camouflage</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SOUTHAMPTON, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> A new study sheds light on the fundamental architecture of the coronavirus that allows the pathogen to disguise itself and get into human cells.<br/><br/>SARS-CoV-2, the virus that causes COVID-19, has a viral coating that is studded with spike proteins, which are the coronavirus's camouflage and infection tools.<br/><br/>According to a preprint paper published in BioArxiv, scientists have detailed the chemical makeup of the proteins by using electron microscopy and spectrometry. <br/><br/>The researchers identified host-derived sugars <br/> or glycans <br/> embedded in the envelope of the spike protein, as well as the concentration of the sugars in each location on the spike.<br/><br/>Glycans are what viruses use for hiding from the immune system and sneaking into human cells.<br/><br/>Writing in a news release, the researchers say SARS-CoV-2's embedded glycan defenses are thinner than those of many other viruses.<br/><br/>This suggests the coronavirus is a "hit and run" virus that moves rapidly from one person to another.<br/><br/>Paper co-author Max Crispin is cited as saying the study about the coronavirus's sugars is "a very encouraging message for vaccine development," and the research team is already working with partners who have designed candidate vaccines.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-are-deciphering-the-coronavirus-s-sugar-camouflage-3985384</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/10/3985384/3985384_47919734017647C1AAB76D361EF56B19_200410_3985384_Scientists_are_deciphering_the_coronavirus_s_sug_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 07:13:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986235</guid>
      <title>NASA is looking at turning a Moon crater into a giant telescope</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> NASA is funding an early-stage concept to build a giant telescope in a crater on the far side of the moon through its NASA Innovative Advanced Concepts program, the space agency announced on April 7.<br/><br/>At a kilometer in diameter, the Lunar Crater Telescope would be the largest filled-aperture radio telescope in the Solar System.<br/><br/>Its location on the Moon's far side would isolate the telescope from electromagnetic interference from Earth, as well as allow it to observe longer wavelengths that are blocked by the Earth's ionosphere.<br/><br/>This would allow scientists to observe fingerprints left by the Big Bang as the universe expanded exponentially in less than a trillionth of a second after it came into existence.<br/><br/>NASA has given the project $125,000 for a nine-month study of the concept. Other projects that received funding from the NASA Innovative Advanced Concepts program include a lunar landing pad and a robotic explorer for Saturn's moon Enceladus.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-is-looking-at-turning-a-moon-crater-into-a-giant-telescope-3986235</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/13/3986235/3986235_04AA9581A9C44B8398D45854670B6520_200413_3986235_NASA_is_looking_at_turning_a_Moon_crater_into_a__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2020 08:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986480</guid>
      <title>Coronavirus may harm the brain and nervous system</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WUHAN <br/> A study of COVID-19 patients in the Chinese city of Wuhan, from where the pandemic originated, found coronavirus could lead to serious neurological complications in perhaps as many as one third of all patients.<br/><br/>In the study of 214 hospitalized COVID-19 patients in Wuhan, researchers reported more than 35 percent had neurological complications, including decreased levels of cognition, stroke, and muscle damage.<br/><br/>Their findings, published in the journal JAMA Neurology on April 10, found 36.4 percent of those studied had neurologic symptoms. Among patients with more severe infections, 45.5 percent showed neurologic manifestations.<br/><br/>Separately, France's National Union of Dermatologists-Venereologists, or SNDV, has reported that certain skin dermatological conditions may possibly be associated with Covid-19 infection.<br/><br/>In an April 6 press release, the organization said these symptoms include appearance of pseudo-frostbite of the extremities, transient hives, and sudden onset of persistent, sometimes painful redness.<br/><br/>The organization recommended that patients with skin conditions of these types consult a dermatologist to rule out the possibility of COVID-19.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/coronavirus-may-harm-the-brain-and-nervous-system-3986480</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/14/3986480/3986480_97BB0AA3F8B549B89D1FC85284577AE7_200414_3986480_Coronavirus_may_harm_the_brain_and_nervous_syste_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 04:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986836</guid>
      <title>Scientists spot new ozone hole in the Arctic</title>
      <description><![CDATA[COLOGNE, GERMANY <br/> Researchers have discovered an unusually large hole in the ozone layer above the Arctic.  <br/><br/>According to observations from the European Space Agency, a new ozone hole has been spotted above the Arctic. The hole covers less than 1 million square kilometers. The Antarctic hole, on the other hand, can extend to around 20 to 25 million square kilometers.<br/><br/>The ESA explains that during this polar winter, strong westerly winds from the polar vortex trapped cold air over the North Pole.<br/><br/>When the polar winter ended, the heat from the first sunlight over the Arctic triggered ozone depletion, causing this unusual mini-hole to form.<br/><br/>This type of ozone hole formation is different from that of the Antarctic ozone hole which appears every year due to extremely cold temperatures and pollution derived from human activity.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/scientists-spot-new-ozone-hole-in-the-arctic-3986836</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/15/3986836/3986836_0676A05647434909BEFF1AA8338286C8_200415_3986836_Scientists_spot_new_ozone_hole_in_the_Arctic_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 04:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3986919</guid>
      <title>Oumuamua's mystery solved?</title>
      <description><![CDATA[SANTA CRUZ, CALIFORNIA <br/> A new study published in Nature suggests the tidal forces that formed Oumuamua may have caused its erratic behavior.<br/><br/>Since its discovery in 2017, the cigar-shaped space object has flummoxed scientists with its odd shape and acceleration movements that gravity effects cannot explain.<br/><br/>Writing in a news release, researchers say that Oumuamua's parent body or bodies may have had a close encounter with a host star.<br/><br/>They say computer models show the tidal forces from stars could rip the parent body apart and turn the original object into an elongated field of debris.<br/><br/>The fragments may have then melted under the intense heat near the star before condescending again to form the strange cigar shape of Oumumua.<br/><br/>Additionally, water-ice could be trapped under Oumuamua's surface. As the object makes its passage through the solar system, the ice could be vaporized and converted to thrust, which gives Oumuamua its gravity-defying accelerations.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/oumuamua-s-mystery-solved--3986919</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/15/3986919/3986919_14347D901A444863ACA860512BF836E6_200415_3986919_Oumuamua_s_mystery_solved__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2020 07:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987214</guid>
      <title>Taiwan is working on a social distancing app to fight COVID-19</title>
      <description><![CDATA[TAIPEI <br/> Taiwan is working on a social distancing app that people can download on a voluntary basis to help prevent the spread of the coronavirus, a cabinet official said on April 11.<br/><br/>In an article published by Taiwan's Central News Agency, Chien Hung-wei, director of the Executive Yuan's Department of Cyber Security, said the social distancing app uses Bluetooth to keep track of when the user gets close to other people. <br/><br/>The app will issue an alert each time the user gets too close to someone else. It will also provide data on how often the user came too close to others during each day. <br/><br/>Chien said the app's primary purpose is to provide users with information about crowded places so that they can avoid them.<br/><br/>The app is currently being tested and will be released within the next two weeks. Use of the app will be voluntary and data will be encrypted and saved in the user's device and will not be collected to track the user's movements, Chien said.<br/><br/>Social distancing guidelines from Taiwan's Central Epidemic Command Center advise people to stay at least one meter apart outdoors and 1.5 meters apart indoors.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/taiwan-is-working-on-a-social-distancing-app-to-fight-covid-19-3987214</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/16/3987214/3987214_71FFD91476334674BB4D341D29FDBA0C_200416_3987214_Taiwan_is_working_on_a_social_distancing_app_to__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 02:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987416</guid>
      <title>The coronavirus has already mutated into three types</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, UNITED KINGDOM <br/> Researchers from the University of Cambridge and Germany have used RNA analysis to identify three types of COVID-19 that evolved during the early stages of the pandemic. This study is published in the Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences.<br/><br/>Citing the team, the University of Cambridge writes in a news release that COVID-19 type A is the "original human virus genome" from the Chinese city of Wuhan.<br/><br/>Mutated versions of type A were discovered in U.S. nationals who reportedly lived in Wuhan. Large numbers of type A virus were also seen in patients living in the U.S. and Australia.<br/><br/>Strangely, the dominant variant in Wuhan was type B, which was prevalent across East Asia, but did not spread much beyond the region. This means either a complex founding event happened in Wuhan, or some factors had resisted type B outside East Asia."<br/><br/>Type C is the main COVID-19 variant in Europe. The presence of type C was detected in early cases from France, Italy, Sweden and England, yet this variant was absent in samples from patients in Mainland China.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-coronavirus-has-already-mutated-into-three-types-3987416</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/16/3987416/3987416_4F45DDC1CC6844AB9CB2D31DB18DEC8E_200416_3987416_The_coronavirus_has_already_mutated_into_three_t_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 10:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3987711</guid>
      <title>Longest Animal Ever Recorded Found in the Deep Sea</title>
      <description><![CDATA[PERTH, AUSTRALIA  <br/> This weird looking string-creature was found off the coasts of Australia along with many other new organisms that live in the deep sea. Here's how researchers bumped into this massive sea monster.<br/><br/>According to a press release from the Schmidt Ocean Institute, researchers found a new submarine creature off the coast of Australia while aboard the Falkor research ship. <br/><br/>The team completed twenty 4,500 meter dives and totaled over 181 hours of deep-sea exploration using a remotely operated submarine called SuBastian.<br/><br/>During this expedition, the marine specialists spotted a type of string-like sea creature called siphonophore Apolemia. Scientists estimated that its outer ring is roughly 46 meters long. Logan Mock-Bunting, a spokesperson for the Schmidt Ocean Institute, told Newsweek that although exact measurements are pending, its length could be over 119 meters long.<br/><br/>Siphonophores are related to corals and jellyfish. They are an entity made up of a connected colony of cloned zooids that work as a team to keep the siphonophore alive.<br/><br/>As we mentioned at the beginning of the video, the siphonophore was not the only new ocean critter they found. We leave you with some breathtaking footage of the beauty and life that occurs in the depths of our oceans.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/longest-animal-ever-recorded-found-in-the-deep-sea-3987711</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/17/3987711/3987711_F7C62477198642DDAA26E92A591FBB19_200417_3987711_Longest_Animal_Ever_Recorded_Found_in_the_Deep_S_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988707</guid>
      <title>NASA discovers 'most similar planet to Earth' ever found</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A team of scientists has discovered an Earth-size exoplanet in the habitable or "Goldilocks" zone of its star while reviewing old data from the Kepler Space Telescope, according to a press release from NASA.<br/><br/>The planet, Kepler-1649c, is located 300 light-years from Earth in the constellation of Cygnus and "is most similar to Earth in size and estimated temperature" of all the exoplanets discovered by Kepler.<br/><br/>Kepler-1649c is 1.06 times the size of Earth and orbits a small red dwarf star once every 19.5 Earth days, from which it receives 75 percent of the amount of light Earth receives from the Sun. <br/><br/>Scientists made the discovery while analyzing old data from Kepler. They found that previous searches with a computer algorithm had misidentified Kepler-1649c as a false positive. <br/><br/>"Out of all the mislabeled planets we've recovered, this one's particularly exciting," said Andrew Vanderburg, a researcher at the University of Texas at Austin and lead author of the paper published on April 15 in the Astrophysical Journal Letters. "If we hadn't looked over the algorithm's work by hand, we would have missed it."<br/><br/>"In terms of size and likely temperature, this is the most similar planet to Earth that has ever been found with Kepler," said co-author Jeff Coughlin at the SETI Institute. "It's incredible to me that we just found it now, seven years after data collection stopped on the original Kepler field."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/nasa-discovers-most-similar-planet-to-earth-ever-found-3988707</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/20/3988707/3988707_9553008FF0CC4746BC931DE155EA20CF_200420_3988707_NASA_discovers__most_similar_planet_to_Earth__ev_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 06:56:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3988677</guid>
      <title>Uranus is leaking gas and now NASA knows all about it</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Writing in the Geophysical Research Letters, NASA says a review of Voyager 2's old data from 1986 showed that Uranus vented a giant blob of gas into space. This pocket of ionized gas, a plasma structure called plasmoid, was 400 km across and 200 km long.<br/><br/>According to NASA's news release, Uranus is special in that it spins almost on its side "like a pig on a spit roast," while the axis of its magnetic field is offset from the spin by 60 degrees. This gives the planet's magnetic field an odd wobble that scientists cannot model.<br/><br/>As solar winds blasted Uranus, the bombardment pinched gas off from the far end of the field. The resulting leak was then accidentally discovered by NASA researchers who were reviewing the old magnetic data.<br/><br/>In the new research, scientists dialed up the reading's resolution to make a data point every two seconds. They spotted a blip in the readings that indicated the planet was making a plasmoid.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/uranus-is-leaking-gas-and-now-nasa-knows-all-about-it-3988677</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/20/3988677/3988677_14FD56A0D7794BC08FC58782C4ABF971_200420_3988677_Uranus_is_leaking_gas_and_now_NASA_knows_all_abo_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 06:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989547</guid>
      <title>Finally, U.S. astronauts going to space on American rockets again</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> The U.S. will send two astronauts to the International Space Station on a SpaceX rocketship from U.S. soil after an 11 year hiatus, according to NASA, <br/><br/>NASA will launch two astronauts to the International Space Station from Florida's Kennedy Space Center, according to the New York Times.<br/><br/>Citing a tweet by NASA Administer Jim Bridenstine, the New York Times reports a Falcon 9 rocket will be utilized for the mission scheduled May 27.<br/><br/>The Falcon 9 rocketship features a reusable second stage with nine Merlin engines.<br/><br/>The New York Times reports NASA's Douglas Hurley and Robert Behnken will pilot the ship from the Dragon spacecraft mounted atop the first stage that will push the capsule to orbit.<br/><br/>The reusable first stage has one Merlin engine and it is capable of reactivating multiple times during the flight to orbit, according to SpaceX.<br/><br/>The Dragon spacecraft will jettison the first stage and fairings before unfurling its solar array, according to NASA.<br/><br/>The Dragon spacecraft has completed multiple supply missions to the ISS and completed its most recent run in March.<br/><br/>According to Space.com, Demo-2 will be the first mission for Dragon to dock itself, instead of relying on robotic arm capture.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/finally-u-s-astronauts-going-to-space-on-american-rockets-again-3989547</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/22/3989547/3989547_CB40B0CB0AD6424893F4B5B170140818_200422_3989547_Finally__U_S__astronauts_going_to_space_on_Ameri_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 10:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3989890</guid>
      <title>When to see Venus in the night sky this year</title>
      <description><![CDATA[IN THE SKY <br/> Venus will reach its greatest brilliancy as the "evening star" this year on April 28. The planet will fade from the night sky near the end of May and return as the "morning star" in the third week of June.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/when-to-see-venus-in-the-night-sky-this-year-3989890</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/23/3989890/3989890_4866D6AC926640FFA386E61ED2960C10_200423_3989890_When_to_see_Venus_in_the_night_sky_this_year_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 07:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3990273</guid>
      <title>'Potentially Hazardous' Asteroid to pass safely on April 29</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> A huge asteroid classified as "potentially hazardous" by NASA will streak past our planet on April 29, accordoing to NASA's Asteroid Watch.<br/><br/>Asteroid 52768, also known as 1998 OR2, is estimated by NASA to be between 1.8 to 4.1 kilometers wide. <br/><br/>It takes Asteroid 1998 OR2 three years and eight months to orbit our Sun. Its journey takes it near Jupiter at its furthest point, but just outside Earth's farthest distance from the Sun on its closest approach.<br/><br/>On April 29 it will pass Earth at a distance that is more than 16 times the average distance between Earth and the Moon.<br/><br/>According to NASA's Center for Near-Earth Object Studies, as of April 21, some 22,582 near-Earth objects had been discovered. <br/><br/>The latest data on the center's website shows that 9,085 of these were 140 meters or larger in size, and 902 were estimated to be larger than one kilometer.<br/><br/>By comparison, the Chicxulub asteroid that wiped out the dinosaurs is estimated to have been 11 to 81 kilometres in diameter.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/-potentially-hazardous-asteroid-to-pass-safely-on-april-29-3990273</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/24/3990273/3990273_CAD0C79DE31A49F1A1030021BCD4D489_200424_3990273__Potentially_Hazardous__Asteroid_to_pass_safely__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 05:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3990215</guid>
      <title>VACCINE: Chinese Researchers Protect Monkeys From Virus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[BEIJING <br/> The vaccine race is on and Chinese researchers may have a head start after they claim they have successfully protected monkeys with a coronavirus vaccine.<br/><br/>According to a study published recently in the preprint server bioRxiv, scientists at Sinovac Biotech, a private Beijing based company, subjected eight rhesus macaque monkeys to two versions of its vaccine.<br/><br/>Three weeks later when the monkeys were exposed to the deadly pathogen, none developed a full-blown infection.<br/><br/>In contrast, four control animals developed high levels of SARS-CoV-2 in several body parts and severe pneumonia.<br/><br/>Despite the limitations of the trail, Sinovac's senior director, Meng Weining told Science Magazine that the results "give us a lot of confidence" that the vaccine will work in humans.<br/><br/>The monkeys given the largest dose of the vaccine had the best response, as researchers were unable to detect the virus in any of their pharynxes or lungs. Monkeys that received a lower dose developed a minor infection in which they appear to have been able to control.<br/><br/>Impressively, the researchers even claimed that the vaccine "neutralized" the strains of the virus isolated from coronavirus patients in China, Italy, Switzerland, Spain, and the United Kingdom.<br/><br/>Acknowledging that monkeys with the virus don't actually develop the most severe symptoms seen in humans, the researchers said, "it's still too early to define the best animal model for studying SARS-CoV-2."<br/><br/>Sinovac is no stranger to developing vaccines, having marketed vaccines for hand, foot, and mouth disease; hepatitis A and B; and the bird flu.<br/><br/>TomoNews is your best source for real news. We cover the funniest, craziest and most talked-about stories on the internet. If you're laughing, we're laughing. If you're outraged, we're outraged. We tell it like it is. And because we can animate stories, TomoNews brings you news like you've never seen before.<br/><br/>Top TomoNews Stories - The most popular videos on TomoNews!<br/>http://bit.ly/Top_TomoNews_Stories<br/><br/>You Idiot! - People doing stupid things<br/>http://bit.ly/You-Idiot<br/><br/>Recent Uploads - The latest stories brought to you by TomoNews<br/>http://bit.ly/Latest-TomoNews<br/><br/>Ultimate TomoNews Compilations - Can't get enough of TomoNews? This playlist is for you! New videos every day<br/>http://bit.ly/Ulitmate_TomoNews_Compi...<br/><br/>Thanks for watching TomoNews!<br/>Like TomoNews on Facebook &#9658;&#9658; http://www.facebook.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Twitter &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://www.twitter.com/TomoNewsUS<br/>Follow us on Instagram &#9658;&#9658; @tomonewsus http://instagram.com/tomonewsus<br/>Subscribe to TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/Subscribe-to-TomoNews<br/>Watch more TomoNews &#9658;&#9658; http://bit.ly/MoreTomoNews  <br/><br/>Visit our website for all the latest videos: http://us.tomonews.com<br/>Check out our Android app: http://bit.ly/1rddhCj<br/>Check out our iOS app: http://bit.ly/1gO3z1f<br/><br/>Get top stories delivered to your inbox every day: http://bit.ly/tomo-newsletter]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/vaccine-chinese-researchers-protect-monkeys-from-virus-3990215</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/24/3990215/3990215_DE92CA5124184027964CEBDD202919FD_200424_3990215_VACCINE__Chinese_Researchers_Protect_Monkeys_Fro_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 03:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3990329</guid>
      <title>COVID toes: Potential new coronavirus symptom</title>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. <br/> American health professionals have observed a new potential coronavirus symptom that appears in the toes of those infected.<br/><br/>According to USA Today, some health professionals treating COVID-19 have noticed purple and blue lesions on the toes of coronavirus patients. This symptom is now being referred to as 'COVID toes' and can often be observed in patients with severe flu or viral pneumonia.<br/><br/>Ebbing Lautenbach, chief of infectious disease at the University of Pennsylvania's School of Medicine, told USA Today that the symptom could be an inflammatory reaction to an infection in an individual's feet, or a clot in the toes' blood vessels.<br/><br/>Lautenbach said patients exhibiting this symptom tend to be children or young adults who are otherwise asymptomatic and would probably test negative for COVID-19 as the infection is in its early stages.<br/><br/>However, Susan Wilcox, Massachusetts General Hospital's chief of critical care for the emergency department, told USA Today that she mostly observed 'COVID toes' in the most severe cases she was treating.<br/><br/>Doctors around the world have also observed other dermatological symptoms related to COVID-19.<br/><br/>In an April 6 press release, France's National Union of Dermatologists-Venereologists reported that certain dermatological conditions could be related to COVID-19.These include the appearance of pseudo-frostbite of the extremities, transient hives, and sudden onset of persistent, sometimes painful redness.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/covid-toes-potential-new-coronavirus-symptom-3990329</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/24/3990329/3990329_07A939201FAF4BC9B151DEB418DC3486_200424_3990329_COVID_toes__Potential_new_coronavirus_symptom_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2020 07:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991335</guid>
      <title>Britain starts human trials on COVID-19 vaccine</title>
      <description><![CDATA[OXFORD, ENGLAND <br/> The University of Oxford has initiated human trials for the first COVID-19 vaccine in Europe, according to the BBC.<br/><br/>Citing the university, BBC reports on April 23 that the experimental COVID-19 vaccine takes the coronavirus's genetic material and inserts the substance into adenoviruses that are responsible for the common cold.<br/><br/>The cold viruses are weakened so that they cannot grow inside the human body after injection." <br/><br/>The modified viruses should make the human cells produce the same spike proteins that stud the surface of the coronaviruses and teach the immune system to recognize COVID-19.<br/><br/>When vaccine recipients actually encounter the coronavirus, their bodies' immune system would then be able to identify the threat and scramble antibodies and killer T cells to fight off the infection.<br/><br/>At the time of report, two volunteers have received the shot, out of around 800 recruited for the first phase human trial.<br/><br/>Citing the doctors, the BBC reports potential side effects include headache, fever and muscle pains a couple of days after the injection.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/britain-starts-human-trials-on-covid-19-vaccine-3991335</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/27/3991335/3991335_31AC290308C2416A98F76F5CC092D0C8_200427_3991335_Britain_starts_human_trials_on_COVID_19_vaccine_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 10:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991318</guid>
      <title>These are the cells most vulnerable to the coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[CAMBRIDGE, MASSACHUSETTS <br/> A new research study details what cells are more susceptible to the coronavirus. Here's what you need to know.<br/><br/>According to research published in the journals Nature and Cell, specialists from around the world have identified cells in the lungs, nasal passages and intestine that are most susceptible to SARS-CoV-2.<br/><br/>Findings of the research show that secretory cells, which produce mucus in the nasal passages, have the RNAs for both proteins that COVID-19 searches for to attack a cell.<br/><br/>Results also suggest that the coronavirus could have mutated to attack interferon, which are proteins released by cells to fight off viruses and infections.<br/><br/>Researchers also found that cells in the intestine that are in charge of partial nutrient absorption called enterocytes also express the RNAs for two proteins, which makes them vulnerable to the coronavirus.<br/><br/>Scientists working on the study hope that these new findings will help specialists working on drug treatments for COVID-19.<br/><br/>In a press release published in MIT news, Alex K. Shalek, the Pfizer-Laubach Career Development Associate Professor of Chemistry said, "Our goal is to get information out to the community and to share data as soon as is humanly possible so that we can help accelerate ongoing efforts in the scientific and medical communities."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/these-are-the-cells-most-vulnerable-to-the-coronavirus-3991318</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/27/3991318/3991318_A9FD665216D741079F0FF9E5F8B0F723_200427_3991318_These_are_the_cells_most_vulnerable_to_the_coron_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2020 09:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991521</guid>
      <title>Metal vaporizes on this planet</title>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW HAVEN, CONNECTICUT <br/> Using the Extreme Precision Spectrometer, or EXPRES, a team of multinational scientists were able to look more closely into the environment of MASCARA-2 b, a large, scorching hot gaseous planet in our galaxy, Yale News reports.<br/><br/>MASCARA-2 b is a gas giant twice the size of Jupiter located 140 parsecs, or 4.3 quadrillion kilometers, away from Earth.<br/><br/>MASCARA-2 b is just 8 million kilometers away from its sun, making its atmosphere reach temperatures of more than 1726.6 degrees Celsius.<br/><br/>Further observations using the EXPRES spectrogram indicate that the gas giant contains small quantities of gaseous iron, magnesium and chromium.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/metal-vaporizes-on-this-planet-3991521</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/28/3991521/3991521_9135492C90784C61A18B3FD37FC47AEB_200428_3991521_Metal_vaporizes_on_this_planet_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3991936</guid>
      <title>White House official says sunlight, humidity help kill coronavirus</title>
      <description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON <br/> Direct sunlight and high humidity can kill the coronavirus in minutes, according to new research announced on April 24 by a senior U.S. official in a press conference with President Donald Trump.<br/><br/>A summary of research from the Department of Homeland Security found that when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity, the coronavirus' half-life, or rate of decay, was 18 hours on a nonporous surface. <br/><br/>When humidity was raised to 80 percent, the halflife fell to six hours. When sunlight was added, the half-life dropped to just two minutes. <br/><br/>When the virus was aerosolized in droplets that hang in the air, its half-life was one hour when the temperature was 70 to 75 degrees Fahrenheit (21 to 24 degrees Celsius) with 20 percent humidity. When sunlight was added to the equation, its half-life was only one-and-a-half minutes. <br/><br/>The new research was announced to reporters at the White House by William Bryan, science and technology advisor to the Department of Homeland Security secretary, who displayed the information on slides.<br/><br/>The study, which was carried out by the National Biodefense Analysis and Countermeasures Center in Maryland, has not yet been released for review and is still awaiting external evaluation.<br/><br/>Bryan's summary of the research leaves many questions unanswered, such as the intensity and wavelength of the ultraviolet light used in the experiment.<br/><br/>In a statement sent to CNN, the Illuminating Engineering Society, a non-profit industry group, said, "Ultraviolet disinfecting 'wands' or other ultraviolet products for residential use <br/> as they are inadequately proven and unregulated <br/> may pose a safety hazard and are unlikely to provide the protection expected."]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/white-house-official-says-sunlight-humidity-help-kill-coronavirus-3991936</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/29/3991936/3991936_41329AEB0BEA4AFAA450B10CA60CD5AC_200429_3991936_White_House_official_says_sunlight__humidity_hel_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 02:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992494</guid>
      <title>Migrating sea turtles find empty beaches, a rare chance to thrive</title>
      <description><![CDATA[MIAMI <br/> Thousands of sea turtles are currently migrating to nesting grounds on beaches across the southeastern United States, just in time to enjoy a rare break from human interference as coronavirus lockdowns keep people indoors.<br/><br/>Experts interviewed by CBS News expect sea turtles to thrive amid the lack of human activity and pollution as beaches are deserted thanks to stay-at-home orders.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/migrating-sea-turtles-find-empty-beaches-a-rare-chance-to-thrive-3992494</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/30/3992494/3992494_E0A86C195EB34DEA80539B5B3B674D83_200430_3992494_Migrating_sea_turtles_find_empty_beaches__a_rare_2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <guid>3992452</guid>
      <title>The Ocean Is Changing More Now Than in the Past 10,000 Years</title>
      <description><![CDATA[LONDON <br/> According to research published in the journal Geophysical Research Letters, scientists have discovered significant changes in the Atlantic Ocean's ecosystem that might have been caused by shifts in ocean circulation.<br/><br/>To examine changes in the ecosystem, researchers used a plastic tube to take samples from sediments in the ocean floor. Scientists then studied the fossil plankton available in newer and older sediments.<br/><br/>Results show that changes in the ocean's water circulation have caused a decline in cold water plankton and a rise in warm water species in southern Iceland as the flow of warm water has overtaken cold waters.<br/><br/>Scientists who participated in the study believe that these shifts have caused some fish species, such as mackerel, to travel northward.<br/><br/>Results also showed that warm water is now reaching the Arctic. Scientists note that this could be aggravating the melting of sea ice there. The shift in the direction of the warm water currents could also affect key fisheries in the U.S. and Canada.]]></description>
      <link>http://us.tomonews.com/the-ocean-is-changing-more-now-than-in-the-past-10-000-years-3992452</link>
      <thumbnail url=""/>
      <media url="https://video-pdu.us.tomonews.net/mcp/us/614/20/04/30/3992452/3992452_67C07F148AC645F48A8139AA68A8AD94_200430_3992452_The_Ocean_Is_Changing_More_Now_Than_in_the_Past__2600.mp4"/>
      <category>Sci&amp;Tech</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2020 01:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
